<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> CSV on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/csv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  CSV on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/csv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried SARS analysis before coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-sars-analysis-before-coronavirus-62138/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-sars-analysis-before-coronavirus-62138/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;m bored of the coronavirus lately and I&amp;rsquo;m bored staying at home, so I want to go out early, so In order to know the trend of Navirus, I analyzed from the same type of SARS virus.
Future outlook  With the epidemic of coronavirus, SARS virus of the same classification is analyzed After that, we also analyze coronavirus Compare the two ##First First of all, I started searching for data because there is no data even if I say to analyze it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to save scraped table in csv with python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-save-scraped-table-in-csv-with-python-add03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-save-scraped-table-in-csv-with-python-add03/</guid>
      <description># About this article  I needed to scrape a table on a web page in my research, so I will introduce the python program used at that time. By the way, I had zero scraping history, so I made it while checking various things, but there was hardly anything explaining how to convert the table on the web page to HTML and then convert the HTML table part to csv.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add CSV export function to admin screen with django-import-export</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/add-csv-export-function-to-admin-screen-with-django-import-export-14a1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/add-csv-export-function-to-admin-screen-with-django-import-export-14a1a/</guid>
      <description>It seems that there are various plugins when I check the admin site of Django.  Since I wanted to import/export the data of the management screen in a format such as CSV, I checked it and it was easy with django-import-export. A memorandum at that time.
Install First install with pip
$ pip install django-import-export Configuration Add import_export to INSTALLED_APPS
# settings.py INSTALLED_APPS = ( ... &amp;#39;import_export&amp;#39;, ) Added to admin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>