<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> support for new programmers on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/support-for-new-programmers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  support for new programmers on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/support-for-new-programmers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder ARC067 C prime factorization solved with Ruby and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/atcoder-arc067-c-prime-factorization-solved-with-ruby-and-python-a97d6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/atcoder-arc067-c-prime-factorization-solved-with-ruby-and-python-a97d6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Regular Contest C-Factors of Factorial Difficulty: 925
This theme, factorization
It is a problem such as a simplified version of * that I solved before * AtCoder ABC057 C prime factorization bit exhaustive search with Ruby and Python*.
Although it is called factorial, integer factor overflow can be seen in C language when actually factoring, so that point may be Difficulty high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I summarized the books that a librarian has read as a Web engineer before joining a new graduate</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-summarized-the-books-that-a-librarian-has-read-as-a-web-engineer-before-joining-a-new-graduate-e54ae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-summarized-the-books-that-a-librarian-has-read-as-a-web-engineer-before-joining-a-new-graduate-e54ae/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hello. I am @sho-hata, a new graduate web engineer.
In this article, I read ** a book that I was at the level of index finger typing ** that I had read in a year and a half from when I decided to become a Web engineer! I would like to introduce it without looking back.
We hope that this article will be a stimulus for those who have read it, and we hope that it will be of use to you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Python (Python version APG4b)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-python-python-version-apg4b-b9418/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-python-python-version-apg4b-b9418/</guid>
      <description># About this article  At AtCoderofthecompetitionprogrammingsite,thereis&amp;rdquo;AtCoderProgrammingGuideforbeginners(APG4b)&amp;rdquo; which is an introductory material for programming. There is. C++, which is the mainstream language for competitive programming, is used as an introductory material for programming. So, in this article, I wrote a Python version of APG4b. Basically, please read APG4b, and refer to this article for Python-specific parts.
Most are based on APG4b, so if this article seems to be a problem, remove it immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After hitting the Qiita API with Python to get a list of articles for beginners, we will worship God articles</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/after-hitting-the-qiita-api-with-python-to-get-a-list-of-articles-for-beginners-we-will-worship-god-articles-97e78/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/after-hitting-the-qiita-api-with-python-to-get-a-list-of-articles-for-beginners-we-will-worship-god-articles-97e78/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Qiita&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Beginner&amp;rdquo; tag and &amp;ldquo;New Programmer Support&amp;rdquo; tag articles for beginners As a new QA engineer, everything is very helpful. Unfortunately, the individual tag page only shows trends and new articles, The specifications make it difficult to find good articles in the past. In this article, first use the Qiita API to write an article for beginners (:= Article with the tag &amp;ldquo;Beginner&amp;rdquo; OR &amp;ldquo;Newcomer programmer support&amp;rdquo;) After creating a program to output all, next read each article in the output list in descending order of likes I would like to introduce the God articles that I felt &amp;ldquo;This is really helpful!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django crispy tutorial (Environment construction on Mac)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-crispy-tutorial-environment-construction-on-mac-01332/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-crispy-tutorial-environment-construction-on-mac-01332/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Introduction&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;   Hello. I&#39;m Sugimoto. I wrote this article for you there, &#34;I would like to make a website in Python.&#34; &#34;I read the net and reference books about Django but I don&#39;t understand it.&#34; I&#39;m writing this for beginners and beginners, so I won&#39;t explain it in depth. please note that. After that, the following is assumed.  Python 3 or higher is installed.  I know a few Linux commands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>