<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mac on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/mac/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mac on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/mac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Google Colaboratory</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-use-google-colaboratory-fc1d7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-use-google-colaboratory-fc1d7/</guid>
      <description>![image.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/587891/ed416201-d330-975f-0707-cea8dd90ab29.png)  Purpose Google Colaboratory can be used.
Please see How to use Google Colaboratory for detailed explanation and code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do when (base) is displayed at the beginning of the Mac terminal</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-to-do-when-base-is-displayed-at-the-beginning-of-the-mac-terminal-f9c19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-to-do-when-base-is-displayed-at-the-beginning-of-the-mac-terminal-f9c19/</guid>
      <description>After launching the Mac terminal,  The familiar (base) characters at the Anaconda prompt start. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Anaconda lately.
(base)username:~$ Cause Since the setting that automatically enables the virtual environment built with Anaconda may be effective, I ran the following command to check.
$ conda config --show | grep auto_activate_base Now that we have a True returned, we know we need to change the settings.
auto_activate_base: True Environment ・MacOS Catalina 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After changing the account name on Mac, I could not use pip or ipython, so I re-installed python and it was cured</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/after-changing-the-account-name-on-mac-i-could-not-use-pip-or-ipython-so-i-re-installed-python-and-it-was-cured-fcccf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/after-changing-the-account-name-on-mac-i-could-not-use-pip-or-ipython-so-i-re-installed-python-and-it-was-cured-fcccf/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  When I changed my mac account name, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use pip or ipython installed by pyenv, so I could use python again. #environment macOS Catalina 10.15.4 Homebrew 2.2.11 pyenv 1.2.17 python 3.8.0 #Background I used brew on mac to install pyenv, and then pyenv was used to install python. After that, I changed my mac account name (and home directory name) for various reasons. Follow the official description to change the account name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MacBook Pro でOpenPose</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/macbook-pro-%E3%81%A7openpose-fccb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/macbook-pro-%E3%81%A7openpose-fccb4/</guid>
      <description>While studying machine learning and Deep Leaning articles on MacBook Pro, I posted an article that you can detect posture on Mac  I found some and tried variously, but it worked, so I will write it as a memorandum.
#environment
 MacBook Pro 15in 2018 2.2 GHz Core i7 32GB Memory Mojave 10.14.6 python 3.7.5 Install python, virtualenv and wget with homebrew  Setup steps Preparation In preparation, set up a Python virtual environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Python on Mac from 2 to 3</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</guid>
      <description># Overview  This article is a step-by-step article on how a beginner himself developed a coupon distribution service for iPhone with RESTful API and swift. It was a very detouring implementation because we implemented it while examining the technical elements one by one.
Python is originally installed on the Mac, but the version is old as of OS 10.15. When actually writing Python, everyone seems to have been updated to 3 series.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>