<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Qiita on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/qiita/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Qiita on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/qiita/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Migrate Qiita articles to GitHub</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ec33706c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ec33706c2/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I think that depending on one service is a risk, so I will write a script to migrate Qiita&amp;rsquo;s article to GitHub.
In addition, my article is as follows. https://github.com/mima3/note
(Added March 29, 2020) Please refer to the following for migration to WordPress. https://qiita.com/mima_ita/items/f4beb31c0ba65e6ab409
Operating environment Python 3.7.4 Windows10
Advance preparation Get an access token for Qiita.
(1) Click &amp;ldquo;Issue a new token&amp;rdquo; from the application tab of the setting screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Analyzing technology life with Qiita article data-Survival analysis using content log-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5ff105185/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5ff105185/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 19th day of the NTT Docomo SI Department Advent Calendar.  Hello! It is Hashimoto of read-ahead engine team. In the business we are working to develop technologies of personal data analysis for the agent service.
In this article, we introduce a method to apply a survival time analysis to Qiita posted article data and quantitatively evaluate the lifespan of content (continuous article posting)**.
Survival time analysis is a method of analyzing the relationship between an event and the period until it occurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Notify the chat of new articles of Qiita Organization to improve learning efficiency of the organization!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fbebd063b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fbebd063b/</guid>
      <description>We are promoting the output activity of Qiita articles in-house. It&#39;s G-awa. The learning method using output is highly recommended and is highly recommended. However, on the other hand, it is difficult for one person to continue alone, so it is important for the team and organization to support each other. If you are alone, you tend to break your heart.  &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-b_wxsoyflcs/WZP38JpI0LI/AAAAABGDA/troMJOw1KGUpq7yueRTgIdPc85o_kexXQCLcBGAs/s400/tamashii_nukeru_man.png&amp;rdquo; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; //2.bp.blogspot.com/-aIs9YKfGlEk/Vy2v2rXYgjI/AAAAAAAA6b0/PuaALahZfJsIluEeFOKgfgOy43qrc8bBQCLcB/s450/enjin_circle_wakamono.png&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;40%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;
I read yesterday&amp;rsquo;s article and it was very helpful :thumbsup: It&amp;rsquo;s a great environment for engineers to grow when there is an environment in which they can encourage each other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>