<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apache on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/apache/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apache on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/apache/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to build Django environment with Win10 WSL Ubuntu18.04 &#43; Anaconda &#43; Apache2</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/steps-to-build-django-environment-with-win10-wsl-ubuntu18.04-anaconda-apache2-f85f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/steps-to-build-django-environment-with-win10-wsl-ubuntu18.04-anaconda-apache2-f85f1/</guid>
      <description>I will summarize the procedure to create a development environment of Django + Apache on Ubuntu 18.04 of Windows 10 WSL  Procedure Allow apache2 to access python via mod_wsgi. Also, we will make VScode usable as a remote IDE that can be used with WSL.
 Install anaconda3 Install django Create a django project and migrate Install apache2 Install mod_wsgi Add to apache2 configuration file Enable vscode  Since WSL cannot use systemctl, the operation of apache changes a little, when using anaconda, you need to change the reference setting by yourself unless you install mod_wsgi with pip, it is hard to understand the setting of apache2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried sending Raspberry Pi data to GCP (free)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-sending-raspberry-pi-data-to-gcp-free-fc564/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-sending-raspberry-pi-data-to-gcp-free-fc564/</guid>
      <description>#I sent the data of Raspberry Pi to GCP (free)  I wanted to create a mechanism to store Raspberry Pi data in MySQL and check it on the Web. For people who want to set up a server in VPS and exchange data.
*This article is intended to acquire and send temperature data on the Rasberry Pi.
Development environment  Windows10 Pro Powershell Windows Subsystem for Linux (Ubuntu)  About GCP Abbreviation for Google Cloud Platform, which is a cloud computing service provided by Google.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>