<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Simulation on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/simulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Simulation on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/simulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple simulation of virus infection</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simple-simulation-of-virus-infection-99363/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simple-simulation-of-virus-infection-99363/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  The following article was published in the Washington Post of March 14, 2020.
 ***Why outbreaks like coronavirus spread exponentially, and how to “flatten the curve”***
https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2020/world/corona-simulator/  The Japanese version is below.
*** Why outbreaks such as coronaviruses can grow so fast and how to &amp;ldquo;flatten the curve&amp;rdquo; ***
https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2020/health/corona-simulation-japanese/
Using the simple principle of contact between balls, In an article that introduced how the number of people infected with the virus will increase and decrease, I think it was very easy to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Introduction to simulation] I tried playing by simulating corona infection ♬</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-simulation-i-tried-playing-by-simulating-corona-infection-65b54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-simulation-i-tried-playing-by-simulating-corona-infection-65b54/</guid>
      <description>In the field of numerical calculation, there have been simulations of free-moving particles and collective movements of Brownian particles in the past.  This time, I will apply this to a simulation of coronavirus infection. There is PSO as a similar simulation, but this time I referred to these python codes. 【reference】 ・Particle swarm optimization (PSO) parameters ・Saved particle swarm optimization (PSO)
what you did ・Code explanation ・Dependence on infection rate ・Dependence on particle density ・Particle motion dependence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numerical calculation of compressible fluid by finite volume method</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/numerical-calculation-of-compressible-fluid-by-finite-volume-method-03e8e/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/numerical-calculation-of-compressible-fluid-by-finite-volume-method-03e8e/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  It is necessary to consider the compressibility of the fluid in the flow around a fast-moving object such as an aircraft or rocket, and in the phenomena involving strong pressure, temperature and density changes such as combustion and explosion. Compressible fluids have various phenomena such as sound waves, shock waves, and aerodynamic heating that are not found in incompressible fluids, and their numerical calculations have different difficulties from incompressible fluids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try frequency control simulation with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-frequency-control-simulation-with-python-c3a5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-frequency-control-simulation-with-python-c3a5d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I recently read a book &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Control Engineering with Python&amp;rdquo;. I would like to try the Python-Control that appears in it, so I will try to simulate frequency control. It is in the control and title, but the main topic is power engineering.
・Explanation of power system and frequency control ・Try using Python-Control
It will be the content.
#What is frequency The 100V electricity we use at home does not always reach 100V, and it vibrates in a fixed cycle as shown in the figure below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X-ray diffraction simulation with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/x-ray-diffraction-simulation-with-python-def78/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/x-ray-diffraction-simulation-with-python-def78/</guid>
      <description>It’s!  Hello. This is my second post. This time I tried to simulate X-ray diffraction with Python. The full code (I use Jupyter Notebook) is GitHub1
#X-Ray Diffraction (XRD) X-ray diffraction is a phenomenon in which X-rays are diffracted in a crystal. X-rays are electromagnetic waves with wavelengths within a certain range (about 1 nm to 1 pm), and diffraction is the propagation of something that has the properties of waves around obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>