<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> GiNZA on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/ginza/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  GiNZA on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/ginza/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A story about trying magic tricks of live coding of natural language processing and dependency analysis with LT in an instant from an empty place</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-trying-magic-tricks-of-live-coding-of-natural-language-processing-and-dependency-analysis-with-lt-in-an-instant-from-an-empty-place-b0472/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-trying-magic-tricks-of-live-coding-of-natural-language-processing-and-dependency-analysis-with-lt-in-an-instant-from-an-empty-place-b0472/</guid>
      <description># wrap up  GiNZA, which carries out ultra-high-precision natural language processing and dependency analysis, is amazing, With Colaboratory, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to build an environment and you can use it easily with just a browser.
During the LT (Lightning Talk) in order to emphasize that crispness On-the-fly environment construction &amp;amp; natural code processing by writing code, Moreover, I tried the &amp;ldquo;magic trick&amp;rdquo; that says I can achieve high precision and high functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Language analysis using natural language processing tool GiNZA (from morphological analysis to vectorization)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-language-analysis-using-natural-language-processing-tool-ginza-from-morphological-analysis-to-vectorization-63ffd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-language-analysis-using-natural-language-processing-tool-ginza-from-morphological-analysis-to-vectorization-63ffd/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Recently, I started using the Python language processing tool &amp;ldquo;GiNZA&amp;rdquo;. I used to use MeCab so far, but I recently (shyly) found out that Python has a library that incorporates state-of-the-art machine learning techniques, so I&amp;rsquo;m currently moving to GiNZA. This time it is the first GiNZA, so I tried to summarize the processing flow as a memorandum while referring to various sites. There are many places that I am new to natural language analysis and I can not reach it, so please refer to the official documents etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>