<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Introduction to Machine Learning on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/introduction-to-machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Introduction to Machine Learning on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/introduction-to-machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>9 steps to become a machine learning expert in the shortest time [Completely free]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/9-steps-to-become-a-machine-learning-expert-in-the-shortest-time-completely-free-19a32/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/9-steps-to-become-a-machine-learning-expert-in-the-shortest-time-completely-free-19a32/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I don&amp;rsquo;t think you need to do Steps 1, 2 and 7 if you don&amp;rsquo;t have time.
1. Learn statistics  Acquisition of Level 2 statistical test  2. Know the principle of ML   Machine Learning -coursera
  Outline of gradient descent optimization algorithm
  3. Learn Python  Python -Google  4. Learn the basics of ML   Machine Learning Crash Course</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning Machine learning learned by a new graduate who has no experience in machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-machine-learning-learned-by-a-new-graduate-who-has-no-experience-in-machine-learning-4a511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-machine-learning-learned-by-a-new-graduate-who-has-no-experience-in-machine-learning-4a511/</guid>
      <description>This article is about how I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI② Advent Calendar 2019 __.  Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the steps that have taken a slightly different step from the general approach to learning machine learning. I would be happy if it could be used as a reference for as many people as possible. I usually write for individual blogs, and I was warmly thinking about writing on my blog, but I thought it was a great opportunity, so I posted it on __qiita for the first time __.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of sites where you can learn machine learning for free</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-sites-where-you-can-learn-machine-learning-for-free-68cc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-sites-where-you-can-learn-machine-learning-for-free-68cc1/</guid>
      <description># Move your hands  Chainer tutorial https://tutorials.chainer.org/ja/
For those who don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate what to learn from, this is the site for the time being Popular because it is written in Japanese and easy to understand
Medical AI specialized course online lecture materials https://japan-medical-ai.github.io/medical-ai-course-materials/#
Also released by Chainer. It is attractive that you can use actual data. For a little application.
&amp;ldquo;DL4US,&amp;rdquo; an educational program for engineers under the supervision of the Matsuo Laboratory of the University of Tokyo https://weblab.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>