<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Poem on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/poem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Poem on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/poem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If Tokyo citizens become severely ill with the new coronavirus, they may be taken to a hospital in Kagoshima prefecture.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b639177f0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b639177f0/</guid>
      <description>#table of contents  Introduction Current status of medical collapse risk Whether or not to secure beds for severely ill persons Severely ill transport model Delivery destination of severely ill Conclusion
#Introduction
 Background Infectious disease designated medical institutions are tight, and it is extremely difficult to secure sufficient beds to accommodate severely ill persons. In various places, measures have been taken to treat patients with mild illness at hotels, homes, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Looking back on the 10 months from beginner programming to becoming Kaggle Expert</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3fbead37b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3fbead37b/</guid>
      <description>I became a Kaggle Expert, so I decided to go and write a poem.  I hope it will be a reference for those who are interested in AI but can not even program **. #1. Initial specifications (February 2019)
 Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in mechanical engineering. Frequent mechanical engineers To be honest, I don&amp;rsquo;t really like linear algebra or statistics. Good at mechanics. AI? That&amp;rsquo;s right. Shogi, isn’t it super strong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Half a year when the Gori Gori literary school almost learned AI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f9988fe89/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f9988fe89/</guid>
      <description># Half-year when the Gori Gori literary system (deviation value 40 first half) learned AI  Hi, it&amp;rsquo;s a rugged ~~ macho~~ humanities. After graduating from commercial high school, I went to the Faculty of Humanities, so it&amp;rsquo;s different from other humanities. It is a thoroughbred world of humanities.
Although it is a vital math skill, I only studied math A up to high school, and just started math at university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Uncle SE whose brain was hardened studied machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/13eea0194/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/13eea0194/</guid>
      <description>## [Introduction]  This article will be on the 19th day of How I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ② Advent Calendar 2019.
Here is how my uncle SE studied machine learning. The motivation was to start with the question, &amp;ldquo;Can you use machine learning?&amp;rdquo; Since I was working in the dark clouds, my honest memory is vague.
career I have been programming for nearly 30 years. Starting with MS BASIC I learned when I was in elementary school, I have touched Z80 assembler, MC68000 assembler, FORTRAN, C (UNIX), C++ (Mac), VB, Java (Android), VB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The story that Purilik that I issued was incorporated into Scipy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0f7d37ff6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0f7d37ff6/</guid>
      <description># What did you do?  scipy.optimize.minimize had a very subtle spec or bug. I thought it was close to a bug, but once it was fixed, it seemed to be a problem for people who are already using it, so I set up an issue and asked, &amp;ldquo;If I fix it, why not pull out it?&amp;rdquo; It was because I wanted to put out a pull request, so I put it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] BEST20 (UTF8 → SJIS) Kanji ranking that appears with garbled characters</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8a7847d06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8a7847d06/</guid>
      <description>## Motivation  (Summary) Just because I wanted to know. There is no better reason.
More details There are many types of garbled patterns. Garbled characters that occur when displaying UTF8 files in SJIS, Garbled characters that occur when displaying UTF8 in EUC, Garbled characters that occur when displaying EUC in UTF8&amp;hellip; You can check what each looks like on this page (https://tools.m-bsys.com/ex/html-mojibake.php).
To be honest, since I work on UTF8 recently, I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen much garbled characters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>