<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> ReKognition on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/rekognition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  ReKognition on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/rekognition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aiming to acquire AWS certification, give it to engineers who are not good at English! Take a screenshot of the English site, extract the text data from the image file, and then try translating it ~ Difference between AWS and Google Cloud API ~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/aiming-to-acquire-aws-certification-give-it-to-engineers-who-are-not-good-at-english-take-a-screenshot-of-the-english-site-extract-the-text-data-from-the-image-file-and-then-try-translating-it-~-difference-between-aws-and-google-cloud-api-~-cb150/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/aiming-to-acquire-aws-certification-give-it-to-engineers-who-are-not-good-at-english-take-a-screenshot-of-the-english-site-extract-the-text-data-from-the-image-file-and-then-try-translating-it-~-difference-between-aws-and-google-cloud-api-~-cb150/</guid>
      <description>#Background  How are AWS certified measures taken? AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and Solution Architect – Associates have a copy of the test book and a practice test, making it an easy environment for studying the test. However, after the developer-associate, there are few Japanese language study books, so if you want to do a mock exam, UdemyandWhizlabs.However,mostofthepracticetestsonthesesitesareinEnglish.(AsofDecember03,2019,thereisoneJapanesemockexaminUdemy)
Difference between Udemy and Whizlabs I thought it would be better to do a lot of mock exams, so I tried English mock exams at Udemy and Whizlabs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the engineer asked for entertainment at the reception</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-the-engineer-asked-for-entertainment-at-the-reception-7ce7c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-the-engineer-asked-for-entertainment-at-the-reception-7ce7c/</guid>
      <description>The other day, at the wedding reception of an acquaintance, I was asked for entertainment for the first time, and I managed to survive.  What should I do I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to own. Singing and dancing are not masters. I can make some movies, but it seems to be done by the side of the bride. .. : Only programming! !
What you did &amp;ldquo;HAPPINESS SCOUTER&amp;rdquo;
If you send a photo via LINE, it will recognize the facial expression of the person in the picture and measure the &amp;ldquo;happy fighting power&amp;rdquo;**!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>