<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anaconda on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/anaconda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Anaconda on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/anaconda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to build Python and Jupyter execution environment with VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-build-python-and-jupyter-execution-environment-with-vs-code-f0788/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-build-python-and-jupyter-execution-environment-with-vs-code-f0788/</guid>
      <description>I have summarized how to build Python and Jupyter execution environment with VS Code. I use Anaconda.  Also, I think that many people who analyze data with Python use Jupyter notebook and Jupyter Lab from their browsers. VS Code is also recommended for such people.
Also, this article is part of the article How to create a Python package using VS Code.
We will proceed on the assumption that Anaconda has been downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning on a gaming PC and comparing the differences in CPU/GPU performance with Colabo [Windows machine learning environment construction procedure definitive version. TF2.0 compatible]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-on-a-gaming-pc-and-comparing-the-differences-in-cpu-gpu-performance-with-colabo-windows-machine-learning-environment-construction-procedure-definitive-version.-tf2.0-compatible-b6fa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-on-a-gaming-pc-and-comparing-the-differences-in-cpu-gpu-performance-with-colabo-windows-machine-learning-environment-construction-procedure-definitive-version.-tf2.0-compatible-b6fa2/</guid>
      <description># In a nutshell  Purchase a cheap gaming PC (Windows), Enable to switch CPU/GPU in virtual environment of Anaconda, Tensorflow-Running the GPU (v2.0) code, With 4 patterns including CPU/GPU of Colaboratory, I compared the performance. I will summarize the performance comparison results and the Windows version environment construction procedure. Article.
*I often hear that GPU is effective for machine learning
 Gaming PCs have GPUs and are cheap these days  ⇒ ** Let&amp;rsquo;s use GPU of gaming PC for machine learning!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python environment construction (Anaconda &#43; VSCode) @ Windows10 [January 2020 edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</guid>
      <description>#Background  When I made a Python environment with Anaconda + VS Code, I was troubled because the latest setting method did not come out, so I will publish my notes for those who will do it now. It seems that there was a VS Code specification change around 2017. Be careful when reading old commentary.
Articles referenced: @Atupon0302: Build Python environment in Windows 10 environment with Anaconda+Visual Studio Code [September 2017]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Build a Python environment that you can enjoy by copying and copying, scraping, machine learning, and practical application [Look for affordable rental properties with SUUMO! ]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-build-a-python-environment-that-you-can-enjoy-by-copying-and-copying-scraping-machine-learning-and-practical-application-look-for-affordable-rental-properties-with-suumo-8ea9b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-build-a-python-environment-that-you-can-enjoy-by-copying-and-copying-scraping-machine-learning-and-practical-application-look-for-affordable-rental-properties-with-suumo-8ea9b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Everyone, do you like data analysis __?
Nice to meet you! I&amp;rsquo;m @haraso_1130 who is the mentor at DMM WEB CAMP
Suddenly, look at the image below.
What a property in 23 wards of Tokyo is 5DK 80,000 yen! ? If you are in the 23 wards, you can comfortably do 80,000 a room a month &amp;hellip;
This property is Using &amp;ldquo;Python&amp;rdquo; Collecting data by &amp;ldquo;scraping&amp;rdquo; Results of data analysis using &amp;ldquo;machine learning&amp;rdquo; It is a property that we were able to discover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Super introduction] Machine learning using Python-From environment construction to simple perceptron implementation-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/super-introduction-machine-learning-using-python-from-environment-construction-to-simple-perceptron-implementation-365f3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/super-introduction-machine-learning-using-python-from-environment-construction-to-simple-perceptron-implementation-365f3/</guid>
      <description># First of all  This article is from the 7th day of the DMM WEBCAMP Advent Calendar. This time it&amp;rsquo;s a super introduction, so I created it for those who have never tried machine learning but want to start **.
The purpose is to get a rough idea of machine learning and try to implement a basic simple perceptron for the time being, so I&amp;rsquo;ve written a lot about the explanation of machine learning etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Built environment for machine learning from 0 (windows10 &#43; Anaconda &#43; VSCode &#43; Tensorflow &#43; GPU version)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/built-environment-for-machine-learning-from-0-windows10-anaconda-vscode-tensorflow-gpu-version-08d3f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/built-environment-for-machine-learning-from-0-windows10-anaconda-vscode-tensorflow-gpu-version-08d3f/</guid>
      <description>I opened the OS for a while and reinstalled the OS, so I rebuilt the environment.  It is a memorandum at that time.
Overview  Machine learning (reinforcement learning) environment built from almost 0 (GPU compatible) Environment  windows10 NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060   Build environment  Anaconda VSCode Tensorflow GPU compatible settings Cooperation between Anaconda and VS Code ChainerRL    Preparation for using Tensorflow GPU version *Not required when using the CPU version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] About package management with conda and pip</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-package-management-with-conda-and-pip-29efe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-package-management-with-conda-and-pip-29efe/</guid>
      <description>[Anaconda](https://www.anaconda.com/) is, in a word, a library of scientific computations etc. attached from the beginning in addition to Python itself. In addition, it has been devised to simplify package management and deployment, and comes with a package management command called conda.  About conda and pip The Python world has been around for quite some time with its own package management tools, which used to be EasyInstall, and later to use pip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Things from building Python environment to running on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/things-from-building-python-environment-to-running-on-windows-fdf02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/things-from-building-python-environment-to-running-on-windows-fdf02/</guid>
      <description>When building the Python environment, I went through various articles saying &amp;quot;Authentication proxy settings, coexistence environment, and execution confirmation are all necessary&amp;quot;, so I think that it would be nice to put them all together.  #Introduction
Content The contents introduced in this article are as follows. Please skip the authentication proxy and coexistence environment construction if necessary.
 Install Anaconda (Windows) Authentication proxy settings Different versions coexistence environment construction Run the program in interactive mode Run Python script  For whom For Python beginners who meet any of the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to install Deep Learning Framework Tensorflow 1.0 on Windows Anaconda environment</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-install-deep-learning-framework-tensorflow-1.0-on-windows-anaconda-environment-fe4c7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-install-deep-learning-framework-tensorflow-1.0-on-windows-anaconda-environment-fe4c7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Until now, we have been doing deep learning by running Tensorflow on the back end of Keras. If you just do machine learning in Python, you can use Keras as before, but there are applications where you want to use models and weights learned in Python in C++. Actually, it would be nice to use a model trained with Keras, but it seems easier to code directly with Tensorflow which also has a C++ API, so I will try to attack from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 3 workarounds for the activate conflict problem when coexisting pyenv and anaconda</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3-workarounds-for-the-activate-conflict-problem-when-coexisting-pyenv-and-anaconda-f732b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3-workarounds-for-the-activate-conflict-problem-when-coexisting-pyenv-and-anaconda-f732b/</guid>
      <description>It is a supplement of [python environment construction final version](http://qiita.com/y__sama/items/5b62d31cb7e6ed50f02c).  20180312 Addendum It seems that conda activate was adopted in conda 4.4.0 released with 2017-12-20. conda/CHANGELOG.md It seems that source activate is not obsolete at the moment, but conda activate is recommended.
Since docker has become proficient recently (I do not feel stress even in a windows environment through a proxy), the need for sandwiching pyenv has decreased, and I am also moving to docker-anaconda, but for reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The easiest way to put Chainer v1.5&#43;CUDA&#43;cuDNN on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-easiest-way-to-put-chainer-v1.5-cuda-cudnn-on-windows-f985b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-easiest-way-to-put-chainer-v1.5-cuda-cudnn-on-windows-f985b/</guid>
      <description>Chainer now depends on Cython, h5py since 1.5. The installation method on Windows is described in [2nd day article (Install Chainer 1.5.0 on Windows)](http://qiita.com/icoxfog417/items/ca1521f9d62183cea234) I would like to add some supplements so that you can easily use proper Chainer on Windows.  This content may contain errors. We will update as soon as we notice. Operation reports are welcome. Thank you for your comment
**Note: As of December 10, 2015, Chainer (v1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>