<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> matplotlib on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/matplotlib/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  matplotlib on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/matplotlib/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Chapter 4] Introduction to Python with 100 knocks</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/chapter-4-introduction-to-python-with-100-knocks-fc4ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/chapter-4-introduction-to-python-with-100-knocks-fc4ad/</guid>
      <description>This article is a sequel to my book [Introduction to Python with 100 knocks](https://qiita.com/hi-asano/items/8e303425052781d95f09).[100knocksChapter4](https://nlp100.github.io/ja/ch04.html) will be explained.  First, install the morphological analyzer MeCab, download neko.txt, and perform morphological analysis to check the contents.
$ mecab &amp;lt;neko.txt&amp;gt; neko.txt.mecab It is &amp;ldquo;I am a cat&amp;rdquo; from Aozora Bunko.
MeCab&amp;rsquo;s default dictionary system is similar to school grammar, but adjective verbs are nouns + auxiliary verbs, and Sa verbs are nouns + verbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Linear regression] Number of explanatory variables and coefficient of determination (adjusted for degrees of freedom)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/linear-regression-number-of-explanatory-variables-and-coefficient-of-determination-adjusted-for-degrees-of-freedom-fab7d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/linear-regression-number-of-explanatory-variables-and-coefficient-of-determination-adjusted-for-degrees-of-freedom-fab7d/</guid>
      <description># at first  For the explanatory variables of linear regression, &amp;ldquo;It is better not to use variables unrelated to the objective variable for learning&amp;rdquo; (*1) I have the image. However, while studying linear regression analysis, I have learned that the coefficient of determination has the following properties.
&amp;ldquo;When an explanatory variable is added, the coefficient of determination cannot fall below that before addition. (So, for accuracy comparison of models with different numbers of explanatory variables, use the &amp;ldquo;coefficient of determination with adjusted degrees of freedom&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create matplotlib color list</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/create-matplotlib-color-list-f8af8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/create-matplotlib-color-list-f8af8/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Recently, most of my hobby and work calculations are done in Python, and graphing is done in Python matplotlib. In order to improve the distinctiveness of the graph, colors are used, but I wanted to keep the color list of matplotlib at hand, and created an image of the color list.
#Sample
#How to make Get the list of colors that matplotlib can handle by referring to the following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can try it with copy and paste! Let&#39;s draw a cool network diagram with Python&#39;s networkx</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/you-can-try-it-with-copy-and-paste-lets-draw-a-cool-network-diagram-with-pythons-networkx-fe9b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/you-can-try-it-with-copy-and-paste-lets-draw-a-cool-network-diagram-with-pythons-networkx-fe9b8/</guid>
      <description>## Let&#39;s draw a network diagram with networkx that can draw a cool network diagram during winter vacation  Do you all have a good winter vacation? Our company has been taking a day off from 28th to 5th and is really thankful to the mice.
But I think engineers should refrain from Mac refugees and improve their skills at such times.
Today we will introduce a library called networkx that can draw network diagrams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>