<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> matplotlib on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/matplotlib/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  matplotlib on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/matplotlib/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Created a tool that visualizes mechanically from repository history in order to objectively know the productivity and soundness of the development team</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/created-a-tool-that-visualizes-mechanically-from-repository-history-in-order-to-objectively-know-the-productivity-and-soundness-of-the-development-team-ceece/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/created-a-tool-that-visualizes-mechanically-from-repository-history-in-order-to-objectively-know-the-productivity-and-soundness-of-the-development-team-ceece/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The productivity and soundness of a software development team can be understood as an internal sensation, but it is difficult for an external person to see it. This information asymmetry has caused problems in relationships with people outside the development team.
Also, for EMs, CTOs that bundle multiple development teams and products, and visualizing each situation with objective numbers and graphs, it is important reference information when considering the overall strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image analysis performed by google Colab for people who start space research</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/image-analysis-performed-by-google-colab-for-people-who-start-space-research-7075a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/image-analysis-performed-by-google-colab-for-people-who-start-space-research-7075a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For those who are new to handling fits files. The image of the galaxy is familiar, so this is an example of a sample that works even with google Colab. There is also a advanced method for searching fits images with skyview written for a little more advanced users.
Basic Server and client basics Space Astronomy exchanges a large amount of data, so knowledge about servers and clients is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software training for those who start space research</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/software-training-for-those-who-start-space-research-f4535/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/software-training-for-those-who-start-space-research-f4535/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I would like to briefly introduce the basics of software for people who aspire to the universe so that they can do it at home. Software is intended for students who have done a little in class. (2020.4.9. First edition for the time being).
For online learning, how to use python using google Colab,
 Online learning using google Colab for those who start space research  Please refer to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[matplotlib] Graph creation sample function for scientific papers</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/matplotlib-graph-creation-sample-function-for-scientific-papers-9bf83/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/matplotlib-graph-creation-sample-function-for-scientific-papers-9bf83/</guid>
      <description># 0. Introduction  This article is a general function of graph creation using matplotlib of python and its brief description. In order to increase the versatility, we have devised a method that corresponds to the increase in the legend, etc. with a repeating function as much as possible. Also, since pandas.dataframe, which is often used in data processing, is used, it is easy to use it as it is for data after calculation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parse Apache access logs with Pandas and Matplotlib</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/parse-apache-access-logs-with-pandas-and-matplotlib-79cd4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/parse-apache-access-logs-with-pandas-and-matplotlib-79cd4/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  Even if you try to analyze the access log of Apache, Tomcat, etc., it is not a surprisingly good tool. I would like to have a tool that supports various output formats and that can filter only the necessary information and visualize it easily, but I can not find it easily.
So, I tried using Pandas and Matplotlib, which are standard in the world of data analysis, to analyze and visualize Apache access logs on Jupyter Notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of all the Python visualization tools used by active graduate students in their research [Application]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-the-python-visualization-tools-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-application-dfabd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-the-python-visualization-tools-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-application-dfabd/</guid>
      <description>#Continuing from the previous session  This article is an application of Python visualization tools. ~~ Since it has become long, I decided to divide the application into two. (Application 2 is still being written) ~~ The application section was added to this article to make it one. If you are new to Python plot, I wrote the basic version last time, so please check here! #Introduction I am currently a graduate student with a 2nd year master&amp;rsquo;s degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of all Python plots used by active graduate students in their research [Basic]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-python-plots-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-basic-52315/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-python-plots-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-basic-52315/</guid>
      <description>Application section [here](https://qiita.com/coffiego/items/dfabde5f8588723b32d6)  https://qiita.com/coffiego/items/dfabde5f8588723b32d6
#Introduction I am currently a graduate student with a 2nd year master&amp;rsquo;s degree. I am studying the Martian atmosphere using numerical simulation. Since I mainly analyzed the results obtained by numerical simulation using Python, I tried to summarize all the functions used in the process. Please note that this is not an exhaustive list. .. .. However, since I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling to use the documentation, I&amp;rsquo;ve summarized it in the hope that if anyone using Python&amp;rsquo;s visualization tools can help with that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scatter rice grains to determine pi (Monte Carlo method)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/scatter-rice-grains-to-determine-pi-monte-carlo-method-2f147/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/scatter-rice-grains-to-determine-pi-monte-carlo-method-2f147/</guid>
      <description># Addition  This is an article that implements the Monte Carlo method. I forgot completely.
1.First of all When I was reading a book for children&amp;rsquo;s statistics [1], I saw an article about spreading rice grains to calculate the pi. It seemed interesting, so I tried to calculate the pi using the randomly generated x, y coordinate data.
[procedure] It&amp;rsquo;s almost like this
 Prepare a square and a circle inscribed in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embed matplotlib graph in Tkinter</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/embed-matplotlib-graph-in-tkinter-45953/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/embed-matplotlib-graph-in-tkinter-45953/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  Recently, there were the following hurdles regarding programming.
(1) I want to create a GUI program in Python. → You can use Tkinter (2) I want to display some calculation results on a graph. → You can use matplotlib (3) I want to embed the graph written in matplotlib in (2) into Tkinter in (1). → NG
I tried to get over it by tampering with the example code, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiita, early Python♪</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/qiita-early-python-be75f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/qiita-early-python-be75f/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;I want to start Python programming, but what should I do?&amp;quot;  I often get the question, so I tried to put together a Qiita page for beginners. Initially
 Python syntax How to use Numpy How to use Pandas How to use matplotlib  I think it is good to take a look at all four.
Python syntax  Python warming up Python Basic Summary Python basic learning  How to use #Numpy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Patent Analysis] I made a patent map in Python without spending money</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/patent-analysis-i-made-a-patent-map-in-python-without-spending-money-5966d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/patent-analysis-i-made-a-patent-map-in-python-without-spending-money-5966d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I thought it would be a good idea to do a patent analysis, so I decided to give it a try. Specifically, for patent analysis, for example, there is the following plot. (The figure is quoted from J-STORE Manual) The vertical axis shows the patent applicant, the horizontal axis shows the year the patent was issued, and the size of the circle shows the number of patents. This is called the bubble chart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to analyze the pitcher who achieved no hit no run</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-to-analyze-the-pitcher-who-achieved-no-hit-no-run-71d65/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-to-analyze-the-pitcher-who-achieved-no-hit-no-run-71d65/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  On June 18, 2014, the Dodgers Clayton Kershaw pitched nine times in the Colorado Rockies v Los Angeles Dodgers match, achieving 15 strikeouts and no-hit nolan. This time we will compare it to our opponent Rockies pitcher and analyze why Clayton Kershaw achieved a no-hit nolan. #environment ・Python 3.7.5 ・Windows10 ・Jupyter Notebook (Anaconda3)
Start analysis (play ball) First, launch Jupyter Notebook with Anaconda Prompt $ jupyter notebook Then import the required libraries %matplotlib inline import requests import xml.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The basics of graph theory with matplotlib animation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-basics-of-graph-theory-with-matplotlib-animation-b55c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-basics-of-graph-theory-with-matplotlib-animation-b55c6/</guid>
      <description>* Basics of graph theory   Animation creation using matplotlib  Will be dealt with here.
Graph theory basics Basics of graph theory https://qiita.com/maskot1977/items/e1819b7a1053eb9f7d61
I wrote this article in the past, and many people like it, but this time I would like to make the content easy to understand with animation.
Animation using #matploblib
You can draw a simple animation as follows.
# -*- coding: UTF-8 -*- import math import matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time series plot started-python version-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/time-series-plot-started-python-version-9e6b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/time-series-plot-started-python-version-9e6b8/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 22nd day article of MicroAd Advent Calendar 2019.
Thing you want to do Time series plots are a very useful tool when visualizing log data. Until now, I have lived such a life that I replaced the dates on the horizontal axis with numbers and plotted and escaped. However, it&amp;rsquo;s different now. You can now plot well with the horizontal axis set to time series!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning with Python, a quick and easy analysis of the weather data of the last 10 years was started.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/beginning-with-python-a-quick-and-easy-analysis-of-the-weather-data-of-the-last-10-years-was-started.-ee6a3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/beginning-with-python-a-quick-and-easy-analysis-of-the-weather-data-of-the-last-10-years-was-started.-ee6a3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I recently started studying Python. Since I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, I&amp;rsquo;d like to make a post that will be useful for those who are new to Python like me. Since I have never written Python, this time I would like to do a simple data analysis while understanding the syntax of python and what kind of library it has.
Reference book: [Immediately usable! Can be practiced in work! How to create AI/machine learning/deep learning apps with Python](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualize functions that appear in high school mathematics &#43; university mathematics using Matplotlib</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/visualize-functions-that-appear-in-high-school-mathematics-university-mathematics-using-matplotlib-e8b75/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/visualize-functions-that-appear-in-high-school-mathematics-university-mathematics-using-matplotlib-e8b75/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 12th day of [Kure National College of Technology Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/kurekosen).  #Introduction As you study math, you will come across various &amp;ldquo;functions&amp;rdquo;. We often differentiate or integrate these functions, or find the extrema or inflection points of the functions. However, since these operations can be calculated by mechanical processing, it is not necessary to pay much attention to what kind of property the original function has and what kind of shape it has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s apply the brand image color to the colormap of matplotlib!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-apply-the-brand-image-color-to-the-colormap-of-matplotlib-1cb5c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-apply-the-brand-image-color-to-the-colormap-of-matplotlib-1cb5c/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  What color do you use when drawing graphs with matplotlib? By default, matplotlib has a pretty colormap, I want to use different color variations for presentations, materials and graphs Have you ever wanted to unify the color images?
In this article, we will add the brand color image to the matplotlib colormap. I will try to adapt!
Class to use matplotlib has two types of classes to create your own colormap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implement Data Visualization Design #2 with matplotlib</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implement-data-visualization-design-#2-with-matplotlib-ee27a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implement-data-visualization-design-#2-with-matplotlib-ee27a/</guid>
      <description># What is the design of data visualization?  Go Ando of THE GUILD, which is famous for its services that focus on UX and UI, has published a note on the points of data visualization.
https://note.mu/goando/n/n4a2735c3d69d
#1?  See below for #1  https://qiita.com/skotaro/items/cdb0732ad1ad2a4b6236
Notes  Regarding fonts, it works on mac, but probably not on other OS, so specify a different font.  plt.rcParams[&amp;#39;font.family&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Hiragino Sans&amp;#39; Is the part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I created a stacked bar graph with matplotlib of Python and tried adding a data label</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-created-a-stacked-bar-graph-with-matplotlib-of-python-and-tried-adding-a-data-label-6f9c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-created-a-stacked-bar-graph-with-matplotlib-of-python-and-tried-adding-a-data-label-6f9c1/</guid>
      <description># draw a stacked bar graph with matplotlib  Motivation When I draw a stacked bar chart in Python, I wish I could display the data label like Excel, and when I looked it up, there was no article that could display the data label, and there was no code to copy and paste. So, I wrote a code that I can copy and paste when I want to attach a data label to a stacked bar graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to summarize the usage of matplotlib of python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-usage-of-matplotlib-of-python-24fc4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-usage-of-matplotlib-of-python-24fc4/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This time I will summarize how to use matplotlib.
Many people have summarized how to use matplotlib, so it may not be new, but I would appreciate it if you could associate.
I have summarized the usage of numpy and pandas in the previous article, so please check if you like.
I tried to summarize python&amp;rsquo;s numpy I tried to summarize how to use pandas of python
In writing this article, the following articles were very helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of basic drawing method of Plotly Express, the de facto standard of Python drawing library in the Reiwa era</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-basic-drawing-method-of-plotly-express-the-de-facto-standard-of-python-drawing-library-in-the-reiwa-era-d8cbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-basic-drawing-method-of-plotly-express-the-de-facto-standard-of-python-drawing-library-in-the-reiwa-era-d8cbe/</guid>
      <description># at first  A library called Plotly Express (official site) that allows you to easily draw interactive operations based on javascript was released a while ago. I found. Since I felt a potential of a dimension that was clearly different from the static drawing that I have used so far, I have summarized the method of drawing a basic visualization method also as a memo. For reference, I am comparing it with the pattern that I wrote a similar figure in matplotlib+seaborn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>