<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>discord on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/discord/</link>
    <description>Recent content in discord on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/discord/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a Discord bot in Python that translates when reacting</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-discord-bot-in-python-that-translates-when-reacting-70abd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-discord-bot-in-python-that-translates-when-reacting-70abd/</guid>
      <description>Bot like this  How to make a bot with Discord is omitted. Read around here. Practical Discord Bot with Python (discordpy explanation)
Source code # Load the installed discord.py import discord from googletrans import Translator # Replace with your bot&amp;#39;s access token TOKEN =&amp;#39;[bot-token]&amp;#39; # Generate objects required for connection client = discord.Client() # Process that runs at startup @client.event async def on_ready(): # After booting, login notification will be displayed in the terminal print(&amp;#39;Logged in&amp;#39;) @client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to discord.py (2)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-discord.py-2-b37e7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-discord.py-2-b37e7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  We run an unofficial server for discord.py (although some developers). Questions are also accepted here. You can also create a personal channel and get support there for those who want long-term support**. If you would like to receive individual support, please enter from the invitation url below and DM to @@Smidora #8931`. https://discord.gg/KPp2Wsu **Please send any questions regarding this article here**
About this article This article is a step-by-step article about discord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a music bot using discord.py and Google Drive API (tested with Docker → deployed on Heroku)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-music-bot-using-discord.py-and-google-drive-api-tested-with-docker-deployed-on-heroku-372e5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-music-bot-using-discord.py-and-google-drive-api-tested-with-docker-deployed-on-heroku-372e5/</guid>
      <description>The used file is placed in [here](https://github.com/ysk0832/hobby/tree/master/discordbot-citron)(excludingauthenticationrelated)  Basically, I made it for my family to enjoy.
Thing you want to do  Send a message on discord bot finds song file from google drive If you find it, download it and play it with your voice.  Also, there are two personal requirements for music bots,
 You can request songs other than yourself I want to keep the bot running  I decided to use google drive and heroku to satisfy these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nest cog with discord.py</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/nest-cog-with-discord.py-59eae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/nest-cog-with-discord.py-59eae/</guid>
      <description># Premise   discord.py python3.6  The code in this article is a simplified code for explanation purposes only, so only nonsense code will appear. Please note.
#cog is getting complicated The command extension of discord.py (https://discordpy.readthedocs.io/en/latest/ext/commands/index.html) has a function called &amp;ldquo;cog&amp;rdquo; that groups together several commands and events. in this way
from discord.ext import commands as c class CogHogeFuga(c.Cog): def __init__(self, bot, hoge): self._bot = bot self._hoge = hoge @c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Latest version] Use discord.py to make the bot speak at regular intervals</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/latest-version-use-discord.py-to-make-the-bot-speak-at-regular-intervals-2917b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/latest-version-use-discord.py-to-make-the-bot-speak-at-regular-intervals-2917b/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  We will explain how to make bot perform periodical processing by using discord.py which is Python&amp;rsquo;s Discord API wrapper that can describe bot simply in chat tool Discord.
Note The code example did not actually work. We modified the code example on April 10, 2020.
Assumption  discord.py 1.3.0a Python 3.6  Version notes Although disc0.1.2 (so-called async version) has been provided for a long time in discord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granting and defeating positions by reactions</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/granting-and-defeating-positions-by-reactions-b50e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/granting-and-defeating-positions-by-reactions-b50e3/</guid>
      <description>#First of all  This article is a simple explanation in Japanese of the code of overseas developer Anson. In addition, since we have obtained confirmation and permission from the individual, secondary distribution is prohibited and it can be used only for personal use.
Original source page Your commentary video
#Overview Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been absorbed in the development of Discord bots, but a bot that is often included in a major server gives me a title if I add a reaction **Are, I wonder how I can do it well &amp;hellip; While I looked up the command.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>