<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> sentiment analysis on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/sentiment-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  sentiment analysis on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/sentiment-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Made a Chrome extension to drive out dark sites from the world with the power of natural language processing</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/859c34823/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/859c34823/</guid>
      <description>#Motivation  Coronavirus pandemic is all the dark news these days&amp;hellip; :pensive: →If you only see the bright news, you will feel positive!
Made A Chrome extension that makes Google search results less visible as the content is darker. Chrome Store: Opty github
Actual screen    Dark site Bright site          How to use Just install the Chrome extension from here and search!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I have no emotions... ← Try to analyze if there are no emotions using various emotion estimators</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2f70ad50d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2f70ad50d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Human communication includes not only language but also many non-verbal information such as facial expressions and gestures. When analyzing and interpreting human behavior mechanically and programmatically, more information can be obtained by adding meaning to such non-verbal information. These technologies are being researched and developed in various fields such as image processing, natural language processing, and voice recognition, and are expected to be applied in many fields such as marketing and robot interaction systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Humans are not so sad creatures</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/177610fbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/177610fbd/</guid>
      <description>With the birth of the Internet, the world has changed dramatically. Now with just one smartphone, you can instantly do various things such as research, shopping, communication, entertainment consumption, and information dissemination.  As efficiency went on, people&amp;rsquo;s tasks continued to diminish, and even ** began to disappear. **The everyday life is spreading, in which people act like the information recommended by AI and like the posts that everyone likes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried sentiment analysis of the whole novel Weather&#39;s Child ☔️</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/10f52c30f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/10f52c30f/</guid>
      <description>![752B7BFA-4985-442D-904C-BEB091269C6C.gif](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/327405/05e5f803-dc12-4db0-bcf5-47661a8e5329.gif)  #1. A brief overview In this article, I will explain how to analyze sentiment by natural language processing the text of the novel **&amp;ldquo;Weather Child&amp;rdquo;**!
In general, emotional analysis is to discover and quantify &amp;ldquo;emotion&amp;rdquo; contained in a sentence and judge the opinion of the sentence. This is an area of current interest because it allows us to mechanically categorize user opinions about our products and services.
On the other hand, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t it possible to use sentiment analysis in addition to reviews and reviews?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Sentiment analysis with Python (word2vec)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/55b4e1682/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/55b4e1682/</guid>
      <description>I recently attended a Python study group sponsored by Team Zet Co., Ltd. The theme this time is &amp;quot;text emotion using word2vec  &amp;ldquo;Analysis.&amp;rdquo; Honestly, it was a pungent theme for me who first touched Python a week ago, but maybe I&amp;rsquo;m going to experience how the grammar I&amp;rsquo;m studying now is being put into shape. I rushed into the train one day before the event.
By the way, let&amp;rsquo;s leave this foreword and go into the main subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make an emotion radar chart of Aozora Bunko&#39;s work</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7a7643b26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7a7643b26/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Introduction This is the 14th day article of &amp;ldquo;Fujitsu Cloud Technologies Advent Calendar 2019&amp;rdquo;. Yesterday was @213&amp;rsquo;sThestoryofthefailurethatoccurredthisyear. ..
Has 213 really survived Friday the 13th? This is where I am concerned.
Main subject People suddenly want to read a book, but depending on the mood at that time, the content may be bright or dark, and the tendency of the book you want to read may change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Automatically generate a polarity dictionary for emotion analysis</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/1b7c765fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/1b7c765fa/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is the 7th day of &amp;ldquo;Natural Language Processing Advent Calendar 2019&amp;rdquo;. I felt the problem in the article of &amp;ldquo;Score the negative/positive degree of news articles by sentiment analysis&amp;rdquo; that I posted earlier, **I can use polar dictionary too much I tried to solve the &amp;ldquo;no problem&amp;rdquo; **. This time we will challenge the automatic generation of a polar dictionary using fasttext.
#reference I have referred to the following when learning fasttext.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What about polarity analysis with order?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/eb7949594/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/eb7949594/</guid>
      <description>I learned a little about polarity analysis (emotion analysis) in Japanese, and I was playing a little bit while being an amateur.  In general polarity analysis (emotion analysis) , the scores of each word against the polarity dictionary are averaged over the entire sentence. However, does that mean that you have a score that matches your intuition?
Natural Language Processing Advent Calendar 2019 4 day.Yesterdaywas kabayan55 &amp;lsquo;s “Astoryaboutapersonwhowantstostudynaturallanguageprocessing” and KazumasaYamamoto &amp;lsquo;s “LearndocumentcategoryclassificationwithCLIofspaCy” It was .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>