<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> quantum computer on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/quantum-computer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  quantum computer on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/quantum-computer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Solve optimization problems with Python-based quantum annealing as easily as possible</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/6a9a6630d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/6a9a6630d/</guid>
      <description>## What?  I&amp;rsquo;m not familiar with quantum computers or Yokuwakara, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure about Ising models, I&amp;rsquo;m not good at formulas like Σ, but I can read it with Python.
The source code is more intuitive than the mathematical formulas and can be understood by moving it anyway, so I think it&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to try Python&amp;rsquo;s study of &amp;ldquo;quantum annealing&amp;rdquo;, which is one of the &amp;ldquo;quantum computers&amp;rdquo;. I summarized it as.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Development of games that take advantage of quantum nature</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/52ab92977/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/52ab92977/</guid>
      <description>Hello Sugo of Quemix.  Here is an overview of the projects currently underway at IPA&amp;rsquo;s unexplored business. By making a game that includes the properties of quantum, we are going to make two games within the period. This time, we will introduce the first game.
#Notes If you try to explain everything such as the history of the game, the details of the rules, the explanation of quantum, etc. so that it can be understood by those who are new to the game, the amount will be too large, so it is a rather broken introduction Please note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Follow QAOA (VQE) flow at Blueqat source code level</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/363c56245/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/363c56245/</guid>
      <description>#QAOA and VQE  QAOA (Quantum Approximate Optimization Algorithm) is an algorithm for optimizing the Ising model using a quantum gate quantum computer. VQE (Variational Quantum Eigensolver) is an algorithm that finds the eigenvalues of a matrix using a quantum gate quantum computer and is often used for quantum chemical calculations.
QAOA and VQE are being actively developed in recent years because quantum computers without error correction can work reasonably well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to run a quantum computer with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ef50cc142/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ef50cc142/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Google has demonstrated quantum transcendenceNewscameoutanditwasatopicrecentlyaboutquantumcomputers,soIwaslightlyinvestigatingHowever,therewasamethodthatanyonecantryandoperateaquantumcomputer(whichwillbedescribedlater,differentfromthemethodbeingdevelopedbyGoogleorthequantumannealingmethod) ** So I have summarized it here. I am not an expert in this area, so there may be some mistakes in the explanation. Please note that.
##reference I have referred to the following to understand the quantum computer and actually operate the quantum computer.
 The world changed by quantum computersMasanobuTerabe(Author),MasayukiOzeki(Author) Publisher; Ohmsha D-wave Leap(registerheretorunthequantumcomputer) Ocean Software Documentation(Pythonlibraryforrunningquantumcomputers)  #What is a quantum computer Regarding the explanation of the quantum computer, the explanation that appeared in the Nikkei newspaper was completed and easy to understand, First of all, I will quote as it is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>