<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Chainer on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/chainer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Chainer on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/chainer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] For the first time after breaking up, I realized that I liked Chainer&#39;s Linear.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-the-first-time-after-breaking-up-i-realized-that-i-liked-chainers-linear.-84d4e/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-the-first-time-after-breaking-up-i-realized-that-i-liked-chainers-linear.-84d4e/</guid>
      <description>2020/05/12 update  https://github.com/pfnet/pytorch-pfn-extras It became possible by importing this.
===
I was notified when the major update of Chainer was announced, and I wondered if it was time to come, but I decided to touch PyTorch as soon as possible for the future, and I made the model I had made with Chainer until now PyTorch I decided to implement it again.
And immediately, I hit an error&amp;hellip;
The relevant part is the following code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried rewriting the MNIST code of Chainer with PyTorch &#43; Ignite</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-rewriting-the-mnist-code-of-chainer-with-pytorch-ignite-35baf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-rewriting-the-mnist-code-of-chainer-with-pytorch-ignite-35baf/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  The impression that I rewrote the MNIST code of Chainer to PyTorch was almost the same. The difference was in the layer above Updater in Chainer and the Ignite layer in PyTorch. Moreover, when chainer-pytorch-migration is actually used, Extensions used in Chainer can also be used in Ignite, and PyTorch+Ignite can be used quite like Chainer. I think that even people who have been using Chainer can naturally get used to PyTorch+Ignite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try extracting features from sensor data with CNN</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-extracting-features-from-sensor-data-with-cnn-fd392/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-extracting-features-from-sensor-data-with-cnn-fd392/</guid>
      <description># I tried convolution with sensor data (1 dimensional vector)  The convolutional neural network is generally used in image processing, but this time, I tried using a one-dimensional vector as seen in sensor data. The point is to convert the data structure using reshape to make it pseudo-three-dimensional (RGB, X, Y), which is the same as the image. I think that convolution can extract features even if there are few learning parameters, and is effective in detecting anomalies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The easiest way to put Chainer v1.5&#43;CUDA&#43;cuDNN on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-easiest-way-to-put-chainer-v1.5-cuda-cudnn-on-windows-f985b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-easiest-way-to-put-chainer-v1.5-cuda-cudnn-on-windows-f985b/</guid>
      <description>Chainer now depends on Cython, h5py since 1.5. The installation method on Windows is described in [2nd day article (Install Chainer 1.5.0 on Windows)](http://qiita.com/icoxfog417/items/ca1521f9d62183cea234) I would like to add some supplements so that you can easily use proper Chainer on Windows.  This content may contain errors. We will update as soon as we notice. Operation reports are welcome. Thank you for your comment
**Note: As of December 10, 2015, Chainer (v1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>