<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CNN on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/cnn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CNN on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/cnn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>For those who want to start machine learning with TensorFlow2</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am currently a M2 student majoring in CS. I usually write machine learning code in PyTorch. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to write for the time being. PyTorch is said to be &amp;ldquo;Define by Run&amp;rdquo;**, and what is good at the same time when the calculation graph and data are sent is that it is easy to debug because you can check the calculation results on the way. As a PyTorch believer, I need to write code in TensorFlow this time, so I will keep a memo so that I don&amp;rsquo;t forget the know-how at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About torch summary can be really used when building a model with Pytorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-torch-summary-can-be-really-used-when-building-a-model-with-pytorch-bfd8f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-torch-summary-can-be-really-used-when-building-a-model-with-pytorch-bfd8f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am building my own model and always ask &amp;ldquo;What is the feature quantity of the input?&amp;rdquo; before connecting to the fully connected layer. If you often type print(model), you can understand the structure of the model, but you can not confirm up to the size of FeatureMap. So, the convenient one is torchsummary.
Who is #torchsummary?
Simply put, you can check the size of the feature map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing her with Python ~Tinder automation project~ Episode 6</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introducing-her-with-python-~tinder-automation-project~-episode-6-4a70f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introducing-her-with-python-~tinder-automation-project~-episode-6-4a70f/</guid>
      <description>#table of contents      What I did Main events     Episode 1 Automatic right swipe    Episode 2 Automatic message transmission Matched with a woman   [Episode 3] ep.3 [Library] ep.3 Exchanged LINE with a matched woman   Episode 3.5 Re-obtaining access token The token could not be obtained with the code so far   Episode 4 Data collection LINE no longer responds   Episode 5 Data analysis profile sentence I was recommended by the people I became friends with for information products   Episode 6 Data analysis image edition Recent acquaintance girls call me late at night (?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>