<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Django on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/django/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Django on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/django/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to know more about individual developers. YouDev has been released.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-know-more-about-individual-developers.-youdev-has-been-released.-ae2cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-know-more-about-individual-developers.-youdev-has-been-released.-ae2cd/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img width=&amp;quot;610&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;eyecatch.png&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/634341/275b16c8-3136-198f-fa76-a17a4cbb41e1.png&amp;quot;&amp;gt;  YouDev has been released. 2020.5.01
YouDev is a service that focuses on individual developers to let them know more about them (I want to know&amp;hellip;).
Even if the service is recognized, I think that the developers have not hit the spot, so individual developers may not only appeal the services released by themselves, but also the developers themselves. I created it.
I&amp;rsquo;m always looking for individual developers, so I&amp;rsquo;m an individual developer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Rebuild Django development environment with Docker! ! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/rebuild-django-development-environment-with-docker-e345f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/rebuild-django-development-environment-with-docker-e345f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I wrote this article before. [Build Django development environment with Docker! (Docker-compose/Django/postgreSQL/nginx)]](https://qiita.com/nokonoko_1203/items/242367a83c313a5e46bf)
The original article was written a long time ago (a year or so?), but now that I have enough knowledge, I thought I could make it a little better, so I decided to try it!
I will not talk about installing Docker in detail, so if you are interested, please check the original article! (Here)willhelp.)
Also, as a clear difference from the previous article, Django thinks as an API delivery server and assumes Vue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Implement JWT login function in Django REST framework</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implement-jwt-login-function-in-django-rest-framework-bc32b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implement-jwt-login-function-in-django-rest-framework-bc32b/</guid>
      <description># Previous article   Django REST framework + Vue.js &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s make SEIYU-like EC site&amp;rdquo; 6 times (plan) Let&amp;rsquo;s create a SEIYU-like EC site (1) Requirements analysis and project initialization Let&amp;rsquo;s create a SEIYU-like EC site (2) Renew the management screen using Xadmin Let&amp;rsquo;s make an SEIYU-like EC site (3) Let&amp;rsquo;s make an explosion API with Django REST framework Create a SEIYU-like EC site (4) Use Vue.js project initialization TypeScript  Even if you do not see the contents so far, you can understand the contents of this time, so I hope that you can have a relationship until the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A story about making a web application that records extensive reading with Django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-making-a-web-application-that-records-extensive-reading-with-django-7c44d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-making-a-web-application-that-records-extensive-reading-with-django-7c44d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Extensive reading of English, it is troublesome to open and record an extensive reading notebook every time I read, and I can&amp;rsquo;t maintain my motivation. ． ． So I made the extensive reading notebook a web application. What I made → https://tadokuapp.herokuapp.com/tadoku/
#function It is not so nice to list dates, titles, word counts, etc. like a paper extensive reader, so the word counts are displayed on the calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Suddenly, if you want to make an inquiry form</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-suddenly-if-you-want-to-make-an-inquiry-form-1b0ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-suddenly-if-you-want-to-make-an-inquiry-form-1b0ba/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you. It is Taro Man.  I usually develop web services.
-Siltrend
#Introduction The other day, suddenly, I wanted to prepare an inquiry form, Furthermore, I wanted to send the contents to my email address, Implemented with Python.
Overall picture In this article, I use Django. Django is very convenient.
#Form definition Form definition is done in forms.py.
Basically, it is created by importing Django standard features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to publish a product at the lowest cost</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-publish-a-product-at-the-lowest-cost-cea8c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-publish-a-product-at-the-lowest-cost-cea8c/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you. It is Taro Man.  I usually develop web services.
-Siltrend
#Introduction 彡(゜)(゜) &amp;ldquo;I want to make a service and publish it~&amp;rdquo; 彡(゜)(゜) &amp;ldquo;But, renting a rental server is a hassle**&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; 彡(゜)(゜) &amp;ldquo;** Server fee ** I don&amp;rsquo;t want to pay&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Have you ever felt this way? There must be.
Use the Heroku Free Plan for that. In this article, I will write about how to publish your application with Heroku&amp;rsquo;s free plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Articles that will allow system development with Django (Python)_Introduction</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/articles-that-will-allow-system-development-with-django-python_introduction-ed641/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/articles-that-will-allow-system-development-with-django-python_introduction-ed641/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Programming such as Python has become more familiar than before There are various obstacles to the challenge of service development.
** &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t graduate from the copybooks for introductory books and tutorials&amp;rdquo; ** &amp;ldquo;I tried making it with copy and paste, but I can&amp;rsquo;t arrange it after that&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I am not confident that the code I wrote is correct&amp;rdquo;
When these are analyzed, they can be decomposed into 5 factors as shown in the figure below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is it still exhausted by MVC? ~ SPA development started with Django x React ~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</guid>
      <description>Recently, sites using JS framework are increasing.  In particular, JS frameworks such as React and Vue are often used for application development called SPA and bring many benefits not only to users of the site but also to developers.
Assumed readers  Web development experience People who have developed web applications using API Someone who knows JavaScript a lot and Python a little I know a little about Django People who have developed using MVC or MTV  There is an article written in more detail in another article, so please see here if you feel that this article is difficult or if you want to learn more deeply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning roadmap that allows you to develop and publish services from scratch with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-roadmap-that-allows-you-to-develop-and-publish-services-from-scratch-with-python-52a3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-roadmap-that-allows-you-to-develop-and-publish-services-from-scratch-with-python-52a3b/</guid>
      <description>## at first  This article aims to &amp;ldquo;be able to develop services with Python from no programming experience&amp;rdquo;, We have arranged the skills to be learned as a learning roadmap.
** 2-3 hours every day (+2 hours on Saturdays and Sundays) ** If you continue, it will be completed in a minimum of 3 months. You can skip the skills you have already learned and proceed.
The outline is the same for other languages such as Ruby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build a Django development environment with Docker! (Docker-compose/Django/postgreSQL/nginx)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-a-django-development-environment-with-docker-docker-compose-django-postgresql-nginx-24236/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-a-django-development-environment-with-docker-docker-compose-django-postgresql-nginx-24236/</guid>
      <description>I tried rebuilding!  Rebuild Django development environment with Docker! ! ! ! 
#Introduction
Team development&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s very difficult to build an environment&amp;hellip; At that time, use Docker (miscellaneous).
This article is a repost of what I gave to qrunchLet&amp;rsquo;s build a Django/postgreSQL/gunicorn/nginx development environment using Docker and Docker-compose, which are very convenient for team development! !
The whole flow is based on almost the following sites, but I intend to make the article easy to understand, such as putting comments in almost all lines of the configuration file etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Starter Kit No.1] Build an automatic data collection bot system with Scrapy&amp;MariaDB&amp;Django&amp;Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/starter-kit-no.1-build-an-automatic-data-collection-bot-system-with-scrapymariadbdjangodocker-dfde3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/starter-kit-no.1-build-an-automatic-data-collection-bot-system-with-scrapymariadbdjangodocker-dfde3/</guid>
      <description>![screencapture-192-168-99-102-admin-nutrition-item-2019-03-04-15_04_19-1024x686.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/514619/8e65d631-de2a-b0f4-18a4-b427fb78e439.png)  #Background
You can easily create a Web service with your needs by automatically synchronizing the database of Web services in the world and adding added value that the original family does not have.
For example, scrape the data of the EC site and keep it as a database yourself, provide a search method that does not exist in the original home, attach a link, and have a lightweight business model like earning by affiliate at the level of individual business Is possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create a LINEBot with Django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-linebot-with-django-f9aa5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-linebot-with-django-f9aa5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I summarized the article about using LINEBot with Django because it was a little researched and it was old.
For the time being, I will create an Omukai Bot that returns the text sent as an introduction to LINE Bot.
Here article uses SDK, but I&amp;rsquo;m a Python beginner ~~ I can&amp;rsquo;t even throw an HTTP request with Python ~~ I want to do it.
I&amp;rsquo;m a Django beginner with less than a week of Django history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Django personal tips</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-personal-tips-3a0e6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-personal-tips-3a0e6/</guid>
      <description>This article is the last day of [Django Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/django).  #Introduction Nice to meet you. Thank you.
I usually develop web applications using Djnago.
-Sill Trend
This year&amp;rsquo;s Django Advent Calendar 2019 was also enjoyed every day. All the articles were interesting and informative. So, in this article, the last day of the calendar, I&amp;rsquo;d like to organize some basic and personal tips for Django. We hope that this article can help make Django even more popular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What non-programmers and web application developers should do to clear the GeoDjango tutorial at explosive speed</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-non-programmers-and-web-application-developers-should-do-to-clear-the-geodjango-tutorial-at-explosive-speed-f386f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-non-programmers-and-web-application-developers-should-do-to-clear-the-geodjango-tutorial-at-explosive-speed-f386f/</guid>
      <description>This is the 24th day article of [FOSS4G Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/foss4g&amp;quot;FOSS4GAdventCalendar2019&amp;quot;).  Introduction (Conclusion) Non-programmer/web application development beginner clears GeoDjango tutorial (Geospatial information starting with GeoDjango) What to do 0.Recognize that web application development is a stacked learning.
 Go through DjangoGirls Tutorial once to get an overview of website construction and Django. 2.Make a Location-Based Web App With Django and GeoDjango Learn how to operate PostgreSQL using DOCKER. The difficulty is low because you can&amp;rsquo;t ask for RESTful API implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Django 2.2] How to display the relation destination in Django? [List View]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-2.2-how-to-display-the-relation-destination-in-django-list-view-1afae/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-2.2-how-to-display-the-relation-destination-in-django-list-view-1afae/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hello. I&amp;rsquo;m ragnar with 1.5 months of Django experience (in practice). When I started Django, I did a tutorial, but when I actually made it, there were so many new concepts that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure what to do.
The first thing that got stuck was relations. Before handling Django, I wrote SQL and operated on DB, so I am not familiar with the concept of Queryset, can I get data with this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create Nginx &#43; uWSGI &#43; Python (Django) environment with docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-nginx-uwsgi-python-django-environment-with-docker-7d72d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-nginx-uwsgi-python-django-environment-with-docker-7d72d/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 16th day of [Web Crew Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/webcrew).  Yesterday was @Hideto-Kiyoshima-wc&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Scala Option/Either/Try Super.
#Introduction My name is @yagiyuuuu, my second year since joining Web Crew Co., Ltd. with a fresh graduate. Currently, I am developing an application environment of Nginx + uWSGI + Python (Django) using Docker. I&amp;rsquo;ve written this article in the hope that it will help anyone developing apps with Django.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Overview of class-based generic view and inherited class relationship</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/overview-of-class-based-generic-view-and-inherited-class-relationship-eb2dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/overview-of-class-based-generic-view-and-inherited-class-relationship-eb2dd/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 13th day of Django Advent Calendar 2019.  In this article, I would like to summarize Django&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Class-based Generic View&amp;rdquo; and its inheritance class relationships.
Premise I refer to and cite the official documentation of Django 3.0, which is the latest version at the time of writing this article.
What is a Class-Based Generic View? First, a &amp;ldquo;view&amp;rdquo; in Django is an encapsulation [^1] of logic that processes user requests and returns responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Steps to develop Django with VSCode</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/steps-to-develop-django-with-vscode-12a5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/steps-to-develop-django-with-vscode-12a5d/</guid>
      <description>2020/03/13 Modified slightly to match VSCode Version 1.43.0  Introduction A beginner yearned for the word debug, and learned that VS Code can actually do it, and tried setting it. The memorandum. I think that the advantage is that once you set it, you can enter the virtual environment and run the server just by pressing the Debug button. You can save yourself the trouble of going back and forth between the browser and Terminal and VS Code and entering source myenv/bin/activate or python manage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I haven&#39;t read the official documentation properly until I understand Django&#39;s static files</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-havent-read-the-official-documentation-properly-until-i-understand-djangos-static-files-109b6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-havent-read-the-official-documentation-properly-until-i-understand-djangos-static-files-109b6/</guid>
      <description>This is the 11th day of the Advent Calendar.  #Introduction Weekend/midnight Pythonista. It&amp;rsquo;s a person who flutters around pandas, numpy, scipy when collecting data at work. As a hobby, I often stumbled on static files when using Django, so I&amp;rsquo;d like to be able to summarize the stumbling points and solutions for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know what they don&amp;rsquo;t understand. We would appreciate if you could point out any mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] To celebrate the release of Django 3.0, I tried ASGI, the spiritual successor to WSGI, but couldn&#39;t use websocket</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/to-celebrate-the-release-of-django-3.0-i-tried-asgi-the-spiritual-successor-to-wsgi-but-couldnt-use-websocket-d7087/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/to-celebrate-the-release-of-django-3.0-i-tried-asgi-the-spiritual-successor-to-wsgi-but-couldnt-use-websocket-d7087/</guid>
      <description># Celebration! Django 3.0 released!  02/12/2019 Django 3.0 has been released. Django 1.0 was released in 2008 and 2.0 was released in December 2017. And 3.0 was released on 12/2 of this year. The upgrade from 1 to 2 took about 10 years, but from 2 to 3 it took less than 2 years, which is a surprising sense of speed. On the other hand, what have I been doing over the last two years?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Asynchronous processing implementation in Django (Celery, Redis)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/asynchronous-processing-implementation-in-django-celery-redis-ded69/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/asynchronous-processing-implementation-in-django-celery-redis-ded69/</guid>
      <description>#About this article  I think that asynchronous processing is essential when creating a web application with Django, and I would like to introduce its introduction with examples. The software to use is Celery(celery), ・About asynchronous processing by django+Celery ・How to implement asynchronous processing with Django I implemented it by referring to the article around here.
##environment ・Python 3.6.8 ・Django 2.2.7 ・CentOS7
What is asynchronous processing? Actually, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know the word asynchronous processing until I actually encountered the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried Django 3.0 asynchronous server</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-django-3.0-asynchronous-server-17cff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-django-3.0-asynchronous-server-17cff/</guid>
      <description>#Foreword  Django 3.0 was officially released 3 days ago. Release node link I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in the addition of ASGI support, among many changes, I want to actually use it. :sunny:
Note: What is ASGI?:briefcase: ASGI (Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface) is the spiritual successor to WSGI and aims to provide a standard interface between asynchronous-enabled Python web servers, frameworks, and applications. While WSGI provided the standard for synchronous Python apps, ASGI provides both asynchronous and synchronous apps with a backwards-compatible implementation of WSGI and multiple servers and application frameworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Hit the Spotify API with Django.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hit-the-spotify-api-with-django.-e991c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hit-the-spotify-api-with-django.-e991c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is from Django Advent Calendar 2019. The target audience is for those who are new to Django.
The previous article was about @yuu-eguci&amp;rsquo;s 500 error. https://qiita.com/yuu-eguci/items/a1e4b0a2f238d5ccc985
This article is about trying to execute Spotify API with Django.
Advance preparation I need to create a user account for Spotify, but the following article by Class Method is very helpful. https://dev.classmethod.jp/etc/about-using-of-spotify-api/
If you want to execute the sample code of the article, please download the chart data in CSV format from the following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deploy Django in 3 minutes using docker-compose</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deploy-django-in-3-minutes-using-docker-compose-d3a56/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deploy-django-in-3-minutes-using-docker-compose-d3a56/</guid>
      <description>I have created docker-compose in a form that can be used even for projects that have already been created, so I will summarize the specifications in an article.  ** Please see How to Use on GitHub → GitHub**
(I&amp;rsquo;m sorry if you change the DB from the default sqlite&amp;hellip;
The deployment environment is Django＋Nginx＋Gunicorn.
Overview Please refer to the README on GitHub for how to use the link provided above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The world changed when I opened a large Python project (Django) with Sourcetrail (Linux)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-world-changed-when-i-opened-a-large-python-project-django-with-sourcetrail-linux-410c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-world-changed-when-i-opened-a-large-python-project-django-with-sourcetrail-linux-410c3/</guid>
      <description>It seems that a tool called Sourcetrail has been released and it seems interesting, so I tried it.  There was an article you have already touched, but it is charming. Ubuntu.
I used it, and the big repository that I can think of was Django, so I will try it with a combination of Python and Django.
Install SourceTrail You can download it from Sourcetrail(GitHub) Release Page. Download 64-bit Linux tar file</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Django Server Error (500) strategy [2019 adokare]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-server-error-500-strategy-2019-adokare-a1e4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-server-error-500-strategy-2019-adokare-a1e4b/</guid>
      <description>This is my first time joining the Advent Calendar. Thank you.  Overview My hobby is Pythonista. This year I introduced to Django and made a website. This time, for the same Django beginner as I am, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to write a rough guide to how to get rid of things that will bother you and make you cry. It is Server Error (500).
At this time, try to display the error content on the screen even temporarily, output a log, or notify Slack of the error content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Django crispy tutorial (Environment construction on Mac)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-crispy-tutorial-environment-construction-on-mac-01332/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-crispy-tutorial-environment-construction-on-mac-01332/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Introduction&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;   Hello. I&#39;m Sugimoto. I wrote this article for you there, &#34;I would like to make a website in Python.&#34; &#34;I read the net and reference books about Django but I don&#39;t understand it.&#34; I&#39;m writing this for beginners and beginners, so I won&#39;t explain it in depth. please note that. After that, the following is assumed.  Python 3 or higher is installed.  I know a few Linux commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create a scraping app with Python&#43;Django&#43;AWS and change jobs</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-scraping-app-with-python-django-aws-and-change-jobs-a9464/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-scraping-app-with-python-django-aws-and-change-jobs-a9464/</guid>
      <description>My name is mogken and I am in the business planning office of an IT venture company.  Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about changing jobs, and I&amp;rsquo;m studying programming to make it appeal to me. It&amp;rsquo;s not so appealing to say that you&amp;rsquo;re just studying with your mouth, so I made a simple web app with Python and Django, built it on AWS, and released the source to Github.
This time, I would like to explain the program (Python) I wrote myself, which also serves as an output for the fixation of knowledge within me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] [Django] How to use ChoiceField and add options</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-django-how-to-use-choicefield-and-add-options-1427a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-django-how-to-use-choicefield-and-add-options-1427a/</guid>
      <description># Overview  I&amp;rsquo;m touching the Choice Field in Django, and I&amp;rsquo;ll leave the time-consuming part as a memorandum. Sample code here
table of contents -About ChoiceField -Sample -Time-consuming part -How to add options later -Field&amp;rsquo;s choices property -ChoiceField code to add choice later
About # ChoiceField -Field to choose one from multiple options -Default drawing is django.forms.widgets.Select -When drawn in the template, it becomes &amp;lt;select name=&amp;quot;field name&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;option value=&amp;quot;choice.key&amp;quot;&amp;gt;choice.value&amp;lt;/option&amp;gt;...&amp;lt;/select&amp;gt; -Reference: Form Fields: ChoiceField</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Django 1.11 LTS Summary of major changes</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-1.11-lts-summary-of-major-changes-f97e5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-1.11-lts-summary-of-major-changes-f97e5/</guid>
      <description>Django 1.11 LTS has been released on April 4, 2017!  Since this version is LTS (Long Term Support), the support period is longer than the non-LTS version. For details on the support period, please check the following URL &amp;ldquo;Supported Versions&amp;rdquo;. https://www.djangoproject.com/download/
Then, I will explain the major changes in release notes.
Python2 support lasted 1.11 1.11 is the last version that supports Python2. From 2.0 below, only Python3 will be supported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Django entry point reading comprehension-manage.py</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-entry-point-reading-comprehension-manage.py-f8ba1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-entry-point-reading-comprehension-manage.py-f8ba1/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  This article is the second day of Django Advent Calendar 2016.
What to do here I will pursue the entry points of Django, also for my own study. There are two ways to run a Django application, each with a different entry point.
 manage.py wsgi.py  This time, we will take up manage.py.
Referenced The explanation by Mr. tokibito is very easy to understand and it will be a great learning experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easy to understand Python web application (Django) for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/easy-to-understand-python-web-application-django-for-beginners-4-introduction-to-routing-settings-and-mtv-design-patterns-fbd23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/easy-to-understand-python-web-application-django-for-beginners-4-introduction-to-routing-settings-and-mtv-design-patterns-fbd23/</guid>
      <description>#Composition of commentary articles     No. Title      1 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (1) [Environment]    2 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (2) [Project creation]    3 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (3) [Application creation/DB setting]    4 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns] ←   5 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (5) [Introduction to DB operation with Django shell]    6 Explanation of Python Web application (Django) for beginners (6) [MTV design pattern completion]     Development environment  OS: Mac OS Sierra (10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Install Python3 and Django on Amazon Linux (EC2) and run the web server</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/install-python3-and-django-on-amazon-linux-ec2-and-run-the-web-server-f9cf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/install-python3-and-django-on-amazon-linux-ec2-and-run-the-web-server-f9cf3/</guid>
      <description>Leave it as a memo instead.  It is a premise that the instance is staggered.
##Install Python3 The version of Python originally included in Amazon Linux is 2.7.12. That&amp;rsquo;s why I will install Python 3 series this time. Fortunately, Python3 is collected in YUM&amp;rsquo;s amzn-main repository.
# yum list | grep python35 python35.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-devel.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-libs.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-pip.noarch 6.1.1-1.23.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-setuptools.noarch 12.2-1.32.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-tools.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-virtualenv.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create a file uploader with Django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-file-uploader-with-django-f7b1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-file-uploader-with-django-f7b1b/</guid>
      <description>Updated with old info and ugly code. (2017/03/16)  Environment  Python 3.5.1 Django 1.9.1 Virtualenv 15.0.1 OS X El Capitan 10.11.6  Final configuration file_uploader ├── db.sqlite3 ├── file_uploader │ ├── __init__.py │ ├── settings.py │ ├── urls.py │ └── wsgi.py ├── manage.py ├── requirements.txt └── upload_form ├── __init__.py ├── admin.py ├── apps.py ├── migrations │ ├── 0001_initial.py │ └── __init__.py ├── models.py ├── static │ └── files │ └── __init__.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Tips] How to do template extends when creating HTML with django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tips-how-to-do-template-extends-when-creating-html-with-django-fcea8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tips-how-to-do-template-extends-when-creating-html-with-django-fcea8/</guid>
      <description>#Overview   Configuration of rough html templates when inheriting Tips on how to use tag important point  #background
 References: django document version 1.9 Django version: 1.9.2 python version: 2.7.10 OS: MacOS X  Things that the creator should decide for themselves are written in upper case, and the rest are written in lower case. Variable name or file name.
Configuration of html templates when inheriting Since I introduced on the official website an efficient method when writing html using template extends, it is almost a translation of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python Django Tutorial (4)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-django-tutorial-4-fef30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-django-tutorial-4-fef30/</guid>
      <description>Materials for study sessions.  I will explain it by following the tutorial of django 1.8. https://docs.djangoproject.com/en/1.8/intro/tutorial04/
The official Japanese document version 1.4 is the latest, so there are some differences, but the general flow is the same, so it is a good idea to read it. http://django-docs-ja.readthedocs.org/en/latest/intro/tutorial04.html
Tutorial 1 Tutorial 2 Tutorial 3
→ Tutorial Summary Create voting form Source: 99b01e3 → 49d2e35
First, let&amp;rsquo;s rewrite detail.html for voting according to the original tutorial so that we can vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Using Unicode 6.0 emoji with django/MySQL</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/using-unicode-6.0-emoji-with-django-mysql-ffc99/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/using-unicode-6.0-emoji-with-django-mysql-ffc99/</guid>
      <description># Purpose  From djangoEmojiaddedinUnicode6.0.
Operating environment  Python 3.2.0 or higher (confirmed to work with 3.4.3) Django 1.4.0 or higher? (Operation confirmed with 1.7.0, 1.8.1) mysqlclient(operationconfirmedwith1.3.3,1.3.6) MySQL 5.5.14 or later (operation confirmed with 5.5.40, 5.6.16)  Python Python 3.2.0 or higher is required to use Unicode 6.0 emoji.
django I haven&amp;rsquo;t exhausted the list of compatible versions of django. It works because it works on 1.7.0 and 1.8.1.
mysqlclient Use mysqlclient for Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Shorten the if-else of Django Template</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/shorten-the-if-else-of-django-template-f85e4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/shorten-the-if-else-of-django-template-f85e4/</guid>
      <description>Shorten the if-else of #Django Template  When using Bootstrap.css in combination with Django&amp;rsquo;s template engine
{% if param.status == 1 %} &amp;lt;!-- Add a class name of active under certain conditions --&amp;gt; &amp;lt;li class=&amp;#34;active&amp;#34;&amp;gt; {% else %} &amp;lt;li&amp;gt; {% endif %} &amp;lt;a href=&amp;#34;#&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Active&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt; ...... Sometimes you have to write something like The indentation gets tricky, It&amp;rsquo;s hard to see how many lines are spent doing all this.
So when I tried to find out how to write it short, I found a built-in filter called &amp;ldquo;yesno&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Set up Django development environment using homebrew on MacOSX Mavericks (10.9)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/set-up-django-development-environment-using-homebrew-on-macosx-mavericks-10.9-f9a01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/set-up-django-development-environment-using-homebrew-on-macosx-mavericks-10.9-f9a01/</guid>
      <description>## I was annoyed by ImportError  Install python with homebrew and django with pip. However, it fails when the server starts.
$ python manage.py runserver  ImportError: No module named django.core.management
 Actually, Python is included in the Mac from the beginning Launch the Terminal app and check the version
$ python --version  Python 2.7.5
 I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice this, and I thought it was Python installed with homebrew.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>