<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Web on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Web on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Prepare a pseudo API server using GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/prepare-a-pseudo-api-server-using-github-actions-e7021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/prepare-a-pseudo-api-server-using-github-actions-e7021/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Perhaps recently, a feature called GitHub Actions has been added. This is the one that can fire certain Actions (shell script executions) for certain events. For example, it is a function for so-called CI/CD that builds when PR of dev branch is merged and pushes it to dev-pages branch.
At this time, I participated in the COVID-19 countermeasure site Hokkaido version, which is currently a big move, and developed using this function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A network diagram was created with COVID-19 data.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-network-diagram-was-created-with-covid-19-data.-204a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-network-diagram-was-created-with-covid-19-data.-204a2/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Create a graph, network diagram, and data table based on the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare COVID-19 infection status data and create a Web application. Did. The created app will be the one with the link below.
App link: https://chomoku.herokuapp.com/covid-19
Below is the screen of the network diagram.
&amp;lt; /a&amp;gt;
The data used is obtained from the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare website. Scraping is just using the pandas read_html function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python newbie tried Hello World in 30 seconds using micro framework Flask</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-newbie-tried-hello-world-in-30-seconds-using-micro-framework-flask-44f93/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-newbie-tried-hello-world-in-30-seconds-using-micro-framework-flask-44f93/</guid>
      <description>## What is Flask   Python micro web framework Minimal functionality provided as standard Django for full stack framework Reference -Comparison of 4 types of Python Web framework  about me Python history 3 days
Reason for doing looks fun
What I did ** ① Flask installation **
pip install Flask ** ② Make hello.py in your favorite folder ** ③ Paste the following
from flask import Flask app = Flask(__name__) @app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easy to understand Python web application (Django) for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/easy-to-understand-python-web-application-django-for-beginners-4-introduction-to-routing-settings-and-mtv-design-patterns-fbd23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/easy-to-understand-python-web-application-django-for-beginners-4-introduction-to-routing-settings-and-mtv-design-patterns-fbd23/</guid>
      <description>#Composition of commentary articles     No. Title      1 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (1) [Environment]    2 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (2) [Project creation]    3 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (3) [Application creation/DB setting]    4 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns] ←   5 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (5) [Introduction to DB operation with Django shell]    6 Explanation of Python Web application (Django) for beginners (6) [MTV design pattern completion]     Development environment  OS: Mac OS Sierra (10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>