<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Blockchain on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/blockchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Blockchain on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Implement blockchain in about 60 lines</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implement-blockchain-in-about-60-lines-e1022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implement-blockchain-in-about-60-lines-e1022/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In the course of Udemy, I roughly understood the contents of the blockchain, so I implemented it. I implement it by myself based on the contents of the course. Mr. Jun Sakai, an active engineer of Silicon Valley, teaches in this course, and by taking the course, you will be able to create the following programs without looking at them. This post also implements wallet and proof_of_work that are not implemented, so if you are interested, please take this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hash chain, a data structure that grows with history</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hash-chain-a-data-structure-that-grows-with-history-727b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hash-chain-a-data-structure-that-grows-with-history-727b1/</guid>
      <description>This article is the data structure and algorithm Advent Calendar 2019 Day 18 article.  On the 17th day, @takilog wrote about &amp;ldquo;Fréchet distance calculation algorithm&amp;rdquo;. It was interesting, so I decided to study a little! On the 19th day, I&amp;rsquo;m in charge of @tsukasa__diary!
Blockchain technology has been attracting attention in various fields such as cryptographic assets, traceability, and intellectual property management as tamper resistant technology. One of the things that play a major role in improving the security of such blockchains is the hash chain data structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Ikiri high school students will explain blockchain to beginners in 10 minutes! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-ikiri-high-school-students-will-explain-blockchain-to-beginners-in-10-minutes-f4991/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-ikiri-high-school-students-will-explain-blockchain-to-beginners-in-10-minutes-f4991/</guid>
      <description>#1. About this article  ##1-1. Introduction This article was touched by me as a high school student when I received [Udemy: An Introduction to Blockchain Development from Scratch Beginning with Python Taught by Active Silicon Valley Engineers](https://www.udemy.com/share/1021OSAkIbdVdQQXo=/) , I wrote this article with the hope that everyone reading this article should attend. I completed this lesson in 2 days, so if you are already accustomed to development, I think it is sufficiently possible to understand and implement in 1 day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I implemented a blockchain that actually moves in about 170 lines</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-implemented-a-blockchain-that-actually-moves-in-about-170-lines-2afe4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-implemented-a-blockchain-that-actually-moves-in-about-170-lines-2afe4/</guid>
      <description>This article is day 6 of [Blockchain Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/blockchain).Yesterdaywas@y-chan&#39;s[Understandingatomicswap](https://qiita.com/y-chan/items/f69b628f65ce12097e4a).   Occurrence of things &amp;ldquo;There are a lot of blockchain commentary books out there, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how it will end up.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Structural blockchain seems easy, but I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand how to make the contents of the block or the mechanism of mining.&amp;rdquo;
I thought &amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t understand the explanation, it&amp;rsquo;s a programmer who should implement it by Mumu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>