<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Dash on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/dash/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Dash on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/dash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Created a new Kyoto corona app with Python web framework Dash</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/created-a-new-kyoto-corona-app-with-python-web-framework-dash-0bd9e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/created-a-new-kyoto-corona-app-with-python-web-framework-dash-0bd9e/</guid>
      <description>I created a new Kyoto corona app using the Python web framework Dash. [Dash](https://dash.plotly.com/) is a framework created using Flask, React, and Plotly, which allows you to quickly create dashboard-like applications. You can also use callbacks to drive your application interactively. It&#39;s a framework that makes it easy for people who like data kneading like me but who don&#39;t know React or Vue very well.  The created application can be found at the following URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Visualize coronavirus infection status with Plotly [For beginners]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/visualize-coronavirus-infection-status-with-plotly-for-beginners-507cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/visualize-coronavirus-infection-status-with-plotly-for-beginners-507cf/</guid>
      <description>Next time https://qiita.com/Naoya_Study/items/851f4032fb6e2a5cd5ed  With the spread of coronavirus infection, various organizations have released cool dashboards that visualize the infection status.
Example 1 WHO Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) Situation Example 2 Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare new coronavirus infection domestic case Example 3 Toyo Keizai ONLINE New Coronavirus Domestic Infection Status It is cool! I want to be able to make this myself. The goal is to create a dashboard like the one above using Python&amp;rsquo;s visualization-specific data frame Dash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A network diagram was created with COVID-19 data.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-network-diagram-was-created-with-covid-19-data.-204a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-network-diagram-was-created-with-covid-19-data.-204a2/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Create a graph, network diagram, and data table based on the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare COVID-19 infection status data and create a Web application. Did. The created app will be the one with the link below.
App link: https://chomoku.herokuapp.com/covid-19
Below is the screen of the network diagram.
&amp;lt; /a&amp;gt;
The data used is obtained from the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare website. Scraping is just using the pandas read_html function.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>