<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> learning on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  learning on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anyway, I gathered a site where you can learn basic free Pythonmachine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/anyway-i-gathered-a-site-where-you-can-learn-basic-free-pythonmachine-learning-823e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/anyway-i-gathered-a-site-where-you-can-learn-basic-free-pythonmachine-learning-823e3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I will introduce the sites that I collected by surfing the net with only the name, link and a brief description. (Add links etc. at any time) I would be happy if you could introduce the site in the comments. We do not include famous sites such as Progate and dot installation. We also introduce a blog. Please note that the contents are not explained. Let&amp;rsquo;s go.
#Codeprep Format: Exercise Price: All free Learning scope: Basic grammar, data manipulation, NumPy, Pandas, OOP It is a fill-in-the-blank format and does not require environment construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I thought about how to learn programming for free.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-thought-about-how-to-learn-programming-for-free.-97e12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-thought-about-how-to-learn-programming-for-free.-97e12/</guid>
      <description># Background  I thought about a low-cost way to learn programming from an empty situation. (Mac) Is the continuation of.
This time, I summarized how to take a smartphone and learn the program for free for those who are new to buying a PC.
OPAC-Library search system Perhaps it is OPAC that university graduates know but middle and high school graduates do not. If you are a university, you will be asked at the first orientation of your first year to search for books, magazines, papers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>