<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Windows on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Windows on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to insert NEologd dictionary in Windows relatively easily-system dictionary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e491f1712/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e491f1712/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I used WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux)+Ubuntu to install the NEologd dictionary for MeCab morphological analysis, but it was relatively easy to install with git for Windows and 7-zip.
Since I wrote about user dictionaries in the previous article ↓, this time it is the system dictionary. https://qiita.com/zincjp/items/c61c441426b9482b5a48
#environment Windows10 64bit Language: Japanese MeCab 0.996-32bit
What to introduce git for Windows 2.20.1 64-bit 7-Zip 18.06 64-bit #Introduction procedure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The matter that was skipped to Microsoft Store when trying to execute Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2f2e5e5a6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2f2e5e5a6/</guid>
      <description>## Target audience   People who started to run Python with PowerShell and were skipped to the Microsoft Store People who ran a Python script with PowerShell and nothing happened Those who have already set the path and were able to run Python originally  ##environment
 Windows10 Home Anaconda3  Conclusion ~~ Although the cause is unknown ~~ It seems that the following path is referenced. Let&amp;rsquo;s change the order of environment variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to install Deep Learning Framework Tensorflow 1.0 on Windows Anaconda environment</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fe4c791b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fe4c791b3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Until now, we have been doing deep learning by running Tensorflow on the back end of Keras. If you just do machine learning in Python, you can use Keras as before, but there are applications where you want to use models and weights learned in Python in C++. Actually, it would be nice to use a model trained with Keras, but it seems easier to code directly with Tensorflow which also has a C++ API, so I will try to attack from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Start a batch file from Python and pass variables.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f953e92d7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f953e92d7/</guid>
      <description># What is a batch file?  This is a file that describes a series of commands executed on Windows. There are two types of batch files with the extension &amp;ldquo;.bat&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;.cmd&amp;rdquo;, but the operation is basically the same. If you would like to know more about this difference, please refer to the following articles. What is .cmd (extension)
Why do you need this feature? It was difficult to learn batch commands simply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The easiest way to put Chainer v1.5&#43;CUDA&#43;cuDNN on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f985b9da6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f985b9da6/</guid>
      <description>Chainer now depends on Cython, h5py since 1.5. The installation method on Windows is described in [2nd day article (Install Chainer 1.5.0 on Windows)](http://qiita.com/icoxfog417/items/ca1521f9d62183cea234) I would like to add some supplements so that you can easily use proper Chainer on Windows.  This content may contain errors. We will update as soon as we notice. Operation reports are welcome. Thank you for your comment
**Note: As of December 10, 2015, Chainer (v1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>