<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> pygame on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/pygame/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  pygame on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/pygame/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a game UI from 1 with pygame2!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/make-a-game-ui-from-1-with-pygame2-4fb17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/make-a-game-ui-from-1-with-pygame2-4fb17/</guid>
      <description># Overview  This article is the 14th day of Future Advent Calendar 2019. Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s article was written by @RuyPKG I want to have fun even with newcomers! ~Preparation of minutes~.
@Shibukawa introduced the game engine at an in-house study session the other day, which is the reason why this article was written. I wanted a UI for a board game implemented in Python, and it was difficult to express movement in HTML, so I decided to try pygame, the Python game engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development of games that take advantage of quantum nature</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/development-of-games-that-take-advantage-of-quantum-nature-52ab9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/development-of-games-that-take-advantage-of-quantum-nature-52ab9/</guid>
      <description>Hello Sugo of Quemix.  Here is an overview of the projects currently underway at IPA&amp;rsquo;s unexplored business. By making a game that includes the properties of quantum, we are going to make two games within the period. This time, we will introduce the first game.
#Notes If you try to explain everything such as the history of the game, the details of the rules, the explanation of quantum, etc. so that it can be understood by those who are new to the game, the amount will be too large, so it is a rather broken introduction Please note.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>