<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> machine learning introduction on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/machine-learning-introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  machine learning introduction on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/machine-learning-introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s take a free Python introductory course for machine learning online until April 27th</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-take-a-free-python-introductory-course-for-machine-learning-online-until-april-27th-93ebf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-take-a-free-python-introductory-course-for-machine-learning-online-until-april-27th-93ebf/</guid>
      <description>Yes~mo :clap:  Today, I&amp;rsquo;m going to take &amp;ldquo;Python introductory course for machine learning **&amp;rdquo; online.
This is an online course for machine learning super beginners, developed by Skill-Up AI Co., Ltd. in cooperation with the Japan Deep Learning Association.
If it is true, it costs about 50,000 yen, but for people who are discerning with the example corona 2020/4/30By 2020/4/27 If you apply, 2020/ You can read the teaching materials until 4/30!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Recommended learning order for beginners of machine learning and deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/recommended-learning-order-for-beginners-of-machine-learning-and-deep-learning-25b08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/recommended-learning-order-for-beginners-of-machine-learning-and-deep-learning-25b08/</guid>
      <description># Target of this article  Purpose of writing the article The words AI and deep learning have been around for a long time, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think there are many people who really understand their meaning. I think it&amp;rsquo;s very dangerous to have a debate about what AI can do, as in Japan today.
I think the reason why there is such a debate about AI in this way is that you do not fully understand the mathematical basis of machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Super introduction] Machine learning using Python-From environment construction to simple perceptron implementation-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/super-introduction-machine-learning-using-python-from-environment-construction-to-simple-perceptron-implementation-365f3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/super-introduction-machine-learning-using-python-from-environment-construction-to-simple-perceptron-implementation-365f3/</guid>
      <description># First of all  This article is from the 7th day of the DMM WEBCAMP Advent Calendar. This time it&amp;rsquo;s a super introduction, so I created it for those who have never tried machine learning but want to start **.
The purpose is to get a rough idea of machine learning and try to implement a basic simple perceptron for the time being, so I&amp;rsquo;ve written a lot about the explanation of machine learning etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>