<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> numpy on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/numpy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  numpy on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/numpy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Application of affine transformation by tensor-From basics to object detection-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/application-of-affine-transformation-by-tensor-from-basics-to-object-detection-11cbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/application-of-affine-transformation-by-tensor-from-basics-to-object-detection-11cbd/</guid>
      <description>This article is about simplifying preprocessing by using affine transformation with tensors. The affine transformation can be applied to images, but the same transformation can be applied to annotations such as Bounding Box. You can also apply different transformations to one object at the same time by extending it to a tensor.  Affine transformation basics The affine transformation represents the movement of points in the following formula.
$$\begin{bmatrix}x&amp;rsquo; \\ y&amp;rsquo;\\ 1 \end{bmatrix} = \begin{bmatrix}a &amp;amp; b &amp;amp; c \\ d &amp;amp; e &amp;amp; f \\ 0 &amp;amp; 0 &amp;amp; 1 \end{bmatrix} \begin{bmatrix}x \\ y \\ 1 \end{bmatrix} \tag{1}$$</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder ABC054 B matrix operation solved with Ruby, Python and numpy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/atcoder-abc054-b-matrix-operation-solved-with-ruby-python-and-numpy-b22db/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/atcoder-abc054-b-matrix-operation-solved-with-ruby-python-and-numpy-b22db/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Beginner Contest B-Template Matching Difficulty: 828
This theme, matrix operation
It&amp;rsquo;s a two-dimensional array, but using a library of matrices can be easier to do.
Ruby require&amp;#39;matrix&amp;#39; class Matrix #Not assignable in v2.3 def []=(i, j, x) @rows[i][j]=x end end n, m = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) rows = Array.new(n + m){gets.chomp.chars.map{|c| (c ==&amp;#39;#&amp;#39;) ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denoising method using wavelet transform</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/denoising-method-using-wavelet-transform-87472/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/denoising-method-using-wavelet-transform-87472/</guid>
      <description>There was a noise removal method that I was convinced that there is a method like this in the kaggle kernel (notebook now), so I will summarize the things I examined about it below with notes.  Method overview An analysis method for a certain signal or waveform is called wavelet transform. I think that I often imagine the Fourier transform as an analysis method, but the Fourier transform expands the waveform to the sum of trigonometric functions (Sain, Kosain), whereas the wavelet transform decomposes it into a waveform of any shape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numpy 100 List of functions that I thought with 100 knocks that I thought This is convenient,</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/numpy-100-list-of-functions-that-i-thought-with-100-knocks-that-i-thought-this-is-convenient-8b2fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/numpy-100-list-of-functions-that-i-thought-with-100-knocks-that-i-thought-this-is-convenient-8b2fb/</guid>
      <description># Overview  I was made to work on 100 knocks of Numpy during the training of the company, but there were many problems that I could not defeat unless I knew the function in the first place, and I realized the lack of knowledge. In this article, I will introduce some of the functions I&amp;rsquo;ve met for the first time that I find useful, as well as a memorandum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of all the Python visualization tools used by active graduate students in their research [Application]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-the-python-visualization-tools-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-application-dfabd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-the-python-visualization-tools-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-application-dfabd/</guid>
      <description>#Continuing from the previous session  This article is an application of Python visualization tools. ~~ Since it has become long, I decided to divide the application into two. (Application 2 is still being written) ~~ The application section was added to this article to make it one. If you are new to Python plot, I wrote the basic version last time, so please check here! #Introduction I am currently a graduate student with a 2nd year master&amp;rsquo;s degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of all Python plots used by active graduate students in their research [Basic]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-python-plots-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-basic-52315/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-python-plots-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-basic-52315/</guid>
      <description>Application section [here](https://qiita.com/coffiego/items/dfabde5f8588723b32d6)  https://qiita.com/coffiego/items/dfabde5f8588723b32d6
#Introduction I am currently a graduate student with a 2nd year master&amp;rsquo;s degree. I am studying the Martian atmosphere using numerical simulation. Since I mainly analyzed the results obtained by numerical simulation using Python, I tried to summarize all the functions used in the process. Please note that this is not an exhaustive list. .. .. However, since I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling to use the documentation, I&amp;rsquo;ve summarized it in the hope that if anyone using Python&amp;rsquo;s visualization tools can help with that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the New Corona really a threat? Verified with Stan (was)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-the-new-corona-really-a-threat-verified-with-stan-was-894dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-the-new-corona-really-a-threat-verified-with-stan-was-894dd/</guid>
      <description>[Notice] [Sequel](https://qiita.com/akeyhero/items/a8aa2d3db2c32c867ff6) is used to determine the lethality rate of COVID-19.  Purpose  Verify if COVID-19&amp;rsquo;s lethality is really high Try the stochastic programming language Stan  What is a probabilistic programming language? It is a programming language that solves nicely by describing statistical relationships (models). As an implementation, it seems to sample by Markov chain Monte Carlo method.
It is not a replacement for the procedural programming language because it has a completely different role and method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scatter rice grains to determine pi (Monte Carlo method)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/scatter-rice-grains-to-determine-pi-monte-carlo-method-2f147/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/scatter-rice-grains-to-determine-pi-monte-carlo-method-2f147/</guid>
      <description># Addition  This is an article that implements the Monte Carlo method. I forgot completely.
1.First of all When I was reading a book for children&amp;rsquo;s statistics [1], I saw an article about spreading rice grains to calculate the pi. It seemed interesting, so I tried to calculate the pi using the randomly generated x, y coordinate data.
[procedure] It&amp;rsquo;s almost like this
 Prepare a square and a circle inscribed in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiita, early Python♪</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/qiita-early-python-be75f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/qiita-early-python-be75f/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;I want to start Python programming, but what should I do?&amp;quot;  I often get the question, so I tried to put together a Qiita page for beginners. Initially
 Python syntax How to use Numpy How to use Pandas How to use matplotlib  I think it is good to take a look at all four.
Python syntax  Python warming up Python Basic Summary Python basic learning  How to use #Numpy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t write Python if you want to speed it up</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/dont-write-python-if-you-want-to-speed-it-up-1c2c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/dont-write-python-if-you-want-to-speed-it-up-1c2c2/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I decided to give a Lightning Talk about Python at work, so I&amp;rsquo;ll write something that can be read in about 5 minutes. The talk theme is &amp;ldquo;Knowledge when trying to speed up in Python&amp;rdquo;. **This isn&amp;rsquo;t an article about Python. **
Target of this article This article is for the following people:
 Python beginner People who are interested in Python but think that it seems not to be speed  Immediate conclusion As the title says, don&amp;rsquo;t write Python (as much as possible) if you want to speed it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NumPy basics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/numpy-basics-3b7ef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/numpy-basics-3b7ef/</guid>
      <description>Features of #NumPy   Compute multidimensional arrays all at once.  ndarray: multidimensional array object  ndarray example  import numpy as np data = np.random.randn(2,3) # random number with 2 columns and 3 rows print(data) # [[-0.4440664 -0.07889544 -0.84781375] # [0.59333292 -0.03008522 1.54106015]] print(data * 10) # multiply # [[-4.44066398 -0.78895438 -8.47813747] # [5.93332925 -0.3008522 15.41060155]] print(data + data) # addition # [[-0.8881328 -0.15779088 -1.69562749] # [1.18666585 -0.06017044 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics with python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/statistics-with-python-25022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/statistics-with-python-25022/</guid>
      <description># Total and average  numpy.sum(data) # sum numpy.mean(data) # mean #Maximum, minimum, and median
numpy.amax(data) numpy.amin(data) numpy.median(data) #dispersion
An index that indicates how far the data is from the average
\sigma^2=\frac{1}{N}\sum_{i=1}^{n} (x_i-\mu)^2 numpy.var(data, ddof = 0) Unbiased distribution The sample variance is a value obtained by further calculating the variance using the sample mean, but this value causes an underestimate bias. Therefore, the one without bias becomes the universal variance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I also wanted to check type hints with numpy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-also-wanted-to-check-type-hints-with-numpy-1f741/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-also-wanted-to-check-type-hints-with-numpy-1f741/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  Type hints added in PEP484 since Python 3.5. I think that it can be applied to ndarray of numpy,anditisatypehintstaticchecktoolmypy, and the results of the wp investigation, such as dealing with third party modules.
Conclusion In conclusion, type hint checking of numpy.ndarray using mypy is possible using numpy-stubs. However, as of now (January 2020), mypy check cannot be performed by specifying the dtype and shape of ndarray. On the other hand, if you want to add type hints including dtype and shape as annotations for readability, the option to use nptyping seems good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to count the number of occurrences of each element included in the list with weight in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-count-the-number-of-occurrences-of-each-element-included-in-the-list-with-weight-in-python-cc3f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-count-the-number-of-occurrences-of-each-element-included-in-the-list-with-weight-in-python-cc3f1/</guid>
      <description># Thing you want to do  Given the following two lists, we want to count the number of occurrences of each element included in a by weighting it with the value of b. Python is 3.7.5.
a = [&amp;#34;A&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;B&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;C&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;A&amp;#34;] b = [1 ,1 ,2 ,2] c = hoge(a, b) print(c) {&amp;quot;A&amp;quot;: 3, &amp;quot;B&amp;quot;: 1, &amp;quot;C&amp;quot;: 2} # I want this output # key and value can be different # ([&amp;quot;A&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;B&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;C&amp;quot;], [3, 1, 2]) *Addition: Comment introduced a simple implementation for the above issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: 3D array image (numpy.array)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-3d-array-image-numpy.array-4cbe3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-3d-array-image-numpy.array-4cbe3/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m not good at imagining a 3D array of numpy with my head, where does axis=1 point? Like so every time, I will summarize my own understanding. Below, &amp;quot;array&amp;quot; refers to np.array.  Trigger In “Essence of Machine Learning” (Author: Koichi Kato), when there is a two-dimensional array X with seven two-dimensional vectors and a two-dimensional array cluster_centers with three two-dimensional vectors, the distance between the two vectors is squared. The calculation for brute force was done as follows (extracted from the third edition pp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to write GP with numpy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-write-gp-with-numpy-10810/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-write-gp-with-numpy-10810/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Nice to meet you, My name is Mimura and I am in charge of the 21st day of Advent Calendar, NTT Docomo Service Innovation Department. This year as well, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write an Advent Calendar with volunteers from DoCoMo, so I&amp;rsquo;d like to write an article.
Suddenly, do you know the regression problem? The regression problem is used in various places such as stock price forecasts. DoCoMo handles this regression problem in various places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Dynamic Mode Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-dynamic-mode-decomposition-702f6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-dynamic-mode-decomposition-702f6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I could only think of Fourier transform or wavelet transform as the method of investigating temporal changes, but I learned that there is a good method called dynamic mode decomposition (DMD) that can extract modes in both temporal and spatial directions. I will record it here in order to deepen my understanding.
The content is almost the same as the reference site, but I will write a slightly translated Google translation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master the comprehension</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/master-the-comprehension-48198/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/master-the-comprehension-48198/</guid>
      <description>#What is a comprehension  Notation that can be used when creating lists and dictionaries in python. Since the for loop is slow in python, comprehension can be used to make a list or dictionary faster when creating a list or dictionary.
Basic When making a list like this.
new_list = [f(myiter) for myiter in origin_list] You can create a dictionary by replacing [] with {}.
new_dict = (indexes[myiter]:f(myiter) \ for myiter in origin_list} The basic pattern is as follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to speed up Pandas apply method with just one sentence (with verification calculation)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-speed-up-pandas-apply-method-with-just-one-sentence-with-verification-calculation-fc4d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-speed-up-pandas-apply-method-with-just-one-sentence-with-verification-calculation-fc4d2/</guid>
      <description>#Conclusion  Just add swifter method before Pandas apply method
Concrete example import pandas as pd import numpy as np import swifter # Create a suitable DataFrame df = pd.DataFrame({&amp;#39;col&amp;#39;: np.random.normal(size=10000000)}) # Add swifter method before apply method. %time df[&amp;#39;col2&amp;#39;] = df[&amp;#39;col&amp;#39;].swifter.apply(lambda x: x**2) # Wall time: 50 ms # For comparison (normal pandas apply method) %time df[&amp;#39;col2&amp;#39;] = df[&amp;#39;col&amp;#39;].apply(lambda x: x**2) # Wall time: 3.48 s How to install $ pip install -U pandas # upgrade pandas $ pip install swifter In case of ```terminal:conda $ conda update pandas # upgrade pandas $ conda install -c conda-forge swifter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do when `Object arrays cannot be loaded when allow_pickle=False` occurs in numpy.load()</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-to-do-when-object-arrays-cannot-be-loaded-when-allow_picklefalse-occurs-in-numpy.load-ee6e1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-to-do-when-object-arrays-cannot-be-loaded-when-allow_picklefalse-occurs-in-numpy.load-ee6e1/</guid>
      <description>- numpy 1.16.3 以降  現象 Pythonコードの例
np.load(&amp;#39;/path/to/file.npy&amp;#39;) 発生するエラーの例
- -------------------------------------------------------------------------- ValueError Traceback (most recent call last) &amp;lt;ipython-input-37-1db66562b57b&amp;gt; in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; - ---&amp;gt; 1 np.load(&#39;tmp.npy&#39;) ~/venv/aep/lib/python3.7/site-packages/numpy/lib/npyio.py in load(file, mmap_mode, allow_pickle, fix_imports, encoding) 451 else: 452 return format.read_array(fid, allow_pickle=allow_pickle, - -&amp;gt; 453 pickle_kwargs=pickle_kwargs) 454 else: 455 # Try a pickle ~/venv/aep/lib/python3.7/site-packages/numpy/lib/format.py in read_array(fp, allow_pickle, pickle_kwargs) 720 # The array contained Python objects. We need to unpickle the data. 721 if not allow_pickle: - -&amp;gt; 722 raise ValueError(&amp;quot;Object arrays cannot be loaded when &amp;quot; 723 &amp;quot;allow_pickle=False&amp;quot;) 724 if pickle_kwargs is None: ValueError: Object arrays cannot be loaded when allow_pickle=False 原因 numpy v1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>