<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> COTOHA on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/cotoha/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  COTOHA on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/cotoha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s right, let&#39;s eat Bubu-zuke. [Natural language processing starting with Kyoto dialect]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/thats-right-lets-eat-bubu-zuke.-natural-language-processing-starting-with-kyoto-dialect-a81d5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/thats-right-lets-eat-bubu-zuke.-natural-language-processing-starting-with-kyoto-dialect-a81d5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I will do natural language processing for the first time. Excited. This article is [Qiita x COTOHA API present project] Let&amp;rsquo;s do text analysis with COTOHA API! ](https://zine.qiita.com/event/collaboration-cotoha-api/?utm_source=qiita&amp;amp;utm_medium=banner) ~~ I want more prizes! ~~ The post was in time.
Immediately the main subject. What to do now First, I will briefly explain what to do. I could do the following ↓
python3 bubuduke.py &amp;quot;Getta&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Do not be good&amp;quot; I will make a Kyoto dialect translator like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will COTOHA exceed humans? Challenge the Japanese test!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/will-cotoha-exceed-humans-challenge-the-japanese-test-668e0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/will-cotoha-exceed-humans-challenge-the-japanese-test-668e0/</guid>
      <description>What is # COTOHA API  The following are the main things you can do with APIs that process natural language and voice provided by NTT Communications.
 Parsing Named entity extraction Proper noun (company name) correction Anaphora analysis Keyword extraction Similarity judgment Sentence type judgment User attribute estimation Stagnation removal Voice recognition error detection Sentiment analysis voice recognition Speech synthesis wrap up  For details, see here This time, I tried the Japanese test using the similarity judgment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responding to Pokemon&#39;s wonderful message by using COTOHA▼</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/responding-to-pokemons-wonderful-message-by-using-cotoha-3e507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/responding-to-pokemons-wonderful-message-by-using-cotoha-3e507/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the # COTOHA world! ▼  This kiji is squid Because I saw a secret ▼▼ Let&amp;#39;s try It’s a lottery ▼▼ [Qiita x COTOHA API present project] Let&amp;rsquo;s do text analysis with COTOHA API! 
#What is Pokemon Nice Message ▼ It is a message display used on the screen of the famous game &amp;ldquo;Pokemon&amp;rdquo; (released from Pokemon)(TheimagebelowisPokemonredandgreen.Fromthegamescreen).The point is that we want to reproduce this (why do you want to do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made an IoT device to naturally learn positive thinking</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-an-iot-device-to-naturally-learn-positive-thinking-75068/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-an-iot-device-to-naturally-learn-positive-thinking-75068/</guid>
      <description>Suddenly, do you know about positive thinking?   Positive thinking (English: positive thinking) is that if you think positively about anything, it will come true and your life will go well [1], try to see the good side of things, It is a thinking method that aims to change the reality by maintaining a simple attitude and changing the &amp;ldquo;thought itself&amp;rdquo;. Positive thinking is said to bring positive reality, and negative thinking brings negative reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have no emotions... ← Try to analyze if there are no emotions using various emotion estimators</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-have-no-emotions...-try-to-analyze-if-there-are-no-emotions-using-various-emotion-estimators-2f70a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-have-no-emotions...-try-to-analyze-if-there-are-no-emotions-using-various-emotion-estimators-2f70a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Human communication includes not only language but also many non-verbal information such as facial expressions and gestures. When analyzing and interpreting human behavior mechanically and programmatically, more information can be obtained by adding meaning to such non-verbal information. These technologies are being researched and developed in various fields such as image processing, natural language processing, and voice recognition, and are expected to be applied in many fields such as marketing and robot interaction systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humans are not so sad creatures</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/humans-are-not-so-sad-creatures-17761/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/humans-are-not-so-sad-creatures-17761/</guid>
      <description>With the birth of the Internet, the world has changed dramatically. Now with just one smartphone, you can instantly do various things such as research, shopping, communication, entertainment consumption, and information dissemination.  As efficiency went on, people&amp;rsquo;s tasks continued to diminish, and even ** began to disappear. **The everyday life is spreading, in which people act like the information recommended by AI and like the posts that everyone likes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have lived a lot of happiness. [Make human disqualification happy using COTOHA API]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-have-lived-a-lot-of-happiness.-make-human-disqualification-happy-using-cotoha-api-972c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-have-lived-a-lot-of-happiness.-make-human-disqualification-happy-using-cotoha-api-972c4/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  During this time, I read Osamu Dazai&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Human Disqualification&amp;rdquo;. Those who have read it will understand, I was reading in a very muddy atmosphere and I felt quite dark.
Well then **Let&amp;rsquo;s rewrite it into a happy sentence. **
Used ・COTOHA API Using the sentiment analysis function, obtain the keyword (emotion keyword) that made the emotion judgment in the sentence and the emotion represented by the emotion keyword.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A program that automatically corrects Takenoko no Sato to Mushroom Mountain</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-program-that-automatically-corrects-takenoko-no-sato-to-mushroom-mountain-a8c7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-program-that-automatically-corrects-takenoko-no-sato-to-mushroom-mountain-a8c7b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction-Introduction of wonderful sweets and the existence of late-deteriorated products-  As you probably know, there is a wonderful sweets called &amp;ldquo;Mushroom Mountain&amp;rdquo;1. A chocolate snack made and sold by Meiji Co., Ltd. since 1975. It has a cute mushroom-like shape with crackers on the stem and chocolate on the umbrella. It was said that the best combination was tried and errored over a development period of 5 years, and while it was easy to hold and functional, it had plenty of chocolate and a moderately salty and crispy feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic quiz generation with COTOHA</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/automatic-quiz-generation-with-cotoha-0329e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/automatic-quiz-generation-with-cotoha-0329e/</guid>
      <description>#1. At the beginning  Qiita made her debut laugh after being taken by something. Previously, I tried to automatically generate a quiz QA using Natural language processing API COTOHA provided by NTT Communications. Every time, a present project with Mr. Qiita was held, so I&amp;rsquo;m really happy. So, I will write about automatic generation of QA quiz using news articles. #2. Development environment *Google Colaboratory *Python3 *COTOHA api (parsing) #3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read a large number of securities reports with COTOHA</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/read-a-large-number-of-securities-reports-with-cotoha-b7a16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/read-a-large-number-of-securities-reports-with-cotoha-b7a16/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I don&amp;rsquo;t know what a financial report is and I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it says, and even if I read the contents of a particular year of a company I want to know, I do not understand unless I compare it with other companies / other years: frowning2: So let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to read a large number of securities reports using COTOHA: wink:
*For basic usage of COTOHA, see @gossy5454&amp;rsquo;s Article</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it possible to extract the profile information of the person from the chat log?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-it-possible-to-extract-the-profile-information-of-the-person-from-the-chat-log-f4cf7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-it-possible-to-extract-the-profile-information-of-the-person-from-the-chat-log-f4cf7/</guid>
      <description>#Purpose   There was an interesting campaign I was wondering how much a person has exposed their profile inadvertently  #Environment or data
Analysis API There is not enough knowledge to do the analysis from scratch by yourself, so this time NTT Communications has published COTOHA API I used.
##raw data This time I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of using the chat log as a base. In Japan, LINE is the mainstream when it comes to chat, but LINE has a chat log export function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To people who are offered but not recruited</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/to-people-who-are-offered-but-not-recruited-0f811/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/to-people-who-are-offered-but-not-recruited-0f811/</guid>
      <description>** [Twitter](https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)introducesartificialintelligenceandarticleswritteninothermedia**,soifyouwanttoknowmoreaboutartificialintelligence,**Pleasefeelfreetofollowus(https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)! **  ** Add Shinjiro Koizumi syntax [Add](https://qiita.com/omiita/items/0f811f15e569bf2539b8#6-%E7%95%AA%E5%A4%96%E7%B7%A8%E5%B0%8F%E6%B3%89%E9%80%B2%E6%AC%A1%E9%83%8E%E6%A7%8B%E6%96%87) Did. ** -- 1. I teach, but I don&amp;rsquo;t explain Prime Minister Abe&amp;rsquo;s Remark &amp;ldquo;I am recruiting but not recruiting&amp;rdquo; I was inspired and created a program that automatically converts the input sentence into a sentence &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m recruiting but not recruiting&amp;rdquo;**!
If you enter &amp;ldquo;Recruit people&amp;rdquo;, it will be converted into the sentence &amp;ldquo;We are recruiting people but not recruiting&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The winner of the one with the highest degree of similarity to the original story in The Most Stupid Hototogisu Won&#39;t Winner</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-winner-of-the-one-with-the-highest-degree-of-similarity-to-the-original-story-in-the-most-stupid-hototogisu-wont-winner-33b69/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-winner-of-the-one-with-the-highest-degree-of-similarity-to-the-original-story-in-the-most-stupid-hototogisu-wont-winner-33b69/</guid>
      <description># Overview  A long time ago, there was a story that said, &amp;ldquo;The most stinky hottogigisu who won the championship 1&amp;rdquo;. If it&#39;s a crow, invite me to nothingness (Izanae) Totogi (Hototogisu) It&amp;rsquo;s like Growing my jet black flame, Firetogisu.
I like all the works, but it&amp;rsquo;s useless even if this kind of hand is too far from the original material, and the best taste is to keep the shape and meaning similar to the original material and to have a sense of jerk I wonder if it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A story of trying to reproduce Katsuno Isono who does not react to inconvenient things by natural language processing.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-of-trying-to-reproduce-katsuno-isono-who-does-not-react-to-inconvenient-things-by-natural-language-processing.-57eb5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-of-trying-to-reproduce-katsuno-isono-who-does-not-react-to-inconvenient-things-by-natural-language-processing.-57eb5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  COTOHA API is a Japanese natural language processing API. It is an API that has various functions and is quite fun to use even a free account can be used 1000/day.
COTOHA API
By the way, do you know Isono-kun? Yes, this is Katsuno Isono from a certain national anime.
The name of this Isono-kun is called something in the play, but when it&amp;rsquo;s inconvenient, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t hear or reacts so-called &amp;ldquo;human-like&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COTOHA API Cornflakes</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/cotoha-api-cornflakes-474ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/cotoha-api-cornflakes-474ca/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a milk boy, please.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Now, I received the unsold chocolates for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind if there&amp;rsquo;s anything like this.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll take you.&amp;rdquo;
What is a milk boy? This is a comedy duo belonging to Yoshimoto Kogyo who won the M-1 Grand Prix 2019. My Navi News has a video of corn flakes, so please check it out. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VjBQtr4lH0k
What is COTOHA API?  Natural language processing technology and speech recognition/synthesis technology that utilize the research results of NTT Group for over 40 years This service is provided so that it can be used easily with API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s do difficult things with COTOHA API-Learn by using Introduction to natural language processing-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-do-difficult-things-with-cotoha-api-learn-by-using-introduction-to-natural-language-processing-0d5b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-do-difficult-things-with-cotoha-api-learn-by-using-introduction-to-natural-language-processing-0d5b5/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the world of natural language processing (NLP) has continued to make remarkable progress. I think many people would like to enter the world of such natural language processing. However, even though it is generally natural language processing, the number of tasks contained in the word is enormous.  &amp;ldquo;What should I start with after all!?&amp;rdquo;
This article is to answer such a voice.
1.First of all This article aims to raise the level of &amp;ldquo;natural language processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whether the COTOHA API can understand Manzai</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/whether-the-cotoha-api-can-understand-manzai-2b81b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/whether-the-cotoha-api-can-understand-manzai-2b81b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article has been entered in Qiita x COTOHA API Present Project.
What is #COTOHA API? It is a service provided by NTT Communications so that APIs can easily use natural language processing technology and speech recognition/synthesis technology that make use of the research results of the NTT Group for over 40 years.
Natural language processing such as syntactic analysis and proper expression extraction, and characteristic &amp;ldquo;summary&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;user attribute estimation&amp;rdquo; can also be used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube live It analyzes the sentiment of the comment and judges the emo part from Youtube LIve.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  It is a suggestion and experiment that it is possible to extract &amp;ldquo;emo&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;highlight&amp;rdquo; with better accuracy than just the number of comments per hour by performing sentiment analysis of comments on Youtube live. ..
In fact, we were able to get the result that the accuracy is likely to improve compared to just looking at the number of comments.
#Introduction
Last time, I borrowed COTOHA API and tried to think freely, not practical Article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miya is not enough for our communication.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/miya-is-not-enough-for-our-communication.-e63f6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/miya-is-not-enough-for-our-communication.-e63f6/</guid>
      <description>#TL;DR  By using the COTOHA API, we have proposed a poem that is close to what you want to convey from the Hyakunin Isshu. As a gateway to more &amp;ldquo;elegant&amp;rdquo; communication, you can bridge between engineers and non-engineers. (May be)
| What I want to convey | Proposed Waka | Meaning | |&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;|&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;|&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;| | I feel very lonely to hear that I will be transferred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Series for busy people] I tried summarizing with parsing to call the news in 30 seconds</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/series-for-busy-people-i-tried-summarizing-with-parsing-to-call-the-news-in-30-seconds-1ec12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/series-for-busy-people-i-tried-summarizing-with-parsing-to-call-the-news-in-30-seconds-1ec12/</guid>
      <description>## I also write this article  [Syntax analysis] Even a computer wants to participate in the quick-press quiz with humans! ! 
TL;DR You can read all the news in one article in 30 seconds! Below is a summarized example.
** [Before Summary] **
 The women&amp;rsquo;s golf US tournament tournament was held in Australia on the final round on the 9th, and Suzu Yamaguchi&amp;rsquo;s score fell sharply to 39th place with a total of 5 overs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural language processing for busy people</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/natural-language-processing-for-busy-people-40710/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/natural-language-processing-for-busy-people-40710/</guid>
      <description>#Overview for busy people  I tried linguistic processing, inspired by the article Ore program Ugocas Omae Genshizinaru. I like the old story &amp;ldquo;Busy People Series&amp;rdquo; 1, so I used the summary API of COTOHA API I tried to make a song for busy people.
*Note Although the lyrics summarized in the output result of the code below (black background part) appear, it is used for the purpose of research on language processing in accordance with Article 32 of the Copyright Act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyPI package for easy use of Cotoha on Google colab</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</guid>
      <description>## 2020/04/10 PyPI package has been released!  For details, see here(I&amp;rsquo;mreallyhappytohaveastar!)
If you want to use it quickly, please refer to the code below
$ pip install cotoha_at_python from cotohacall.main import cotoha_call import os os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_ID&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Your ID&amp;#39; os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_SECRET&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Ypur Secret&amp;#39; sentence =&amp;#39;API service that enables highly accurate natural language analysis of Japanese. With the COTOHA API, you can easily use the natural language analysis technology that utilizes the research results of NTT Group for over 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The result of having Mr. COTOHA summarize My memories of Mentos and Go. With COTOHA fastest tutorial</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-result-of-having-mr.-cotoha-summarize-my-memories-of-mentos-and-go.-with-cotoha-fastest-tutorial-16e67/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-result-of-having-mr.-cotoha-summarize-my-memories-of-mentos-and-go.-with-cotoha-fastest-tutorial-16e67/</guid>
      <description># Memories of Mentos and Go  Mentos has a deep feeling. At that time, I was participating in a Go club, Playing a Go stone to drop the opponent&amp;rsquo;s Go stone He was playing &amp;ldquo;shooting Go&amp;rdquo;. Heian nobles must have been entertaining, The club president, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand the naive play, went mad. According to him, the important go stone breaks, so stop it. Go stones cannot be fixed if they break.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>