<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>maya on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/maya/</link>
    <description>Recent content in maya on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/maya/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of meta-programming decorator on the subject of menu registration of maya</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-meta-programming-decorator-on-the-subject-of-menu-registration-of-maya-212ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-meta-programming-decorator-on-the-subject-of-menu-registration-of-maya-212ca/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you all. The annual [Maya Advent Calender 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/maya) season has come. This is the article on the 19th day. In this article, I&#39;ll introduce a technique in which a specific object in Python has information other than the code content and that information is used in a different process to make it work. In this way, operating programming one level above, that is, programming the program itself is called **metaprogramming**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>callback using pyside:MEventMessage</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/callback-using-pysidemeventmessage-5b01b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/callback-using-pysidemeventmessage-5b01b/</guid>
      <description>*This article is the 14th day of Maya Advent Calendar 2019. *  I&amp;rsquo;m very sorry, but I will participate.
When you want to execute some processing when the state transitions on maya scriptJob is a staple, but I will try using OpenMaya.MEventMessage, which is simpler and lighter.
This time I briefly wrote about how to use it on the pyside GUI. Let&amp;rsquo;s change the label text by looking at the selected node type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to speed up the process of obtaining vertex positions</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-speed-up-the-process-of-obtaining-vertex-positions-0b40a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-speed-up-the-process-of-obtaining-vertex-positions-0b40a/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 7th day article of [**Maya Advent Calender 2019**](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/Maya).  When you create a tool for modeling in Maya, you may get the vertex position of the selected object. However, in a model with a large number of vertices, acquiring all vertex positions with MEL or cmds will be slow and will hinder modeling work. OpenMaya is often introduced as a method of increasing the processing speed, but for me it was a high threshold and I was wondering if there is a way to increase the processing speed with cmds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Techniques to stop the drawing of the screen and reduce the waiting time for baking</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/techniques-to-stop-the-drawing-of-the-screen-and-reduce-the-waiting-time-for-baking-d8b18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/techniques-to-stop-the-drawing-of-the-screen-and-reduce-the-waiting-time-for-baking-d8b18/</guid>
      <description># at first  This article is the 12th day article of Maya Advent Calendar 2019.
In CG animation production, there is a barren waiting time to wait for baking in every process. This time, I will introduce a technique to reduce the waiting time for baking.
Overall flow Stop Maya screen drawing. ↓ Cause heavy processing. ↓ Restart Maya screen drawing and check the result.
It will be the flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Ass/Alembic with HtoA</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-ass-alembic-with-htoa-71a09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-ass-alembic-with-htoa-71a09/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Every year elderly The annual Houdini Advent Calendar. I thought about what to write, but since I am only touching Arnold this year, I would like to write information that may be helpful in HtoA (Arnold for Houdini). Arnold is one of the renderers,
 Houdini(HtoA) Maya(MtoA) 3ds Max (MaxtoA) Cinema4D (C4DtoA) Softimage (SitoA) Katana (KtoA) Gaffer (Gaffer Arnold) Blender (BtoA) Others such as Golaem, Massive, Nuke etc. also support Arnold.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>