<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Dedicated on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/dedicated/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Dedicated on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/dedicated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to detect the iris from the camera image</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-detect-the-iris-from-the-camera-image-2c6cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-detect-the-iris-from-the-camera-image-2c6cc/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  We have summarized the presentation contents of 56th Computer Vision Study Group @ Kanto held on Saturday, January 19, 2020. The materials for the day can be viewed from here.
The source code is available on Github below. https://github.com/33taro/gaze_cv
#Iris detection procedure
Iris detection is a theme that I was studying when I was a university student, so I think it would be easy to do with advanced OpenCV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head direction estimation using Python and OpenCV&#43;dlib</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/head-direction-estimation-using-python-and-opencv-dlib-1e68a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/head-direction-estimation-using-python-and-opencv-dlib-1e68a/</guid>
      <description>#Head direction estimation?  Head direction estimation, or Head Pose Estimation in English. It is an algorithm that estimates the direction of the face and the inclination of the head from the input image information and facial feature amount data. Recently, it is widely used for Vtuber development.
Head direction estimation method Qiita has already introduced several methods for estimating the head direction. This is very well summarized in the Qiita article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to detect face landmarks easily with python and dlib</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-detect-face-landmarks-easily-with-python-and-dlib-bbc58/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-detect-face-landmarks-easily-with-python-and-dlib-bbc58/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When I was a student, I was doing research on facial landmark detection while talking about it. I was amazed at how incredibly easy it is now.
So I would like to actually try it. If you would like to implement it for the time being, please read from &amp;ldquo;Easy face landmark detection&amp;rdquo;.
About face landmark detection method It seems that there are three main methods for detecting face landmarks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>