<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> AdventCalendar on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/adventcalendar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  AdventCalendar on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/adventcalendar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/863fe92c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/863fe92c3/</guid>
      <description>#00 Introduction  *This article is the 7th day of Kinki University Advent Calendar 2019. *Basically, it is written for college students.
 This time, I will write on the assumption that RaspberryPi ZeroW which is cheap and suitable for trying is used, but you can do it with the same procedure for other RaspberryPi. *I rushed into some of the guys who were carrying a classmate who loves JavaScript. Gomenne  By the way, haven&amp;rsquo;t you heard of RaspberryPi?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [You can see from the photo] In 10 minutes, how to start kaggle from initial status (novice) to Contributor.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/22954bb7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/22954bb7b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Nikkei xTECH Business AI Advent Calendar 2019 I will be in charge of the 4th day of the road to AI Dojo &amp;ldquo;Kaggle&amp;rdquo;.
#kaggle&amp;rsquo;s say depends on status
Users are ranked in kaggle. It is called Progression. It&amp;rsquo;s a progress level or something like a title.
Depending on this rank, the degree of attention to the posted script and the degree of influence of the statement differ.
When you register, you will be given the title novice, and if you meet certain conditions, you will become Contributor, If you want to become a higher rank from there, you must make statements that collect good evaluations from others, obtain medals, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] BEST20 (UTF8 → SJIS) Kanji ranking that appears with garbled characters</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8a7847d06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8a7847d06/</guid>
      <description>## Motivation  (Summary) Just because I wanted to know. There is no better reason.
More details There are many types of garbled patterns. Garbled characters that occur when displaying UTF8 files in SJIS, Garbled characters that occur when displaying UTF8 in EUC, Garbled characters that occur when displaying EUC in UTF8&amp;hellip; You can check what each looks like on this page (https://tools.m-bsys.com/ex/html-mojibake.php).
To be honest, since I work on UTF8 recently, I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen much garbled characters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>