<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitHub on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/github/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitHub on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If you create a program that automatically starts/ends the verification environment for pull requests, the verification progressed</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-you-create-a-program-that-automatically-starts-ends-the-verification-environment-for-pull-requests-the-verification-progressed-216fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-you-create-a-program-that-automatically-starts-ends-the-verification-environment-for-pull-requests-the-verification-progressed-216fc/</guid>
      <description># Article summary  I wanted to put the sales involved in the development with GitHub Flow, that is, the development with a simple pull operation, and created such an environment. At that time, I made and released a web application that supplements some missing functions, so I will write various stories about it. (It&amp;rsquo;s not about whether or not you can actually use this web app, but rather that you want to improve your development with a similar flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show grass on Google Nest Hub</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/show-grass-on-google-nest-hub-403ff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/show-grass-on-google-nest-hub-403ff/</guid>
      <description>I bought the Pixel 4 and received the Google Nest Hub. It seems to be usable as a digital photo frame. Since I&#39;m sorry, I will display the grass image on GitHub.  Google Nest Hub settings Immediately after purchase, Nest Hub will display an art gallery prepared by Google. Change this to a setting that allows you to view your favorite image.
 Launch the Google Home app on your iOS or Android device   If you bought Nest Hub, you should have installed it  Go to Nest Hub&amp;gt; Photo Frame   Change the display image setting to Google Photos  Change &amp;ldquo;Personal Photo Organize&amp;rdquo; setting to &amp;ldquo;Real-time shared albums only&amp;rdquo;   Without this setting, GitHub grass images, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete everything with Jupyter ~Introduction to nbdev~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/complete-everything-with-jupyter-~introduction-to-nbdev~-c4634/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/complete-everything-with-jupyter-~introduction-to-nbdev~-c4634/</guid>
      <description>This article was posted on the 4th day of the Buchan Advent Calendar 2019.  This is an article for Jupyterer. Please check the formula for more details, as some are not fully understood. 
What is nbdev Perhaps succinctly, it&amp;rsquo;s a Python programming environment that completes your work in one Jupyter Notebook by including the role of an IDE. Created by fast.aiandcurrentlyindevelopmentfastaiv2 also uses nbdev.
At present, trial and error such as EDA and model construction are often done using Jupyter Notebook, and it exists as a role of &amp;ldquo;exploring&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you use GitPod, you can use IDE and jupyter on iPad, so it&#39;s the best!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-gitpod-you-can-use-ide-and-jupyter-on-ipad-so-its-the-best-dbb64/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-gitpod-you-can-use-ide-and-jupyter-on-ipad-so-its-the-best-dbb64/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  **Using GitPod, you can use IDE and jupyter on iPad, so it&amp;rsquo;s the best! **
Features of #GitPod GitPod has the following features.
 VS code-like IDE available Available in chrome and firefox Can be used by linking to an account with GitHub Public repositories are free, private repositories are available for a fee (9$/month ~)  #This goal and procedure
on chrome on iPad Build a Python programming environment (IDE and jupyterlab).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>