<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Kaggle on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/kaggle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Kaggle on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/kaggle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Hands-on for beginners] Kaggle&#39;s Predicting house prices is read line by line (1st part: Data reading)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hands-on-for-beginners-kaggles-predicting-house-prices-is-read-line-by-line-1st-part-data-reading-a7f5e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hands-on-for-beginners-kaggles-predicting-house-prices-is-read-line-by-line-1st-part-data-reading-a7f5e/</guid>
      <description># theme  A job that operates a real estate system as a service, a story broke out that there is no loss in doing hands-on at the field level. That&amp;rsquo;s why we decided to challenge kaggle&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;House Price&amp;rdquo; problem, which is a famous title. So, if you make a note of this properly, it will be useful for later, so I decided to post it to qiita after reading the line by line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Denoising method using wavelet transform</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/denoising-method-using-wavelet-transform-87472/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/denoising-method-using-wavelet-transform-87472/</guid>
      <description>There was a noise removal method that I was convinced that there is a method like this in the kaggle kernel (notebook now), so I will summarize the things I examined about it below with notes.  Method overview An analysis method for a certain signal or waveform is called wavelet transform. I think that I often imagine the Fourier transform as an analysis method, but the Fourier transform expands the waveform to the sum of trigonometric functions (Sain, Kosain), whereas the wavelet transform decomposes it into a waveform of any shape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to predict Titanic survival on PyCaret</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-titanic-survival-on-pycaret-a377f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-titanic-survival-on-pycaret-a377f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The other day, I tried using the machine learning library PyCaret that was released. Data feature analysis and performance comparison work with multiple models will be automated, and the work time of data scientists up to now will be considerably reduced.
This time, I will apply PyCaret to the Titanic survival prediction problem, submit the prediction result to Kaggle, and see the result.
**This is a follow-up article to I tried to classify wine quality with PyCaret, which I posted last time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to learn machine learning from scratch (March 2020 edition)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-machine-learning-from-scratch-march-2020-edition-b5992/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-machine-learning-from-scratch-march-2020-edition-b5992/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Data science and machine learning are fun! However, do you have the experience that you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to study? By the way, I am one of them. In this article, *** What is machine learning in the first place? Even if you are a beginner who knows the word AI but do not know the details, you will learn the learning method *** to learn from the basic foundations necessary to gain knowledge and experience and be able to tackle machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] First data analysis/machine learning (Kaggle)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-first-data-analysis-machine-learning-kaggle-8d77e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-first-data-analysis-machine-learning-kaggle-8d77e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  As I was about to get a job (spring break in the fourth year of university), I suddenly wanted to become a data scientist, so I started working on Kaggle for the time being.
This time, I worked on a tutorial of Kaggle&amp;quot;Titanic&amp;rdquo;.
I have experience in statistical analysis in my research, but since I do not understand machine learning at all, I decided to study with reference to the code of the incredibly excellent person!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to understand (engineering) UMAP, which is stronger than t-SNE</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-understand-engineering-umap-which-is-stronger-than-t-sne-06ab8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-understand-engineering-umap-which-is-stronger-than-t-sne-06ab8/</guid>
      <description>Do you know UMAP?  I know
If you&amp;rsquo;ve heard it but don&amp;rsquo;t know it, this article will help you understand it.
#What is UMAP
It is a method to reduce and visualize dimensions faster and with higher performance than t-SNE. Compare with the commonly used t-SNE. The following figure is a visualization of Fashion MNIST.
(From Understanding UMAP)
Compared to t-SNE, UMAP seems to have distinct clusters. Similar categories are placed near each other and dissimilar categories are placed far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle Kernel Method Summary [Table Time Series Data]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggle-kernel-method-summary-table-time-series-data-4c0f3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggle-kernel-method-summary-table-time-series-data-4c0f3/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will write something like a standard for each data type in the Kaggle competition. In addition, I think it would be nice if it could be a hint when accuracy is not obtained regardless of the competition.  This time we will touch on the following competition datasets. In the case of competition, there is no Kernel, so I&amp;rsquo;ll try to put together Notebooks. Predict Future Sales Avocado Prices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle&#39;s Kernel Method Summary [Image Edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggles-kernel-method-summary-image-edition-11bd7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggles-kernel-method-summary-image-edition-11bd7/</guid>
      <description>Click here for the previous article  Kaggle Kernel Summary [Table Time Series Data]
In this article, including myself, I would like to know something like a standard for each data type in the Kaggle competition! I will write for people like. In addition, I think it would be nice if it could be a hint when accuracy is not obtained regardless of the competition.
This time we will look at various kernels, not just the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Looking back on the 10 months from beginner programming to becoming Kaggle Expert</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/looking-back-on-the-10-months-from-beginner-programming-to-becoming-kaggle-expert-3fbea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/looking-back-on-the-10-months-from-beginner-programming-to-becoming-kaggle-expert-3fbea/</guid>
      <description>I became a Kaggle Expert, so I decided to go and write a poem.  I hope it will be a reference for those who are interested in AI but can not even program **. #1. Initial specifications (February 2019)
 Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in mechanical engineering. Frequent mechanical engineers To be honest, I don&amp;rsquo;t really like linear algebra or statistics. Good at mechanics. AI? That&amp;rsquo;s right. Shogi, isn’t it super strong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Full disclosure of methods used in machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/full-disclosure-of-methods-used-in-machine-learning-61b62/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/full-disclosure-of-methods-used-in-machine-learning-61b62/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  There are increasing opportunities for anyone to learn machine learning, such as kaggle and learning sites. On the other hand, I feel that there are many people who have too much information and don&amp;rsquo;t get the overall feeling.
Therefore, I will publish the methods used in machine learning introduced in various reference books and articles. Please refer to that link for detailed coding.
Since various information is also sent on SNS, please feel free to read the article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle&#39;s feature management was better than I thought with PostgreSQL, so I made a directory that anyone can use with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggles-feature-management-was-better-than-i-thought-with-postgresql-so-i-made-a-directory-that-anyone-can-use-with-docker-44814/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggles-feature-management-was-better-than-i-thought-with-postgresql-so-i-made-a-directory-that-anyone-can-use-with-docker-44814/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 19th day of [Kaggle Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/kaggle).  Hi, my name is kiccho1101! Writing an article for the first time in my life! Thank you!
Introduction This time, I tried to use Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s feature quantity management with PostgreSQL, but it was faster than I thought, so I would like to introduce it.
The created directory is here: https://github.com/kiccho1101/datascience-template ↑ The README has a usage example using the data of Titanic competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easily build a GCP environment for Kaggle at high speed</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/easily-build-a-gcp-environment-for-kaggle-at-high-speed-507fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/easily-build-a-gcp-environment-for-kaggle-at-high-speed-507fc/</guid>
      <description>#GCP had a great feature added  Previously, I wrote an article Easily build a GCP environment for Kaggle. This time, I found an easier way to build it, so I&amp;rsquo;ll write it as an improved version of the previous article. A notebook function has been added to the lower AI platform. What this means is that you can get it ready for use without having to do the work to make the jupyter notebook introduced in the previous article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Student Kaggler, who cannot analyze data, analyzes himself</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/student-kaggler-who-cannot-analyze-data-analyzes-himself-2ec0b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/student-kaggler-who-cannot-analyze-data-analyzes-himself-2ec0b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  ###Self-introduction My name is Chizu Chizu. I&amp;rsquo;m 14 and I&amp;rsquo;m 2 now. It is a hobby type, but I was particularly typing. (Past tense)
Now I&amp;rsquo;m a low skill Kagler.
I got a bronze medal in &amp;ldquo;tentatively&amp;rdquo; IEEE. We&amp;rsquo;ll see later on why it&amp;rsquo;s a tentative one.
After getting tired of AtCoder, I got into Kaggle. I will definitely become a master by my own power.
What made me want to write I wanted to write an advent calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The first Kaggle (kaggle ①)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-first-kaggle-kaggle-0290b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-first-kaggle-kaggle-0290b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is the story of participating in the Kaggle competition for the first time. First try it out in a &amp;ldquo;Titanic&amp;rdquo; competition.
#table of contents
 What is Kaggle Register for Kaggle Participate in the Titatic competition Write the code Submit the learning results Summary reference  #1.What is Kaggle
It is read as kaguru. Kaggle is a US-based community site for people involved in data science and machine learning around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I participated in Kaggle&#39;s NFL competition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-participated-in-kaggles-nfl-competition-cf01b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-participated-in-kaggles-nfl-competition-cf01b/</guid>
      <description>## Competition overview   Held from October 10, 2019 to November 27, 2019 (https://www.kaggle.com/c/nfl-big-data-bowl-2020/ ) Predict the number of yards the attacker will advance in an American football run play  Available data  General information and player-specific information is given for each run play -General information: -Weather, temperature, wind speed, wind direction -Stadium, location, turf condition - Start time -Home/away score -Number of downs (attack ends after 4 times *1) -Number of yards required to continue the attack -Number of yards advanced ← Predict this -etc&amp;hellip; -Information by player *2 -NFL ID -Location information (X, Y) -Movement information (S: speed, A: acceleration) -Orientation (Dir: Body orientation, Orientation: Face orientation) - Birthday - height, weight -Home/away -Jersey number -Position -etc&amp;hellip;  *1: If you advance 10 yards or more within 4 downs, you will continue to attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Until [Kaggle Master] and after that</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/until-kaggle-master-and-after-that-9caac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/until-kaggle-master-and-after-that-9caac/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  **12/13 I added the time and study time for each! ** **12/18 We revised the part until it became Kaggle Master! ** **12/20 Added some parts! **
Purpose of the article In this article, I will introduce you to what I have done since I started to study programming until I became a Kaggle Master. I will also share some of the things that made me happy to become a Kaggle Master, and I hope that it will give you an opportunity to increase your motivation to work on Kaggle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle competition process as seen from the score transition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggle-competition-process-as-seen-from-the-score-transition-49d54/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggle-competition-process-as-seen-from-the-score-transition-49d54/</guid>
      <description># Kaggle competition process from the perspective of score transition  This article is on the 6th day of Advent Calendar of Road to AI Dojo &amp;ldquo;Kaggle&amp;rdquo; by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ① Advent Calendar 2019 This is an article.
This article is for Kaggle newbies who don&amp;rsquo;t know how to get started with Kaggle. While watching the score transition of the competition, I will write an article about what the kagglers are doing at a certain time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For non-programmers] How to walk Kaggle</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-non-programmers-how-to-walk-kaggle-2d27e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-non-programmers-how-to-walk-kaggle-2d27e/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 3rd day of Advent Calendar from [Kaggle Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/kaggle).  &amp;ldquo;** Kaggle I&amp;rsquo;m interested, but it&amp;rsquo;s scary and scary&amp;hellip; **&amp;rdquo; I think it will be useful for those who are thinking!
*The following information is as of December 2019
Until I meet # Kaggle
My background before I met Kaggle is roughly the following.
 Marketer ⇒ Consultant Bunka (art history major) No programming experience (I touched HTML a little) Black screen is in awe&amp;hellip;  It was like this, but I learned Python &amp;amp; machine learning in the last year, and I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to understand Kaggle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [You can see from the photo] In 10 minutes, how to start kaggle from initial status (novice) to Contributor.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/you-can-see-from-the-photo-in-10-minutes-how-to-start-kaggle-from-initial-status-novice-to-contributor.-22954/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/you-can-see-from-the-photo-in-10-minutes-how-to-start-kaggle-from-initial-status-novice-to-contributor.-22954/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Nikkei xTECH Business AI Advent Calendar 2019 I will be in charge of the 4th day of the road to AI Dojo &amp;ldquo;Kaggle&amp;rdquo;.
#kaggle&amp;rsquo;s say depends on status
Users are ranked in kaggle. It is called Progression. It&amp;rsquo;s a progress level or something like a title.
Depending on this rank, the degree of attention to the posted script and the degree of influence of the statement differ.
When you register, you will be given the title novice, and if you meet certain conditions, you will become Contributor, If you want to become a higher rank from there, you must make statements that collect good evaluations from others, obtain medals, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Use Kaggle API inside Docker container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</guid>
      <description># things to do   Start container using Kaggle official image (kaggle/python) Download csv file with kaggle ~ command Download public notebook with kaggle ~ command  First summary  DL kaggle.json (kaggle.com &amp;gt;My Account &amp;gt;Create New API Token button) 2.$ docker run -it --rm --mount type=bind,src=pwd,dst=/root/dev kaggle/python $ pip install kaggle $ mkdir ~/.kaggle $ cp /root/dev/kaggle.json ~/.kaggle 6.$ chmod 600 ~/.kaggle/kaggle.json $ kaggle competitions download -c titanic -p input/titanic $ unzip input/titanic/titanic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle&#39;s initial equipment-a cell that collects frequently used codes-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggles-initial-equipment-a-cell-that-collects-frequently-used-codes-c946c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggles-initial-equipment-a-cell-that-collects-frequently-used-codes-c946c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When working on Kaggle1, which is a competition platform for data science, Python2 written in Notebook3(orJupyterNotebook[^JupyterNotebook]orGoogleColaboratory[^GoogleColaboratory])istheexecutionenvironment.]]Ithinkthereisa&amp;quot;highlyusedcode&amp;rdquo;.Inordertoreuseit,Iwillintroduceitinonecellasaformatthatiseasytocopyandpasteanyway.Wehopethatbyreusingthecontentsofthiscell,wecanimprovetheefficiencyofdataanalysisinKaggle.(Thisis“Kaggle&amp;rsquo;sinitialequipment”!)
*This article is based on the Notebook published by Kaggler (Kaggle participant) predecessors and the book [Technology of data analysis that wins at Kaggle]. However, it is the individual subjectivity as of December 2019. Therefore, please see for your reference.
#Conclusion
What is Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s initial equipment?
This cell!
#Display Notebook from IPython.core.interactiveshell import InteractiveShell InteractiveShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle Tutorial Know-how in the top 2% of Titanic</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggle-tutorial-know-how-in-the-top-2-of-titanic-d8a1f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggle-tutorial-know-how-in-the-top-2-of-titanic-d8a1f/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  Since I started studying machine learning, I tried Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s tutorial for beginners, Titanic.
At first, I tried to play around with the feature amount on my own, referring to Japanese Web information, but even if the training data showed good accuracy, when I submitted the test data, the accuracy did not rise as expected, It was difficult to break the wall of 80% and I was in agony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is it the moon that triggered the huge earthquake? -&gt; Monthly</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-it-the-moon-that-triggered-the-huge-earthquake-monthly-9db5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-it-the-moon-that-triggered-the-huge-earthquake-monthly-9db5b/</guid>
      <description>## 0. Abstract   In many cases, huge earthquakes (M&amp;gt;8) are triggered by the deformation of the earth due to tidal stress caused by the moon. There were also some papers that treated the earthquakes that occurred in the past statistically and discussed the relationship with the tide. However, it goes without saying that even though we discussed the Tidal Phase Angle, we could not find anything that clearly showed Lunar Age or Lunar Phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Keras usage example: Input (Embedding &#43; Flatten)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/keras-usage-example-input-embedding-flatten-f76b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/keras-usage-example-input-embedding-flatten-f76b1/</guid>
      <description># 1. Install Keras  The installation method of Tensorflow and Theano is introduced in various sites, so the detailed explanation is omitted here. Keras installation is
pip install Keras All you have to do is change the config file and select Theano or Tensorflow. If you use Tensorflow in the backend, it will automatically use the GPU.
When using Tensorflow with Keras, the following errors may occur as of January 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>