<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HTML on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/html/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HTML on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/html/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Automation] Detect changes in website and notify LINE</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/431cea6b9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/431cea6b9/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am a high school student. Due to the influence of this corona, I could not go to school, and I was told to regularly visit the website prepared by the school and study at home according to the instructions written on that site, but the website is heavy and every day Checking for updates is a hassle. But I want to get the information as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Suddenly, if you want to make an inquiry form</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/1b0ba10a6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/1b0ba10a6/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you. It is Taro Man.  I usually develop web services.
-Siltrend
#Introduction The other day, suddenly, I wanted to prepare an inquiry form, Furthermore, I wanted to send the contents to my email address, Implemented with Python.
Overall picture In this article, I use Django. Django is very convenient.
#Form definition Form definition is done in forms.py.
Basically, it is created by importing Django standard features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning roadmap that allows you to develop and publish services from scratch with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/52a3bbacd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/52a3bbacd/</guid>
      <description>## at first  This article aims to &amp;ldquo;be able to develop services with Python from no programming experience&amp;rdquo;, We have arranged the skills to be learned as a learning roadmap.
** 2-3 hours every day (+2 hours on Saturdays and Sundays) ** If you continue, it will be completed in a minimum of 3 months. You can skip the skills you have already learned and proceed.
The outline is the same for other languages such as Ruby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easy to understand Python web application (Django) for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fbd235008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fbd235008/</guid>
      <description>#Composition of commentary articles     No. Title      1 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (1) [Environment]    2 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (2) [Project creation]    3 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (3) [Application creation/DB setting]    4 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns] ←   5 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (5) [Introduction to DB operation with Django shell]    6 Explanation of Python Web application (Django) for beginners (6) [MTV design pattern completion]     Development environment  OS: Mac OS Sierra (10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Tips] How to do template extends when creating HTML with django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fcea8bc7f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fcea8bc7f/</guid>
      <description>#Overview   Configuration of rough html templates when inheriting Tips on how to use tag important point  #background
 References: django document version 1.9 Django version: 1.9.2 python version: 2.7.10 OS: MacOS X  Things that the creator should decide for themselves are written in upper case, and the rest are written in lower case. Variable name or file name.
Configuration of html templates when inheriting Since I introduced on the official website an efficient method when writing html using template extends, it is almost a translation of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>