<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HTML on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/html/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HTML on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/html/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Automation] Detect changes in website and notify LINE</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/automation-detect-changes-in-website-and-notify-line-431ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/automation-detect-changes-in-website-and-notify-line-431ce/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am a high school student. Due to the influence of this corona, I could not go to school, and I was told to regularly visit the website prepared by the school and study at home according to the instructions written on that site, but the website is heavy and every day Checking for updates is a hassle. But I want to get the information as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Suddenly, if you want to make an inquiry form</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-suddenly-if-you-want-to-make-an-inquiry-form-1b0ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-suddenly-if-you-want-to-make-an-inquiry-form-1b0ba/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you. It is Taro Man.  I usually develop web services.
-Siltrend
#Introduction The other day, suddenly, I wanted to prepare an inquiry form, Furthermore, I wanted to send the contents to my email address, Implemented with Python.
Overall picture In this article, I use Django. Django is very convenient.
#Form definition Form definition is done in forms.py.
Basically, it is created by importing Django standard features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning roadmap that allows you to develop and publish services from scratch with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-roadmap-that-allows-you-to-develop-and-publish-services-from-scratch-with-python-52a3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-roadmap-that-allows-you-to-develop-and-publish-services-from-scratch-with-python-52a3b/</guid>
      <description>## at first  This article aims to &amp;ldquo;be able to develop services with Python from no programming experience&amp;rdquo;, We have arranged the skills to be learned as a learning roadmap.
** 2-3 hours every day (+2 hours on Saturdays and Sundays) ** If you continue, it will be completed in a minimum of 3 months. You can skip the skills you have already learned and proceed.
The outline is the same for other languages such as Ruby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to save scraped table in csv with python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-save-scraped-table-in-csv-with-python-add03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-save-scraped-table-in-csv-with-python-add03/</guid>
      <description># About this article  I needed to scrape a table on a web page in my research, so I will introduce the python program used at that time. By the way, I had zero scraping history, so I made it while checking various things, but there was hardly anything explaining how to convert the table on the web page to HTML and then convert the HTML table part to csv.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>