<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Ubuntu on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/ubuntu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Ubuntu on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/ubuntu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want my mom to get angry when my memory is crazy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-want-my-mom-to-get-angry-when-my-memory-is-crazy-097b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-want-my-mom-to-get-angry-when-my-memory-is-crazy-097b7/</guid>
      <description># Even in 2020, I am alive with worry about memory  8GB laptop, VS Code + some build + Chrome with 20 tabs open ** I run out of memory in no time **. It is a very strict user experience such as stall for each OS.
When I think about it, there were many times when I was a child ** I was scolded by my mother if I left things out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Language analysis using natural language processing tool GiNZA (from morphological analysis to vectorization)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-language-analysis-using-natural-language-processing-tool-ginza-from-morphological-analysis-to-vectorization-63ffd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-language-analysis-using-natural-language-processing-tool-ginza-from-morphological-analysis-to-vectorization-63ffd/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Recently, I started using the Python language processing tool &amp;ldquo;GiNZA&amp;rdquo;. I used to use MeCab so far, but I recently (shyly) found out that Python has a library that incorporates state-of-the-art machine learning techniques, so I&amp;rsquo;m currently moving to GiNZA. This time it is the first GiNZA, so I tried to summarize the processing flow as a memorandum while referring to various sites. There are many places that I am new to natural language analysis and I can not reach it, so please refer to the official documents etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build OpenCV3 &amp; Python3 environment on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-opencv3-python3-environment-on-ubuntu-f8922/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-opencv3-python3-environment-on-ubuntu-f8922/</guid>
      <description># Build environment with Ubuntu  The standard package is only for Python2, so prepare it yourself. It seems that there is a problem with cmake&amp;rsquo;s detection process of Python 3.4, and it did not work easily, so make a memorandum.
Target environment  cmake can&amp;rsquo;t get python3 library path and target opencv_python3 becomes unavailable (I think ubuntu 14.04 can&amp;rsquo;t detect python3)  It&amp;rsquo;s relatively easy to do in a windows environment, but I never thought that Ubuntu would be such a pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Ansible infrastructure automation tool for those who are not good at Ruby</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ansible-infrastructure-automation-tool-for-those-who-are-not-good-at-ruby-fcc83/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ansible-infrastructure-automation-tool-for-those-who-are-not-good-at-ruby-fcc83/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I think I can start learning Ruby with Ruby, but I think it would be nice to be able to write the same thing in python. Nowadays, in the shadow of chef, which is famous as an infrastructure automation tool, automation tools using python I heard it was there and tried using it immediately. Here we will introduce the procedure to start a remote environment with vagrant and set up the remote machine with ansible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>