<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VSCode on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/vscode/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VSCode on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/vscode/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python development environment options for May 2020</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-development-environment-options-for-may-2020-80ba4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-development-environment-options-for-may-2020-80ba4/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python is attractive because you can write and run it immediately after installing it. If you really want to write it in business
 Python version control tool Package manager Editor (IDE) Linter Formatter Type checker  At least you need to prepare. However, in this area, new things are released every day due to the rage, so it is difficult to unequivocally present &amp;ldquo;this is the best practice&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set VS Code to PyCharm.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/set-vs-code-to-pycharm.-70917/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/set-vs-code-to-pycharm.-70917/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I said, &amp;ldquo;Everyone in Pythonista should use the dexterous IDE, PyCharm, for everyday development to develop explosive speeds.&amp;rdquo;
I have been in PyCharm swamp for more than half a year since I was a Pythonista kid.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m here recently.&amp;rdquo;
I said, &amp;ldquo;People don&amp;rsquo;t really understand PyCharm&amp;rsquo;s intelligence, it&amp;rsquo;s free and I&amp;rsquo;m using tools like VS Code!!!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want this!!!! I was wondering why PyCharm is so amazing!!!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With VS Code&#39;s SSH connection function, edit and debug the code in Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/with-vs-codes-ssh-connection-function-edit-and-debug-the-code-in-raspberry-pi-26ab9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/with-vs-codes-ssh-connection-function-edit-and-debug-the-code-in-raspberry-pi-26ab9/</guid>
      <description>What is #VSCode?  Abbreviation for source code editor &amp;ldquo;Visual Studio Code&amp;rdquo; developed by Microsoft. As a free, lightweight, and multifunctional editor, it is rapidly gaining popularity.
From 2019/10 edition, SSH connection function to RaspberryPi (ARM v8) is officially supported, so I wrote the result of trying remote editing of Python code in Raspberry Pi.
** In conclusion, we were able to achieve debugging with breakpoints and a comfortable remote development environment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debug multiprocess program in python with VSCode</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/debug-multiprocess-program-in-python-with-vscode-544e7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/debug-multiprocess-program-in-python-with-vscode-544e7/</guid>
      <description>How to debug a program using VS&#39;s multiprocessing module on VSCode  Intended reader  Python code using multiprocessing module works fine in console but VSCode Those who don&amp;rsquo;t work when trying to debug with Those who want to understand python multi-process program but do not understand without a debugger When debugging with VS Code ↓ Those who are in trouble with such an error  Exception escaped from start_client failed to launch debugger for child process AssertionError: can only join a child process RuntimeError: already started How to do Debugging a program using the multiprocessing module requires the following three points</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procedure to attach to JupyterLab on remote server from VS Code and debug</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/procedure-to-attach-to-jupyterlab-on-remote-server-from-vs-code-and-debug-3b921/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/procedure-to-attach-to-jupyterlab-on-remote-server-from-vs-code-and-debug-3b921/</guid>
      <description># 1. Explain in this post  Follow the steps below to build an environment for debugging using JupyterLab and VS Code.
 Start JupyterLab on the remote server Call the Python class from JupyterLab. Remotely attach to the above notebook of JupyterLab from VS Code on the local PC for debugging. Illustrated below.  If you watch the video below, you will have an image of what you can do specifically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build Python and Jupyter execution environment with VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-build-python-and-jupyter-execution-environment-with-vs-code-f0788/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-build-python-and-jupyter-execution-environment-with-vs-code-f0788/</guid>
      <description>I have summarized how to build Python and Jupyter execution environment with VS Code. I use Anaconda.  Also, I think that many people who analyze data with Python use Jupyter notebook and Jupyter Lab from their browsers. VS Code is also recommended for such people.
Also, this article is part of the article How to create a Python package using VS Code.
We will proceed on the assumption that Anaconda has been downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried applying input interpolation to UE4 Python VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-applying-input-interpolation-to-ue4-python-vs-code-c3997/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-applying-input-interpolation-to-ue4-python-vs-code-c3997/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python can be used in UE4, I have written the source in VSCode, but it is painful if there is no input interpolation. So I verified the method of input interpolation. Verifying with UE4.24+VS Code
##UE4 setting
enable plugins From Edit/Plugins Enable Python Editor Script Plugin
Create a Python stub Python Editor From Edit/Project Setting Enable Python/Developer Mode.
By enabling this, after restarting UE4, Python stub data for use in input interpolation will be created under ProjectPath\Intermediate\PythonStub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Docker development container conveniently with VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/use-docker-development-container-conveniently-with-vs-code-d3b52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/use-docker-development-container-conveniently-with-vs-code-d3b52/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction   Developing in local environment, deploying to Linux environment and testing is troublesome I want to create a development environment that feels good to use Docker However, various settings and construction are troublesome  For such a person, it is an introduction of how to use the extension function &amp;ldquo;Remote-Containers&amp;rdquo; that can conveniently build and operate a development environment using Docker container from VS Code.
Greatness of this extension VS Code&amp;rsquo;s extension function &amp;ldquo;Remote-Containers&amp;rdquo; is to launch VS Code in a container and communicate with VS Code of the host machine so that you can perform in-container development as if you were developing in a local environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python environment construction (Anaconda &#43; VSCode) @ Windows10 [January 2020 edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</guid>
      <description>#Background  When I made a Python environment with Anaconda + VS Code, I was troubled because the latest setting method did not come out, so I will publish my notes for those who will do it now. It seems that there was a VS Code specification change around 2017. Be careful when reading old commentary.
Articles referenced: @Atupon0302: Build Python environment in Windows 10 environment with Anaconda+Visual Studio Code [September 2017]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django server start with VScode instead of Pycharm</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-server-start-with-vscode-instead-of-pycharm-2d104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-server-start-with-vscode-instead-of-pycharm-2d104/</guid>
      <description># introduction  It&amp;rsquo;s been 3 days since I started Django for self-development. Looking for a handle name (&amp;lsquo;ω&amp;rsquo;) Learn by moving! Introduction to Python Django development. In the book, I was developing and starting the server with Pycharm, and as a self-developed person mainly with VScode recently, it felt like uumm. I think the code can be modified, but I can manage to start the server with VScode. So, I implemented it using the debugging function I learned at VScode Meetup held on 12/18!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[No venv required] The strongest Python development environment created with Remote Containers [VS Code/Docker]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/no-venv-required-the-strongest-python-development-environment-created-with-remote-containers-vs-code-docker-1fc39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/no-venv-required-the-strongest-python-development-environment-created-with-remote-containers-vs-code-docker-1fc39/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python has been attracting attention because it shines in the top 1 popular languages 1 and becomes a test subject for the IPA Basic Information Engineer Exam 2.
But wait a minute! Are you able to benefit from the Python ecosystem and develop properly?
By creating a good development environment, not only can the development be made more efficient by input interpolation and formatters , but also unexpected problems can be prevented by static analysis, ① Easy ② Explosion speed ③ You can write programs safely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to develop Django with VSCode</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/steps-to-develop-django-with-vscode-12a5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/steps-to-develop-django-with-vscode-12a5d/</guid>
      <description>2020/03/13 Modified slightly to match VSCode Version 1.43.0  Introduction A beginner yearned for the word debug, and learned that VS Code can actually do it, and tried setting it. The memorandum. I think that the advantage is that once you set it, you can enter the virtual environment and run the server just by pressing the Debug button. You can save yourself the trouble of going back and forth between the browser and Terminal and VS Code and entering source myenv/bin/activate or python manage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only 8 Techniques to Watch Your Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/only-8-techniques-to-watch-your-data-scientist-ab06b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/only-8-techniques-to-watch-your-data-scientist-ab06b/</guid>
      <description>#Beware of data scientists  As of 2019, there should be a lot of people out there who want to be distracted by data scientists. However, those who don&amp;rsquo;t know how to be more pretentious than others. I completely removed the muddy data scientist aspect and wondered how I could be distracted. You can put your conclusion into practice immediately tomorrow. If you want to be a data scientist, give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Python environment for VS Pro with VS Code on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-python-environment-for-vs-pro-with-vs-code-on-windows-03e8e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-python-environment-for-vs-pro-with-vs-code-on-windows-03e8e/</guid>
      <description>The following is assumed. I will also write the version at hand when creating the article.   Windows10 VS Code installed (1.40.1) Windows version Python installed (3.8.0)  After installing Python also installed on the right on Windows ⇒ online-judge-tools    #Goal You can execute test in sample case with Ctrl+Shift+B, Create an environment where you can manually execute a test with Ctrl+Shift+T.
Folder structure I did the following: One file for each question, and throw it all under src.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story that tried Sourcetrail × macOS × VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/story-that-tried-sourcetrail-macos-vs-code-b2da7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/story-that-tried-sourcetrail-macos-vs-code-b2da7/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I will try it immediately because the code visualization tool called Sourcetrail has been made open source. It looks interesting.
What is Source Trail @ IT&amp;rsquo;s article (Sourcetrail, a code visualization tool for C++ and Python is open source)
 Sourcetrail combines features such as interactive dependency graphs, concise code views, and efficient code searching to provide source code overviews and details.
 By statically analyzing the source code and visualizing it, developers are freed from reading a huge amount of existing source code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>