<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> DeepLearning on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/deeplearning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  DeepLearning on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/deeplearning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AnimeGAN that converts live-action film into anime style (Windows10, Python3.6)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/animegan-that-converts-live-action-film-into-anime-style-windows10-python3.6-44804/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/animegan-that-converts-live-action-film-into-anime-style-windows10-python3.6-44804/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I tried AnimeGAN, which transforms live-action film into anime style.
System environment  Windows10 (RTX2080 Max-Q, i7-8750H, RAM16GB) Anaconda 2020.02 Python 3.6 CUDA 9.0  Introduction Clone AnimeGAN.
Create an environment for animegan.
$ conda create -n animegan python=3.6 $ conda activate animegan $ pip install tensorflow-gpu==1.8.0 $ pip install tqdm $ pip install scipy $ pip install opencv-python $ cd AnimeGAN-master Put dataset on AnimeGAN-master.
Copy and paste the contents of Haoyao-style to checkpoint\AnimeGAN_Hayao_lsgan_300_300_1_3_10</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Implementation explanation] Japanese BERT x unsupervised learning (information maximization clustering) to classify livedoor news: Google Colaboratory (PyTorch)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-japanese-bert-x-unsupervised-learning-information-maximization-clustering-to-classify-livedoor-news-google-colaboratory-pytorch-6a887/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-japanese-bert-x-unsupervised-learning-information-maximization-clustering-to-classify-livedoor-news-google-colaboratory-pytorch-6a887/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will implement and explain how clustering is performed by using the Japanese version BERT in Google Colaboratory and performing unsupervised learning information maximization clustering for livedoor news.   Using the Japanese version of BERT with Google Colaboratory, the content until vectorization of sentences, Information maximization clustering for unsupervised learning in MNIST  About this, I have explained it in the series articles so far, so please see here first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction] Reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-reinforcement-learning-0ff56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-reinforcement-learning-0ff56/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;script async src=&amp;quot;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.0/MathJax.js?config=TeX-AMS_CHTML&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  MathJax.Hub.Config({ tex2jax: { inlineMath: [[&#34;\\(&#34;,&#34;\\)&#34;] ], displayMath: [[&#39;$$&#39;,&#39;$$&#39;], [&#34;\\[&#34;,&#34;\\]&#34;]] } });  This is a summary of a quick study of reinforcement learning. I hope it will be a reference for beginners.
What is reinforcement learning? The position of reinforcement learning is like this.
【the term】 - Supervised learning - Input and output as teacher data - Regression and classification problems - Unsupervised learning - No teacher data - Extract data features and transform expressions What we will do in reinforcement learning is We will “learn behaviors that maximize future value”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The relationship between brain science and unsupervised learning. Information maximization with unsupervised learning MNIST: Google Colabratory (PyTorch)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-relationship-between-brain-science-and-unsupervised-learning.-information-maximization-with-unsupervised-learning-mnist-google-colabratory-pytorch-e3c01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-relationship-between-brain-science-and-unsupervised-learning.-information-maximization-with-unsupervised-learning-mnist-google-colabratory-pytorch-e3c01/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will explain unsupervised learning and brain science, and IIC&#39;s implementation of high performance in MNIST for unsupervised learning.  The papers of interest in this article are: Invariant Information Clustering for Unsupervised Image Classification and Segmentation is.
In this paper, we utilize an index called mutual information to classify handwritten digit images by unsupervised learning clustering.
It is called IIC (Invariant Information Clustering).
In this article, we will discuss brain science and unsupervised learning, IIC points, and implementation examples in MNIST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Neural network super introduction that can be understood even by cats</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-neural-network-super-introduction-that-can-be-understood-even-by-cats-489a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-neural-network-super-introduction-that-can-be-understood-even-by-cats-489a4/</guid>
      <description>![IMG_0489.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/458623/93e891ee-1dc8-fa4e-7bb5-5a1922ffe589.png)  Written  What is a neural network? a unit? weight? bias? Activation function Overview of NN Summary  The goal is to get a general idea of the neural network. I don&amp;rsquo;t use mathematical formulas, so people who are allergic to mathematics should also check it.
#1.What is a neural network?
A neural network is something like the one below. When written in English, it is Neural Network, so it is often abbreviated as NN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Implementation explanation] How to use Japanese version BERT in Google Colaboratory (PyTorch)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-how-to-use-japanese-version-bert-in-google-colaboratory-pytorch-e522a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-how-to-use-japanese-version-bert-in-google-colaboratory-pytorch-e522a/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will explain how to use the Japanese version of BERT with Google Colaboratory.  About the BERT itself, the book I wrote last year
&amp;ldquo;Learn while making! Development deep learning with PyTorch&amp;rdquo;
Is explained in detail in.
If you want to know how BERT works, please see the above book.
Since the book only dealt with the English version, this post will explain how to use BERT in the Japanese version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try running wav2pix, which creates a face image from audio (there is also an anime face generator)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-running-wav2pix-which-creates-a-face-image-from-audio-there-is-also-an-anime-face-generator-159ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-running-wav2pix-which-creates-a-face-image-from-audio-there-is-also-an-anime-face-generator-159ce/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The world of deep learning, especially Generative Adversarial Networks (GAN), has grown dramatically in recent years, and I think that research is progressing in various fields such as text-to-image, voice conversion, and sound source separation.
In this talk, I will loosely write about wav2pix, which generates face images from voice.
Paper: WAV2PIX: SPEECH-CONDITIONED FACE GENERATION USING GENERATIVEADVERSARIAL NETWORKS
#Overview https://imatge-upc.github.io/wav2pix/
The proposed model consists of the following three modules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AI engineers want to be aware of Python implementation know-how / tips summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ai-engineers-want-to-be-aware-of-python-implementation-know-how-tips-summary-c0e8a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ai-engineers-want-to-be-aware-of-python-implementation-know-how-tips-summary-c0e8a/</guid>
      <description>This article summarizes the points, tips, and know-how that data scientists and AI engineers should be aware of when implementing programs in Python.   ● May 16, 2020: Added Book: Self-propelled programmer author: Mr. Shimizukawa, provided detailed explanations to this article and answers to my questions. Click this link to move to the comment. 
 We published a book in April 2020.
[Qiita] I wrote a book that teaches a good balance between machine learning implementation and algorithms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simple method to obtain MNIST correct rate of 97% or more by unsupervised learning (without transfer learning)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simple-method-to-obtain-mnist-correct-rate-of-97-or-more-by-unsupervised-learning-without-transfer-learning-0aa24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simple-method-to-obtain-mnist-correct-rate-of-97-or-more-by-unsupervised-learning-without-transfer-learning-0aa24/</guid>
      <description>First article posted as job hunting news.  I tried to read and implement a paper on IIC (Invariant Information Clustering), which is said to be highly accurate and has unsupervised learning. IIC is a method of clustering by maximizing mutual information. IIC paper here
 Invariant Information Clustering for Unsupervised Image Classification and Segmentation Xu Ji, João F. Henriques, Andrea Vedaldi
 The framework used is TensorFlow 2.0. The target data is familiar MNIST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I wrote a book that teaches a well-balanced implementation of machine learning and algorithms.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-wrote-a-book-that-teaches-a-well-balanced-implementation-of-machine-learning-and-algorithms.-db5c5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-wrote-a-book-that-teaches-a-well-balanced-implementation-of-machine-learning-and-algorithms.-db5c5/</guid>
      <description>I wrote a book that uses the scikit-learn library to teach a well-balanced implementation of machine learning and algorithms.  Introduction to machine learning for people aiming to become AI engineers, learning the algorithm flow while implementing it (Dentsu International Information Service Takuya Shimizu, Yutaro Ogawa, Technical Review) https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/4297112094/
It has already been released.
Machine learning ・Implementation of various algorithms ・Mechanism of operation of each algorithm
I wrote this for those who want to learn these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried using magenta/TensorFlow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-magenta-tensorflow-c754d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-magenta-tensorflow-c754d/</guid>
      <description>Automatic generation of melody using # magenta/TensorFlow  background Since I want to be able to manipulate MIDI data using Python this time, I came to a tool called Magenta while browsing various sites.
 What is #Magenta Recently, a new project called Magenta from Google was opened on Github. https://github.com/tensorflow/magenta
  Magenta is a project that uses neural networks to generate art and music.
  It aims to evolve machine learning creativity and to be a community of artists and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Check your squat form with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/check-your-squat-form-with-deep-learning-bd59e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/check-your-squat-form-with-deep-learning-bd59e/</guid>
      <description>**The video used in this article was recorded a long time ago, and I currently refrain from exercising at the gym. **  #Introduction This is the second edition of &amp;ldquo;Muscle Training x Deep Learning&amp;rdquo;. The first is here (Deep learning made it easier to see the time-lapse of physical changes). &amp;ldquo;Form check&amp;rdquo; that many trainees (people who love muscle training) have become habitual. You can fix your smartphone during the training, take a selfie, and look back later to know the habit of your form and improve the quality of your training afterwards!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] (◎◎) {Let Python do the boring stuff.........(He? Hona Python will do the homework}} (゜) (゜)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/let-python-do-the-boring-stuff.........he-hona-python-will-do-the-homework-86258/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/let-python-do-the-boring-stuff.........he-hona-python-will-do-the-homework-86258/</guid>
      <description># Did you make Python do boring stuff?  I didn&amp;rsquo;t let it do A book on the cover with a robot like this C-3PO playing grass
It&amp;rsquo;s well-known as a good Python book, and many people have read it.
So who read this book and did Python actually do the boring stuff? Isn&amp;rsquo;t it quite small? I think there are many people who are satisfied with reading. I was one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deep learning of Raspberry Pi 3 B&#43; &amp; PyTorch for real-time classification of multiple objects in camera images</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-of-raspberry-pi-3-b-pytorch-for-real-time-classification-of-multiple-objects-in-camera-images-a09b4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-of-raspberry-pi-3-b-pytorch-for-real-time-classification-of-multiple-objects-in-camera-images-a09b4/</guid>
      <description>I got Razpai 3B+ and picamera because of university class. Since I&#39;m free, I decided to let Razpai classify using deep learning. However, instead of classifying the pictures taken in advance, it classifies the objects in the real-time image from picamera and displays them in a nice way.  It may be at the student level, but I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it if you can refer to even a part of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Released a web service for handwriting scoring using DeepLearning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/released-a-web-service-for-handwriting-scoring-using-deeplearning-2cf76/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/released-a-web-service-for-handwriting-scoring-using-deeplearning-2cf76/</guid>
      <description>As a hobby, I personally developed a web service that AI automatically marks the readability of characters when I write them in a browser, and released it about 2 weeks ago: relaxed:  []((https://letters.choo.works/) Letters-AI handwriting scoring app
The core technology is front-end implementation with DeepLearning image recognition and Preact. In this article, we will describe Service outline, technical details, and impressions regarding the developed application.
Service overview Function introduction Since it has a small number of pages and is lightweight, it is probably faster to see the application regarding the function, but I will explain the function including an overview of the technology used with screenshots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How the AI department and development team work (in my case)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-the-ai-department-and-development-team-work-in-my-case-0fc60/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-the-ai-department-and-development-team-work-in-my-case-0fc60/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will introduce the working style of Ogawa, who belongs to the development team of the AI Technology Department.  This article is an introduction for me.
The way you work depends on the member, and also on the family structure. I am married but I have no children.
Also, different departments work differently.
In this article, I will introduce the working week for me (Yutaro Ogawa) of AI Technology Department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Deep Learning] I tried to see if a machine learning beginner could make a prediction for the first place in a boat race.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-i-tried-to-see-if-a-machine-learning-beginner-could-make-a-prediction-for-the-first-place-in-a-boat-race.-c203f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-i-tried-to-see-if-a-machine-learning-beginner-could-make-a-prediction-for-the-first-place-in-a-boat-race.-c203f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It&amp;rsquo;s been a month since I started studying deep learning.
I thought I could understand the basics, so I wondered if I could do something.
Then, suddenly, I came up with an estimate of the ranking of this boat race.
I was not convinced that I could predict the rank, but I knew that open source of boat race data was open to the public, so I thought I had to try this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to learn machine learning from scratch (March 2020 edition)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-machine-learning-from-scratch-march-2020-edition-b5992/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-machine-learning-from-scratch-march-2020-edition-b5992/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Data science and machine learning are fun! However, do you have the experience that you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to study? By the way, I am one of them. In this article, *** What is machine learning in the first place? Even if you are a beginner who knows the word AI but do not know the details, you will learn the learning method *** to learn from the basic foundations necessary to gain knowledge and experience and be able to tackle machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [2020 version for beginners] Recommended study method for those who want to become AI engineers by themselves</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2020-version-for-beginners-recommended-study-method-for-those-who-want-to-become-ai-engineers-by-themselves-e47bf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2020-version-for-beginners-recommended-study-method-for-those-who-want-to-become-ai-engineers-by-themselves-e47bf/</guid>
      <description># Service introduction (AI Academy and AI Academy Bootcamp)  This is an AI learning service for individuals operated by us.
① AI Academy Online AI programming learning service where you can learn Python, machine learning, deep learning for almost free *About 300 types of practical content can be used for 980 yen per month.
② AI Academy Bootcamp Short-term intensive AI programming boot camp for individuals (AI programming school) Python course (50,000 yen per month) Data Scientist Course (¥120,000 for 2 months) Machine learning engineer course (120,000 yen for 2 months)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is the network since VGG really improving? The story</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-the-network-since-vgg-really-improving-the-story-16022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-the-network-since-vgg-really-improving-the-story-16022/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, AI competitions don&amp;rsquo;t produce useful models just overtraining the dataset &amp;amp; outperforming the game? The purpose of this study is to investigate the story with the wide-angle fundus dataset 1. Also, as an introduction, we will explain how to fine-turn from the learned weights of ImageNet2 using the network implemented in tf.keras.
All code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deep learning made it easy to see the time-lapse of physical changes</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-made-it-easy-to-see-the-time-lapse-of-physical-changes-f0e60/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-made-it-easy-to-see-the-time-lapse-of-physical-changes-f0e60/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  &amp;ldquo;Self-portraits (body)&amp;rdquo; that many trainees (people who love muscle training) have become accustomed. It&amp;rsquo;s blissful to take a picture of your pumped body after training and look back later. In addition, if you display the captured image in animation like a time lapse, you can understand that muscle growth is more like a hand! This article uses deep learning to drastically make it easier to see the timelapse of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [With Japanese model] Sentence vector model recommended for people who will process natural language in 2020</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/with-japanese-model-sentence-vector-model-recommended-for-people-who-will-process-natural-language-in-2020-1df94/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/with-japanese-model-sentence-vector-model-recommended-for-people-who-will-process-natural-language-in-2020-1df94/</guid>
      <description>## Summary   Create and publish a Japanese model of Sentence-BERT (Papers,Implementation). did. By using this Japanese model, anyone can easily create high-quality sentence vectors. Please use it. Sentence-BERT uses pre-trained BERTmodelandSiameseNetwork , Is a method of creating a highly accurate sentence vector. Cosine similarity using accuracy evaluation of English version (STSbenchmarkandrankcorrelationcoefficientofspearmanofcorrectlabel.1Inthecaseof(closerisbetter),themethodusingtheaverageofsimplewordvectors(GloVe)is0.58,andthemodelcorrespondingtothescalecreatedthistimeisaround0.85(PapersSeeTable2). The accuracy is 0.17 when using the CLS vector of the bare BERT and 0.46 when using the average of the BERT embeddings, which is worse than the result of the average of the word vector (0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried using PIFu that generates a 3D model of a person from one image</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-pifu-that-generates-a-3d-model-of-a-person-from-one-image-ecf40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-pifu-that-generates-a-3d-model-of-a-person-from-one-image-ecf40/</guid>
      <description>What is #PIFu  Image quote (left): Sumire Uesaka Official Blog Nekomori Meeting
PIFu: Pixel-Aligned Implicit Function for High-Resolution Clothed Human Digitization
If you explain roughly,
A machine learning model that generates a 3D model of a person with clothes from a single image
is.
 We introduce Pixel-aligned Implicit Function (PIFu), a highly effective implicit representation that locally aligns pixels of 2D images with the global context of their corresponding 3D object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Image classification with wide-angle fundus image dataset</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/image-classification-with-wide-angle-fundus-image-dataset-8c011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/image-classification-with-wide-angle-fundus-image-dataset-8c011/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, as an introduction, we aim to use TensorFlow 2.0 and perform image classification with Deep Learning for the time being. The image dataset is not so interesting as MNIST, so we will use the wide-angle fundus image dataset 1 published by Tsukazaki Hospital. The network is a simple 10-layer CNN.
All Code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Landscape transformation by AI † Different world transformation †</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/landscape-transformation-by-ai-different-world-transformation-93d2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/landscape-transformation-by-ai-different-world-transformation-93d2c/</guid>
      <description># Introduction († horror transformation †)     Before conversion After conversion     !      Did you understand?
This uses GAN (Hostile Generation Network) to add &amp;ldquo;horror&amp;rdquo; features to photos and convert them.
Let&amp;rsquo;s leave the principle behind for now, and take a look at the possibilities of GAN!
Seasonal conversion, Aurora conversion, Fireworks conversion    Before conversion After conversion     !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A science university student started studying deep learning in his spare time</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-science-university-student-started-studying-deep-learning-in-his-spare-time-30329/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-science-university-student-started-studying-deep-learning-in-his-spare-time-30329/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  My specs I gave the title &amp;ldquo;Science University Student&amp;rdquo;, but I think there is a punch like &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m actually an information student&amp;rdquo; only in these articles. If so, it will be an article that hopeless for university students who are not information systems, so I will clarify my features first. I am in the second year of university, belonging to the Department of Physics, Faculty of Science. I&amp;rsquo;m in the manufacturing circle, so programming (Python) is a bit of a bit of skill, but I&amp;rsquo;m just a beginner in deep learning**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Automatic collection of stock prices using python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/automatic-collection-of-stock-prices-using-python-12c64/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/automatic-collection-of-stock-prices-using-python-12c64/</guid>
      <description># Purpose  Automatically collect stock prices using Python
For details, see Automatic stock price collection using python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] An amateur stumbled upon Deep Learning made from scratch Memo: Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-upon-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-7-8541c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-upon-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-7-8541c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I suddenly started to study &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning from scratch-the theory and implementation of deep learning learned with Python&amp;rdquo; It is a memo of the trip.
The execution environment is macOS Mojave + Anaconda 2019.10, and the Python version is 3.7.4. For details, please refer to Chapter 1 of this memo.
(To other chapters of this memo: Chapter 1/Chapter2/Chapter3/Chapter4/Chapter5/Chapter6/Chapter7/Chapter8)/Summary))
#7 Convolutional Neural Network
This chapter describes Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning with Pascal-VOC dataset of MobileNetV2-SSDLite [Docker version remake]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-with-pascal-voc-dataset-of-mobilenetv2-ssdlite-docker-version-remake-107dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-with-pascal-voc-dataset-of-mobilenetv2-ssdlite-docker-version-remake-107dd/</guid>
      <description>**PINTO_model_zoo** [![GitHub stars](https://img.shields.io/github/stars/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo.svg?style=social&amp;amp;label=Stars)](https://github.com/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo)  &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://github-link-card.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo.png&amp;quot;width=&amp;quot;460px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
1. Introduction I remade the MobileNet V2-SSD Lite training environment construction article that I wrote about a year ago into an ultra-simple specification. If you start work from the stage where the latest Docker for GPU is introduced, I think you can start training in about 15 minutes. I think there are almost no mistakes. After learning, I plan to do Integer Quantization of the trained model (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deep Learning Association G test study method (for beginners) [2020 edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-association-g-test-study-method-for-beginners-2020-edition-001ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-association-g-test-study-method-for-beginners-2020-edition-001ed/</guid>
      <description># In this article, we will explain to beginners how to study for the Deep Learning Association G test (an example)  (Last update: February 3, 2020)
Click here for more information on the G test. What is the Deep Learning Association G Test?
*This document&amp;rsquo;s calligraphy is used with the permission of the publisher (or the image in the common database of the publishing industry from the publisher Dotcom).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Image registration: From SIFT to deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/image-registration-from-sift-to-deep-learning-9598c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/image-registration-from-sift-to-deep-learning-9598c/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  There are few Japanese articles about image registration (as of January 22, 2020), so I thought it was very easy to understand Image Registration: From SIFT to Deep Learning was translated or summarized. Some parts have been omitted or added, so please read the original article if you want to get the original text.
Source code
What is image registration? Image registration is the process of correcting the misalignment between two images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] An amateur stumbled on Deep Learning made from scratch Memo: Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-on-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-5-8707e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-on-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-5-8707e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I suddenly started studying [Deep Learning from scratch&amp;ndash;the theory and implementation of deep learning learned with Python] It is a memo of the trip.
The execution environment is macOS Mojave + Anaconda 2019.10, and the Python version is 3.7.4. For details, please refer to Chapter 1 of this memo.
(To other chapters of this memo: Chapter 1/Chapter2/Chapter3/Chapter4/Chapter5/Chapter6/Chapter7/Chapter8)/Summary))
#5 Error Back Propagation
This chapter describes the backpropagation method for speeding up the calculation of weight parameters in learning neural networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make an Anpanman painter discrimination machine</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-an-anpanman-painter-discrimination-machine-30a44/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-an-anpanman-painter-discrimination-machine-30a44/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I thought about learning AI and making a simple application with the technology I learned, I tried to make something like the following. The reason why I chose Anpanman was because it was a cartoon character that I could easily write. I wanted to handle GAN as a model, and that it is possible to detect abnormalities by learning only normal images I thought I would make it ANOGAN, but when I looked it up, it was called EfficientGAN in the high-speed version of ANOGAN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Detect image distortion by deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-detect-image-distortion-by-deep-distance-learning-54585/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-detect-image-distortion-by-deep-distance-learning-54585/</guid>
      <description>There is a lot of research being done on image anomaly detection using deep learning.  As an approach for detecting abnormal products using only normal data for industrial products, For now, @daisukelab&amp;rsquo;s Learning with self-teaching is the most powerful. In this research, As a problem, the accuracy of some images was sluggish, and we tried to make an error class data by trial and error ** There was a comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Try the latest method of deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-try-the-latest-method-of-deep-distance-learning-d2a3a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-try-the-latest-method-of-deep-distance-learning-d2a3a/</guid>
      <description>Previously, using **deep distance learning** [&amp;quot;image anomaly detection&amp;quot;](https://qiita.com/shinmura0/items/06d81c72601c7578c6d3#%E3%83%99%E3%83%B3%E3%83%81%E3%83%9E%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AF).  After that, The latest method of deep distance learning &amp;ldquo;AdaCos&amp;rdquo; appeared.
In this article, I would like to apply AdaCos to &amp;ldquo;anomaly detection&amp;rdquo; and do a simple benchmark. The entire code is here
*This is the presentation material of Python Data Analysis Study Group #15.
#From the conclusion By applying AdaCos to anomaly detection, we found the following:
 Same accuracy as ArcFace Thank you for not tuning parameters  #AdaCos AdaCos is said to be the latest method of deep distance learning, but as of January 2020, more than half a year has passed since the paper was published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning Graph Convolutional Networks with PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-graph-convolutional-networks-with-pytorch-42913/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-graph-convolutional-networks-with-pytorch-42913/</guid>
      <description>** [Twitter](https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)introducesartificialintelligenceandarticleswritteninothermedia**,soifyouwanttoknowmoreaboutartificialintelligence,**Pleasefeelfreetofollowus(https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)! **  Learning with PyTorch Graph Convolutional Networks In this article, I will explain GCN, which has been attracting a lot of attention as a neural network that can vectorize (embed) graph structures in recent years, and PyTorch Geometric, a library that can easily use GCN. The fields of application range from biology to traffic jam prediction and recommender systems. This article is GCN creator&amp;rsquo;s blog articleand[PyTorchGeometricofficialtutorial](https://pytorch-geometric.readthedocs.io/en(/latest/index.html) is used as a reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction to Style GAN] I played with A man&#39;s life ♬</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-style-gan-i-played-with-a-mans-life-5c936/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-style-gan-i-played-with-a-mans-life-5c936/</guid>
      <description>To be clear, just by using Example, the frequently played video (conversion from male to female) can be reproduced immediately, and it is really amazing when you try it.  This time, this is an introduction article by trying only the first entrance. The reference is as follows. 【reference】 ① I tried using StyleGAN ② Try to mix Yukichi Fukuzawa with StyleGan ③ Puzer/stylegan-encoder ④ NVlabs/stylegan Currently, styleGAN2 seems to be out, but first of all, I would like to try the first step of StyleGAN and have a real feeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning method with original data of CenterNet(Objects as Points)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-method-with-original-data-of-centernetobjects-as-points-9a37c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-method-with-original-data-of-centernetobjects-as-points-9a37c/</guid>
      <description>What is #CenterNet  CenterNet is the object detection method proposed in the paper Objects as Points.
After detecting the center of the object as a feature point, the size of the width and height is predicted, so it seems that there are advantages such as lighter calculation than conventional methods.
I tried to detect the positions of tennis players, balls, and courts using CenterNet, I want to do the same thing using CenterNet .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Pokemon sword shield] I tried to visualize the basis of deep learning judgment by taking the Osanke classification as an example</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pokemon-sword-shield-i-tried-to-visualize-the-basis-of-deep-learning-judgment-by-taking-the-osanke-classification-as-an-example-2c3ec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pokemon-sword-shield-i-tried-to-visualize-the-basis-of-deep-learning-judgment-by-taking-the-osanke-classification-as-an-example-2c3ec/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Do you guys play Pokemon? I bought it for the first time in 10 years ~~ I got it from Santa. Aiming to get serious, we plan to stay home and select carefully during the year-end and New Year holidays. I was wondering if AdventCalendar could do something with Pokemon news items, so I tried ** a method that shows the basis of judgment of deep learning model ** using Pokemon Okayama family classification as an example ** Saw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Since IBM MAX supports ARM, it runs on Raspberry Pi.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/since-ibm-max-supports-arm-it-runs-on-raspberry-pi.-93f30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/since-ibm-max-supports-arm-it-runs-on-raspberry-pi.-93f30/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  Do you know IBM MAX? It is provided by IBM and you can use the service that can connect the deep-learned model with REST API as a container compatible with Docker. It can also be called from Node-RED. From around November 2019, it became compatible with IoT devices equipped with ARM CPUs including Raspberry Pi, embedded devices, and PCs equipped with ARM CPU, so in this article, I will use IBM MAX with Raspberry Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] For the first time after breaking up, I realized that I liked Chainer&#39;s Linear.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-the-first-time-after-breaking-up-i-realized-that-i-liked-chainers-linear.-84d4e/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-the-first-time-after-breaking-up-i-realized-that-i-liked-chainers-linear.-84d4e/</guid>
      <description>2020/05/12 update  https://github.com/pfnet/pytorch-pfn-extras It became possible by importing this.
===
I was notified when the major update of Chainer was announced, and I wondered if it was time to come, but I decided to touch PyTorch as soon as possible for the future, and I made the model I had made with Chainer until now PyTorch I decided to implement it again.
And immediately, I hit an error&amp;hellip;
The relevant part is the following code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I don&#39;t want to admit... The dynamical system representation of Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-dont-want-to-admit...-the-dynamical-system-representation-of-neural-network-47833/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-dont-want-to-admit...-the-dynamical-system-representation-of-neural-network-47833/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 18th day article of [NTT Communications Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/nttcom).  Yesterday was @yusuke84&amp;rsquo;s article, Thinking about WebRTC Platform SkyWay support. **Merry Christmas! **:santa::christmas_tree::gift::santa::christmas_tree::gift::santa::christmas_tree::gift::santa::christmas_tree::gift::santa::christmas_tree::gift::santa: :christmas_tree::gift:
#Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s the company&amp;rsquo;s Advent Calendar, so let&amp;rsquo;s write some technical tips at the beginning to keep up with the flow! So, I was searching for information about Neural Network, but in the end, I settled on a story that I was interested in, which was more theoretical than implementation, and this article is the end of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Generate Pokemon with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/generate-pokemon-with-deep-learning-e85de/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/generate-pokemon-with-deep-learning-e85de/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 16th day article of Kinki University Advent Calendar 2019. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the decoction is, but I will generate a Pokemon image with Gan. In the future, I would like to add a description of Pokemon picture book to the generated image. The source code is here
DCGAN DCGAN was used for image generation. For details, see Papers. The implementation used DCGAN-tensorflow,butforsomereasontherewasabugintheofficialsourcecode,sofixed is used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Ver 4 to make sandwich man&#39;s control by machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ver-4-to-make-sandwich-mans-control-by-machine-learning-2a164/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ver-4-to-make-sandwich-mans-control-by-machine-learning-2a164/</guid>
      <description>The fourth volume to make a sandwich man&#39;s control with deep learning! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! !  I&amp;rsquo;m in charge of Natural Language Processing Advent Calendar 2019 (I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for delaying one day!!!) https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/nlp
I want to automatically make a control like Sandwich Man, and I want to sell it to a comedy office for 4000 trillion yen. And I want to see Sandwich Man!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Improve PyTorch execution environment with Docker November 2019</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/improve-pytorch-execution-environment-with-docker-november-2019-a451c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/improve-pytorch-execution-environment-with-docker-november-2019-a451c/</guid>
      <description>## Overview   Develop a deep learning execution environment with PyTorch in a Docker container After Docker version 19.03, if you have the GPU driver of the host OS and nvidia-container-runtime, everything else will be locked in a container In most cases, you can reproduce the environment with one command  Preparation The following preparations are required.
 docker version 19.03 or later -See Official Documentation(thislinkisforUbuntu) nvidia-container-runtime -Install by referring to README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I made an AI that cuts out images with good feeling using Saliency Map</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-an-ai-that-cuts-out-images-with-good-feeling-using-saliency-map-833d3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-an-ai-that-cuts-out-images-with-good-feeling-using-saliency-map-833d3/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  In this article, I will implement a method for cropping images using Saliency Map using deep learning with Python and PyTorch while reading the paper.
When it comes to images in deep learning, we often try to classify handwritten numbers and detect people, but I would like you to see that you can also do such things.
This article participates in DeNA 20 New Graduate Advent Calendar 2019-Qiita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Until [Kaggle Master] and after that</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/until-kaggle-master-and-after-that-9caac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/until-kaggle-master-and-after-that-9caac/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  **12/13 I added the time and study time for each! ** **12/18 We revised the part until it became Kaggle Master! ** **12/20 Added some parts! **
Purpose of the article In this article, I will introduce you to what I have done since I started to study programming until I became a Kaggle Master. I will also share some of the things that made me happy to become a Kaggle Master, and I hope that it will give you an opportunity to increase your motivation to work on Kaggle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] LINE notification from real-time video recognition with DeepStream SDK</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/line-notification-from-real-time-video-recognition-with-deepstream-sdk-3bb25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/line-notification-from-real-time-video-recognition-with-deepstream-sdk-3bb25/</guid>
      <description>#LINE notification from high-speed video recognition with DeepStream SDK  This article is the 7th day of Docomo Advent Calendar 2019.
My name is Sakai from NTT Docomo Service Innovation Department. In my work, I am working on the research and development of image recognition engines that use Deep Learning and their commercialization. This time, we used the GPU-based video recognition acceleration tool &amp;ldquo;DeepStream SDK&amp;rdquo; to detect cars from the video at high speed and notify the result to LINE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Problem that torch.cuda.is_available() of pytorch gives false</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/problem-that-torch.cuda.is_available-of-pytorch-gives-false-7962d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/problem-that-torch.cuda.is_available-of-pytorch-gives-false-7962d/</guid>
      <description>#Environment  ・Ubuntu 16.04 ・Python 3.7.3 ・Pytorch 1.2.0
GPU cannot be used with #pytorch
I thought about deeplearning, but it&amp;rsquo;s slow so check if you can see cuda in ipython.
In [1]: import torch In [2]: torch.cuda.is_available() Out[2]: False why? As a possible cause, I thought that NVIDIA-driver is not working,
(base) user@user:~$ nvidia-smi Tue Dec 3 11:29:10 2019 +------------------------------------------------- ----------------------------+ | NVIDIA-SMI 390.116 Driver Version: 390.116 | |-------------------------------+----------------- -----+----------------------+ | GPU Name Persistence-M| Bus-Id Disp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] P100-PCIE-16GB was added to the GPU of Google Colab somehow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/p100-pcie-16gb-was-added-to-the-gpu-of-google-colab-somehow-56633/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/p100-pcie-16gb-was-added-to-the-gpu-of-google-colab-somehow-56633/</guid>
      <description>* * This article is based on November 24, 2019.  While thinking that everyone may already know. .. .. ..
About Google colab GPU gacha I think it&amp;rsquo;s well known that you have a GPU gacha. See below for details. https://qiita.com/koshian2/items/d33edc963ed6cfcad77e
Trigger I thought that it was faster than usual, and when I checked the GPU, P100 was added as follows. GPU speed comparison Immediately, I compared the training speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] PyTorch super introduction PyTorch basics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pytorch-super-introduction-pytorch-basics-df87f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pytorch-super-introduction-pytorch-basics-df87f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This series is described as a summary of learning of PyTorch which is a machine learning framework of Python. This time, I have written a summary of the basics of PyTorch. It may be difficult to read as a reading material because I try to write down the main points rather than to convey it, but I hope you can use it to understand the points.
What is #PyTorch As I mentioned earlier, PyTorch is a Python machine learning framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to predict horse racing by doing everything from data collection to deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-horse-racing-by-doing-everything-from-data-collection-to-deep-learning-55e49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-horse-racing-by-doing-everything-from-data-collection-to-deep-learning-55e49/</guid>
      <description># Overview  A student majoring in information systems at a certain T university. While looking at various articles of Qiita, I found such an article.
 If you have deep learning, you can exceed 100% recovery rate in horse racing  Regarding the 100% recovery rate in this article, it is unclear whether it will be valid in other periods because the number of betting tickets that were simulated for purchase is small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Paper and Implementation] When asked, Is this data set difficult?...</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/paper-and-implementation-when-asked-is-this-data-set-difficult...-74917/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/paper-and-implementation-when-asked-is-this-data-set-difficult...-74917/</guid>
      <description>Learning a convolutional neural network (CNN) takes time.  Especially, if you try to get accuracy without transfer learning, it takes about 5 days** There are times. The paper introduced in this paper quantitatively describes the difficulty of datasets. By evaluating, classification accuracy can be estimated quickly without learning CNN. Is that.
*The entire code was placed on here. *The figures in this paper are basically taken from the paper (Spectral Metric for Dataset Complexity Assessment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What an amateur stumbled upon in Deep Learning made from scratch Memo: Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-an-amateur-stumbled-upon-in-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-1-1945a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-an-amateur-stumbled-upon-in-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-1-1945a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Suddenly, I thought &amp;ldquo;[Deep Learning from scratch-the theory and implementation of deep learning learned with Python]&amp;rdquo; (https://www.oreilly.co.jp/books/9784873117584/) and &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning from scratch ( 2)-Natural language processing&amp;rdquo; I decided to study.
However, I am very worried whether I will not be able to take the time to continue. However, when I completed [Language Processing 100 Knock 2015]2-3yearsago,Amateurlanguageprocessing100knocks I continued to post to Qiita, and thanks to everyone&amp;rsquo;s likes and comments, I was able to finish it, so again this time Qiita&amp;rsquo;s I decided to help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] (Saved version: updated from time to time) A collection of useful tutorials for doing data analysis hackathons by Team AI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/saved-version-updated-from-time-to-time-a-collection-of-useful-tutorials-for-doing-data-analysis-hackathons-by-team-ai-f8e32/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/saved-version-updated-from-time-to-time-a-collection-of-useful-tutorials-for-doing-data-analysis-hackathons-by-team-ai-f8e32/</guid>
      <description>We at Team AI hold machine learning study sessions and data analysis hackathons every day in Shibuya.  The goal is to have a community of 1 million people, mainly in Tokyo.
I hope this movement of data analysis will spread throughout Japan and around the world. We have put together a useful tutorial for doing data analysis hackathons. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun, so everyone, especially the locals, should try it out for yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Statistics for programmers] There is more than one way to calculate the average value</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/statistics-for-programmers-there-is-more-than-one-way-to-calculate-the-average-value-fec65/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/statistics-for-programmers-there-is-more-than-one-way-to-calculate-the-average-value-fec65/</guid>
      <description>## table of contents  Statistics for Programmers-Table of Contents
Related article  Average, Median, Mode  Overview When calculating the average value, I generally think of adding all the values and dividing by the number of elements. However, there are several other average values, such as weighted average and geometric average, which can be used depending on the application. The commonly known method of dividing the total by the number of elements is called the arithmetic mean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction to TensorBoard: image] Visualize TensorFlow image processing to deepen understanding</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-tensorboard-image-visualize-tensorflow-image-processing-to-deepen-understanding-fae68/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-tensorboard-image-visualize-tensorflow-image-processing-to-deepen-understanding-fae68/</guid>
      <description>#TensorBoard accelerates understanding of TensorFlow  I output to TensorBoard in order to check the process of convolution processing and pooling processing of TensorFlow. It is a memo of the image confirmation method at that time. As a premise, please refer to [[Introduction to TensorBoard] Visualize TensorFlow process to deepen understanding] for basic usage. Environment: python3.5 tensorflow1.21
Reference link  -Installing TensorFlow on Windows It was easy even for beginners of Python -[Explanatory commentary] TensorFlow basic syntax and concept -[Commentary for beginners] TensorFlow tutorial MNIST (for beginners) -[Introduction to TensorBoard] Visualize TensorFlow processing to deepen understanding -[Introduction to TensorBoard: Projector] Making TensorFlow processing look cool -[TensorFlow tutorial MNIST (for beginners) visualized with TensorBoard] (http://qiita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Roughly think about the loss function</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/roughly-think-about-the-loss-function-f8a8c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/roughly-think-about-the-loss-function-f8a8c/</guid>
      <description>I have a personality that I don&#39;t want to think too deeply about, and I would like to have a rough and intuitive understanding if possible.  So let&amp;rsquo;s do a little research on this loss function as well so that we can understand it intuitively.
What is a loss function? What is a loss function in the first place? It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult function to explain, but it seems to be a function that reduces the difference between two values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to install Deep Learning Framework Tensorflow 1.0 on Windows Anaconda environment</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-install-deep-learning-framework-tensorflow-1.0-on-windows-anaconda-environment-fe4c7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-install-deep-learning-framework-tensorflow-1.0-on-windows-anaconda-environment-fe4c7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Until now, we have been doing deep learning by running Tensorflow on the back end of Keras. If you just do machine learning in Python, you can use Keras as before, but there are applications where you want to use models and weights learned in Python in C++. Actually, it would be nice to use a model trained with Keras, but it seems easier to code directly with Tensorflow which also has a C++ API, so I will try to attack from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Sine curve estimation with self-made deep learning module (python) &#43; LSTM</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/sine-curve-estimation-with-self-made-deep-learning-module-python-lstm-ff31b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/sine-curve-estimation-with-self-made-deep-learning-module-python-lstm-ff31b/</guid>
      <description>2017.9.16 Added.  Recently I upgraded a little. https://github.com/uyuutosa/Optimizer_with_theano
Also, I made it possible to try neural style by copy and paste. http://qiita.com/uyuutosa/items/09557f2f99e77a1b9cc2 For reference only.
I made my own deep learning module in Python (on the way). For my own study. The name is Optimizer with no twist. We aim to establish a network with a small number of keystrokes. I use theano internally, but I think that Define by Run chainer is upward compatible, so May change to chainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Keras usage example: Input (Embedding &#43; Flatten)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/keras-usage-example-input-embedding-flatten-f76b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/keras-usage-example-input-embedding-flatten-f76b1/</guid>
      <description># 1. Install Keras  The installation method of Tensorflow and Theano is introduced in various sites, so the detailed explanation is omitted here. Keras installation is
pip install Keras All you have to do is change the config file and select Theano or Tensorflow. If you use Tensorflow in the backend, it will automatically use the GPU.
When using Tensorflow with Keras, the following errors may occur as of January 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-f9aa6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-f9aa6/</guid>
      <description># Series table of contents   I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Introduction- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Implementation- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ Restart‼ ~ I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ What this is Alpha Zero ~ I tried to create a neutral network in Excel to understand the theory of machine learning-Image recognition mnist-  Last time continued&amp;hellip; In this field, I am an outsider, without studying &amp;ldquo;the theory of machine learning&amp;rdquo; at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Implementation-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-implementation-fdb97/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-implementation-fdb97/</guid>
      <description># Series table of contents   I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Introduction- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Implementation- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Izou battle version- I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ Restart‼ ~ I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ What this is Alpha Zero ~ I tried to create a neutral network in Excel to understand the theory of machine learning-Image recognition mnist-  Last time continued&amp;hellip; In this field, I am an outsider, without studying &amp;ldquo;the theory of machine learning&amp;rdquo; at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deep Learning (under attendance)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-under-attendance-f8352/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-under-attendance-f8352/</guid>
      <description>Taking classes at MPS Yokohama  I am having a difficult time because I am a beginner in programming and mathematics. (We will check Markdown notation and TeX notation and rewrite later)
Motivation for attending: Ultimately, I want to customize the appropriate Deep Learning library (tensorflow) etc. and use it for work (advertisement operation tool) and play (home electronics operation from sensing??).
Textbook (learning source) MPS lecture slides Lecture video</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>