<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Natural Language Processing on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/natural-language-processing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Natural Language Processing on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/natural-language-processing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Machine learning] Use WordNet to mechanically extract similar words</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/machine-learning-use-wordnet-to-mechanically-extract-similar-words-f82e9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/machine-learning-use-wordnet-to-mechanically-extract-similar-words-f82e9/</guid>
      <description>#Outline of natural language processing  Before touching on WordNet, let me briefly touch on natural language processing. In order for a machine to understand sentences in natural language processing, the following morphological analysis, syntactic analysis, semantic analysis, and contextual analysis are required in order.
Morphological analysis It is the work of dividing from natural language text data without annotations of information into columns of morphemes (the smallest unit that has meaning in the language) based on information such as the grammar of the target language and the part of speech of words called a dictionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube live It analyzes the sentiment of the comment and judges the emo part from Youtube LIve.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  It is a suggestion and experiment that it is possible to extract &amp;ldquo;emo&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;highlight&amp;rdquo; with better accuracy than just the number of comments per hour by performing sentiment analysis of comments on Youtube live. ..
In fact, we were able to get the result that the accuracy is likely to improve compared to just looking at the number of comments.
#Introduction
Last time, I borrowed COTOHA API and tried to think freely, not practical Article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try the book Introduction to Natural Language Application Development in 15 Steps-Chapter 2 Step 03 Memo Morphological Analysis and Wakachi</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/try-the-book-introduction-to-natural-language-application-development-in-15-steps-chapter-2-step-03-memo-morphological-analysis-and-wakachi-fb592/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/try-the-book-introduction-to-natural-language-application-development-in-15-steps-chapter-2-step-03-memo-morphological-analysis-and-wakachi-fb592/</guid>
      <description># Content  This is a memo for yourself when reading Introduction to Natural Language Processing Application. This time in Chapter 2, Step 03, I will write down my point.
#Preparation
 Personal Mac PC: MacOS Mojave version 10.14.6 docker version: Both Client and Server version 19.03.2  Chapter overview Understand the operation of MeCab and try tuning. We will also check morphological analyzers other than MeCab.
#03.1 MeCab
dictionary Written by MeCab is based on a dictionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything for beginners to be able to do machine learning</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/everything-for-beginners-to-be-able-to-do-machine-learning-fcd09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/everything-for-beginners-to-be-able-to-do-machine-learning-fcd09/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is for the purpose of enabling machine learning while doing what was presented as a &amp;ldquo;knowledge necessary for doing machine learning&amp;rdquo; **, which was issued as a subject for an internship destination. is. You will only become a Apprentice Machine Learning Engineer by doing all of this article. On the contrary, you can easily expose the basics of machine learning simply by doing all of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construction of environment for using CaboCha on google cola borboratory</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/construction-of-environment-for-using-cabocha-on-google-cola-borboratory-fb890/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/construction-of-environment-for-using-cabocha-on-google-cola-borboratory-fb890/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Language processing 100 knocks Chapter 5 of 2015: I made a lot of trouble to use CaboCha necessary for dependency analysis, so I will summarize it.
About #google colabratory Mainly used as a python cloud environment, but shell commands can be used.
!{Shell command} !pip install library name You can use shell commands like this.
The OS you are using seems to be Ubuntu, so check it with a command</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>