<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> MachineLearning on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/machinelearning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  MachineLearning on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/machinelearning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Neural network super introduction that can be understood even by cats</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-neural-network-super-introduction-that-can-be-understood-even-by-cats-489a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-neural-network-super-introduction-that-can-be-understood-even-by-cats-489a4/</guid>
      <description>![IMG_0489.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/458623/93e891ee-1dc8-fa4e-7bb5-5a1922ffe589.png)  Written  What is a neural network? a unit? weight? bias? Activation function Overview of NN Summary  The goal is to get a general idea of the neural network. I don&amp;rsquo;t use mathematical formulas, so people who are allergic to mathematics should also check it.
#1.What is a neural network?
A neural network is something like the one below. When written in English, it is Neural Network, so it is often abbreviated as NN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Trying to make a typed web application with Python&#39;s web framework ``FastAPI&#39;&#39; and TypeScriptOpenAPI-technology stack for machine learning webapp</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/trying-to-make-a-typed-web-application-with-pythons-web-framework-fastapi-and-typescriptopenapi-technology-stack-for-machine-learning-webapp-9278f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/trying-to-make-a-typed-web-application-with-pythons-web-framework-fastapi-and-typescriptopenapi-technology-stack-for-machine-learning-webapp-9278f/</guid>
      <description># Intro  Introducing FastAPI+TypeScript+OpenAPI as a technology stack for creating web applications with machine learning and image processing implemented in Python as the back end.
#Motivation
 I want to set up a web server (API server) quickly with Python -Uses like using Flask until now &amp;ldquo;In Python&amp;rdquo; -Because it is a machine learning / image processing service &amp;ldquo;Crispy&amp;rdquo; -I want to enjoy validation I want type assurance for both server and client -Machine learning and image processing apps tend to have many parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Data analysis started with python (data preprocessing-machine learning)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/data-analysis-started-with-python-data-preprocessing-machine-learning-b7dc7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/data-analysis-started-with-python-data-preprocessing-machine-learning-b7dc7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For beginners, I would like to explain from data preprocessing in python to machine learning model construction. Use gradient boosting for machine learning.
Source code https://gitlab.com/ceml/qiita/-/blob/master/src/python/notebook/first_time_ml.ipynb
Content of this article table of contents  Data preprocessing 1-1. Read data 1-2. Combine data 1-3. Compensation for missing areas 1-4. Feature creation 1-5. Data division Machine learning 2-1. Dataset creation and model definition 2-2. Model training and evaluation 2-3. Check the importance of features  About dataset ・Provided by: California Institute of Technology ・Contents: Heart disease test data ・URL: https://archive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] For those who want to start machine learning with TensorFlow2</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am currently a M2 student majoring in CS. I usually write machine learning code in PyTorch. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to write for the time being. PyTorch is said to be &amp;ldquo;Define by Run&amp;rdquo;**, and what is good at the same time when the calculation graph and data are sent is that it is easy to debug because you can check the calculation results on the way. As a PyTorch believer, I need to write code in TensorFlow this time, so I will keep a memo so that I don&amp;rsquo;t forget the know-how at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Port from argparse to hydra</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/port-from-argparse-to-hydra-3c09c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/port-from-argparse-to-hydra-3c09c/</guid>
      <description>This is a reminder of what I checked when converting the Python argparse settings to hydra.  Finally, I wrote a convenient function that only hydra has.
Introduction When writing an experiment script for machine learning in python, argparse was used as a setting method for hyperparameters. However, as the experiment became more complicated, there was a desire to have a considerable number of lines in the file that describes the setting of argparse and to structure the setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] MS Learn Recommended Learning Path February Issue [Introduction to AI]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ms-learn-recommended-learning-path-february-issue-introduction-to-ai-0281a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ms-learn-recommended-learning-path-february-issue-introduction-to-ai-0281a/</guid>
      <description>## MS Learning&#39;s first recommended learning path![Introduction to AI]    MS Learn is a Microsoft learning platform.
-Introduction to Machine Learning in Python and Azure Notebooks: Jupyter Notebooks running on Python and Azure Notebooks to predict patterns and identify trends. Learning Path to learn how to leverage the libraries associated with
-Explain Machine Learning and Azure Data Science Virtual Machine: Azure Data, which is a pre-configured virtual machine service for performing data science tasks in Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Dimension curse] Can the number of sensors be changed to ∞ to detect anomalies?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/dimension-curse-can-the-number-of-sensors-be-changed-to-to-detect-anomalies-1a800/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/dimension-curse-can-the-number-of-sensors-be-changed-to-to-detect-anomalies-1a800/</guid>
      <description>Since the IOT became popular, efforts have been made to increase the number of sensors in order to predictively maintain machinery.  Is being done.
Rumor has it that there are cases where 100 sensors are attached to one machine.
The question is, is it justified to increase the number of sensors? In other words, does **adding extra sensors not affect the anomaly detection performance? When That is it.
In this paper, we focus on the curse of dimension, “When we increase the number of extra sensors, we detect anomalies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] About torch summary can be really used when building a model with Pytorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-torch-summary-can-be-really-used-when-building-a-model-with-pytorch-bfd8f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-torch-summary-can-be-really-used-when-building-a-model-with-pytorch-bfd8f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am building my own model and always ask &amp;ldquo;What is the feature quantity of the input?&amp;rdquo; before connecting to the fully connected layer. If you often type print(model), you can understand the structure of the model, but you can not confirm up to the size of FeatureMap. So, the convenient one is torchsummary.
Who is #torchsummary?
Simply put, you can check the size of the feature map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Detect image distortion by deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-detect-image-distortion-by-deep-distance-learning-54585/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-detect-image-distortion-by-deep-distance-learning-54585/</guid>
      <description>There is a lot of research being done on image anomaly detection using deep learning.  As an approach for detecting abnormal products using only normal data for industrial products, For now, @daisukelab&amp;rsquo;s Learning with self-teaching is the most powerful. In this research, As a problem, the accuracy of some images was sluggish, and we tried to make an error class data by trial and error ** There was a comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Try the latest method of deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-try-the-latest-method-of-deep-distance-learning-d2a3a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-try-the-latest-method-of-deep-distance-learning-d2a3a/</guid>
      <description>Previously, using **deep distance learning** [&amp;quot;image anomaly detection&amp;quot;](https://qiita.com/shinmura0/items/06d81c72601c7578c6d3#%E3%83%99%E3%83%B3%E3%83%81%E3%83%9E%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AF).  After that, The latest method of deep distance learning &amp;ldquo;AdaCos&amp;rdquo; appeared.
In this article, I would like to apply AdaCos to &amp;ldquo;anomaly detection&amp;rdquo; and do a simple benchmark. The entire code is here
*This is the presentation material of Python Data Analysis Study Group #15.
#From the conclusion By applying AdaCos to anomaly detection, we found the following:
 Same accuracy as ArcFace Thank you for not tuning parameters  #AdaCos AdaCos is said to be the latest method of deep distance learning, but as of January 2020, more than half a year has passed since the paper was published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Half a year when the Gori Gori literary school almost learned AI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</guid>
      <description># Half-year when the Gori Gori literary system (deviation value 40 first half) learned AI  Hi, it&amp;rsquo;s a rugged ~~ macho~~ humanities. After graduating from commercial high school, I went to the Faculty of Humanities, so it&amp;rsquo;s different from other humanities. It is a thoroughbred world of humanities.
Although it is a vital math skill, I only studied math A up to high school, and just started math at university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The guy who predicts the number of views from the title of Jarjar&#39;s video</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-guy-who-predicts-the-number-of-views-from-the-title-of-jarjars-video-06f6f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-guy-who-predicts-the-number-of-views-from-the-title-of-jarjars-video-06f6f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This time, I will talk about making a model that predicts the number of views from the title of Jarjar&amp;rsquo;s video. Since NLP is a complete amateur, I tried to imitate the appearance by referring to the articles of other people.
What is jar jar JALJAL is a comedy group with the most momentum*, consisting of Junpei Goto and Shusuke Fukutoku, who belong to the Yoshimoto Kogyo Tokyo headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I made a muscle training estimation application using Qore SDK</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-muscle-training-estimation-application-using-qore-sdk-d6519/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-muscle-training-estimation-application-using-qore-sdk-d6519/</guid>
      <description>## tl;dr   I made a muscle training estimation app Qore uses an algorithm called reservoir computing Performed a task of classifying time series data from acceleration data that can be acquired with a smartphone -Code Pretty good -99.6% accuracy with test data This should make you a muscle engineer  Strategy  Collect accelerometer data with a smartphone (iphone) Time series data with three components on the x, y and z axes is available Learn with 4 types of muscle training: push-ups, abs, squats, abs You can tell what kind of muscle training you did with only your smartphone  Data collection   Do your muscle workout with your smartphone in your pants pocket -This time, in any muscle training, put the smartphone in the pocket in the same direction -It seems that it will be more difficult to estimate if it is set in a different direction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Hands-on to visualize your tweet while understanding BERT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hands-on-to-visualize-your-tweet-while-understanding-bert-09fda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hands-on-to-visualize-your-tweet-while-understanding-bert-09fda/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 13th day article of [NTT Communications Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/nttcom).  Yesterday was @nitky&amp;rsquo;s article, &amp;ldquo;We deal with threat intelligence in a mood&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/nitky/items/ccefd0353b74aa21e357).
#Introduction Hi, my name is yuki uchida, and I belong to the SkyWay team of NTT Communications. This article is an article that visualizes your tweet using the language model BERT used for natural language processing, which was recently applied to Google search. I will write in a hands-on format so that as many people as possible can try it out, so if you are interested, please give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] First satellite data analysis with Tellus</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/first-satellite-data-analysis-with-tellus-0bde3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/first-satellite-data-analysis-with-tellus-0bde3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted on the 21st day of Cisco Advent Calendar 2019 by Cisco Systems LLC. What kind of connection does Cisco have with satellite data in the first place? I think that there is a question, so I will introduce it including that.
What you can do with this article  Know what satellite data is Find out what the satellite data platform Tellus is Know how to use Tellus development environment Satellite data can be analyzed using Tellus development environment Understanding what NDVI and NDWI are  Finally you can   Display high-definition satellite image by selecting date and position Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:42:49 GMT, North 35.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Student Kaggler, who cannot analyze data, analyzes himself</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/student-kaggler-who-cannot-analyze-data-analyzes-himself-2ec0b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/student-kaggler-who-cannot-analyze-data-analyzes-himself-2ec0b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  ###Self-introduction My name is Chizu Chizu. I&amp;rsquo;m 14 and I&amp;rsquo;m 2 now. It is a hobby type, but I was particularly typing. (Past tense)
Now I&amp;rsquo;m a low skill Kagler.
I got a bronze medal in &amp;ldquo;tentatively&amp;rdquo; IEEE. We&amp;rsquo;ll see later on why it&amp;rsquo;s a tentative one.
After getting tired of AtCoder, I got into Kaggle. I will definitely become a master by my own power.
What made me want to write I wanted to write an advent calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Performance study of latest ensemble learning Sklearn Stacking (Compare LBGM, RGF, ET, RF, LR, KNN models with Heamy and Sklearn)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/performance-study-of-latest-ensemble-learning-sklearn-stacking-compare-lbgm-rgf-et-rf-lr-knn-models-with-heamy-and-sklearn-61b3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/performance-study-of-latest-ensemble-learning-sklearn-stacking-compare-lbgm-rgf-et-rf-lr-knn-models-with-heamy-and-sklearn-61b3b/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  Stacking sklearn, it might be a standard because it was a very good child when I tried using it
| library | layer1 | layer2 | public score | speed | | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; | &amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | | lgbm model | lgb |-| 0.74162 |-| heamy single stacking | lbg, rgf, et, rf, lr, knn | lr | 0.76076 | 64s | heamy multiple stacking | lgb, rgf, et, rf, lr, knn | lgb, lr | 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Employee 2vec: Extract member characteristics from Slack history and visualize organizational structure</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/employee-2vec-extract-member-characteristics-from-slack-history-and-visualize-organizational-structure-05e2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/employee-2vec-extract-member-characteristics-from-slack-history-and-visualize-organizational-structure-05e2c/</guid>
      <description>It is the 7th day of [ABEJA Advent Calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/abeja).  #Introduction
Last time, I dropped a piece of information that couldn&amp;rsquo;t make a VIP channel in Slack, but it&amp;rsquo;s not good to think that ABEJA is just playing with VIP, so I decided to send it to Tech a little this time. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll try the following two stories. If it&amp;rsquo;s hard to understand, maybe you can jump to the bottom and see the graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] First image classifier</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/first-image-classifier-a8902/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/first-image-classifier-a8902/</guid>
      <description>Hello. In my work, I&#39;m far from engineering and I can&#39;t write much by doing what I&#39;ve done,  I have a little time, so I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize what I learned a little. Advent calendar I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid! You can write an article that you just did a tutorial! That means one&amp;hellip;
Assumed readers I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a lot about machine learning, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched on implementation so much so I will touch on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Use Kaggle API inside Docker container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</guid>
      <description># things to do   Start container using Kaggle official image (kaggle/python) Download csv file with kaggle ~ command Download public notebook with kaggle ~ command  First summary  DL kaggle.json (kaggle.com &amp;gt;My Account &amp;gt;Create New API Token button) 2.$ docker run -it --rm --mount type=bind,src=pwd,dst=/root/dev kaggle/python $ pip install kaggle $ mkdir ~/.kaggle $ cp /root/dev/kaggle.json ~/.kaggle 6.$ chmod 600 ~/.kaggle/kaggle.json $ kaggle competitions download -c titanic -p input/titanic $ unzip input/titanic/titanic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I don&#39;t want to search for high para because it is IQ1 (how to use lightgbm_tuner)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-dont-want-to-search-for-high-para-because-it-is-iq1-how-to-use-lightgbm_tuner-dee7f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-dont-want-to-search-for-high-para-because-it-is-iq1-how-to-use-lightgbm_tuner-dee7f/</guid>
      <description>This article is posted on [IQ1&#39;s 2nd Advent Calendar 2019](https://adventar.org/calendars/4711).  IQ1 machine learning For machine learning, data preprocessing and model hyper search are inevitable. However, I have an IQ of 1, so I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do it if I can do preprocessing of data and high-para search. If you put the preprocessing of data into this modern gradient boosting tree system algorithm (such as lightgbm), you can handle the missing values as they are and you do not have to preprocess the categorical variables, so it will be a world relatively friendly to IQ1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Paper and Implementation] When asked, Is this data set difficult?...</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/paper-and-implementation-when-asked-is-this-data-set-difficult...-74917/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/paper-and-implementation-when-asked-is-this-data-set-difficult...-74917/</guid>
      <description>Learning a convolutional neural network (CNN) takes time.  Especially, if you try to get accuracy without transfer learning, it takes about 5 days** There are times. The paper introduced in this paper quantitatively describes the difficulty of datasets. By evaluating, classification accuracy can be estimated quickly without learning CNN. Is that.
*The entire code was placed on here. *The figures in this paper are basically taken from the paper (Spectral Metric for Dataset Complexity Assessment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] I tried using the Tensorflow Object Detection API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is IchiLab from RHEMS Giken.
This time using the Object Detection API of TensorFlow, Let me detect the object I want to recognize, I finally tried it on an Android device.
Many helpful sites have helped me, Still, I had a lot of points that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve with just one or two pages.
In this article, I will pick up the parts that I stumbled upon to make a difference, I hope that the number of people who do the same will be reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] (Saved version: updated from time to time) A collection of useful tutorials for doing data analysis hackathons by Team AI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/saved-version-updated-from-time-to-time-a-collection-of-useful-tutorials-for-doing-data-analysis-hackathons-by-team-ai-f8e32/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/saved-version-updated-from-time-to-time-a-collection-of-useful-tutorials-for-doing-data-analysis-hackathons-by-team-ai-f8e32/</guid>
      <description>We at Team AI hold machine learning study sessions and data analysis hackathons every day in Shibuya.  The goal is to have a community of 1 million people, mainly in Tokyo.
I hope this movement of data analysis will spread throughout Japan and around the world. We have put together a useful tutorial for doing data analysis hackathons. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun, so everyone, especially the locals, should try it out for yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Translation] scikit-learn 0.18 User Guide 4.1. Pipeline and Feature Union: Combination of estimators</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/translation-scikit-learn-0.18-user-guide-4.1.-pipeline-and-feature-union-combination-of-estimators-fdfd2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/translation-scikit-learn-0.18-user-guide-4.1.-pipeline-and-feature-union-combination-of-estimators-fdfd2/</guid>
      <description>Google translated http://scikit-learn.org/0.18/modules/pipeline.html  scikit-learn 0.18 User Guide 4. Dataset conversion
 4.1. Pipeline and FeatureUnion: Estimator combination 4.1.1. Pipeline: Chain estimation Pipeline can be used to combine multiple estimators into one. I can do it. It is convenient because the steps that process the data, such as feature selection, normalization, and classification, are often fixed. The pipeline serves two purposes here.
-Convenience: To fit the whole sequence of estimators, just call fit and predict the data once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understand the TensorFlow namespace and master shared variables</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understand-the-tensorflow-namespace-and-master-shared-variables-ffe99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understand-the-tensorflow-namespace-and-master-shared-variables-ffe99/</guid>
      <description>## Intro  This is the 9th day article of TensorFlow Advent Calendar 2016.
TensorFlow was released in November 2015, but the &amp;ldquo;namespace&amp;rdquo; function was supported from the beginning. This is used in graph visualization with TensorBoard, but of course it&amp;rsquo;s not the only one. Namespaces are very useful for managing identifiers. I recall C++ when it comes to strong &amp;ldquo;namespace&amp;rdquo; support, but I&amp;rsquo;ll quote it from a C++ instruction book (self-study C++).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Talk to improve the bottleneck of machine learning algorithm with Cython</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/talk-to-improve-the-bottleneck-of-machine-learning-algorithm-with-cython-fe83f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/talk-to-improve-the-bottleneck-of-machine-learning-algorithm-with-cython-fe83f/</guid>
      <description>#About this article   Talk about how to make Python faster Find CPU bound processing bottlenecks by profiling Improve the bottleneck you find with Cython  #Introduction We recently implemented a recommendation algorithm called Bayesian Personalized Ranking (BPR). I tried to write the code with reference to the formula of this paper, but when I tried to execute it, it was a bit too slow and I could not use it, so I improved the processing speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] TensorFlow Deep MNIST for Experts 翻訳</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-deep-mnist-for-experts-%E7%BF%BB%E8%A8%B3-fa9cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-deep-mnist-for-experts-%E7%BF%BB%E8%A8%B3-fa9cf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Beforeandprevious using Beginner tutorial translation and actually using TensorFlow I did machine learning. This time I translated the tutorial for Expert.
Deep MNIST for Experts TensorFlow is a powerful library for performing large-scale numerical calculations. One of the best tasks is the training and execution of deep neural networks. In this tutorial we will learn the basic building blocks of a TensorFlow model while building a deep convolutional MNIST classifier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to compress the image using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-compress-the-image-using-machine-learning-fb6ee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-compress-the-image-using-machine-learning-fb6ee/</guid>
      <description>![original_compressed.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.amazonaws.com/0/77079/2f7e9fc7-d91a-bd40-dca9-bed85174e317.png)  #Introduction Try compressing the image using K-Means, which is a typical clustering algorithm. First, I will explain the K-Means algorithm. After that, I will explain about image compression using K-Means. For details, refer to Coursera Machine Learning.
What is clustering? Dividing a collection of data into several groups (clusters) according to the similarity between the data. K-Means algorithm Intuitive description of algorithm The K-Means algorithm is roughly divided into the following three processes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Multi-armed bandit problem</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/multi-armed-bandit-problem-f9a38/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/multi-armed-bandit-problem-f9a38/</guid>
      <description>## wrap up  I tried solving the multi-armed bandit problem with Thompson Sampling.
What is the multi-armed bandit problem? (For Bernoulli Bandit) I have multiple slot machines and when I play them, I get a hit or a miss. The probability of winning is different for each slot, but its value is unknown. At this time, I want to win a lot with a certain number of game plays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Tool to support machine learning in Python MALSS (Introduction)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tool-to-support-machine-learning-in-python-malss-introduction-fe1cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tool-to-support-machine-learning-in-python-malss-introduction-fe1cc/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;Font color=&amp;quot;red&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Support Python3 (2016.01.25)&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;  I made a tool called MALSS (Machine Learning Support System) that supports machine learning in Python (PyPI/GitHub). We would be happy if you could give us your opinions.
I&amp;rsquo;m writing the rest here.
 Tool MALSS (basic) that supports machine learning in Python Tool MALSS (application) that supports machine learning in Python  Purpose A rich open source development environment has made it really easy to use machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Calculation of support vector machine (SVM) (using cvxopt)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/calculation-of-support-vector-machine-svm-using-cvxopt-faba9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/calculation-of-support-vector-machine-svm-using-cvxopt-faba9/</guid>
      <description>Hello.  The calculation of the support vector machine (SVM) is based on the procedure (using cvxopt) of Discontinuation creation &amp;ldquo;soft margin SVM&amp;rdquo; about artificial intelligenceIfyoufollowitexactly,youwillfeelalittlelikecalculatingthesolutionyourself.Inthefollowing1,theconvergentsolutionofLagrangemultiplieralpha,tabplot,etc.arealsoplotted(```class×prediction==1``Highlightthedatathatbecomes`.prediction==0istheboundaryline).
$ ./svm.py file = classification.txt (len=200) cvxopt result status: optimal delta = 5.684342e-14 class = (&#39;-1&#39;,&#39;+1&#39;) confusion matrix: [[96 7] [34 63]] #!/usr/bin/env python # -*- coding: utf-8 -*- # support vector machine (SVM) calculation Use # cvxopt.solvers.qp (Quadratic Programming) from __future__ import print_function import numpy as np import cvxopt Ccoeff = [30, 30] # soft margin coefficients of class SIGMA = 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Calculate tf-idf with scikit-learn</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/calculate-tf-idf-with-scikit-learn-f8697/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/calculate-tf-idf-with-scikit-learn-f8697/</guid>
      <description>**This post is the fourth day article of [Reality Escape Advent Calendar 2013](http://katryo.hatenablog.com/entry/2013/12/19/001823). **  2nd dayusesthehtmlfetchedusingtheBingAPI,so[2ndday](http://qiita.com/katryo(/items/62291ba328de9d12bd30) is easier to understand if you read it first.
Put this article in 3 lines  I checked a Python library called scikit-learn Day 2 Calculated tf-idf of word in html saved Confirmed word to tfidf mapping  Reference scikit-learn formula, text feature extraction document
Calculating tfidf of words in Tweet using scikit-learn</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>