<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TensorflowLite on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/tensorflowlite/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TensorflowLite on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/tensorflowlite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning with Raspberry Pi 4 and Coral USB Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-with-raspberry-pi-4-and-coral-usb-accelerator-12aff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-with-raspberry-pi-4-and-coral-usb-accelerator-12aff/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article summarizes the installation procedure of Raspberry Pi 4 and Coral USB Accelerator as a method of machine learning with edge device.
Raspberry Pi 4 is the latest generation of the current model. The CPU and memory performance have been greatly improved, and USB 3.0 is also supported.
Coral USB Accelerator is Google&amp;rsquo;s dedicated ASIC developed by Google for machine learning on edge devices.
This dedicated ASIC is called Edge TPU, and you can use TensorFlow Lite&amp;rsquo;s flake work specialized for inference at the edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] About the shortest path to create an image recognition model by machine learning and implement an Android application</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-the-shortest-path-to-create-an-image-recognition-model-by-machine-learning-and-implement-an-android-application-453a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-the-shortest-path-to-create-an-image-recognition-model-by-machine-learning-and-implement-an-android-application-453a2/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article   How to easily create an image recognition model and share it as an application  Execution environment  google colaboratory (Runtime: GPU)(tensorflow 2.0)(Google Chrome) win 10 Android Studio (3.5.2) android 9.0(Huawei mate 10 pro)  What to write in this article  Dataset creation method for image recognition model How to create image recognition model How to load the created image recognition model in Android Studio My failure (?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] I tried using the Tensorflow Object Detection API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is IchiLab from RHEMS Giken.
This time using the Object Detection API of TensorFlow, Let me detect the object I want to recognize, I finally tried it on an Android device.
Many helpful sites have helped me, Still, I had a lot of points that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve with just one or two pages.
In this article, I will pick up the parts that I stumbled upon to make a difference, I hope that the number of people who do the same will be reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>