<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Streamlit on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/streamlit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Streamlit on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/streamlit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Easy explosion] Make a web application in minutes with Streamlit without the need for HTML files</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/easy-explosion-make-a-web-application-in-minutes-with-streamlit-without-the-need-for-html-files-566c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/easy-explosion-make-a-web-application-in-minutes-with-streamlit-without-the-need-for-html-files-566c2/</guid>
      <description>## What is Streamlit?  Streamlit is an open source framework for Python.
Goal this time For the time being, I would like to easily make something like a web application. The most difficult part in creating a web application is the processing of the back end and the creation of HTML files, but Streamlit seems to have no need to do those tasks at all. You can make a web page with just one Python file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] I wrote a test of Streamlit that can make a visualization application easily</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-i-wrote-a-test-of-streamlit-that-can-make-a-visualization-application-easily-ca558/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-i-wrote-a-test-of-streamlit-that-can-make-a-visualization-application-easily-ca558/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When making a web application that contains graphs based on Python, I have favored the combination of the graph library Plotly + web application framework Dash by Plotly. However, this time I met a big newcomer Streamlit with a great potential to threaten the position of Dash, so I will drop the memo I wrote down the test.
What is # Streamlit?
 Streamlit — The fastest way to build custom ML tools   Streamlit is an open-source app framework for Machine Learning and Data Science teams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>