<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pycharm on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/pycharm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pycharm on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/pycharm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Set VS Code to PyCharm.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7091714be/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7091714be/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I said, &amp;ldquo;Everyone in Pythonista should use the dexterous IDE, PyCharm, for everyday development to develop explosive speeds.&amp;rdquo;
I have been in PyCharm swamp for more than half a year since I was a Pythonista kid.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m here recently.&amp;rdquo;
I said, &amp;ldquo;People don&amp;rsquo;t really understand PyCharm&amp;rsquo;s intelligence, it&amp;rsquo;s free and I&amp;rsquo;m using tools like VS Code!!!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want this!!!! I was wondering why PyCharm is so amazing!!!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Use AWS interpreter with Pycharm</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fd4c64ad7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fd4c64ad7/</guid>
      <description>## things to do  Develop with local pycharm using AWS instance interpreter!
background When it is extremely difficult to install a specific module, it is very easy to use the already installed AWS AMI or docker container. However, I want to do coding with an IDE such as pycharm, so it is a little difficult to enter the server and develop with vim. .. With pycharm, I logged in to the server with remote, I found a function that can be coded using the interpreter of that server, so I tried it and made a note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The strongest Python integrated development environment PyCharm</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f88d50da8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f88d50da8/</guid>
      <description># Strongest Python integrated development environment PyCharm  When learning a new language, a good IDE will be the best teacher, so I think it should be used actively without being stingy. So, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at PyCharm, the most powerful integrated development environment in Python. I think it is the most, so I wrote it assuming Web application development with Django.
The data on functions and price system are as of PyCharm 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] pycharm shortcut</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fa8ba1880/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fa8ba1880/</guid>
      <description>Pycharm Community Edition came out, so I tried using it immediately.  On Mac
Command+F search Command + R replacement Command+shift+F grep search Command+shift+R grep replacement Command + Option + R execution Command+Option+D Debug execution Command + O class name filter Command+shift+O File name filter</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>