<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Selenium on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/selenium/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Selenium on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/selenium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>(◎◎) {Let Python do the boring stuff.........(He? Hona Python will do the homework}} (゜) (゜)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/let-python-do-the-boring-stuff.........he-hona-python-will-do-the-homework-86258/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/let-python-do-the-boring-stuff.........he-hona-python-will-do-the-homework-86258/</guid>
      <description># Did you make Python do boring stuff?  I didn&amp;rsquo;t let it do A book on the cover with a robot like this C-3PO playing grass
It&amp;rsquo;s well-known as a good Python book, and many people have read it.
So who read this book and did Python actually do the boring stuff? Isn&amp;rsquo;t it quite small? I think there are many people who are satisfied with reading. I was one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I want to sell a product that was exhibited by Mercari python scraping</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-sell-a-product-that-was-exhibited-by-mercari-python-scraping-c50ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-sell-a-product-that-was-exhibited-by-mercari-python-scraping-c50ca/</guid>
      <description>## Trigger  Do you sell anything you no longer need using Mercari? I also sell unnecessary books in Mercari, but since they are old reference books and study books, they are hard to sell. .. ..
Mercari will offer a &amp;ldquo;sellable price&amp;rdquo; when listing. However, if I set it to a high price, I can&amp;rsquo;t sell it, and if it&amp;rsquo;s too cheap, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve lost something.
Before setting the price of an exhibit, I conduct a search to find out what the real market price is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Selenium environment on Amazon Linux 2 in the shortest time</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-selenium-environment-on-amazon-linux-2-in-the-shortest-time-371d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-selenium-environment-on-amazon-linux-2-in-the-shortest-time-371d2/</guid>
      <description>This article is the Amazon Linux 2 version of [Build Selenium environment with Amazon Linux at the shortest](https://qiita.com/onorioriori/items/4fa271daa3621e8f6fd9).  If you want to build Selenium environment on Amazon Linux, please refer to the link above.
Overview By the end of June 30, 2020, Amazon Linux security update provision will end, Made it possible to build a Selenium environment on Amazon Linux 2. The procedure is almost unchanged, but there are some changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Since it is Criboch, you can collect endless illustrations indefinitely.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/since-it-is-criboch-you-can-collect-endless-illustrations-indefinitely.-224c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/since-it-is-criboch-you-can-collect-endless-illustrations-indefinitely.-224c4/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s the final day of **[IPFactory Advent Calender 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/ipfactory)**.  Everyone in Cribbotch! Let&amp;rsquo;s survive 6 hours of sex with a nice illustration!! Oh, it&amp;rsquo;s over
#specification Using Web Scraping ● Automatically collect images posted on Jie. If you change it a little, it might be P●x●v. #contents I will also put it on GitHub ~~ (later) ~~
from bs4 import BeautifulSoup from selenium import webdriver from selenium.webdriver.common.by import By from selenium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s automatically display the lyrics of the song playing on iTunes with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-automatically-display-the-lyrics-of-the-song-playing-on-itunes-with-python-4d388/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-automatically-display-the-lyrics-of-the-song-playing-on-itunes-with-python-4d388/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There are times when you want to display lyrics while playing a song in iTunes (the name has changed from Catalina to music). However, it is troublesome to manually search and display the lyrics each time the song changes. Let Python do the hassle.
(Updated January 4, 2020) Improved. → &amp;ldquo;[Let&amp;rsquo;s automatically display the lyrics of the song playing on iTunes with Python (improved version)]&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/saba/items/22b44e1045dbc3f9b0bc)&amp;quot;
#Thing you want to do Play music with &amp;ldquo;Music&amp;rdquo;, a standard Mac app, and automatically display the lyrics on the lyrics site each time the song switches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The back side of the ring-fit adventure stock bot that eradicates resale yard</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-back-side-of-the-ring-fit-adventure-stock-bot-that-eradicates-resale-yard-6024a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-back-side-of-the-ring-fit-adventure-stock-bot-that-eradicates-resale-yard-6024a/</guid>
      <description>#2020/01/11  Ringfit Adventure Arrival bot has been renewed because it has frozen. Thank you for your continued support for Listed Dolphin @ Ringfit Adventure.
Overview Get notified when Ringfit Adventures arrives at a list price on Amazon Ringfit adventure arrival bot I made. I will introduce the back side of this bot. Eradicate the resale yard.
#Background
Ringfit Adventure is very popular. The product has been in short supply since its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A story that analyzes the delivery of Nico Niko.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-that-analyzes-the-delivery-of-nico-niko.-ccd89/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-that-analyzes-the-delivery-of-nico-niko.-ccd89/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;m a VTuber Marginal Geek. In December, &amp;ldquo;Virtual to Live&amp;rdquo; was held at Ryogoku Kokugikan, and it was also streamed live by Nico Nico. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even go to the field and even see them in real time, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait until the disk came out. That&amp;rsquo;s why I bought an online ticket and saw the time shift. Well, than expected. I wanted to save it until I could not see the time shift, so I started analyzing Nico Niko with Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping a dynamic site with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/scraping-a-dynamic-site-with-docker-6cc97/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/scraping-a-dynamic-site-with-docker-6cc97/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is the 13th day article from Kinki University Advent Calendar 2019.
First of all, note that scraping is basically the last method you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t do if you don&amp;rsquo;t need it. This time, scraping Qiita&amp;rsquo;s tag ranking, Qiita has an api and gets tag ranking there. There was no api to do (as of December 8, 2019) so I scraped it. If you can get the information you want with api, get it with api.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wear Instagram</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/wear-instagram-3d933/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/wear-instagram-3d933/</guid>
      <description>What kind of photos do you post when you post photos on instagram? [^1]  I think that SNS for showing to others, it is easy to unconsciously produce a fulfilling self **. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s what your actions are tied to ** your SNS&amp;rsquo;s past posts?
I would like to express such a situation.
 This article is Keio SFC Tokui Lab (Computational Creativity Lab.) Also serves as a commentary on the summer camp 2019 hackathon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web scraping with Selenium (Python)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/web-scraping-with-selenium-python-9d6d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/web-scraping-with-selenium-python-9d6d1/</guid>
      <description>When you build a machine learning system that uses Python, you can use data that can be used without restrictions on control mechanisms such as patents called open data that are open to the public on the Internet.  Of course, I use the acquired data to update the model efficiently, but there are times when I want to automate. This time, I will try to use Selenium with the so-called Web scraping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand in 10 minutes Selenium</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understand-in-10-minutes-selenium-9a3c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understand-in-10-minutes-selenium-9a3c8/</guid>
      <description>What is # [Selenium](https://selenium.dev/)  Selenium is a framework for automating web browser operations. Developed by ThoughtWorks in 2004 to automate UI testing of web applications. https://selenium.dev/history/
Originally developed for the purpose of UI testing and JavaScript testing of web applications, it is used for various purposes other than testing, such as task automation and website crawling.
This article describes the environment setup and basic usage for operating Chrome via Selenium in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Fully automatic connection] 90 minutes and 12 hours solved with Colaboratory file only [Use Selenium]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fully-automatic-connection-90-minutes-and-12-hours-solved-with-colaboratory-file-only-use-selenium-8869b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fully-automatic-connection-90-minutes-and-12-hours-solved-with-colaboratory-file-only-use-selenium-8869b/</guid>
      <description>Are you using Google Colaboratory? It&#39;s the best, isn&#39;t it?  Google Colaboratory is a Jupyter notebook environment that runs on a browser. Moreover, GPU and TPU machines can be used free of charge. That&amp;rsquo;s the best.
However, there were two rules about usage time (described later), and it was also a addictive point to crawl Colaboratory users.
&amp;ldquo;When I wake up in the morning, the connection will be cut&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to predict horse racing by doing everything from data collection to deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-horse-racing-by-doing-everything-from-data-collection-to-deep-learning-55e49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-horse-racing-by-doing-everything-from-data-collection-to-deep-learning-55e49/</guid>
      <description># Overview  A student majoring in information systems at a certain T university. While looking at various articles of Qiita, I found such an article.
 If you have deep learning, you can exceed 100% recovery rate in horse racing  Regarding the 100% recovery rate in this article, it is unclear whether it will be valid in other periods because the number of betting tickets that were simulated for purchase is small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate web processes with Heroku &#43; Selenium &#43; Chrome</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/automate-web-processes-with-heroku-selenium-chrome-76ae1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/automate-web-processes-with-heroku-selenium-chrome-76ae1/</guid>
      <description># Automate web process with Heroku + Selenium + Chrome   Automate web process with Heroku + Selenium + Chrome -Introduction -Purpose -Related Article -Execution environment -Source Code -Scenario and Assumptions -Create Automatic Process -Python API configuration -API mainframe -FX rate acquisition -Heroku Settings -Chrome and Driver Settings -[Driver version setting](#driver%e3%83%90%e3%83%bc%e3%82%b8%e3%83%a7%e3%83%b3%e3%81%ae%e8%a8(%ad%e5%ae%9a)  Introduction This article is for Mac environment, but the procedure is the same for Windows environment. Please read the environment-dependent part and try again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>