<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> clustering on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/clustering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  clustering on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/clustering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understanding the k-means method</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0d5d22a12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0d5d22a12/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Here is a summary of what I learned about the k-means method. The most basic clustering algorithm.
##reference In understanding the k-means method, I have referred to the following.
 Introduction to machine learning for language processing (natural language processing series)DaiyaTakamura(Author),ManabuOkumura(supervision) Publisher; Corona Essence of machine learningKoichiKato(Author) Publisher; SB Creative Co., Ltd.  #k-means method overview
What is k-means method The k-means method is an algorithm that first divides the data into appropriate clusters, and then adjusts the data so that the data can be divided in a good manner using the average of the clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to compress the image using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fb6ee6b8e/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fb6ee6b8e/</guid>
      <description>![original_compressed.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.amazonaws.com/0/77079/2f7e9fc7-d91a-bd40-dca9-bed85174e317.png)  #Introduction Try compressing the image using K-Means, which is a typical clustering algorithm. First, I will explain the K-Means algorithm. After that, I will explain about image compression using K-Means. For details, refer to Coursera Machine Learning.
What is clustering? Dividing a collection of data into several groups (clusters) according to the similarity between the data. K-Means algorithm Intuitive description of algorithm The K-Means algorithm is roughly divided into the following three processes:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>