<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MySQL on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/mysql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MySQL on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/mysql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF beginner tried building a problem server (web) [problem]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ctf-beginner-tried-building-a-problem-server-web-problem-a1830/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ctf-beginner-tried-building-a-problem-server-web-problem-a1830/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Do you know CTF (Capture The Flag)? Through the CTF, you can experience and learn about security issues. If so, I will try to explain the problem by making a vulnerable server myself. I have created a server for CTF rudimentary problems.
important point By nature, the server is vulnerable, so Please do not implement the contents of this article as it is in a production environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use: Django-MySQL</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/use-django-mysql-972f8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/use-django-mysql-972f8/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 5th day of [Django Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/django).  #Introduction Django&amp;rsquo;s ORM can issue sufficient queries for development by making full use of select_related, prefetch_related, Preftch, Q object, etc.
However, there are some things that cannot be done, and there are cases where you have to write raw SQL. For example, when multiple indexes are pasted, USE_IDNEX to specify the index you want to use, IGNORE_INDEX to specify the index you do not want to use, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate large numbers of simple queries with MySQL</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/accelerate-large-numbers-of-simple-queries-with-mysql-10e21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/accelerate-large-numbers-of-simple-queries-with-mysql-10e21/</guid>
      <description>No matter how light a query is, for example, if the RTT between the web server and MySQL is 5ms and you execute 20 queries, the RTT alone will take 100ms.  The technique of using bulk insert (a query that writes multiple lines after VALUES) is well known when inserting a lot of data. However, this technique cannot be used in the following cases.
 I want to insert 1 row at a time into multiple tables I want to combine multiple UPDATEs and SELECTs  For example, there was the following scene in one of our projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>