<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> AdventCalendar2019 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/adventcalendar2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  AdventCalendar2019 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/adventcalendar2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Time series plot started-python version-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/time-series-plot-started-python-version-9e6b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/time-series-plot-started-python-version-9e6b8/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 22nd day article of MicroAd Advent Calendar 2019.
Thing you want to do Time series plots are a very useful tool when visualizing log data. Until now, I have lived such a life that I replaced the dates on the horizontal axis with numbers and plotted and escaped. However, it&amp;rsquo;s different now. You can now plot well with the horizontal axis set to time series!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle SE whose brain was hardened studied machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/uncle-se-whose-brain-was-hardened-studied-machine-learning-13eea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/uncle-se-whose-brain-was-hardened-studied-machine-learning-13eea/</guid>
      <description>## [Introduction]  This article will be on the 19th day of How I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ② Advent Calendar 2019.
Here is how my uncle SE studied machine learning. The motivation was to start with the question, &amp;ldquo;Can you use machine learning?&amp;rdquo; Since I was working in the dark clouds, my honest memory is vague.
career I have been programming for nearly 30 years. Starting with MS BASIC I learned when I was in elementary school, I have touched Z80 assembler, MC68000 assembler, FORTRAN, C (UNIX), C++ (Mac), VB, Java (Android), VB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of class-based generic view and inherited class relationship</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/overview-of-class-based-generic-view-and-inherited-class-relationship-eb2dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/overview-of-class-based-generic-view-and-inherited-class-relationship-eb2dd/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 13th day of Django Advent Calendar 2019.  In this article, I would like to summarize Django&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Class-based Generic View&amp;rdquo; and its inheritance class relationships.
Premise I refer to and cite the official documentation of Django 3.0, which is the latest version at the time of writing this article.
What is a Class-Based Generic View? First, a &amp;ldquo;view&amp;rdquo; in Django is an encapsulation [^1] of logic that processes user requests and returns responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning Machine learning learned by a new graduate who has no experience in machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-machine-learning-learned-by-a-new-graduate-who-has-no-experience-in-machine-learning-4a511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-machine-learning-learned-by-a-new-graduate-who-has-no-experience-in-machine-learning-4a511/</guid>
      <description>This article is about how I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI② Advent Calendar 2019 __.  Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the steps that have taken a slightly different step from the general approach to learning machine learning. I would be happy if it could be used as a reference for as many people as possible. I usually write for individual blogs, and I was warmly thinking about writing on my blog, but I thought it was a great opportunity, so I posted it on __qiita for the first time __.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>