<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Spark on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/spark/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Spark on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/spark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance verification of data preprocessing for machine learning (numerical data edition) (1)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/performance-verification-of-data-preprocessing-for-machine-learning-numerical-data-edition-1-cf176/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/performance-verification-of-data-preprocessing-for-machine-learning-numerical-data-edition-1-cf176/</guid>
      <description>First Edition: March 10, 2020 &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;  Author: Soichi Takashige, Masahiro Ito, Hitachi, Ltd.
#Introduction In this post, I will introduce the design know-how of data preprocessing and the results of performance verification of data preprocessing when designing a system incorporating a machine learning model.
The second article introduces know-how for performance improvement and verification results in data preprocessing using Python.
Post list:
 Data preprocessing for systems that use machine learning Performance Verification of Data Preprocessing for Machine Learning (Numerical Data) (Part 1) (Posted) Performance Verification of Data Preprocessing for Machine Learning (Numerical Data) (Part 2)  #About the benchmark (BigBench) referenced in the performance verification Before introducing design know-how and performance verification results, we will introduce the benchmarks that were referenced as references in verification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data preprocessing for systems using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/data-preprocessing-for-systems-using-machine-learning-48825/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/data-preprocessing-for-systems-using-machine-learning-48825/</guid>
      <description>First Edition: March 3, 2020 &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;  Author: Soichi Takashige, Masahiro Ito, Hitachi, Ltd.
#Introduction In this post, I will introduce the design know-how of data preprocessing and the performance verification results of numerical data preprocessing when designing a system incorporating a machine learning model.
The first article introduces the data preprocessing of machine learning system and its design.
Post list:
 Data preprocessing for systems that use machine learning (this post) Performance verification of data preprocessing for machine learning (numerical data) (1) Performance Verification of Data Preprocessing for Machine Learning (Numerical Data) (Part 2)  #Outline and flow of AI projects Data analysis utilizing AI technology such as machine learning is drawing attention, and the number of projects utilizing AI is increasing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>