<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> GANs on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/gans/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  GANs on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/gans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried moving food with SinGAN</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5781d6032/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5781d6032/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I have disturbed the empty frame of Production/Counting Advent Calendar 2019.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with SinGAN a lot lately, so I&amp;rsquo;ll try to summarize the results. SinGAN is a paper that became a hot topic because it was selected as the best paper at ICCV 2019. It&amp;rsquo;s great for learning with just one image and generating images of any size with the same features. ![Screenshot from 2019-12-24 18-23-29.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Generate Pokemon with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e85dedb40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e85dedb40/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 16th day article of Kinki University Advent Calendar 2019. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the decoction is, but I will generate a Pokemon image with Gan. In the future, I would like to add a description of Pokemon picture book to the generated image. The source code is here
DCGAN DCGAN was used for image generation. For details, see Papers. The implementation used DCGAN-tensorflow,butforsomereasontherewasabugintheofficialsourcecode,sofixed is used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] History of major GAN studies (as of November 2019)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/c6bf085e7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/c6bf085e7/</guid>
      <description>### For people like this: point_up_tone1:  GAN (Generative Adversarial Network) was announced in 2014, but due to epoch-making research, there are many derivative researches recently, and what is it? .. I myself made full use of Google professor to do various research, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any Japanese literature that summarizes major related research in an easy-to-understand way, sorry! So, this article is for those who want to get an outline of the flow of GAN-related research, or for those who want to jump over each research ~~ one by one with quick and one-click jumping to the paper and code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>