<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PySimpleGUI on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/pysimplegui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PySimpleGUI on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/pysimplegui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an image processing viewer with PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-an-image-processing-viewer-with-pysimple-gui-30f54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-an-image-processing-viewer-with-pysimple-gui-30f54/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you can do with this article:   Viewer for selecting and displaying images Pass parameters to perform image processing Display the processed image  For a basic explanation of PySimPleGUI, please refer to If you use Tkinter, try using PySimpleGUI
Verification environment  windows10 macOS (catalina) Python3.7 Library -tkinter -PySimpleGUI -Pillow  Trigger It was interesting to see the article of Automatically generate ASCII art that created the above image and actually moved it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic usage of PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/basic-usage-of-pysimple-gui-376da/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/basic-usage-of-pysimple-gui-376da/</guid>
      <description>[●Text body (41 pages in PDF format: 1.22MB)](http://www.k-techlabo.org/www_python/PySimpleGUI.pdf) Updated March 12, 2020  (→Mirror site DL) －－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－
(2020/03/12) I teach programming at school. I made a text of PySimple GUI for use in educational settings.
There are many GUI libraries for Python, but PySimpleGUI is probably the easiest for beginners. There is a sense of security that it is based on Tkinter.
Although this text is still in a state of incompleteness, if it is used in the educational field, we will correct and update the content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw a graph with PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</guid>
      <description># What you can do by reading this article  With PySimple GUI, you can:
 You can draw bar graphs, line graphs, etc. Graph that refreshes display periodically  For the basic operation of PySimpleGUI, please refer to If you use Tkinter, try using PySimpleGUI.
Overview I think there are many people who analyze data as a way to use Python. Also, some people may want to visualize the results of analysis as line graphs or bar graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>