<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Data Science on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/data-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Data Science on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I have read 10 books related to time series data, so I write a book review.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/58c3e1135/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/58c3e1135/</guid>
      <description>#About the standing position of each book  I&amp;rsquo;m worried about what kind of axis to explain the standing position, but this time I tried to position it as &amp;ldquo;arbitrary and prejudiced&amp;rdquo; on the two axes of &amp;ldquo;target reader level&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;relationship with time series&amp;rdquo;.
#Introduction At work, I use various methods for various data regarding data analysis, but when I analyze it, there are surprisingly many time series data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Acquiring &amp; Analyzing New Corona Statistical Data with Python: Johns Hopkins University Data Edition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ab60bbba8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ab60bbba8/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I will post to Quiita after a long time. Recently, I started to analyze statistical data on pandemic of new coronavirus (as personal life work, not work?). And I&amp;rsquo;ve posted some on my blog.
 Status of each country from the view of lifesaving rate of the new Corona: What is the policy adopted by that advanced country with a very low lifesaving rate? │YUUKOU&amp;rsquo;s experience value Understanding the lifesaving rate of the new Corona: the strength of the United States, the critical United Kingdom, the Netherlands, China where the transition is too beautiful │ YUUKOU&amp;rsquo;s experience value  For example, we may post a chart that plots the time series transition of lifesaving rate as the result of data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning algorithms (support vector machines)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d17cb02b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d17cb02b7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Step-by-step about the theory, the implementation in python, and the analysis using scikit-learn of the algorithm taken up in &amp;ldquo;Classification of machine learning&amp;rdquo; Learn with. I wrote it for personal learning, so I would like you to take a look at any mistakes.
This time about Support Vector Machine. Despite its old history, it is a popular technique in the field of machine learning. It has a high generalization performance, and was the strongest algorithm until it was broken into deep learning by ILSVRC2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried implementing adversarial validation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/6f48c78ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/6f48c78ed/</guid>
      <description>### What is this article  After explaining what adversarial validation is, here is the code I tried to implement. I will write it here as a memorandum and organize knowledge.
The code that I referred to when posting this article is here
What is adversarial validation? If the distribution of train data is different from that of test data, the distribution of validation data may also be close to the distribution of train data, and test data may not be predicted well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Books on data science to read in 2020</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fe47446dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fe47446dd/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Przemek Chojecki](https://towardsdatascience.com/@pchojecki),[[DataScienceBooksyoushouldreadin2020](https://towardsdatascience.com/data-science-books-you-should-read-in-2020-358f70e1d9b2)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
Data science is arguably one of the hottest markets right now. Almost all companies are looking for or considering a data science role.
So it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to become a data scientist. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re already a data scientist and want to promote to a senior position, it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to hone your skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle Kernel Method Summary [Table Time Series Data]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/4c0f3baea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/4c0f3baea/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will write something like a standard for each data type in the Kaggle competition. In addition, I think it would be nice if it could be a hint when accuracy is not obtained regardless of the competition.  This time we will touch on the following competition datasets. In the case of competition, there is no Kernel, so I&amp;rsquo;ll try to put together Notebooks. Predict Future Sales Avocado Prices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle&#39;s Kernel Method Summary [Image Edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/11bd7381b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/11bd7381b/</guid>
      <description>Click here for the previous article  Kaggle Kernel Summary [Table Time Series Data]
In this article, including myself, I would like to know something like a standard for each data type in the Kaggle competition! I will write for people like. In addition, I think it would be nice if it could be a hint when accuracy is not obtained regardless of the competition.
This time we will look at various kernels, not just the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Process huge excel files with Python to improve productivity</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/33983de6c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/33983de6c/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Benedikt Droste](https://towardsdatascience.com/@droste.benedikt),&amp;quot;[BoostyourefficiencyandprocessExcel-fileswithPython](https://towardsdatascience.com/boost-your-efficiency-and-process-excel-files-with-python-cae650c85d6c)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
When you&amp;rsquo;re working with data, you inevitably come into contact with Excel. Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t use it for yourself, it will be needed by clients and colleagues. Excel excels in spreadsheets with small datasets.
But I always lamented when I saw an Excel sheet with tens of thousands of rows and hundreds of columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Data analysis Appropriate use of data analysis tools for beginners</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/742180491/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/742180491/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article and target audience  There are many tools for data analysis. Here, data analysis tools include Excel, programming, dashboard tools, BI tools, etc.
In this article, for those who are new to data analysis and those who are going to do data analysis, we will explain what kind of analysis tool should be used for what kind of situation.
The most important reason to decide what kind of analysis tool to use in what situation is that the right tool can make data analysis efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For non-programmers] How to walk Kaggle</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2d27ea4b9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2d27ea4b9/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 3rd day of Advent Calendar from [Kaggle Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/kaggle).  &amp;ldquo;** Kaggle I&amp;rsquo;m interested, but it&amp;rsquo;s scary and scary&amp;hellip; **&amp;rdquo; I think it will be useful for those who are thinking!
*The following information is as of December 2019
Until I meet # Kaggle
My background before I met Kaggle is roughly the following.
 Marketer ⇒ Consultant Bunka (art history major) No programming experience (I touched HTML a little) Black screen is in awe&amp;hellip;  It was like this, but I learned Python &amp;amp; machine learning in the last year, and I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to understand Kaggle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [First data science ⑤] I tried to help my friend&#39;s first property search by data analysis</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3aa0d6f88/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3aa0d6f88/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you. My name is S.I, a third year college student in the Department of Information Engineering.  My experience with Python is a little dealt with in a college experiment.
The data science division of Bracket Co., Ltd., where I am an intern, has the task of creating a crawler during the trial period to collect, process, visualize data, and briefly describe what I learned.
Task Theme My university friend will live alone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>