<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> scraping on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/scraping/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  scraping on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/scraping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Notify LINE of TV appearance information of your favorite entertainer</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/notify-line-of-tv-appearance-information-of-your-favorite-entertainer-fef55/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/notify-line-of-tv-appearance-information-of-your-favorite-entertainer-fef55/</guid>
      <description>#Purpose  I miss watching my favorite idol and comedians appear on TV, so I decided to notify them via LINE. #Overview Yahoo! TV G Guide was used to obtain information on TV programs, and to notify using LINE Notify. I set the program to run on Raspberrypi every morning at 9am.
Acquisition of program information For example, in the case of a terrestrial program of &amp;ldquo;Chiaki Bimura&amp;rdquo; (Regional setting Tokyo), such a URL is used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Practical Beautiful Soup ~Scraping the triple odds table on the official website for boat racing~</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-practical-beautiful-soup-~scraping-the-triple-odds-table-on-the-official-website-for-boat-racing~-f8d80/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-practical-beautiful-soup-~scraping-the-triple-odds-table-on-the-official-website-for-boat-racing~-f8d80/</guid>
      <description># Purpose  Data collection is a pain. I thought that I would like to analyze boat racing in the future, so as a practice of data collection Odds table of official boat racing site.
Overview  I can only think of a convenient language = python for scraping, so I use python3.7. Python 3.7 is called beatutiful soup ~~ It seems a little erotic ~~ It seems that the library with the name is convenient for scraping By using the beautifulsoup css selector, you can specify the location of the table without deciphering the html one by one!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Crawling &amp; Scraping Chapter 4 Summary</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-crawling-scraping-chapter-4-summary-fdecf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-crawling-scraping-chapter-4-summary-fdecf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Learning summary of &amp;ldquo;Python crawling &amp;amp; scraping [enhanced and revised version] Practical development guide for data collection and analysis&amp;rdquo; The fourth chapter of this time was mainly about the points to note when making a crawler under the theme of &amp;ldquo;methods for practical use&amp;rdquo;.
#4.1 Crawler characteristics ##4.1.1 Crawler with state
  Create a crawler that supports cookies when crawling sites that require login -Python&amp;rsquo;s Requests library automatically sends cookies to the server by using Session object</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 questions to check before web scraping</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/10-questions-to-check-before-web-scraping-ff0ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/10-questions-to-check-before-web-scraping-ff0ca/</guid>
      <description>With [Web scraping](https://www.octoparse.jp/), you can get the information you need in seconds and the great value behind it. But before we do that, there are 10 questions to ask.  #1.Is Web scraping illegal?
[robot.txt](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robots_exclusion_standard If you are allowed to crawl according to the terms of the file, we recommend that you read the Terms of Service (ToS) of the target website in advance to assess the legal feasibility of your data project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make an interactive LINE BOT 004 (answer the closing date of listed companies)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-make-an-interactive-line-bot-004-answer-the-closing-date-of-listed-companies-fcebc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-make-an-interactive-line-bot-004-answer-the-closing-date-of-listed-companies-fcebc/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  Last time, I implemented the function to acquire stock price information, but as a real problem, &amp;ldquo;I did not bother to ask BOT, I used the stock application It&amp;rsquo;s only a matter of time before I get the tsukumi saying, ``It&amp;rsquo;s more convenient&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;, and I&amp;rsquo;m probably using a certain portfolio management app on a daily basis without fail, so I would like BOT to pinpoint the stock price now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>