<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>websocket on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/websocket/</link>
    <description>Recent content in websocket on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/websocket/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A story that analyzes the delivery of Nico Niko.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-that-analyzes-the-delivery-of-nico-niko.-ccd89/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-that-analyzes-the-delivery-of-nico-niko.-ccd89/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;m a VTuber Marginal Geek. In December, &amp;ldquo;Virtual to Live&amp;rdquo; was held at Ryogoku Kokugikan, and it was also streamed live by Nico Nico. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even go to the field and even see them in real time, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait until the disk came out. That&amp;rsquo;s why I bought an online ticket and saw the time shift. Well, than expected. I wanted to save it until I could not see the time shift, so I started analyzing Nico Niko with Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I saw you not working</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-saw-you-not-working-d5220/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-saw-you-not-working-d5220/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There are people who smash without working in a club activity, so it is a story that I can always see the state of the club room. With OpenCV and WebSocket, I was able to easily create what I could see in real time. I will leave it.
Operating environment CentOS Linux release 7.5.1804 Python 3.6.8 Logitech Webcam C270
Implementation Install the following
pip install opencv-python pip install flask pip install gevent pip install gevent-websocket Directory structure ├ main.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s create a web chat using WebSocket with AWS serverless (Python)!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-create-a-web-chat-using-websocket-with-aws-serverless-python-d8095/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-create-a-web-chat-using-websocket-with-aws-serverless-python-d8095/</guid>
      <description>This article is the second day of NTT Technocross [Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/ntt-tx).  Hello. My name is Yasuda. I am in charge of new AI-related product development at NTT Technocross. It&amp;rsquo;s a gap from the main subject immediately, but drawing a manga is a recent break, and I&amp;rsquo;m drawing the following manga.
Data link understood by manga Enterprise architecture in the AI era understood with manga IT strategy understood by manga &amp;hellip; Well, in this article, I&amp;rsquo;d like to see how to do &amp;ldquo;WebSocket&amp;rdquo; without AWS server.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>