<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> tips on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  tips on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Django personal tips</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3a0e6256d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3a0e6256d/</guid>
      <description>This article is the last day of [Django Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/django).  #Introduction Nice to meet you. Thank you.
I usually develop web applications using Djnago.
-Sill Trend
This year&amp;rsquo;s Django Advent Calendar 2019 was also enjoyed every day. All the articles were interesting and informative. So, in this article, the last day of the calendar, I&amp;rsquo;d like to organize some basic and personal tips for Django. We hope that this article can help make Django even more popular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Tips] How to do template extends when creating HTML with django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fcea8bc7f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fcea8bc7f/</guid>
      <description>#Overview   Configuration of rough html templates when inheriting Tips on how to use tag important point  #background
 References: django document version 1.9 Django version: 1.9.2 python version: 2.7.10 OS: MacOS X  Things that the creator should decide for themselves are written in upper case, and the rest are written in lower case. Variable name or file name.
Configuration of html templates when inheriting Since I introduced on the official website an efficient method when writing html using template extends, it is almost a translation of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>