<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Java on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/java/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Java on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoder ABC 107 B string manipulation solved with Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3f2be6fca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3f2be6fca/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Beginner Contest 107 B-Grid Compression Difficulty: 434
This theme, string operation
Ruby h, w = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) a = [] h.times do |i| s = gets.chomp a.push(s) if s.index(&amp;#39;#&amp;#39;) end (w-1).downto(0) do |i| if a.all?{|x| x[i] ==&amp;#39;.&amp;#39;} a.each do |x| x[i] =&amp;#39;&amp;#39; end end end puts a a.push(s) if s.count(&amp;#39;.&amp;#39;) != w a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Solving AtCoder ARC 086 C hashes in Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/1c6f21934/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/1c6f21934/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Regular Contest 086 C-Not so Diverse Difficulty: 431
This theme, hash sorting
Ruby Speaking of duplicate lists, it&amp;rsquo;s a hash.
n, k = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) a = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) h = Hash.new(0) a.each do |x| h[x] += 1 end puts n-h.values.sort.reverse[0, k].inject(:+) h.sort_by{|key, v| -v}.each do |key, v| puts n-h.values.sort.reverse[0, k].inject(:+) ~~Ruby doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a destructive sort of hashes, but it seems to have few uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoder AGC 033 A breadth-first search solved with Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5d3059a10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5d3059a10/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Grand Contest 033 A-Darker and Darker Difficulty: 1245
This theme, breadth-first search
Ruby This is an advanced version of AtCoder Typical Contest 002 A-breadth-first search that I solved earlier. In particular, there are severe conditions such as execution time limit: 1 sec.
h, w = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) cm = Array.new(h + 2){Array.new(w + 2, 0)} que = [] 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoder ABC 131 D Array Sorting Solved with Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a136574d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a136574d1/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Beginner Contest 131 D-Megalomania Difficulty: 594
This theme, array sort
Ruby It&amp;rsquo;s an array sort, so I think it&amp;rsquo;s easy to implement. ~~ I chose a lighter problem because it is the first Python. ~~
n = gets.to_i a = Array.new(n){gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i)} a.sort_by!{|x| x[1]} ans = 0 n.times do |i| ans += a[i][0] if ans &amp;gt;a[i][1] puts &amp;#34;No&amp;#34; exit end end puts &amp;#34;Yes&amp;#34; a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 10 Open Source Web Crawlers for 2020</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a104a63fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a104a63fb/</guid>
      <description>[Web crawler](https://www.octoparse.jp/blog/what-is-web-crawler/) is a database that automatically collects information such as texts, images and videos published on the Internet. It is a program stored in. Various web crawlers play an important role in the big data boom, making it easy for people to scrape data.  Among the various web crawlers, there are many open source web crawler frameworks. Open source web crawlers allow users to program based on source code or frameworks, also provide resources to assist with scraping, and simplify data extraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [#1] Make Minecraft with Python. -Survey and design-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fd9ff0c94/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fd9ff0c94/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;font color=&amp;quot;grey&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Part of pictures, articles, images on this page are copyrighted by Mojang AB.&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;  #Overview This project reproduces the world-famous sandbox game &amp;ldquo;Minecraft&amp;rdquo; in the programming language &amp;ldquo;Python&amp;rdquo;.
Next article: [#2] Make Minecraft with Python. -Model drawing and player implementation-
##Trigger My first exposure to programming came from “Minecraft”.
That was over 4 years ago. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in so-called remodeling contents called &amp;ldquo;MOD&amp;rdquo; in Minecraft, and entered the world of programming, &amp;ldquo;I want to make it myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [January 2020] Reiwa, let&#39;s start the development container at full speed with VS Code&#39;s Remote Container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/084a0770c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/084a0770c/</guid>
      <description># Start a dash from &amp;quot;Development environment + container containing all projects&amp;quot; with Remote Conainer of VS Code! ?  Are you using VS Code Remote Conainer for development? You can use Remote SSH if you just enter an existing container, but let&amp;rsquo;s use Remote Container as a &amp;ldquo;part of local development environment&amp;rdquo;, rather as ** local development environment = Remote Container **. It&amp;rsquo;s Reiwa! ~~ (It&amp;rsquo;s been 2 years already&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Five languages basic grammar comparison (C#, Java, Python, Ruby, Kotlin)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/252d81e87/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/252d81e87/</guid>
      <description># Basic grammar comparison of 5 languages (C#, Java, Python, Ruby, Kotlin)  table of contents -Console output
-Variable Declaration
-Conditional branch
-Repeat
-Collection
Console output C# //System can be omitted System.Console.Write(&amp;#34;Hello &amp;#34;); Console.Write(&amp;#34;World&amp;#34;); &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Hello World Console.WriteLine(&amp;#34;Hello &amp;#34;); Console.WriteLine(&amp;#34;Workd&amp;#34;); &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Hello World 
Java System.out.print(&amp;#34;Hello &amp;#34;); System.out.print(&amp;#34;World&amp;#34;); &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Hello World System.out.println(&amp;#34;Hello &amp;#34;); System.out.println(&amp;#34;World&amp;#34;); &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Hello World 
Python print(&amp;#34;Hello&amp;#34;) print(&amp;#34;World&amp;#34;) &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Hello World print(&amp;#34;Hello &amp;#34;, end=&amp;#34;&amp;#34;) print(&amp;#34;World&amp;#34;) &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Hello World</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What is the programming language you learn at the end of your life? (If you want to catch up with a club with a lifetime salary of 300 million yen)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/eaa6815ef/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/eaa6815ef/</guid>
      <description># Introduction Do you learn new programming languages every year?  It&amp;rsquo;s poem&amp;rsquo;s time to borrow the place of java advent calendar. I wrote about Java in the Android project a few years ago. The complement of modern IDEs is great. Today&amp;rsquo;s story is what everyone loves and what programming language to learn. However, the adult version.
Now, everyone who has been writing code for some years in some language. As a matter of course, Java is something I have learned and I have written at work, I think that most people write only Java.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 7 trends in 2020 software development</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/4d9c3bd94/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/4d9c3bd94/</guid>
      <description>The following is an article by Tiara Brown Neil ([hackernoon](https://hackernoon.com/@theneil248)),[7SoftwareDevelopmentTrends2020Revealed](https://hackernoon.com/software-development-trends-2020-revealed-spi305m) is a Japanese translation.  7 Software Development Trends 2020 Revealed Did you know? Over half of IT projects have failed. For many of us who are aware of the complexity and dynamic nature of the software development industry, it&amp;rsquo;s less shocking.
Keeping pace is essential to survive in this unpredictable industry with constant innovation and progress. The wise not only take advantage of software development services, but weigh the pros and cons of all technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Discover the most dangerous functions on github</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2be9016f8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2be9016f8/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  The other day, at work, I was excited by &amp;ldquo;I am renovating or writing Ichibanya Bay function&amp;rdquo;. Everyone told me a lot, but it was an overwhelming victory for the &amp;ldquo;command pattern main loop function (1500 lines)&amp;rdquo; I wrote. Why did you write such a code?
So, today, I will discover the &amp;ldquo;most world-wide function&amp;rdquo; from github to heal my injured pride. In other words, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to see a yaw function rather than the one I wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What failed when Javaer changed to Pythonista</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fe4a12472/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fe4a12472/</guid>
      <description># at first  This is the 12/2 charge article for PyCon JP Advent Calendar 2016. There are other interesting articles, so if you are interested, please check it out. I have written Java in some places, but it may be wrong because it has been a while, so I hope you can read it while thinking about it.
Purpose As the subject says, I&amp;rsquo;ll share the mistakes I&amp;rsquo;ve made so that anyone reading this can make the transition from Javaer to Pythonista smoother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Should I fix that copy and paste?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fe1b3443a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fe1b3443a/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s true that copy clones of source code are more reliable than code clones, but in many cases the existence of code clones often hurts us at the last minute.  After the person in charge escaped, corrected the source code until late at night, and released it, in fact, I was told that &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m making it with copy and paste, so please test all the other places again&amp;rdquo; and start over Is very, very sad.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>