<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> data visualization on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/data-visualization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  data visualization on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/data-visualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Data analysis Appropriate use of data analysis tools for beginners</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/742180491/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/742180491/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article and target audience  There are many tools for data analysis. Here, data analysis tools include Excel, programming, dashboard tools, BI tools, etc.
In this article, for those who are new to data analysis and those who are going to do data analysis, we will explain what kind of analysis tool should be used for what kind of situation.
The most important reason to decide what kind of analysis tool to use in what situation is that the right tool can make data analysis efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introducing the potential of Plotly&#39;s scatter plots with practical examples</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/63646234e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/63646234e/</guid>
      <description>Hello! This article is Kaggle&#39;s advent calendar,  Scatter plot of Python data visualization library &amp;ldquo;Plotly&amp;rdquo; I thought that it goes well with competitions such as Kaggle, so I would like to introduce it.
First of all, I would like to see a concrete example. Example 1 Plots the word&amp;rsquo;s distributed representation with 3D compression Example 2 Plot rental data for 23 wards of Tokyo on map data What do you think!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>