<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> WebAPI on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/webapi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  WebAPI on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/webapi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Automate background removal of latest person images in directory with Python and API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0ff9d49f4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0ff9d49f4/</guid>
      <description># Thing you want to do   Background removal of portrait image Finely specify the input destination of the image to be background-removed and the output destination of the background-removed image. Browse the latest image in the folder Automation of them  Occasionally you may want to perform face recognition from an image using OpenCV or facenet and do some processing. Of course, these tools will recognize your face, but I have found that there are times when the accuracy of face recognition drops dramatically due to unnecessary things such as the background in the image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Prepare a pseudo API server using GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e7021b051/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e7021b051/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Perhaps recently, a feature called GitHub Actions has been added. This is the one that can fire certain Actions (shell script executions) for certain events. For example, it is a function for so-called CI/CD that builds when PR of dev branch is merged and pushes it to dev-pages branch.
At this time, I participated in the COVID-19 countermeasure site Hokkaido version, which is currently a big move, and developed using this function.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>