<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>React on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/react/</link>
    <description>Recent content in React on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/react/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Created a tool that visualizes mechanically from repository history in order to objectively know the productivity and soundness of the development team</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/created-a-tool-that-visualizes-mechanically-from-repository-history-in-order-to-objectively-know-the-productivity-and-soundness-of-the-development-team-ceece/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/created-a-tool-that-visualizes-mechanically-from-repository-history-in-order-to-objectively-know-the-productivity-and-soundness-of-the-development-team-ceece/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The productivity and soundness of a software development team can be understood as an internal sensation, but it is difficult for an external person to see it. This information asymmetry has caused problems in relationships with people outside the development team.
Also, for EMs, CTOs that bundle multiple development teams and products, and visualizing each situation with objective numbers and graphs, it is important reference information when considering the overall strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Released a web service for handwriting scoring using DeepLearning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/released-a-web-service-for-handwriting-scoring-using-deeplearning-2cf76/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/released-a-web-service-for-handwriting-scoring-using-deeplearning-2cf76/</guid>
      <description>As a hobby, I personally developed a web service that AI automatically marks the readability of characters when I write them in a browser, and released it about 2 weeks ago: relaxed:  []((https://letters.choo.works/) Letters-AI handwriting scoring app
The core technology is front-end implementation with DeepLearning image recognition and Preact. In this article, we will describe Service outline, technical details, and impressions regarding the developed application.
Service overview Function introduction Since it has a small number of pages and is lightweight, it is probably faster to see the application regarding the function, but I will explain the function including an overview of the technology used with screenshots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it still exhausted by MVC? ~ SPA development started with Django x React ~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</guid>
      <description>Recently, sites using JS framework are increasing.  In particular, JS frameworks such as React and Vue are often used for application development called SPA and bring many benefits not only to users of the site but also to developers.
Assumed readers  Web development experience People who have developed web applications using API Someone who knows JavaScript a lot and Python a little I know a little about Django People who have developed using MVC or MTV  There is an article written in more detail in another article, so please see here if you feel that this article is difficult or if you want to learn more deeply.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>