<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> IoT on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/iot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  IoT on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/iot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] RaspberryPi sensor sample file distribution URL summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/c0e658ec5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/c0e658ec5/</guid>
      <description>#RaspberryPi sensor sample file distribution URL summary  The company that sells the sensors collectively records the sample files on a CD and sells them as a set, but I summarized the companies that publish the files on the Web.
##OSOYOO OSOYOO Raspberry Pi Learn electronic work kit Beginners&amp;rsquo; practice parts set Rasppie 11 actual example Circuit wiring diagram and sample sketch programming Raspberry Pi super introduction starter learning kit LED control switch I2C LCD temperature/humidity sensor micro servo human sensor A/D converter Buzzer Atmospheric pressure sensor Relay module control Infrared remote control etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The image is binarized. Furthermore, the shortest distance between two regions can be calculated (ver1.0).</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/05a6506da/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/05a6506da/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  *A revised version has been created. https://qiita.com/Fumio-eisan/items/10c54af7a925b403f59f
I am working in the manufacturing industry, but I feel the flow of actively introducing IoT and AI technologies. I do not belong to the system department that mainly handles these technologies. However, I want to feel the flow myself! I think. There is a Raspberry Pi as a tool that is relatively easy to handle, so I am tentatively planning what can be done with this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I couldn&#39;t escape from the futon, so I made a fully automatic futon peeler.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/bef574953/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/bef574953/</guid>
      <description># Overview  It is known that escaping from the futon by itself on a cold winter morning is accompanied by a great deal of mental distress, and a decline in activity in the morning in the winter brings a great loss to the Japanese economy. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is the case, but for the time being, if I leave home early in the morning, my graduation will be jeopardized, so I decided to take measures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The story that the guards were confined when the laboratory became IoT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b623cb17a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b623cb17a/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 20th day of Retty Advent Calendar 2019.  Yesterday, Mr. Hirano&amp;rsquo;s “Retty Data Analysis Team-Review of the 2nd year after launch ~Data platform/data democratization/statistical model~”.
Nice to meet you. My name is Koda and I&amp;rsquo;m currently an intern at Retty as a 20-year-old engineer.
For the time being, I was wondering what to write after registering for participation, but I made my own entry/exit management system (electronic lock) that is used in the laboratory of the university I am attending, so I will talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Report from the site. What I think is necessary to utilize AI/IoT in the manufacturing industry</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f90b1d2c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f90b1d2c4/</guid>
      <description>I will post Qiita for the first time. ‥  I&amp;rsquo;m always indebted to you, but I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for not posting.
Introduction As is said to be the &amp;ldquo;cliff of 2025,&amp;rdquo; digital transformation is an urgent issue for the manufacturing industry. While emerging countries are chasing after quality and cost, I feel the harshness of Japan at the factory. I wonder, &amp;ldquo;Is Japanese quality really good?&amp;rdquo; (Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just my factory!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easy IoT to start with Razpai and MESH</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2d66629a5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2d66629a5/</guid>
      <description>Ubiregi Advent Calendar 2019 On the 4th day, we will introduce easy IoT using Razpai and MESH.  What to make We make a very simple thing: pressing a &amp;ldquo;button&amp;rdquo; on the MESH block will post a fixed message to Slack. As an application, I attach a monitor to Raspberry Pi and use it as an intercom. I think that I would like to see it. While living alone, there is a problem that I do not know if people are visiting while I am away, so if I put a MESH button instead, it seems like I can notify the smartphone that a person came.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A guidebook for doing IoT with MicroPython at the last minute</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ea30fe111/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ea30fe111/</guid>
      <description>This article is the second day of [Python Part 2 Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/python2).Thefirstdaywas@ssh-22&#39;s[Advancedstringreplacementusingre.sub](https://qiita.com/ssh-22/items/a42ca0fe7ead4d280bfc).   Arduino, Raspberry Pi is a rapidly growing ecosystem in the IoT area, but Raspberry Pi can be implemented in Python, but Arduino is much easier to use for a little electronic control. However, there are probably people who want to write in Python, which is familiar to them, rather than the Arduino language (like C/C++). In this article, I would like to write a guide to easily start development using MicroPython, which is embedded Python, in a financial sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easy and easy IoT life using Micropython!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/af55f42f6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/af55f42f6/</guid>
      <description>#This post is  Python Advent Calendar 2019 It will be the third post.
Micropython is nice Aside from the Raspberry Pi The so-called ESP32 system can use Wifi, but like Arduino, it is a substitute that burns the program ROM and executes it, basically the program is like C language using Arduino IDE. I write.
···But
HTTP request is dull www The IoT is the result of linking edge point data to SaaS To be honest, it makes you motivated when HTTP requests are slow&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I installed the IoT platform Rimotte</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/392782870/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/392782870/</guid>
      <description>### What is Limotte  Rimotte is an All-In-One platform for always-on apps such as IoT. It is used by using the “Station” that is installed and used on Windows and a web browser that runs on Android, iOS, Windows, MacOS, Linux, etc. Not limited to IoT, it can be used for applications that are used without being connected to the Internet, and applications such as measurement, monitoring, automation, and AI can be easily realized.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>