<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RPA on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/rpa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in RPA on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/rpa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What automation should I do in RPA, VBA, or programming languages?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-automation-should-i-do-in-rpa-vba-or-programming-languages-d322b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-automation-should-i-do-in-rpa-vba-or-programming-languages-d322b/</guid>
      <description>It is called business automation, but there are many tools for automation. You mean, &amp;quot;You don&#39;t have to use that special tool for that task!?&amp;quot; So, I tried to categorize by business type, environment, user type, etc.  1. Automation of core operations (accounting, HR, CRM, ERP, etc.) RPA recommendation level: ☆☆☆☆☆
Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to introduce packaged software for human resources, salary, management accounting, supply chain, cost accounting, CRM, etc. for basic business as a company independent of the industry and automation of business unique to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Run Blue Prism process using Python (SOAP)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/run-blue-prism-process-using-python-soap-fae08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/run-blue-prism-process-using-python-soap-fae08/</guid>
      <description>Introduction   With Blue Prism, a process (robot) can be exposed as a WebService and can be executed externally. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll write a client in Python and call a Blue Prism process.
There are two prerequisites for running the process exposed as a WebService. Another article and set the preconditions.
  A. Blue Prism server service is running B. public There is a runtime resource started by the switch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What I have learned in the past year as an old man (age mismatch)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-i-have-learned-in-the-past-year-as-an-old-man-age-mismatch-e7d26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-i-have-learned-in-the-past-year-as-an-old-man-age-mismatch-e7d26/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Write what you are learning every day as an elderly person. I am inspired by how younger generations are eager to learn technology. Since the front and Web systems are too various to be able to keep up with learning, I specialize in the fields of my interest.
By the way, there is no organization theory or anything like that.
Self-introduction  Soon to be 50 years old (looks like &amp;ldquo;is that right?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>