<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Tkinter on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/tkinter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Tkinter on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/tkinter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Important units seen from Python lecture materials at Kyoto University</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/important-units-seen-from-python-lecture-materials-at-kyoto-university-dc3dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/important-units-seen-from-python-lecture-materials-at-kyoto-university-dc3dc/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  February 13 Kyoto University has released Python lecture materials free of charge. Relation: Lecture Material Repository Introduction article-Qiita Introduction article-CodeZine
The content is quite fulfilling. (Not perfect&amp;hellip;) It seems that learning at home will be the key for the future, partly because of COVID-19, so let&amp;rsquo;s make effective use of it. I myself use the basics of Python obscurely, so I would like to take this opportunity to fully understand it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an image processing viewer with PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-an-image-processing-viewer-with-pysimple-gui-30f54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-an-image-processing-viewer-with-pysimple-gui-30f54/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you can do with this article:   Viewer for selecting and displaying images Pass parameters to perform image processing Display the processed image  For a basic explanation of PySimPleGUI, please refer to If you use Tkinter, try using PySimpleGUI
Verification environment  windows10 macOS (catalina) Python3.7 Library -tkinter -PySimpleGUI -Pillow  Trigger It was interesting to see the article of Automatically generate ASCII art that created the above image and actually moved it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Othello game development made with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/othello-game-development-made-with-python-8794c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/othello-game-development-made-with-python-8794c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I developed an Othello game using Python. Anyone can easily play
github page https://github.com/chihina/othello-game-python
Development environment python3.7.1 For other, please check requirement.txt on the following github page. https://github.com/chihina/othello-game-python
Until the game starts First, execute git clone with the following command.
git clone https://github.com/chihina/othello-game-python.git Next, install the libraries in a batch with the following command.
pip -r install requirement.txt This concludes the environment construction. It&amp;rsquo;s easy. The following command will start the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embed matplotlib graph in Tkinter</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/embed-matplotlib-graph-in-tkinter-45953/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/embed-matplotlib-graph-in-tkinter-45953/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  Recently, there were the following hurdles regarding programming.
(1) I want to create a GUI program in Python. → You can use Tkinter (2) I want to display some calculation results on a graph. → You can use matplotlib (3) I want to embed the graph written in matplotlib in (2) into Tkinter in (1). → NG
I tried to get over it by tampering with the example code, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw a graph with PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</guid>
      <description># What you can do by reading this article  With PySimple GUI, you can:
 You can draw bar graphs, line graphs, etc. Graph that refreshes display periodically  For the basic operation of PySimpleGUI, please refer to If you use Tkinter, try using PySimpleGUI.
Overview I think there are many people who analyze data as a way to use Python. Also, some people may want to visualize the results of analysis as line graphs or bar graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUI creation in python using tkinter part 1</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/gui-creation-in-python-using-tkinter-part-1-1c155/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/gui-creation-in-python-using-tkinter-part-1-1c155/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  When executing a tool made with python, it is okay to call it from the command line if it is made by myself, but for tools used by people who are not related to development, it is better to be able to operate from the screen It is convenient. I investigated various ways to make an application with python and summarized the contents made. It&amp;rsquo;s still not very well made, so I plan to gradually adjust it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Async/await with Kivy and tkinter</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/async-await-with-kivy-and-tkinter-973cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/async-await-with-kivy-and-tkinter-973cb/</guid>
      <description>2018 was a shock to me. I used to play around with [Kivy][kivy] of GUI Framekwork, but I found that using a generator can make ugly code full of callback functions surprisingly readable. Then, while trying various things, I became able to understand async/await asynchronous processing, which was a magic that was unfamiliar to me until then, and I was able to create a little asynchronous processing library. In this article   The process until I realized the wonderfulness of the generator and the native coroutine born from it How to implement async/await with Kivy and tkinter using it  I want to write it down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pyenv does not work with tcl-tk installed by homebrew.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pyenv-does-not-work-with-tcl-tk-installed-by-homebrew.-5a8e2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pyenv-does-not-work-with-tcl-tk-installed-by-homebrew.-5a8e2/</guid>
      <description># Problems encountered  When I tried to use tkinter from python installed using pyenv on Mac, I got the following error:
Traceback (most recent call last): File &amp;quot;./annotate.py&amp;quot;, line 3, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; import tkinter File &amp;quot;/Users/???/.pyenv/versions/3.7.4/lib/python3.7/tkinter/__init__.py&amp;quot;, line 36, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; import _tkinter # If this fails your Python may not be configured for Tk ModuleNotFoundError: No module named&#39;_tkinter&#39;  The environment is
 MacOS Catalina 10.15.1 pyenv 1.2.15  #How to find (and didn&amp;rsquo;t solve) Gugu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Support System with Python3</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/presentation-support-system-with-python3-d3f44/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/presentation-support-system-with-python3-d3f44/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is @seigo2016 of 1st year N high school programming class. It will be N high ad curry day 8. I was worried about what to write because it was a neat article, but I talked a lot about the current main project &amp;ldquo;Itokake Mandala Color Simulator&amp;rdquo; at U22 etc. So, this time I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the recent short-term project &amp;ldquo;PSS ~ Presentation Support System~&amp;rdquo;.
Purpose of # PSS ~Presentation Support System~ I think that you often give presentations using PowerPoint, Google Slide, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a Christmas tree lighting game with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-christmas-tree-lighting-game-with-python-3ee27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-christmas-tree-lighting-game-with-python-3ee27/</guid>
      <description># Made  *The video is double speed. I made a game in Python that connects electric paths and lights a Christmas tree light bulb. GUI uses Tkinter. The original story is a game that appeared on NORAD&amp;rsquo;s Santa tracking website a few years ago. Remembering that I loved it all the time, I decided to make it with Python, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying and can use nowadays.
#Environment
Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use tkinter in pyenv python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-tkinter-in-pyenv-python-a5f83/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-tkinter-in-pyenv-python-a5f83/</guid>
      <description>## Issue  The following error occurs when you do python -m tkinter or import tkinter with python installed by pyenv. When I read the article on the net, it said that it was cured by brew install tcl-tk, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work. However, apparently it seems that the recently released pyenv v1.2.14 fixes the compatibility with tcl-tk, and GitHub issue I also wrote a solution, so I will share it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>