<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> language processing 100 knocks on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/language-processing-100-knocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  language processing 100 knocks on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/language-processing-100-knocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easily learn 100 language processing knocks 2020 with Google Colaboratory</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/easily-learn-100-language-processing-knocks-2020-with-google-colaboratory-e4694/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/easily-learn-100-language-processing-knocks-2020-with-google-colaboratory-e4694/</guid>
      <description># 100 language processing What is knock 2020  100 language processing knock 2020
It is a collection of problems on the above site. I quote from the site.
 100 Language Processing Knock is a collection of problems aimed at learning programming, data analysis, and research skills in a fun way while tackling practical and exciting challenges.
 I am very grateful to be able to publish such wonderful things for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Language processing 100 knock 2020 first chapter</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/language-processing-100-knock-2020-first-chapter-15e68/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/language-processing-100-knock-2020-first-chapter-15e68/</guid>
      <description>[Language processing 100 knocks 2020 version](https://nlp100.github.io/ja/) has been published, so I will solve it at this opportunity.  It&amp;rsquo;s a copy of my own jupyter notebook in markdown, so the explanation is less. I hope that it will be a little reference, and I also posted to Qiita what I plan to put together on a blog and GitHub. I don&amp;rsquo;t like the teachers who can provide such wonderful teaching materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 100 language processing knocks 2020 version released! What has changed</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/100-language-processing-knocks-2020-version-released-what-has-changed-3c179/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/100-language-processing-knocks-2020-version-released-what-has-changed-3c179/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  100 knocks of language processing that have been popular for a long time as a collection of problems that you can enjoy learning the basics of natural language processing, its 2020 version was released on 4/6 ! This is the first revision in five years. 2015 version but those who are interested, those who feel sorry that the 15th edition Qiita article is no longer useful, 15th edition For the person who was doing halfway, but the 20-year edition is coming out and it seems to be heartbreaking, I will summarize what has changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction to Python with 100 language processing knocks</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-python-with-100-language-processing-knocks-02d82/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-python-with-100-language-processing-knocks-02d82/</guid>
      <description>This article is for people who want to get started with natural language processing in Python, with little knowledge of C but little of Python. We are aiming for the shortest route that can solve Chapter 1 of [Language Processing 100 Knock 2015](http://www.cl.ecei.tohoku.ac.jp/nlp100/) which is famous as an introduction to natural language processing. ..  (4/8 postscript, Chapter 1 is the same for 2020 version)
This Qiita already has a lot of articles about 100 knocks, but I thought that it might be difficult for beginners to learn Python, so I wrote this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Answers and impressions of 100 language processing knocks-Part 1</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/answers-and-impressions-of-100-language-processing-knocks-part-1-234e7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/answers-and-impressions-of-100-language-processing-knocks-part-1-234e7/</guid>
      <description>advent calendar The first day, but write something easy to write without any special feeling  this is I have written 100 knocks of language processing,soIwillwriteeachanswerandimpression(currently11/30PM20:30Sothepartthatcanbewrittenisthefirstpart)
Assumptions  Environment -Link of Dockerfile(includingunrelatedones) Ability -I have touched mecab and gensim without knowing anything How to solve -For the time being, I solved it myself, and I checked the question every 10 questions by annoying -There is also a part to put two answers Excuse -Correction of wrong answer noticed during compilation is not in time Thanks -It is very appreciated as a self-taught person who goes through the darkness to release these teaching materials  Reflection I was re-reading the code myself to draw this article, so it was a pseudo code review</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 100 amateur language processing knocks: Summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/100-amateur-language-processing-knocks-summary-fb50b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/100-amateur-language-processing-knocks-summary-fb50b/</guid>
      <description>It is a summary of the challenge record of [100 language processing knock 2015](http://www.cl.ecei.tohoku.ac.jp/nlp100/).  :warning:** This is not a challenge record of 100 processing of language knock 2020.Theold2015version is the target. Please note: bangbang:**
Challenge environment Ubuntu 16.04 LTS + Python 3.5.2 :: Anaconda 4.1.1 (64-bit). (Only Problem 00andProblem01arePython2.7.)
#Chapter 1: Preparatory exercise
 Reviewing somewhat advanced programming language topics while working on materials that deal with text and strings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>