<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Optimization on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/optimization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Optimization on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/optimization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If Tokyo citizens become severely ill with the new coronavirus, they may be taken to a hospital in Kagoshima prefecture.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-tokyo-citizens-become-severely-ill-with-the-new-coronavirus-they-may-be-taken-to-a-hospital-in-kagoshima-prefecture.-b6391/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-tokyo-citizens-become-severely-ill-with-the-new-coronavirus-they-may-be-taken-to-a-hospital-in-kagoshima-prefecture.-b6391/</guid>
      <description>#table of contents  Introduction Current status of medical collapse risk Whether or not to secure beds for severely ill persons Severely ill transport model Delivery destination of severely ill Conclusion
#Introduction
 Background Infectious disease designated medical institutions are tight, and it is extremely difficult to secure sufficient beds to accommodate severely ill persons. In various places, measures have been taken to treat patients with mild illness at hotels, homes, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of research proposal that won first place at KDDCUP 2019 and adoption</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-research-proposal-that-won-first-place-at-kddcup-2019-and-adoption-09557/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-research-proposal-that-won-first-place-at-kddcup-2019-and-adoption-09557/</guid>
      <description>It is Docomo&#39;s Ochiai. In this article, we will introduce the [^1] initiative that won the 1st division of [KDD Cup](https://www.kdd.org/kdd2019/kdd-cup), a competition for data analysis held at KDD2019. I will.  KDD Cup 2019 Overview The outline of KDD was introduced in previous article, so focus on KDD Cup here. I will explain. The KDD Cup is a data science competition attached to the KDD and has a tradition of first being 1997 and more than 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>