<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> optimization on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/optimization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  optimization on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/optimization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If Tokyo citizens become severely ill with the new coronavirus, they may be taken to a hospital in Kagoshima prefecture.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-tokyo-citizens-become-severely-ill-with-the-new-coronavirus-they-may-be-taken-to-a-hospital-in-kagoshima-prefecture.-b6391/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-tokyo-citizens-become-severely-ill-with-the-new-coronavirus-they-may-be-taken-to-a-hospital-in-kagoshima-prefecture.-b6391/</guid>
      <description>#table of contents  Introduction Current status of medical collapse risk Whether or not to secure beds for severely ill persons Severely ill transport model Delivery destination of severely ill Conclusion
#Introduction
 Background Infectious disease designated medical institutions are tight, and it is extremely difficult to secure sufficient beds to accommodate severely ill persons. In various places, measures have been taken to treat patients with mild illness at hotels, homes, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction of research proposal that won first place at KDDCUP 2019 and adoption</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-research-proposal-that-won-first-place-at-kddcup-2019-and-adoption-09557/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-research-proposal-that-won-first-place-at-kddcup-2019-and-adoption-09557/</guid>
      <description>It is Docomo&#39;s Ochiai. In this article, we will introduce the [^1] initiative that won the 1st division of [KDD Cup](https://www.kdd.org/kdd2019/kdd-cup), a competition for data analysis held at KDD2019. I will.  KDD Cup 2019 Overview The outline of KDD was introduced in previous article, so focus on KDD Cup here. I will explain. The KDD Cup is a data science competition attached to the KDD and has a tradition of first being 1997 and more than 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Basics of trajectory generation (Scipy&#39;s optimize method for nonlinear optimal control problems)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/basics-of-trajectory-generation-scipys-optimize-method-for-nonlinear-optimal-control-problems-fc7ae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/basics-of-trajectory-generation-scipys-optimize-method-for-nonlinear-optimal-control-problems-fc7ae/</guid>
      <description>Description of trajectory generation, trajectory planning, and how to obtain modern numerical solutions for optimal control problems.  [Additional March 2017] I have released it as a python library as a development system of the contents written here. Please note that the theory implemented below is the Legendre-Gauss-Lobatto pseudospectral method, and the content on the current page is different from the Legendre-Gauss pseudospectral method. https://github.com/istellartech/OpenGoddard https://istellartech.github.io/OpenGoddard/
How to use OpenGoddard 1 How to use OpenGoddard 2 How to use OpenGoddard 3 How to use OpenGoddard 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] A note when accelerating genetic algorithms using multiprocessing</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-a-note-when-accelerating-genetic-algorithms-using-multiprocessing-fa13a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-a-note-when-accelerating-genetic-algorithms-using-multiprocessing-fa13a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  If you google Google and parallel processing, you will see many articles about the module called multiprocessing, so I tried it in the article I wrote before.
[Python] Trying optimization of FX systre parameter with genetic algorithm
The genetic algorithm evaluates many individuals and performs genetic processing such as selection and crossover according to their fitness, but since the evaluation of each individual is completely independent, it is suitable for parallel processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Think menu with combination optimization</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/think-menu-with-combination-optimization-f8be1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/think-menu-with-combination-optimization-f8be1/</guid>
      <description># &amp;lt;i class=&#39;fa fa-graduation-cap&#39; /&amp;gt; Problem  My doctor told me to limit my calorie intake for a week. The minimum required amount of nutrients A and B was also specified. How can I eat what I like as much as possible?
Formulation It is an assignment problem in Combination Optimization Problem. Let&amp;rsquo;s assume that food candidates are given, and let 0-1 variable $x$ represent which one to choose.
 Variable$x_i \in \{0, 1\}$$i$ Whether to select the $th dishObjective function$\sum_i{Preferences_i x_i}$$\rightarrow$ Max Constraints$\sum_i{x_i} = 7 $Choose 7 days $\sum_i{calories_ix_i} \le 90 $calorie restriction $\sum_i{Nutrient A_i x_i} \ge 95 $Minimum acquisition amount $\sum_i{Nutrient B_i x_i} \ge 95 $Minimum acquisition amount  Try to solve with python The optimization library is pulp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>