<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> visualization on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/visualization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  visualization on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/visualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Calendar-type heat map (with holiday display)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-calendar-type-heat-map-with-holiday-display-06a80/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-calendar-type-heat-map-with-holiday-display-06a80/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article  Create a heat map in calendar format with holidays as shown below.
By the way, in the data, the post date of @yaotti&amp;rsquo;s post acquired using Qiita API is used as 1 post = 1 event.
Similar visualization method  Contributions Calendar Contribution Graph Grass grass  Although it is called with various names, the following figure on GitHub is also simple and good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A summary of all Python plots used by active graduate students in their research [Basic]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-python-plots-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-basic-52315/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-summary-of-all-python-plots-used-by-active-graduate-students-in-their-research-basic-52315/</guid>
      <description>Application section [here](https://qiita.com/coffiego/items/dfabde5f8588723b32d6)  https://qiita.com/coffiego/items/dfabde5f8588723b32d6
#Introduction I am currently a graduate student with a 2nd year master&amp;rsquo;s degree. I am studying the Martian atmosphere using numerical simulation. Since I mainly analyzed the results obtained by numerical simulation using Python, I tried to summarize all the functions used in the process. Please note that this is not an exhaustive list. .. .. However, since I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling to use the documentation, I&amp;rsquo;ve summarized it in the hope that if anyone using Python&amp;rsquo;s visualization tools can help with that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The result of making and sharing an Italian honeymoon map album in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-result-of-making-and-sharing-an-italian-honeymoon-map-album-in-python-4e136/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-result-of-making-and-sharing-an-italian-honeymoon-map-album-in-python-4e136/</guid>
      <description>I went on a honeymoon to Italy a while ago. I took about 1,000 photos when I noticed it on a tour of Milan, Venice, Florence, Pisa, Rome and Pompeii in one week.  There was some free time, so I took a walk around 10,000 steps every day, so I wanted to make a record with the route included, so I made a map album&amp;hellip;!
Visualization The whole picture looks something like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the amount of pollen dispersal, the vegetation of Sugi and the effect of wind from open data (Visualization)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/analyzing-the-amount-of-pollen-dispersal-the-vegetation-of-sugi-and-the-effect-of-wind-from-open-data-visualization-e9fa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/analyzing-the-amount-of-pollen-dispersal-the-vegetation-of-sugi-and-the-effect-of-wind-from-open-data-visualization-e9fa0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is a sequel to the previous &amp;ldquo;Visualizing the amount of pollen dispersal and the vegetation of Sugi and the effect of wind from open data (pretreatment)&amp;rdquo;. The previous article is from the link below. https://qiita.com/TakuTaku36/items/40cb590b0ae0c6340f8c This time, we will visualize and analyze winds that may be affecting pollen dispersal amounts, sugi vegetation, and prevalence of pollinosis by prefecture at each observation point in Japan.
#Wind visualization There is a little time left from the previous preprocessing of the data before the compilation of this visualization, and during that time it has been slightly improved so that it can be handled easily by merging the data, so it is not exactly the same, but it is not bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try using PHATE, a dimension reduction and visualization method for biological data</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-using-phate-a-dimension-reduction-and-visualization-method-for-biological-data-b4b95/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-using-phate-a-dimension-reduction-and-visualization-method-for-biological-data-b4b95/</guid>
      <description># Try using PHATE, a dimension reduction and visualization method for biological data  PHATE (Moon, KR, van Dijk, D., Wang, Z. et al. Nature Biotechnology 37, 1482–1492 (2019)) Try to use. There are a lot of methods of dimension reduction used in biology papers, but each method has advantages and disadvantages. The following methods are often used as typical ones.
 PCA: principal component analysis. Take out the axis of maximum dispersion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing pollen dispersal amount, vegetation of Sugi and influence of wind from open data (pretreatment)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/analyzing-pollen-dispersal-amount-vegetation-of-sugi-and-influence-of-wind-from-open-data-pretreatment-40cb5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/analyzing-pollen-dispersal-amount-vegetation-of-sugi-and-influence-of-wind-from-open-data-pretreatment-40cb5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  TechTrain&amp;rsquo;s Advent Calendar (https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/techtrain) I&amp;rsquo;m in charge of the 11th day, and I&amp;rsquo;m a first-year college student learning Python for two and a half months. I will summarize what I analyzed lightly.
Content Looking at the hay fever prevalence data in each prefecture, it was found that the hay fever prevalence was high in a wide area in the Kanto region, including Tokyo, where there is no image of sugi growing so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implement Data Visualization Design #2 with matplotlib</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implement-data-visualization-design-#2-with-matplotlib-ee27a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implement-data-visualization-design-#2-with-matplotlib-ee27a/</guid>
      <description># What is the design of data visualization?  Go Ando of THE GUILD, which is famous for its services that focus on UX and UI, has published a note on the points of data visualization.
https://note.mu/goando/n/n4a2735c3d69d
#1?  See below for #1  https://qiita.com/skotaro/items/cdb0732ad1ad2a4b6236
Notes  Regarding fonts, it works on mac, but probably not on other OS, so specify a different font.  plt.rcParams[&amp;#39;font.family&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Hiragino Sans&amp;#39; Is the part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to confirm missing values (Kaggle:House Prices)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-confirm-missing-values-kagglehouse-prices-0301e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-confirm-missing-values-kagglehouse-prices-0301e/</guid>
      <description>#at first  One of the important things in analyzing data is checking the data content. This time, we will introduce a method for confirming missing values that can be performed by non-engineers.
#Load dataset Import pandas and load the dataset. This time we will use the data from train.csv from House Prices: Advanced Regression Techniques from kaggle.
House Prices: Advanced Regression Techniques https://www.kaggle.com/c/house-prices-advanced-regression-techniques
import pandas as pd data = pd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I created a stacked bar graph with matplotlib of Python and tried adding a data label</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-created-a-stacked-bar-graph-with-matplotlib-of-python-and-tried-adding-a-data-label-6f9c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-created-a-stacked-bar-graph-with-matplotlib-of-python-and-tried-adding-a-data-label-6f9c1/</guid>
      <description># draw a stacked bar graph with matplotlib  Motivation When I draw a stacked bar chart in Python, I wish I could display the data label like Excel, and when I looked it up, there was no article that could display the data label, and there was no code to copy and paste. So, I wrote a code that I can copy and paste when I want to attach a data label to a stacked bar graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualize quickly with Pandas</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/visualize-quickly-with-pandas-16c20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/visualize-quickly-with-pandas-16c20/</guid>
      <description>There are several libraries that visualize data in Python, but Pandas alone is quite good.  Visualization using Pandas can be completed in the method chain, which can prevent random scattering of temporary variables. In this article, I will introduce visualization recipes, focusing on the ones I often use in practice.
#Preparation
Environment  Python 3.6.8 jupyter==1.0.0 pandas==0.25.3  data I borrow the following two data this time.
 Titanic: Machine Learning from Disaster | Kaggle Crimes in Boston | Kaggle  Create a DataFrame called titanic and crime respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>