<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Keras on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/keras/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Keras on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/keras/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Transform a real ferocious crocodile image into a 100 crocodile-smiling neural style with Keras</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5fed6bf9d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5fed6bf9d/</guid>
      <description>#What is neural style conversion?  Neural style conversion is one of the machine learning techniques that transforms a target image into the style (texture) of another image to generate a new image. It&amp;rsquo;s a technology used in apps that change Van Gogh&amp;rsquo;s image of a city or people. Now, let&amp;rsquo;s try using this technology to see if this time we can transform a real, ferocious crocodile image that seems to eat humans into a gentle crocodile crocodile by transforming its style into a crocodile style that will die 100 days later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is the network since VGG really improving? The story</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/16022f2db/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/16022f2db/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, AI competitions don&amp;rsquo;t produce useful models just overtraining the dataset &amp;amp; outperforming the game? The purpose of this study is to investigate the story with the wide-angle fundus dataset 1. Also, as an introduction, we will explain how to fine-turn from the learned weights of ImageNet2 using the network implemented in tf.keras.
All code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [TensorFlow 2.x supported version] TensorFlow (Keras) using TFRecord &amp; DataSet to learn a large amount of data</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/11140a570/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/11140a570/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is an updated version of the previous article. How to train a large amount of data using TFRecord &amp;amp; DataSet with TensorFlow &amp;amp; Keras-Qiita
One thing I want to do is &amp;ldquo;I want an efficient way to learn huge data that does not fit in memory.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a method that allows CPU data reading and GPU calculation to be processed in parallel. Using the DataSet API, you can efficiently learn from the data saved in a specific format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Image classification with wide-angle fundus image dataset</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8c011c219/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8c011c219/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, as an introduction, we aim to use TensorFlow 2.0 and perform image classification with Deep Learning for the time being. The image dataset is not so interesting as MNIST, so we will use the wide-angle fundus image dataset 1 published by Tsukazaki Hospital. The network is a simple 10-layer CNN.
All Code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Detect image distortion by deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/54585fccb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/54585fccb/</guid>
      <description>There is a lot of research being done on image anomaly detection using deep learning.  As an approach for detecting abnormal products using only normal data for industrial products, For now, @daisukelab&amp;rsquo;s Learning with self-teaching is the most powerful. In this research, As a problem, the accuracy of some images was sluggish, and we tried to make an error class data by trial and error ** There was a comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Try the latest method of deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d2a3a46c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d2a3a46c3/</guid>
      <description>Previously, using **deep distance learning** [&amp;quot;image anomaly detection&amp;quot;](https://qiita.com/shinmura0/items/06d81c72601c7578c6d3#%E3%83%99%E3%83%B3%E3%83%81%E3%83%9E%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AF).  After that, The latest method of deep distance learning &amp;ldquo;AdaCos&amp;rdquo; appeared.
In this article, I would like to apply AdaCos to &amp;ldquo;anomaly detection&amp;rdquo; and do a simple benchmark. The entire code is here
*This is the presentation material of Python Data Analysis Study Group #15.
#From the conclusion By applying AdaCos to anomaly detection, we found the following:
 Same accuracy as ArcFace Thank you for not tuning parameters  #AdaCos AdaCos is said to be the latest method of deep distance learning, but as of January 2020, more than half a year has passed since the paper was published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Continue making stock price forecasting AI for 10 hours a day 1st month</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8e5cb7130/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8e5cb7130/</guid>
      <description>I resumed learning Python last December 3rd. I was wondering if I could make something for practice, but I came up with the idea of creating an AI for stock price forecasting, so I decided to give it a try. As a result, we have AI that can predict (and possibly even predict) that stock prices will rise or fall by more than 1% with 64% accuracy. Project 1 is the main subject because of the process of getting into the main subject of Project 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Noise2Noise Explanation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/939b80bb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/939b80bb2/</guid>
      <description># Noise2Noise explanation (method to learn denoising network only with images with noise)  I would like to explain and summarize a paper on noise removal Noise2Noise: Learning Image Restoration without Clean Data. Since it is a 2018 paper and it has a big impact, I feel that it is old to write an introduction article, but there was an article on implementation in Qiita, but there was no article explaining the contents, so memorandum I will leave it as.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] First image classifier</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a89025933/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a89025933/</guid>
      <description>Hello. In my work, I&#39;m far from engineering and I can&#39;t write much by doing what I&#39;ve done,  I have a little time, so I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize what I learned a little. Advent calendar I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid! You can write an article that you just did a tutorial! That means one&amp;hellip;
Assumed readers I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a lot about machine learning, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched on implementation so much so I will touch on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Paper and Implementation] When asked, Is this data set difficult?...</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/74917f13c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/74917f13c/</guid>
      <description>Learning a convolutional neural network (CNN) takes time.  Especially, if you try to get accuracy without transfer learning, it takes about 5 days** There are times. The paper introduced in this paper quantitatively describes the difficulty of datasets. By evaluating, classification accuracy can be estimated quickly without learning CNN. Is that.
*The entire code was placed on here. *The figures in this paper are basically taken from the paper (Spectral Metric for Dataset Complexity Assessment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Score-CAM implementation with keras. Comparison with Grad-CAM</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/95c518254/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/95c518254/</guid>
      <description># Overview   Implemented the method &amp;ldquo;Score-CAM&amp;rdquo; of Paper posted on arxiv on October 3, 2019 with keras. Comparison with Grad-CAM, Grad-CAM++. Implemented the independently accelerated Faster Score-CAM. Applied to the model trained on DAGM dataset. The code can be found on github.  What is # Score-CAM?
 One of the visualization methods of the basis of judgment of CNN -There is a wonderful summary on here for understanding the judgment basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] From environment construction to deep learning tutorial</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ff8dc42d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ff8dc42d1/</guid>
      <description>Deep learning has become a hot topic these days,  &amp;ldquo;I want to study, but I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what I can do&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
For such people, we will introduce the methods from Mac environment construction to deep learning execution.
python environment construction Machine learning and deep learning are python. For the time being, prepare the environment construction of python. First, let&amp;rsquo;s install python. Let&amp;rsquo;s open the terminal and run it in order.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>