<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> sympy on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/sympy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  sympy on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/sympy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Control Engineering] Transfer function graphing in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5e006ebbf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5e006ebbf/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  ・This page was created because I received a comment from the qiita page (https://qiita.com/sato235/items/f991411074c578d1640c) that I wrote last time that it would be interesting to output a waveform graph for consideration.
#2.Reference #2.1. Books [1] Hiroki Minami, Ohmsha, &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Control Engineering with Python&amp;rdquo;
#2.2. Web page a) Author support page for [1], https://y373.sakura.ne.jp/minami/pyctrl b) Previous self page, https://qiita.com/sato235/items/f991411074c578d1640c c) Graphing function of matlab function of control module, http://matsulib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Pauli matrices and dual quaternions in Clifford algebra</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fafe77f9a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fafe77f9a/</guid>
      <description>The length with the direction can be expressed by a vector. Clifford algebra makes it possible to handle areas and volumes by combining vectors. We introduce a Pauli matrix as a three-dimensional Clifford algebra representation matrix and confirm that it is isomorphic to a biquaternion. The calculation by SymPy is attached.  This is a series article.
 Complex vector considered with real vector Bi-complex numbers considered by expression matrix Quaternion considered by expression matrix Pauli matrices and dual quaternions considered in Clifford algebra ← this article  This article has related articles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>