<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> TensorFlow on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/tensorflow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  TensorFlow on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/tensorflow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simple method to obtain MNIST correct rate of 97% or more by unsupervised learning (without transfer learning)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simple-method-to-obtain-mnist-correct-rate-of-97-or-more-by-unsupervised-learning-without-transfer-learning-0aa24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simple-method-to-obtain-mnist-correct-rate-of-97-or-more-by-unsupervised-learning-without-transfer-learning-0aa24/</guid>
      <description>First article posted as job hunting news.  I tried to read and implement a paper on IIC (Invariant Information Clustering), which is said to be highly accurate and has unsupervised learning. IIC is a method of clustering by maximizing mutual information. IIC paper here
 Invariant Information Clustering for Unsupervised Image Classification and Segmentation Xu Ji, João F. Henriques, Andrea Vedaldi
 The framework used is TensorFlow 2.0. The target data is familiar MNIST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Japanese preprocessing for machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/japanese-preprocessing-for-machine-learning-0daf9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/japanese-preprocessing-for-machine-learning-0daf9/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  A memorandum when creating a simple neural network with text as training data in order to understand the mechanism of a chatbot using machine learning.
#Purpose Apply the rule-based chatbot created in English text to Japanese text to operate. Preprocess the Japanese text and make sure it can be passed through the neural network. As training data, Web scraping of support pages related to Niantic&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Pokemon GO&amp;rdquo; was used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] For those who want to start machine learning with TensorFlow2</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am currently a M2 student majoring in CS. I usually write machine learning code in PyTorch. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to write for the time being. PyTorch is said to be &amp;ldquo;Define by Run&amp;rdquo;**, and what is good at the same time when the calculation graph and data are sent is that it is easy to debug because you can check the calculation results on the way. As a PyTorch believer, I need to write code in TensorFlow this time, so I will keep a memo so that I don&amp;rsquo;t forget the know-how at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried using magenta/TensorFlow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-magenta-tensorflow-c754d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-magenta-tensorflow-c754d/</guid>
      <description>Automatic generation of melody using # magenta/TensorFlow  background Since I want to be able to manipulate MIDI data using Python this time, I came to a tool called Magenta while browsing various sites.
 What is #Magenta Recently, a new project called Magenta from Google was opened on Github. https://github.com/tensorflow/magenta
  Magenta is a project that uses neural networks to generate art and music.
  It aims to evolve machine learning creativity and to be a community of artists and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is the network since VGG really improving? The story</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-the-network-since-vgg-really-improving-the-story-16022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-the-network-since-vgg-really-improving-the-story-16022/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, AI competitions don&amp;rsquo;t produce useful models just overtraining the dataset &amp;amp; outperforming the game? The purpose of this study is to investigate the story with the wide-angle fundus dataset 1. Also, as an introduction, we will explain how to fine-turn from the learned weights of ImageNet2 using the network implemented in tf.keras.
All code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [TensorFlow 2.x supported version] TensorFlow (Keras) using TFRecord &amp; DataSet to learn a large amount of data</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-2.x-supported-version-tensorflow-keras-using-tfrecord-dataset-to-learn-a-large-amount-of-data-11140/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-2.x-supported-version-tensorflow-keras-using-tfrecord-dataset-to-learn-a-large-amount-of-data-11140/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is an updated version of the previous article. How to train a large amount of data using TFRecord &amp;amp; DataSet with TensorFlow &amp;amp; Keras-Qiita
One thing I want to do is &amp;ldquo;I want an efficient way to learn huge data that does not fit in memory.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a method that allows CPU data reading and GPU calculation to be processed in parallel. Using the DataSet API, you can efficiently learn from the data saved in a specific format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Image classification with wide-angle fundus image dataset</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/image-classification-with-wide-angle-fundus-image-dataset-8c011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/image-classification-with-wide-angle-fundus-image-dataset-8c011/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, as an introduction, we aim to use TensorFlow 2.0 and perform image classification with Deep Learning for the time being. The image dataset is not so interesting as MNIST, so we will use the wide-angle fundus image dataset 1 published by Tsukazaki Hospital. The network is a simple 10-layer CNN.
All Code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning with Pascal-VOC dataset of MobileNetV2-SSDLite [Docker version remake]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-with-pascal-voc-dataset-of-mobilenetv2-ssdlite-docker-version-remake-107dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-with-pascal-voc-dataset-of-mobilenetv2-ssdlite-docker-version-remake-107dd/</guid>
      <description>**PINTO_model_zoo** [![GitHub stars](https://img.shields.io/github/stars/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo.svg?style=social&amp;amp;label=Stars)](https://github.com/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo)  &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://github-link-card.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo.png&amp;quot;width=&amp;quot;460px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
1. Introduction I remade the MobileNet V2-SSD Lite training environment construction article that I wrote about a year ago into an ultra-simple specification. If you start work from the stage where the latest Docker for GPU is introduced, I think you can start training in about 15 minutes. I think there are almost no mistakes. After learning, I plan to do Integer Quantization of the trained model (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] (First post) Talk about numerical calculation of influenza and new type pneumonia coronavirus with Tensorflow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/first-post-talk-about-numerical-calculation-of-influenza-and-new-type-pneumonia-coronavirus-with-tensorflow-acd6e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/first-post-talk-about-numerical-calculation-of-influenza-and-new-type-pneumonia-coronavirus-with-tensorflow-acd6e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Summary  Flu Coronavirus  I analyzed about using a mathematical model.
###background This time I tried to numerically calculate the infectious disease model, but please understand that I am not a professional of mathematical models such as infectious disease model. Since I majored in physics at university and graduate school, I have only touched computer science a little. The background of this post is that I&amp;rsquo;m interested in coronavirus, which is a hot topic right now, for quantitative analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The fastest way to try EfficientNet</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-fastest-way-to-try-efficientnet-d90fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-fastest-way-to-try-efficientnet-d90fa/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR   Pre-learned weights by imagenet is published on Tensorflow Hub -EfficientNet B0-All released up to B7 -Use feature vectors for transfer learning available Transfer learning using official TensorFlow Hub and introduction of the fastest way to try EfficientNet -Run Image classification demo in Google Colabratory environment -If you can prepare the environment, you should be able to confirm the operation with the same code as the demo -All you have to do is change the URL that represents the model to be DL in tensorflow-hub library  #Introduction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make an Anpanman painter discrimination machine</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-an-anpanman-painter-discrimination-machine-30a44/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-an-anpanman-painter-discrimination-machine-30a44/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I thought about learning AI and making a simple application with the technology I learned, I tried to make something like the following. The reason why I chose Anpanman was because it was a cartoon character that I could easily write. I wanted to handle GAN as a model, and that it is possible to detect abnormalities by learning only normal images I thought I would make it ANOGAN, but when I looked it up, it was called EfficientGAN in the high-speed version of ANOGAN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] TensorFlow 2.1 is here!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-2.1-is-here-599bf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-2.1-is-here-599bf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is the last article in the Advent Calendar for Tensorflow 2.0. (Large delay) Tensorflow 2.0 has been released! Then Tensorflow 2.1 had already arrived, so Here are the changes and evolved points based on Release Note.
Main topic  GPU package integration Cloud TPU support Ragged Tensor Dataset support Last release in Python 2  GPU package integration From Tensorflow 2.1, the purpose of inserting tensorflow-gpu is gone, Only pip install tensorflow will support tensorflow as GPU!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I have a question. I can&#39;t make protocol buffers for raspberry pi 3 modelB.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-have-a-question.-i-cant-make-protocol-buffers-for-raspberry-pi-3-modelb.-09b78/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-have-a-question.-i-cant-make-protocol-buffers-for-raspberry-pi-3-modelb.-09b78/</guid>
      <description>In order to perform image recognition on the Raspberry Pi, I have installed &amp;quot;protocolbuffers&amp;quot; based on Qiita&#39;s posts. I get an error with &amp;quot;./configure&amp;quot;. After that, I am trying to &amp;quot;make&amp;quot;, but &amp;quot;make: *** target is not specified and makefile cannot be found. Cancel.&amp;quot; is displayed and I cannot proceed.  Could anyone please tell me how to solve it? Posted by: https://qiita.com/kobayuta/items/59c7b84caf8994071357
The following error code: $ cd protobuf-3.7.1 $ .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to visualize Boeing playing violin with pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-boeing-playing-violin-with-pose-estimation-b3b85/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-boeing-playing-violin-with-pose-estimation-b3b85/</guid>
      <description># I tried to detect the feature point of the right wrist joint  #Introduction
This article was posted on the 22nd day of the Fujitsu Systems Web Technology Advent Calendar 2019. All content in the article is the personal opinion, and the content of the writing is the author&amp;rsquo;s own responsibility. It does not matter which organization you belong to. (Goodbye)
Overview I enjoy playing violin as a hobby, but playing the violin is difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Pokemon sword shield] I tried to visualize the basis of deep learning judgment by taking the Osanke classification as an example</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pokemon-sword-shield-i-tried-to-visualize-the-basis-of-deep-learning-judgment-by-taking-the-osanke-classification-as-an-example-2c3ec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pokemon-sword-shield-i-tried-to-visualize-the-basis-of-deep-learning-judgment-by-taking-the-osanke-classification-as-an-example-2c3ec/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Do you guys play Pokemon? I bought it for the first time in 10 years ~~ I got it from Santa. Aiming to get serious, we plan to stay home and select carefully during the year-end and New Year holidays. I was wondering if AdventCalendar could do something with Pokemon news items, so I tried ** a method that shows the basis of judgment of deep learning model ** using Pokemon Okayama family classification as an example ** Saw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Case where hand recognition has reached a practical level</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/case-where-hand-recognition-has-reached-a-practical-level-3e43b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/case-where-hand-recognition-has-reached-a-practical-level-3e43b/</guid>
      <description>In HandTracking of MediaPipe (Google), I will write about the gesture implementation that is being talked about in Issue.  It worked like this Seeing is believing that the picture is worth a thousand words. MediaPipe With the announcement of MediaPipe at CVPR 2019 in June this year, Hand Tracking has been released as one of the applications. MediaPipe doesn&amp;rsquo;t require you to write code called ML pipeline A framework for building ML applications using only visualization tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [TF2.0 Application] High-speed parallelization of general-purpose Data Augmentation with the strong dataset function of TF</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tf2.0-application-high-speed-parallelization-of-general-purpose-data-augmentation-with-the-strong-dataset-function-of-tf-52844/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tf2.0-application-high-speed-parallelization-of-general-purpose-data-augmentation-with-the-strong-dataset-function-of-tf-52844/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the previous article &amp;ldquo;The story that the dataset function that can be used in TensorFlow was strong&amp;quot;&amp;quot;[[TF2.0application]tf.data.&amp;ldquo;DataAugmentationisfasterthanDataAugmentation]&amp;quot;(https://qiita.com/Suguru_Toyohara/items/49c2914b21615b554afa)&amp;quot;, which is a slightly enhanced version of Data Augmentation.
While using tf.data.Dataset for speed enhancement and keras.preprocessing.image system ** We have succeeded in realizing code that can be processed in parallel. ** I will post the actual mechanism and how it came to this point after the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A struggle note after a machine learning amateur who changed jobs to a non-IT company was assigned to an AI project</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-struggle-note-after-a-machine-learning-amateur-who-changed-jobs-to-a-non-it-company-was-assigned-to-an-ai-project-11386/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-struggle-note-after-a-machine-learning-amateur-who-changed-jobs-to-a-non-it-company-was-assigned-to-an-ai-project-11386/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 8th day of How I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ② Advent Calendar 2019. We hope that it will be helpful for those who are new to the market.
Programming experience  School days (robot engineering, fluid mechanics):  :new: C/C++; embedded, computational fluid dynamics, research tools :new: Matlab; A little in modern control theory   Previous job (ADAS):  C/C++; embedded, in-house tool :new: Python; Algorithm prototyping and data organization *Not related to AI   Current position (construction and civil engineering construction management):  C++; built-in Python; Machine Learning/Deep Learning :new: JavaScript (Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Noise2Noise Explanation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/noise2noise-explanation-939b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/noise2noise-explanation-939b8/</guid>
      <description># Noise2Noise explanation (method to learn denoising network only with images with noise)  I would like to explain and summarize a paper on noise removal Noise2Noise: Learning Image Restoration without Clean Data. Since it is a 2018 paper and it has a big impact, I feel that it is old to write an introduction article, but there was an article on implementation in Qiita, but there was no article explaining the contents, so memorandum I will leave it as.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Do Houdini with Python3! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/do-houdini-with-python3-a0194/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/do-houdini-with-python3-a0194/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The second adcare article this year. The first one was &amp;ldquo;[Verify new installation method of SideFX Labs Tool, Package function]&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/takavfx/items/d1698b89df6fb1b86f9c). So this time, let&amp;rsquo;s take a different angle.
It is Python material.
Due to various reasons, the base of my work has already moved to Python3 series, and Python3 series is regularly used. When making a stand-alone tool, it is 3 series. When you have to write Python processing because of M○y○ etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] First image classifier</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/first-image-classifier-a8902/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/first-image-classifier-a8902/</guid>
      <description>Hello. In my work, I&#39;m far from engineering and I can&#39;t write much by doing what I&#39;ve done,  I have a little time, so I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize what I learned a little. Advent calendar I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid! You can write an article that you just did a tutorial! That means one&amp;hellip;
Assumed readers I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a lot about machine learning, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched on implementation so much so I will touch on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] About the shortest path to create an image recognition model by machine learning and implement an Android application</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-the-shortest-path-to-create-an-image-recognition-model-by-machine-learning-and-implement-an-android-application-453a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-the-shortest-path-to-create-an-image-recognition-model-by-machine-learning-and-implement-an-android-application-453a2/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article   How to easily create an image recognition model and share it as an application  Execution environment  google colaboratory (Runtime: GPU)(tensorflow 2.0)(Google Chrome) win 10 Android Studio (3.5.2) android 9.0(Huawei mate 10 pro)  What to write in this article  Dataset creation method for image recognition model How to create image recognition model How to load the created image recognition model in Android Studio My failure (?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build RaspberryPi for Python and machine learning study (RaspberryPi4 &amp; Buster version (RaspberryPi3 is also available))</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-raspberrypi-for-python-and-machine-learning-study-raspberrypi4-buster-version-raspberrypi3-is-also-available-d370a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-raspberrypi-for-python-and-machine-learning-study-raspberrypi4-buster-version-raspberrypi3-is-also-available-d370a/</guid>
      <description>## [Content]   ** 2020/02/19 We reviewed some contents and confirmed the operation with Raspberry Pi 3 model B. ** ** Added Node-RED environment construction. **  Finally the Raspberry Pi 4 model B has started selling in Japan. In order to use it immediately, I rewrote the previously posted [Building Raspberry Pi for Python and machine learning study] to the Raspberry Pi 4th edition. In addition to the hardware, I have the latest version of Raspbian (Buster 20200213).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Summarize the method of preprocessing text (natural language processing) with tf.data.Dataset api</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summarize-the-method-of-preprocessing-text-natural-language-processing-with-tf.data.dataset-api-c4f6f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summarize-the-method-of-preprocessing-text-natural-language-processing-with-tf.data.dataset-api-c4f6f/</guid>
      <description>It is the 11th day of [TensorFlow2.0 Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/tensorflow2).  I would like to summarize the method of preprocessing text using tf.data.Dataset API.
This article will explain in the following order.
 Explain what the tf.data.Dataset API is and how effective it is Explain the actual text preprocessing procedure Summary of tips for improving performance  Since the explanation is long (the code is long&amp;hellip;) If you want to take a bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view by looking at only the code, here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Verification] There is no easy way to exceed 100% recovery rate for horse racing just because it is deep-planned.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/verification-there-is-no-easy-way-to-exceed-100-recovery-rate-for-horse-racing-just-because-it-is-deep-planned.-3f215/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/verification-there-is-no-easy-way-to-exceed-100-recovery-rate-for-horse-racing-just-because-it-is-deep-planned.-3f215/</guid>
      <description># Now, the beginning of the mystery solving  Original article: With a deep learning, the recovery rate can exceed 100% in horse racing
First try to move I will purchase the program and try it. As described in the explanation, basically it worked with copy and paste, but the following two places did not work as they are, so I fixed it here.
 Parsing date data Column names of features used for learning and inference  It doesn&amp;rsquo;t look exactly the same because it contains random elements, but the graphs also moved in roughly the same way, so it seems to have been reproduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [ML-Aents] I tried machine learning using TensorFlow of Unity and Python (v0.11β compatible)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ml-aents-i-tried-machine-learning-using-tensorflow-of-unity-and-python-v0.11%CE%B2-compatible-687f0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ml-aents-i-tried-machine-learning-using-tensorflow-of-unity-and-python-v0.11%CE%B2-compatible-687f0/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any Japanese article about v0.11.0, so please take a note.
This article is for beginners. Unity beginners mimic one of ML-Agents official tutorials do it It is one of the machine learning, __ which I tried __ Reinforcement Learning.
I will make something like this. :arrow_up:__
For those who know how to operate Unity easily, but who have not done machine learning yet. Rather than focusing on theory, I introduce you to Zakuri so that you can experience while moving your hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] With deep learning, you can exceed 100% recovery rate in horse racing</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/with-deep-learning-you-can-exceed-100-recovery-rate-in-horse-racing-334a8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/with-deep-learning-you-can-exceed-100-recovery-rate-in-horse-racing-334a8/</guid>
      <description>![4370674310_b118d0f62a_c.jpg](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/280076/a136d9bb-956d-2b10-6418-85302ddbbc07.jpeg)  pohotos by Ronnie Macdonald
It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I was told that &amp;ldquo;AI takes away human work&amp;rdquo; **, but now some people say that &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m in a period of disillusionment&amp;rdquo; **. Thanks to that, I was not robbed of my work, and I am swayed by a crowded train every day. The scams that rob you are also a good thing.
While the development of such AI seems to take a little longer, it is now easy to obtain an environment for learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] I tried using the Tensorflow Object Detection API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is IchiLab from RHEMS Giken.
This time using the Object Detection API of TensorFlow, Let me detect the object I want to recognize, I finally tried it on an Android device.
Many helpful sites have helped me, Still, I had a lot of points that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve with just one or two pages.
In this article, I will pick up the parts that I stumbled upon to make a difference, I hope that the number of people who do the same will be reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction to TensorBoard: image] Visualize TensorFlow image processing to deepen understanding</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-tensorboard-image-visualize-tensorflow-image-processing-to-deepen-understanding-fae68/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-tensorboard-image-visualize-tensorflow-image-processing-to-deepen-understanding-fae68/</guid>
      <description>#TensorBoard accelerates understanding of TensorFlow  I output to TensorBoard in order to check the process of convolution processing and pooling processing of TensorFlow. It is a memo of the image confirmation method at that time. As a premise, please refer to [[Introduction to TensorBoard] Visualize TensorFlow process to deepen understanding] for basic usage. Environment: python3.5 tensorflow1.21
Reference link  -Installing TensorFlow on Windows It was easy even for beginners of Python -[Explanatory commentary] TensorFlow basic syntax and concept -[Commentary for beginners] TensorFlow tutorial MNIST (for beginners) -[Introduction to TensorBoard] Visualize TensorFlow processing to deepen understanding -[Introduction to TensorBoard: Projector] Making TensorFlow processing look cool -[TensorFlow tutorial MNIST (for beginners) visualized with TensorBoard] (http://qiita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Roughly think about the loss function</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/roughly-think-about-the-loss-function-f8a8c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/roughly-think-about-the-loss-function-f8a8c/</guid>
      <description>I have a personality that I don&#39;t want to think too deeply about, and I would like to have a rough and intuitive understanding if possible.  So let&amp;rsquo;s do a little research on this loss function as well so that we can understand it intuitively.
What is a loss function? What is a loss function in the first place? It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult function to explain, but it seems to be a function that reduces the difference between two values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to install Deep Learning Framework Tensorflow 1.0 on Windows Anaconda environment</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-install-deep-learning-framework-tensorflow-1.0-on-windows-anaconda-environment-fe4c7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-install-deep-learning-framework-tensorflow-1.0-on-windows-anaconda-environment-fe4c7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Until now, we have been doing deep learning by running Tensorflow on the back end of Keras. If you just do machine learning in Python, you can use Keras as before, but there are applications where you want to use models and weights learned in Python in C++. Actually, it would be nice to use a model trained with Keras, but it seems easier to code directly with Tensorflow which also has a C++ API, so I will try to attack from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Keras usage example: Input (Embedding &#43; Flatten)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/keras-usage-example-input-embedding-flatten-f76b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/keras-usage-example-input-embedding-flatten-f76b1/</guid>
      <description># 1. Install Keras  The installation method of Tensorflow and Theano is introduced in various sites, so the detailed explanation is omitted here. Keras installation is
pip install Keras All you have to do is change the config file and select Theano or Tensorflow. If you use Tensorflow in the backend, it will automatically use the GPU.
When using Tensorflow with Keras, the following errors may occur as of January 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understand the TensorFlow namespace and master shared variables</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understand-the-tensorflow-namespace-and-master-shared-variables-ffe99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understand-the-tensorflow-namespace-and-master-shared-variables-ffe99/</guid>
      <description>## Intro  This is the 9th day article of TensorFlow Advent Calendar 2016.
TensorFlow was released in November 2015, but the &amp;ldquo;namespace&amp;rdquo; function was supported from the beginning. This is used in graph visualization with TensorBoard, but of course it&amp;rsquo;s not the only one. Namespaces are very useful for managing identifiers. I recall C++ when it comes to strong &amp;ldquo;namespace&amp;rdquo; support, but I&amp;rsquo;ll quote it from a C++ instruction book (self-study C++).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-f9aa6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-f9aa6/</guid>
      <description># Series table of contents   I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Introduction- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Implementation- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ Restart‼ ~ I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ What this is Alpha Zero ~ I tried to create a neutral network in Excel to understand the theory of machine learning-Image recognition mnist-  Last time continued&amp;hellip; In this field, I am an outsider, without studying &amp;ldquo;the theory of machine learning&amp;rdquo; at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Implementation-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-implementation-fdb97/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-othello-ai-with-tensorflow-without-understanding-the-theory-of-machine-learning-implementation-fdb97/</guid>
      <description># Series table of contents   I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Introduction- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Implementation- I tried to make Othello AI with tensorflow without understanding the theory of machine learning-Izou battle version- I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ Restart‼ ~ I tried to make Othello AI after trying to understand the theory of machine learning ~ What this is Alpha Zero ~ I tried to create a neutral network in Excel to understand the theory of machine learning-Image recognition mnist-  Last time continued&amp;hellip; In this field, I am an outsider, without studying &amp;ldquo;the theory of machine learning&amp;rdquo; at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] python/tensorflow beginner builds jupyter&#43;tensorflow environment and does Hello World</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-tensorflow-beginner-builds-jupyter-tensorflow-environment-and-does-hello-world-fcb29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-tensorflow-beginner-builds-jupyter-tensorflow-environment-and-does-hello-world-fcb29/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  Amazon.co.jp: TensorFlow started, practice! Latest Google Machine Learning (Next Publishing) E-book: Keiji Ariyama: Kindle Store
It seems to be difficult for beginners if you are operating vim etc. when doing, so it is a procedure memo that makes it easy to operate on the note called jupyter. (* Even though it is said, the terminal operation starts in the middle!)
jupyter image image
Docker image that TensorFlow can be used with Jupyter-Memo Memo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I set up TensowFlow and am addicted</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-set-up-tensowflow-and-am-addicted-fe5ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-set-up-tensowflow-and-am-addicted-fe5ba/</guid>
      <description># The beginning of things  When I installed TensowFlow using pip and tried to check the operation, I got the following error. Thanks to this guy, TensowFlow has been confirmed to work properly. It has already broken at the import stage of tensorflow&amp;hellip;
 File &amp;quot;&amp;lt;stdin&amp;gt;&amp;quot;, line 1, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; File &amp;quot;/Library/Python/2.7/site-packages/tensorflow/__init__.py&amp;quot;, line 23, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; from tensorflow.python import * File &amp;quot;/Library/Python/2.7/site-packages/tensorflow/python/__init__.py&amp;quot;, line 49, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; from tensorflow import contrib File &amp;quot;/Library/Python/2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [TF] How to save and load Tensorflow learning parameters</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tf-how-to-save-and-load-tensorflow-learning-parameters-fc400/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tf-how-to-save-and-load-tensorflow-learning-parameters-fc400/</guid>
      <description>Use **tf.train.Saver** to save and load the parameters learned by Tensorflow.  Save To save, use the save method of the saver class you created.
saver = tf.train.Saver() Some processing #Save saver.save(sess, &amp;quot;model.ckpt&amp;quot;) Saving can be done at the end of learning or at a timing in the middle of learning.
read When loading, use the restore method of the saver class you created. You need a session, so load it after creating the session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] TensorFlow Deep MNIST for Experts 翻訳</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-deep-mnist-for-experts-%E7%BF%BB%E8%A8%B3-fa9cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-deep-mnist-for-experts-%E7%BF%BB%E8%A8%B3-fa9cf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Beforeandprevious using Beginner tutorial translation and actually using TensorFlow I did machine learning. This time I translated the tutorial for Expert.
Deep MNIST for Experts TensorFlow is a powerful library for performing large-scale numerical calculations. One of the best tasks is the training and execution of deep neural networks. In this tutorial we will learn the basic building blocks of a TensorFlow model while building a deep convolutional MNIST classifier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understanding TensorFlow with arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understanding-tensorflow-with-arithmetic-fb5c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understanding-tensorflow-with-arithmetic-fb5c2/</guid>
      <description>TensorFlow is mainly a library for implementing machine learning, especially multi-layer neural networks (deep learning), but you do not need such a difficult story to understand the basic mechanism.  In this article, I would like to understand the mechanism of TensorFlow based on simple calculations such as arithmetic.
TensorFlow features First, I would like to summarize the features of TensorFlow. TensorFlow is a tool for describing the Flow (computation processing) of Tensor (corresponding to multidimensional array, matrix, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>