<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PEP8 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/pep8/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PEP8 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/pep8/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Why is the Python logging library camelCase?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/why-is-the-python-logging-library-camelcase-ad2d0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/why-is-the-python-logging-library-camelcase-ad2d0/</guid>
      <description>When I was talking about Python coding standards with a friend, I suddenly said, &amp;quot;Why some libraries ([`logging`](https://docs.python.org/ja/3/library/logging.html)etc.) does camelCase have been adopted?”  #logging example code. The method name such as getLogger is camelCase. import logging logger = logging.getLogger(&amp;#39;simple_example&amp;#39;) logger.setLevel(logging.DEBUG) In fact, PEP8 &amp;ldquo;Function and variable names&amp;rdquo; says:
 Function names should be in lower case only. Also, for readability, words should be separated by underscores as needed.
The names of variables follow the same convention as functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python naming convention (since PEP8)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-naming-convention-since-pep8-bc3bd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-naming-convention-since-pep8-bc3bd/</guid>
      <description>Python has &amp;quot;[PEP8: Python code style guide](https://pep8-ja.readthedocs.io/ja/latest/)&amp;quot;, which also describes naming conventions such as variable names and function names.  By matching the naming convention and coding style, you can reduce the burden on people who read the source code and those who review it. Please refer not only to the naming convention but also to the naming method described in &amp;ldquo;Readable Code&amp;rdquo;.
PEP8    Usage Naming Convention     Private, private One underscore at the beginning   Name collision avoidance in subclasses Two underscores at the beginning   Special property, special method Add two underscores before and after (Because it is prepared in the language specification, do not define it yourself)   Collision avoidance with reserved words and built-in function names Last one underscore       Usage Naming Convention     Package Short names in all lowercase, no underscores   Module All names in lowercase, separated by underscores   Classes, exceptions CapWords method (connect uppercase words only at the beginning, do not use underscore)   Function, Method Lowercase letters only, with words separated by underscores   Constant Uppercase letters only, words separated by underscores   Variable lowercase only, with words separated by underscores if necessary   1-character variable Never use l (lowercase ell), O (uppercase O), I (uppercase eye) (depending on the font the numbers 1, 0 (I can&amp;rsquo;t tell that))    Other than PEP8    Usage Naming Convention     Discard variable 1 underscore (when a variable is needed but not used in a for loop or split assignment)    Reedable code  Don&amp;rsquo;t abbreviate words (Obviously omitted names are OK) Information and meaning can be added to the name (flag and check do not know what flag or what value was checked) Communicate information by name so that no comment is required Use single-character variables for temporary variables that can be used within the viewable range (up to 25 lines)  Such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python coding with PEP8 and PEP257 is not embarrassing to show to others!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-coding-with-pep8-and-pep257-is-not-embarrassing-to-show-to-others-34f2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-coding-with-pep8-and-pep257-is-not-embarrassing-to-show-to-others-34f2a/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Hello. Promptly, is the source code you wrote easy to read?
There are many opportunities for others to see my own code, such as when co-developed by multiple people, when it is published on the Internet, when it is delivered, and so on. If the code you write at such times is well-formatted, not only the reader but also the reader will be able to understand the code quickly and without misunderstanding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>