<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scikit-learn on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/scikit-learn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scikit-learn on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/scikit-learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Machine learning] Understanding decision trees from both scikit-learn and mathematics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/53efe3e96/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/53efe3e96/</guid>
      <description>#1. Purpose  If you want to do machine learning, anyone can use scikit-learn etc. to implement it relatively easily. However, in order to achieve results at work or to improve your level, The explanation &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand the background but I got this result&amp;rdquo; clearly shows the weakness.
In this article, the purpose of ** is 2-3, &amp;ldquo;I will use scikit-learn first because the theory is good,&amp;rdquo; and 4 and &amp;ldquo;understand the background from mathematics&amp;rdquo; **.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] About sklearn.preprocessing.Imputer</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/19c81e16c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/19c81e16c/</guid>
      <description>Currently (2020/03/03), all the teaching materials of N prep schools are released free of charge due to the suspension of elementary and junior high school due to the spread of COVID-19 infection. It is said that I am also working on &amp;quot;Introduction to machine learning&amp;quot;, but a little trouble occurred in &amp;quot;12. How to handle missing values&amp;quot;.  error
 ImportError: cannot import name&amp;rsquo;Imputer&amp;rsquo; from&amp;rsquo;sklearn.preprocessing&amp;rsquo;
 The version of scikit-learn that I use is 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Machine learning] Understand logistic regression from both scikit-learn and mathematics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ee2a0687c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ee2a0687c/</guid>
      <description>#1. Purpose  If you want to do machine learning, anyone can use scikit-learn etc. to implement it relatively easily. However, in order to achieve results at work or to improve your level, The explanation &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand the background, but I got this result&amp;rdquo; is clearly weak.
In this article, the two aims are to &amp;ldquo;use the scikit-learn first because the theory is good&amp;rdquo; and to &amp;ldquo;understand the background from mathematics&amp;rdquo; from the fourth and later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build JupyterLab (Python) environment with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/1f82f1644/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/1f82f1644/</guid>
      <description># What we could achieve  Since we were able to build the following environment with Docker, we summarized the flow from Docker image build to JupyterLab startup.
 Easy Python version switching (Python3 ⇄ Python2) Easy startup of JupyterLab 1 Can be deleted as soon as the environment is no longer needed I want to easily build an environment on Mac and Windows  Actually built environment  macOS Catalina (MacBook Pro(15-inch, Late2016)) Windows 10  Docker image You need to login to get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to use machine learning for work? 03_Python coding procedure</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7f444e131/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7f444e131/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  So far, I&amp;rsquo;ve delivered an article with the theme &amp;ldquo;How to use machine learning for work?&amp;rdquo; In this third installment, we will introduce concrete programming under the theme of &amp;ldquo;Python coding procedure&amp;rdquo;.
If you also read the back number, you can understand the whole from machine learning basics to Python coding, so please use it.
 Part 1: Understanding the purpose of machine learning Part 2: Overview of AI development project  Since various information is also sent on SNS, please feel free to read the article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried handwriting recognition of runes with scikit-learn</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/02943c926/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/02943c926/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 15th day of the Fujitsu Systems Web Technology Advent Calendar.  (Promise) The content of this article is my own opinion and does not represent the organization to which I belong.
Introduction In this article, we use scikit-learn, a Python machine learning library. I have summarized the procedure and the result when I tried handwriting recognition of runes **. While the advent calendars of this Advent Calendar are putting in great features and know-how that are likely to be useful for actual work, However, I made something that was just fun for me, and I cannot help being so enthusiastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Performance study of latest ensemble learning Sklearn Stacking (Compare LBGM, RGF, ET, RF, LR, KNN models with Heamy and Sklearn)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/61b3b7fa7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/61b3b7fa7/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  Stacking sklearn, it might be a standard because it was a very good child when I tried using it
| library | layer1 | layer2 | public score | speed | | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; | &amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | | lgbm model | lgb |-| 0.74162 |-| heamy single stacking | lbg, rgf, et, rf, lr, knn | lr | 0.76076 | 64s | heamy multiple stacking | lgb, rgf, et, rf, lr, knn | lgb, lr | 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Matching application I tried to take statistics of strong people &amp; created a machine learning model</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/54bab8463/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/54bab8463/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hello everyone.
Do you use a matching app? ! I feel good as one of those who have recently matched with a matching app.
By the way, the matching app I was using was able to refer to the data of other popular members. (Probably people who have received more than 100 like are displayed.)
When I saw it, I was disappointed.
&amp;ldquo;Like, I didn&amp;rsquo;t get 100&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; ** &amp;ldquo;I want to be a man who exceeds 100&amp;rdquo; **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Environment construction of auto-sklearn that semi-automates machine learning (Mac&amp;Docker)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ffd7f4235/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ffd7f4235/</guid>
      <description>What is # auto-sklearn  A library that can semi-automatically perform preprocessing of machine learning, algorithm selection, and hyperparameter search. See below for detailed explanation.
What is auto-sklearn? Automatic machine learning with WPython auto sklearn Data analysis with Python: Automation of machine learning
Build an environment for auto-sklearn on mac As a premise, auto-sklearn is developed on Ubuntu, and it works on Linux but may not work on Mac or Window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Translation] scikit-learn 0.18 User Guide 4.1. Pipeline and Feature Union: Combination of estimators</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fdfd207b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fdfd207b3/</guid>
      <description>Google translated http://scikit-learn.org/0.18/modules/pipeline.html  scikit-learn 0.18 User Guide 4. Dataset conversion
 4.1. Pipeline and FeatureUnion: Estimator combination 4.1.1. Pipeline: Chain estimation Pipeline can be used to combine multiple estimators into one. I can do it. It is convenient because the steps that process the data, such as feature selection, normalization, and classification, are often fixed. The pipeline serves two purposes here.
-Convenience: To fit the whole sequence of estimators, just call fit and predict the data once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Predict the value of the water level gauge by machine learning using open data of data city Sabae</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fe2e04b8c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fe2e04b8c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When I was looking for something good as an example of using open data, I found that the water level data was published on the site of Data City Sabae, so I tried machine learning using it. It was
http://data.city.sabae.lg.jp/top_page/
Download data There is the following notation in the &amp;ldquo;Disaster prevention&amp;rdquo; group on the &amp;ldquo;Open data&amp;rdquo; page on the above site.
Water level data (Sabae City, Fukui Prefecture) Nontegawa Drainage Pump Station [CSV] It is the data of the water level gauge in Sabae city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Tool to support machine learning in Python MALSS (Introduction)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fe1ccd572/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fe1ccd572/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;Font color=&amp;quot;red&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Support Python3 (2016.01.25)&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;  I made a tool called MALSS (Machine Learning Support System) that supports machine learning in Python (PyPI/GitHub). We would be happy if you could give us your opinions.
I&amp;rsquo;m writing the rest here.
 Tool MALSS (basic) that supports machine learning in Python Tool MALSS (application) that supports machine learning in Python  Purpose A rich open source development environment has made it really easy to use machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Calculate tf-idf with scikit-learn</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f86971afc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f86971afc/</guid>
      <description>**This post is the fourth day article of [Reality Escape Advent Calendar 2013](http://katryo.hatenablog.com/entry/2013/12/19/001823). **  2nd dayusesthehtmlfetchedusingtheBingAPI,so[2ndday](http://qiita.com/katryo(/items/62291ba328de9d12bd30) is easier to understand if you read it first.
Put this article in 3 lines  I checked a Python library called scikit-learn Day 2 Calculated tf-idf of word in html saved Confirmed word to tfidf mapping  Reference scikit-learn formula, text feature extraction document
Calculating tfidf of words in Tweet using scikit-learn</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>