<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> python2.7 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/python2.7/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  python2.7 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/python2.7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Get and create nodes added and updated in new version</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-and-create-nodes-added-and-updated-in-new-version-33170/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-and-create-nodes-added-and-updated-in-new-version-33170/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 10th day article of Houdini Advent Calender 2019.
Houdini18.0 was released at the end of last month!
I think that many people have already used it, but the node introduced in New feature movie Besides, it seems that small updates have been made.
Therefore, this article will show you how to get and create the added and updated nodes in Houdini 18.0.
#Definition of added and updated nodes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to get help on HDA (with extra Python script)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-get-help-on-hda-with-extra-python-script-1737c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-get-help-on-hda-with-extra-python-script-1737c/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 8th day article of [**Houdini Advent Calender 2019**](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/houdini).  Nowadays, Houdini is used in various industries, and I think various HDAs are being developed by various companies. On the other hand, if management and documentation are not maintained, **you can not understand how to use HDA created by others, and you can not know what kind of HDA exists **.
This article will show you how to create tooltips and your own documentation for the parameters shown below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Things from building Python environment to running on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/things-from-building-python-environment-to-running-on-windows-fdf02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/things-from-building-python-environment-to-running-on-windows-fdf02/</guid>
      <description>When building the Python environment, I went through various articles saying &amp;quot;Authentication proxy settings, coexistence environment, and execution confirmation are all necessary&amp;quot;, so I think that it would be nice to put them all together.  #Introduction
Content The contents introduced in this article are as follows. Please skip the authentication proxy and coexistence environment construction if necessary.
 Install Anaconda (Windows) Authentication proxy settings Different versions coexistence environment construction Run the program in interactive mode Run Python script  For whom For Python beginners who meet any of the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If you use Python, you should know! 10 convenient libraries</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-python-you-should-know-10-convenient-libraries-f76a9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-python-you-should-know-10-convenient-libraries-f76a9/</guid>
      <description>*This article is intended to be useful for everyone&#39;s learning by prosta editorial department publishing a very popular Python grammar article now.  Reference site: If you use Python, you should know! 10 handy libraries
If you use #Python you should know! 10 convenient libraries
Python has many standard and external libraries, but due to their abundance, it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to know which one to use. This time, I will introduce a Python library that is useful to know from among them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [OpenCV; Python] Summary of findcontours function</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/opencv-python-summary-of-findcontours-function-fd3d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/opencv-python-summary-of-findcontours-function-fd3d8/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&#39;t find any more detailed explanation about findcontours for Python version of OpenCV on the internet, so I&#39;d like to note that I tried it myself. If you made a mistake, please point it out.  #findcontours function When you want to extract the contours of an image with OpenCV, use the function findContours. The first argument is the input image, the second argument is the extraction mode, and the third argument is the approximation method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Fixed] I was addicted to the alphanumeric judgment of Python strings.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fixed-i-was-addicted-to-the-alphanumeric-judgment-of-python-strings.-f738a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fixed-i-was-addicted-to-the-alphanumeric-judgment-of-python-strings.-f738a/</guid>
      <description>*** Addition ***  The article was flawed, so please read the additional notes below the text.
I&amp;rsquo;m addicted One day I was writing a web app on Google App Engine (Python).
There are times when you want to determine the characters that can be used in passwords in web services, right?
When I looked it up, I could use string.isalnum() to check if it was alphanumeric, so I used it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>