<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python2.7 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/python2.7/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python2.7 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/python2.7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A note on creating a python development environment on macOS Catalina</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-note-on-creating-a-python-development-environment-on-macos-catalina-521c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-note-on-creating-a-python-development-environment-on-macos-catalina-521c6/</guid>
      <description>*Memo will be updated at any time*  Aiming to build a python development environment
In the environment I upgraded from Mojave to Catalina, when I did it normally, it did not work as expected with python3 or pip3 due to the difference in version, so I try using pyenv and see if it works.
It&amp;rsquo;s actually better to use Docker, but for now&amp;hellip;
homebrew Start from here.
/bin/bash -c &amp;quot;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get and create nodes added and updated in new version</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-and-create-nodes-added-and-updated-in-new-version-33170/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-and-create-nodes-added-and-updated-in-new-version-33170/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 10th day article of Houdini Advent Calender 2019.
Houdini18.0 was released at the end of last month!
I think that many people have already used it, but the node introduced in New feature movie Besides, it seems that small updates have been made.
Therefore, this article will show you how to get and create the added and updated nodes in Houdini 18.0.
#Definition of added and updated nodes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get help on HDA (with extra Python script)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-get-help-on-hda-with-extra-python-script-1737c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-get-help-on-hda-with-extra-python-script-1737c/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 8th day article of [**Houdini Advent Calender 2019**](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/houdini).  Nowadays, Houdini is used in various industries, and I think various HDAs are being developed by various companies. On the other hand, if management and documentation are not maintained, **you can not understand how to use HDA created by others, and you can not know what kind of HDA exists **.
This article will show you how to create tooltips and your own documentation for the parameters shown below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>