<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>astropy on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/astropy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in astropy on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/astropy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Image analysis performed by google Colab for people who start space research</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/image-analysis-performed-by-google-colab-for-people-who-start-space-research-7075a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/image-analysis-performed-by-google-colab-for-people-who-start-space-research-7075a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For those who are new to handling fits files. The image of the galaxy is familiar, so this is an example of a sample that works even with google Colab. There is also a advanced method for searching fits images with skyview written for a little more advanced users.
Basic Server and client basics Space Astronomy exchanges a large amount of data, so knowledge about servers and clients is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software training for those who start space research</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/software-training-for-those-who-start-space-research-f4535/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/software-training-for-those-who-start-space-research-f4535/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I would like to briefly introduce the basics of software for people who aspire to the universe so that they can do it at home. Software is intended for students who have done a little in class. (2020.4.9. First edition for the time being).
For online learning, how to use python using google Colab,
 Online learning using google Colab for those who start space research  Please refer to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it the moon that triggered the huge earthquake? -&gt; Monthly</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-it-the-moon-that-triggered-the-huge-earthquake-monthly-9db5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-it-the-moon-that-triggered-the-huge-earthquake-monthly-9db5b/</guid>
      <description>## 0. Abstract   In many cases, huge earthquakes (M&amp;gt;8) are triggered by the deformation of the earth due to tidal stress caused by the moon. There were also some papers that treated the earthquakes that occurred in the past statistically and discussed the relationship with the tide. However, it goes without saying that even though we discussed the Tidal Phase Angle, we could not find anything that clearly showed Lunar Age or Lunar Phase.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>