<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DynamoDB on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/dynamodb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DynamoDB on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/dynamodb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[AWS] Data migration from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-data-migration-from-dynamodb-to-aurora-mysql-fe2f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-data-migration-from-dynamodb-to-aurora-mysql-fe2f9/</guid>
      <description>I have migrated data from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL, so I will write the method.  Please note that the data migration does not mean that all tables are migrated because we have migrated the data stored in one table.
Method I think there are several possible ways to migrate from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL, but I wrote the code in disposable (?) Python to make the transition quickly and reliably Even though it is disposable, there is a possibility that data may be migrated again, so we made it possible to reuse</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[DynamoDB] [Docker] Build a development environment for DynamoDB and Django with docker-compose</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/dynamodb-docker-build-a-development-environment-for-dynamodb-and-django-with-docker-compose-fca2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/dynamodb-docker-build-a-development-environment-for-dynamodb-and-django-with-docker-compose-fca2c/</guid>
      <description># Build a development environment for DynamoDB and Django with docker-compose  Introduction DynamoDB is cheap and fast. Did you know that there is a Docker Image for developing such DynamoDB locally? We will inquire about an example of development environment construction using such Docker Image.
Environment The following image versions are used according to the production environment. Use dynamodb-admin for DynamoDB GUI operation. Node is used to build the environment together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>