<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JupyterLab on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/jupyterlab/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JupyterLab on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/jupyterlab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Summary of statistical data analysis methods using Python that can be used in business</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-statistical-data-analysis-methods-using-python-that-can-be-used-in-business-21c19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-statistical-data-analysis-methods-using-python-that-can-be-used-in-business-21c19/</guid>
      <description># Overview  I think it is very important to verify the effects after conducting various prototypes with WEB services, I think that basic statistics can be used enough as a method. This time, we summarized the method of statistical data analysis using Python+JupyterLab (Docker) for the purpose of basic statistics, verification of the effects of prototypes that can be used in business, and data analysis.
The notebook I used this time is also available below, so please refer to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build JupyterLab (Python) environment with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-jupyterlab-python-environment-with-docker-1f82f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-jupyterlab-python-environment-with-docker-1f82f/</guid>
      <description># What we could achieve  Since we were able to build the following environment with Docker, we summarized the flow from Docker image build to JupyterLab startup.
 Easy Python version switching (Python3 ⇄ Python2) Easy startup of JupyterLab 1 Can be deleted as soon as the environment is no longer needed I want to easily build an environment on Mac and Windows  Actually built environment  macOS Catalina (MacBook Pro(15-inch, Late2016)) Windows 10  Docker image You need to login to get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For data science] Oreole Jupyter cheat sheet [Jupyter Notebook/Lab]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-data-science-oreole-jupyter-cheat-sheet-jupyter-notebook-lab-0f5dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-data-science-oreole-jupyter-cheat-sheet-jupyter-notebook-lab-0f5dd/</guid>
      <description>I usually do **data analysis and model construction** mainly on Jupyter.  I will make a note of how many times I will research it. (Updated from time to time)
Development I want to reload the modified .py module Modules that have already been imported will be cached, or will not be updated when imported normally. ** You can reload (reimport) with the following. **
import importlib importlib.reload(hoge) # hoge is an imported module I didn&amp;rsquo;t know this much until recently, and I restarted every time, so it&amp;rsquo;s really a scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build RaspberryPi for Python and machine learning study (RaspberryPi4 &amp; Buster version (RaspberryPi3 is also available))</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-raspberrypi-for-python-and-machine-learning-study-raspberrypi4-buster-version-raspberrypi3-is-also-available-d370a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-raspberrypi-for-python-and-machine-learning-study-raspberrypi4-buster-version-raspberrypi3-is-also-available-d370a/</guid>
      <description>## [Content]   ** 2020/02/19 We reviewed some contents and confirmed the operation with Raspberry Pi 3 model B. ** ** Added Node-RED environment construction. **  Finally the Raspberry Pi 4 model B has started selling in Japan. In order to use it immediately, I rewrote the previously posted [Building Raspberry Pi for Python and machine learning study] to the Raspberry Pi 4th edition. In addition to the hardware, I have the latest version of Raspbian (Buster 20200213).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If you use GitPod, you can use IDE and jupyter on iPad, so it&#39;s the best!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-gitpod-you-can-use-ide-and-jupyter-on-ipad-so-its-the-best-dbb64/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-gitpod-you-can-use-ide-and-jupyter-on-ipad-so-its-the-best-dbb64/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  **Using GitPod, you can use IDE and jupyter on iPad, so it&amp;rsquo;s the best! **
Features of #GitPod GitPod has the following features.
 VS code-like IDE available Available in chrome and firefox Can be used by linking to an account with GitHub Public repositories are free, private repositories are available for a fee (9$/month ~)  #This goal and procedure
on chrome on iPad Build a Python programming environment (IDE and jupyterlab).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>