<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> automation on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  automation on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] (◎◎) {Let Python do the boring stuff.........(He? Hona Python will do the homework}} (゜) (゜)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/let-python-do-the-boring-stuff.........he-hona-python-will-do-the-homework-86258/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/let-python-do-the-boring-stuff.........he-hona-python-will-do-the-homework-86258/</guid>
      <description># Did you make Python do boring stuff?  I didn&amp;rsquo;t let it do A book on the cover with a robot like this C-3PO playing grass
It&amp;rsquo;s well-known as a good Python book, and many people have read it.
So who read this book and did Python actually do the boring stuff? Isn&amp;rsquo;t it quite small? I think there are many people who are satisfied with reading. I was one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Things to keep in mind when creating automation tools for the manufacturing site with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/things-to-keep-in-mind-when-creating-automation-tools-for-the-manufacturing-site-with-python-ab30e/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/things-to-keep-in-mind-when-creating-automation-tools-for-the-manufacturing-site-with-python-ab30e/</guid>
      <description># Motivation for this article #  Last year, I changed jobs from a production engineering job to a data analysis job, and I have more opportunities to write Python. I am currently involved in a project to develop a preprocessing tool for machine learning. Meanwhile, looking back when I was working as a production engineer, I thought that there were various tasks that could be automated . Based on the knowledge of Python obtained after changing jobs and the knowledge of the days of production engineers, I will describe the material that can be used when working again at the manufacturing site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Automate background removal of latest person images in directory with Python and API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/automate-background-removal-of-latest-person-images-in-directory-with-python-and-api-0ff9d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/automate-background-removal-of-latest-person-images-in-directory-with-python-and-api-0ff9d/</guid>
      <description># Thing you want to do   Background removal of portrait image Finely specify the input destination of the image to be background-removed and the output destination of the background-removed image. Browse the latest image in the folder Automation of them  Occasionally you may want to perform face recognition from an image using OpenCV or facenet and do some processing. Of course, these tools will recognize your face, but I have found that there are times when the accuracy of face recognition drops dramatically due to unnecessary things such as the background in the image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A program that automatically corrects Takenoko no Sato to Mushroom Mountain</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-program-that-automatically-corrects-takenoko-no-sato-to-mushroom-mountain-a8c7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-program-that-automatically-corrects-takenoko-no-sato-to-mushroom-mountain-a8c7b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction-Introduction of wonderful sweets and the existence of late-deteriorated products-  As you probably know, there is a wonderful sweets called &amp;ldquo;Mushroom Mountain&amp;rdquo;1. A chocolate snack made and sold by Meiji Co., Ltd. since 1975. It has a cute mushroom-like shape with crackers on the stem and chocolate on the umbrella. It was said that the best combination was tried and errored over a development period of 5 years, and while it was easy to hold and functional, it had plenty of chocolate and a moderately salty and crispy feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What automation should I do in RPA, VBA, or programming languages?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-automation-should-i-do-in-rpa-vba-or-programming-languages-d322b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-automation-should-i-do-in-rpa-vba-or-programming-languages-d322b/</guid>
      <description>It is called business automation, but there are many tools for automation. You mean, &amp;quot;You don&#39;t have to use that special tool for that task!?&amp;quot; So, I tried to categorize by business type, environment, user type, etc.  1. Automation of core operations (accounting, HR, CRM, ERP, etc.) RPA recommendation level: ☆☆☆☆☆
Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to introduce packaged software for human resources, salary, management accounting, supply chain, cost accounting, CRM, etc. for basic business as a company independent of the industry and automation of business unique to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Fast automated test creation using pyATS|Genie&#39;s hidden move Blitz</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fast-automated-test-creation-using-pyatsgenies-hidden-move-blitz-fa008/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fast-automated-test-creation-using-pyatsgenies-hidden-move-blitz-fa008/</guid>
      <description>This article was posted as the 11th day of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by volunteers from Cisco.  2017 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco
#Introduction
Hello. pyATS|GenieI&#39;m@tahigash3fromthedevelopmentteam.Inthisarticle,I&amp;rsquo;llshowyouaneasywaytocreateanetworktestusingpyATS|Genie.
Please refer to the previous article for a brief introduction and installation of pyATS|Genie. Easily check multi-vendor networks with pyATS/Genie and Robot Framework
Worries about network automation I have enumerated the worries of those who have not done network automation yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] It is also useful in everyday life!? Semi-automation of Cospa&#39;s strongest experimental design method with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/it-is-also-useful-in-everyday-life-semi-automation-of-cospas-strongest-experimental-design-method-with-python-90838/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/it-is-also-useful-in-everyday-life-semi-automation-of-cospas-strongest-experimental-design-method-with-python-90838/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;!-- title How to get a lot of information with a small number of experiments with Python Automatically create an efficient experimental plan in Python Automatically create a good experiment plan for COSPA in Python I experimented 30,000 times, but actually 16 times was enough Reduce 30,000 experiments to 16 Also useful for everyday life!?--&amp;gt;  Overview  I will explain (roughly) the &amp;ldquo;experimental design method&amp;rdquo; that greatly improves the number of experiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I installed the IoT platform Rimotte</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-installed-the-iot-platform-rimotte-39278/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-installed-the-iot-platform-rimotte-39278/</guid>
      <description>### What is Limotte  Rimotte is an All-In-One platform for always-on apps such as IoT. It is used by using the “Station” that is installed and used on Windows and a web browser that runs on Android, iOS, Windows, MacOS, Linux, etc. Not limited to IoT, it can be used for applications that are used without being connected to the Internet, and applications such as measurement, monitoring, automation, and AI can be easily realized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to automatically generate a port management table from Config of L2SW</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-automatically-generate-a-port-management-table-from-config-of-l2sw-75ec5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-automatically-generate-a-port-management-table-from-config-of-l2sw-75ec5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In the previous article, I introduced an example of automatically generating Config from the port management table. I tried to automatically generate L2SW Config from the port management table + parameter table + Jinja2 template
In some cases, you may want to create a port management table from the already created Config. This time, using a Python parser library called TTP (Template Text Parser), I automatically generated a CSV format port management table from the L2SW Config file.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>