<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Docker on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Docker on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a lightweight FastAPI development environment using Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-a-lightweight-fastapi-development-environment-using-docker-fcd38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-a-lightweight-fastapi-development-environment-using-docker-fcd38/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I often use FastAPI recently, and I wanted to quickly build it with Docker and dispose of it. As a memo, I&amp;rsquo;d like to leave a lightweight construction method.
Preparation  Environment that can use Docker and Docker Compose  $ docker --version Docker version 19.03.8, build afacb8b7f0  The file structure looks like this  . ├── Dockerfile ├── docker-compose.yml ├── main.py └── requirements.txt Source You can clone from here https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try running wav2pix, which creates a face image from audio (there is also an anime face generator)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-running-wav2pix-which-creates-a-face-image-from-audio-there-is-also-an-anime-face-generator-159ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-running-wav2pix-which-creates-a-face-image-from-audio-there-is-also-an-anime-face-generator-159ce/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The world of deep learning, especially Generative Adversarial Networks (GAN), has grown dramatically in recent years, and I think that research is progressing in various fields such as text-to-image, voice conversion, and sound source separation.
In this talk, I will loosely write about wav2pix, which generates face images from voice.
Paper: WAV2PIX: SPEECH-CONDITIONED FACE GENERATION USING GENERATIVEADVERSARIAL NETWORKS
#Overview https://imatge-upc.github.io/wav2pix/
The proposed model consists of the following three modules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebuild Django development environment with Docker! ! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/rebuild-django-development-environment-with-docker-e345f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/rebuild-django-development-environment-with-docker-e345f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I wrote this article before. [Build Django development environment with Docker! (Docker-compose/Django/postgreSQL/nginx)]](https://qiita.com/nokonoko_1203/items/242367a83c313a5e46bf)
The original article was written a long time ago (a year or so?), but now that I have enough knowledge, I thought I could make it a little better, so I decided to try it!
I will not talk about installing Docker in detail, so if you are interested, please check the original article! (Here)willhelp.)
Also, as a clear difference from the previous article, Django thinks as an API delivery server and assumes Vue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Todo application with Django ① Build environment with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-todo-application-with-django-build-environment-with-docker-b9ba0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-todo-application-with-django-build-environment-with-docker-b9ba0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I made a Todo application that is a representative of the tutorial with Django. I intend to write it in as much detail as possible, including the meaning of the code.
 Please point out any mistakes! :bow:  Target person Those who want to get started with django
##List of articles Create Todo application with Django ① Build environment with Docker Create Todo application with Django ②Create folder list page Create Todo application with Django ③ Create task list page Create Todo application with Django ④ Implement folder and task creation function Create Todo application with Django ⑤ Create task editing function</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When creating Lambda Layers, docker-lambda and yumda are convenient</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/when-creating-lambda-layers-docker-lambda-and-yumda-are-convenient-a6fd8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/when-creating-lambda-layers-docker-lambda-and-yumda-are-convenient-a6fd8/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  A layer corresponding to each runtime version can be created with the docker-lambda build image!
$ docker run --rm -v $(pwd):/var/task lambci/lambda:build-python3.8 \ &amp;gt; pip install -r requirements.txt -t python/lib/python3.8/site-packages/ Software packages that you want to run on AWS Lambda can be layered with yumda!
$ docker run --rm -v $(pwd)/git-layer:/lambda/opt lambci/yumda:2 yum install -y &amp;lt;package&amp;gt; Preparing the environment from scratch is quite difficult A common caveat with AWS Lambda and Lambda Layers is the handling of native binaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python development flow using Poetry, Git and Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-development-flow-using-poetry-git-and-docker-43efd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-development-flow-using-poetry-git-and-docker-43efd/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is a sister article of Python development flow using pipenv, Git and Docker I wrote earlier. Now that the development of Pipenv is not very active, I think that there will be occasions when Poetry is used in projects using Python. So I&amp;rsquo;ll try to summarize the development flow using Poetry again.
Overall flow  Installation of development environment Project initialization Docker  #Prerequisite environment
 Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Pascal-VOC dataset of MobileNetV2-SSDLite [Docker version remake]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-with-pascal-voc-dataset-of-mobilenetv2-ssdlite-docker-version-remake-107dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-with-pascal-voc-dataset-of-mobilenetv2-ssdlite-docker-version-remake-107dd/</guid>
      <description>**PINTO_model_zoo** [![GitHub stars](https://img.shields.io/github/stars/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo.svg?style=social&amp;amp;label=Stars)](https://github.com/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo)  &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://github-link-card.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/PINTO0309/PINTO_model_zoo.png&amp;quot;width=&amp;quot;460px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
1. Introduction I remade the MobileNet V2-SSD Lite training environment construction article that I wrote about a year ago into an ultra-simple specification. If you start work from the stage where the latest Docker for GPU is introduced, I think you can start training in about 15 minutes. I think there are almost no mistakes. After learning, I plan to do Integer Quantization of the trained model (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment installation by introducing Docker Image of Kaggle on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/environment-installation-by-introducing-docker-image-of-kaggle-on-windows-66bf0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/environment-installation-by-introducing-docker-image-of-kaggle-on-windows-66bf0/</guid>
      <description>I will record as a reminder the part that was clogged up when I tried to easily build the environment on my windows notebook using Kaggle&#39;s Docker Image.  Basically, I am referring to the article of &amp;ldquo;Tenshiki Graffiti&amp;rdquo;, so please refer to here first, and OS is not Win10 Pro except windows. And if you are using Docker toolbox, I think it will be helpful.
Stumble point ① Execution of yaml of docker-compose does not work due to error of volume name After creating the docker-compose yaml file as in the above article, I got an error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Django development environment with Docker! (Docker-compose/Django/postgreSQL/nginx)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-a-django-development-environment-with-docker-docker-compose-django-postgresql-nginx-24236/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-a-django-development-environment-with-docker-docker-compose-django-postgresql-nginx-24236/</guid>
      <description>I tried rebuilding!  Rebuild Django development environment with Docker! ! ! ! 
#Introduction
Team development&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s very difficult to build an environment&amp;hellip; At that time, use Docker (miscellaneous).
This article is a repost of what I gave to qrunchLet&amp;rsquo;s build a Django/postgreSQL/gunicorn/nginx development environment using Docker and Docker-compose, which are very convenient for team development! !
The whole flow is based on almost the following sites, but I intend to make the article easy to understand, such as putting comments in almost all lines of the configuration file etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a music bot using discord.py and Google Drive API (tested with Docker → deployed on Heroku)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-music-bot-using-discord.py-and-google-drive-api-tested-with-docker-deployed-on-heroku-372e5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-music-bot-using-discord.py-and-google-drive-api-tested-with-docker-deployed-on-heroku-372e5/</guid>
      <description>The used file is placed in [here](https://github.com/ysk0832/hobby/tree/master/discordbot-citron)(excludingauthenticationrelated)  Basically, I made it for my family to enjoy.
Thing you want to do  Send a message on discord bot finds song file from google drive If you find it, download it and play it with your voice.  Also, there are two personal requirements for music bots,
 You can request songs other than yourself I want to keep the bot running  I decided to use google drive and heroku to satisfy these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Introduction to Docker] I tried to summarize various findings of Docker obtained by studying (Windows/Python)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-docker-i-tried-to-summarize-various-findings-of-docker-obtained-by-studying-windows-python-f7eea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-docker-i-tried-to-summarize-various-findings-of-docker-obtained-by-studying-windows-python-f7eea/</guid>
      <description>There was a person in charge of specialized infrastructure related things in the company, and he was kind to the environment, but it would be bad if I had to study Docker around myself as soon as possible. I&#39;ve finally been introduced to Docker recently, so I&#39;ll try to put together and try what I have learned as a memorandum.  Since I have been working on unfamiliar work such as infrastructure around my career, please forgive me for things that are rough (shallow) in terms of knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried building a service to sell machine-learned data at explosive speed with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-building-a-service-to-sell-machine-learned-data-at-explosive-speed-with-docker-d690e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-building-a-service-to-sell-machine-learned-data-at-explosive-speed-with-docker-d690e/</guid>
      <description>About 3 years ago [The result of my own development of a machine learning stock price forecast program at WEB shop \| Masamnet](http://masamunet.com/2016/11/09/web%E5%B1%8B%E3%81%AE%E8%87%AA%E5%88%86%E3%81%8C%E6%A9%9F%E6%A2%B0%E5%AD%A6%E7%BF%92%E6%A0%AA%E4%BE%A1%E4%BA%88%E6%83%B3%E3%83%97%E3%83%AD%E3%82%B0%E3%83%A9%E3%83%A0%E3%82%92%E9%96%8B%E7%99%BA/) I wrote an article, and I did not do much with machine learning or stocks, but at the beginning of this year&#39;s end of the year, I dared to I tried various things.  So, I got a pretty good result, so I will write the technical background until it started as a service as it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypothesis/Verification (170) 11 essential skills that developers in 2020 should know → Answers → Sort → Sort items (8 items) → Add content</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hypothesis-verification-170-11-essential-skills-that-developers-in-2020-should-know-answers-sort-sort-items-8-items-add-content-39e1c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hypothesis-verification-170-11-essential-skills-that-developers-in-2020-should-know-answers-sort-sort-items-8-items-add-content-39e1c/</guid>
      <description>11 essential skills developers should know for 2020  https://qiita.com/rana_kualu/items/c79a16ff503c86b27483
11 Essential Skills Software Developers should Learn in 2020 https://dev.to/javinpaul/11-essential-skills-software-developers-should-learn-in-2020-1bio
 Top 11 Essentials Skills for Software Developers in 2020
  Containers (Docker and Kubernetes) Cloud Platform (AWS, GCP, or Azure) Data Structure and Algorithm A Version Control Tool (Git) One Text Editors (VIM) IDEs (VSCode or IntelliJIDEA) Database and SQL UNIX (Linux) An OOP Programming language (C++, Java or Python) Networking basics One Scripting language  Answer Self-assess 11 skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Starter Kit No.1] Build an automatic data collection bot system with Scrapy&amp;MariaDB&amp;Django&amp;Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/starter-kit-no.1-build-an-automatic-data-collection-bot-system-with-scrapymariadbdjangodocker-dfde3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/starter-kit-no.1-build-an-automatic-data-collection-bot-system-with-scrapymariadbdjangodocker-dfde3/</guid>
      <description>![screencapture-192-168-99-102-admin-nutrition-item-2019-03-04-15_04_19-1024x686.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/514619/8e65d631-de2a-b0f4-18a4-b427fb78e439.png)  #Background
You can easily create a Web service with your needs by automatically synchronizing the database of Web services in the world and adding added value that the original family does not have.
For example, scrape the data of the EC site and keep it as a database yourself, provide a search method that does not exist in the original home, attach a link, and have a lightweight business model like earning by affiliate at the level of individual business Is possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Docker development container conveniently with VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/use-docker-development-container-conveniently-with-vs-code-d3b52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/use-docker-development-container-conveniently-with-vs-code-d3b52/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction   Developing in local environment, deploying to Linux environment and testing is troublesome I want to create a development environment that feels good to use Docker However, various settings and construction are troublesome  For such a person, it is an introduction of how to use the extension function &amp;ldquo;Remote-Containers&amp;rdquo; that can conveniently build and operate a development environment using Docker container from VS Code.
Greatness of this extension VS Code&amp;rsquo;s extension function &amp;ldquo;Remote-Containers&amp;rdquo; is to launch VS Code in a container and communicate with VS Code of the host machine so that you can perform in-container development as if you were developing in a local environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build JupyterLab (Python) environment with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-jupyterlab-python-environment-with-docker-1f82f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-jupyterlab-python-environment-with-docker-1f82f/</guid>
      <description># What we could achieve  Since we were able to build the following environment with Docker, we summarized the flow from Docker image build to JupyterLab startup.
 Easy Python version switching (Python3 ⇄ Python2) Easy startup of JupyterLab 1 Can be deleted as soon as the environment is no longer needed I want to easily build an environment on Mac and Windows  Actually built environment  macOS Catalina (MacBook Pro(15-inch, Late2016)) Windows 10  Docker image You need to login to get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django-SES and Amazon SES got stuck when trying to operate mail (introducing the fastest operation procedure)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-ses-and-amazon-ses-got-stuck-when-trying-to-operate-mail-introducing-the-fastest-operation-procedure-44893/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-ses-and-amazon-ses-got-stuck-when-trying-to-operate-mail-introducing-the-fastest-operation-procedure-44893/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  This is the 24th day article of Django Advent Calendar 2019. I wrote this article on Christmas Eve proud of myself thinking about Django. Lol
Even though I&amp;rsquo;m still a beginner, I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying Django, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been stuck for hours at some point (a little new way to do it?). Even if the reference was in English, there were no articles that were just right, so I decided to write this article with the feeling that &amp;ldquo;I do not want other people to stumbl here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[No venv required] The strongest Python development environment created with Remote Containers [VS Code/Docker]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/no-venv-required-the-strongest-python-development-environment-created-with-remote-containers-vs-code-docker-1fc39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/no-venv-required-the-strongest-python-development-environment-created-with-remote-containers-vs-code-docker-1fc39/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python has been attracting attention because it shines in the top 1 popular languages 1 and becomes a test subject for the IPA Basic Information Engineer Exam 2.
But wait a minute! Are you able to benefit from the Python ecosystem and develop properly?
By creating a good development environment, not only can the development be made more efficient by input interpolation and formatters , but also unexpected problems can be prevented by static analysis, ① Easy ② Explosion speed ③ You can write programs safely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaggle&#39;s feature management was better than I thought with PostgreSQL, so I made a directory that anyone can use with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggles-feature-management-was-better-than-i-thought-with-postgresql-so-i-made-a-directory-that-anyone-can-use-with-docker-44814/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggles-feature-management-was-better-than-i-thought-with-postgresql-so-i-made-a-directory-that-anyone-can-use-with-docker-44814/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 19th day of [Kaggle Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/kaggle).  Hi, my name is kiccho1101! Writing an article for the first time in my life! Thank you!
Introduction This time, I tried to use Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s feature quantity management with PostgreSQL, but it was faster than I thought, so I would like to introduce it.
The created directory is here: https://github.com/kiccho1101/datascience-template ↑ The README has a usage example using the data of Titanic competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The story that the guards were confined when the laboratory became IoT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-story-that-the-guards-were-confined-when-the-laboratory-became-iot-b623c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-story-that-the-guards-were-confined-when-the-laboratory-became-iot-b623c/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 20th day of Retty Advent Calendar 2019.  Yesterday, Mr. Hirano&amp;rsquo;s “Retty Data Analysis Team-Review of the 2nd year after launch ~Data platform/data democratization/statistical model~”.
Nice to meet you. My name is Koda and I&amp;rsquo;m currently an intern at Retty as a 20-year-old engineer.
For the time being, I was wondering what to write after registering for participation, but I made my own entry/exit management system (electronic lock) that is used in the laboratory of the university I am attending, so I will talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Nginx &#43; uWSGI &#43; Python (Django) environment with docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-nginx-uwsgi-python-django-environment-with-docker-7d72d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-nginx-uwsgi-python-django-environment-with-docker-7d72d/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 16th day of [Web Crew Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/webcrew).  Yesterday was @Hideto-Kiyoshima-wc&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Scala Option/Either/Try Super.
#Introduction My name is @yagiyuuuu, my second year since joining Web Crew Co., Ltd. with a fresh graduate. Currently, I am developing an application environment of Nginx + uWSGI + Python (Django) using Docker. I&amp;rsquo;ve written this article in the hope that it will help anyone developing apps with Django.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I touched Apache Kafka</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-touched-apache-kafka-2a8ef/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-touched-apache-kafka-2a8ef/</guid>
      <description>This is the 15th day of MDC Advent Calendar 2019.  What is Kafka OSS distributed messaging system (messaging queue) created by LinkedIn. High throughput, high scalability. Written in Java (Scala).
It consists of three components: Producer, Broker, and Consumer. It relays the data streamed from Producer to Consumer. Data is also persisted due to obstacles. A delivery guarantee is also realized. · Producer: Deliver message · Broker: Passing messages from Producer to Consumer · Consumer: Receive message</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping a dynamic site with Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/scraping-a-dynamic-site-with-docker-6cc97/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/scraping-a-dynamic-site-with-docker-6cc97/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is the 13th day article from Kinki University Advent Calendar 2019.
First of all, note that scraping is basically the last method you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t do if you don&amp;rsquo;t need it. This time, scraping Qiita&amp;rsquo;s tag ranking, Qiita has an api and gets tag ranking there. There was no api to do (as of December 8, 2019) so I scraped it. If you can get the information you want with api, get it with api.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve PyTorch execution environment with Docker November 2019</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/improve-pytorch-execution-environment-with-docker-november-2019-a451c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/improve-pytorch-execution-environment-with-docker-november-2019-a451c/</guid>
      <description>## Overview   Develop a deep learning execution environment with PyTorch in a Docker container After Docker version 19.03, if you have the GPU driver of the host OS and nvidia-container-runtime, everything else will be locked in a container In most cases, you can reproduce the environment with one command  Preparation The following preparations are required.
 docker version 19.03 or later -See Official Documentation(thislinkisforUbuntu) nvidia-container-runtime -Install by referring to README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solving the frequent Fernet Key cryptography error for containerized Apache-Airflow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/solving-the-frequent-fernet-key-cryptography-error-for-containerized-apache-airflow-068a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/solving-the-frequent-fernet-key-cryptography-error-for-containerized-apache-airflow-068a2/</guid>
      <description>![AirflowLogo.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/538885/a8895a6d-3950-c59f-420f-68f2b4e51a69.png)  The Issue For security purposes, sensitive connection and administrative information is encrypted with a Fernet key before being stored in Airflow&amp;rsquo;s backend database. This includes any passwords for your connection objects as well as service account keys for e.g. Google Cloud.
However, if you have built Airflow webserver as a containerized service, then every time you modify and rebuild your container you run the risk of invalidating your Fernet key and losing access to your connections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Explanation with image] Use pickle with Kaggle NoteBook</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/explanation-with-image-use-pickle-with-kaggle-notebook-7badc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/explanation-with-image-use-pickle-with-kaggle-notebook-7badc/</guid>
      <description># things to do   Pickle data set of csv file Load the pickle file into another notebook  What is # pickle? A python object that saves binary data https://docs.python.org/ja/3/library/pickle.html
What are you happy about? Read quickly It&amp;rsquo;s binary data, so parsing is fast. You can also use learned models as pickles
This verification article is wonderful Python: I checked the persistence format of pandas
Try with Titanic data Let&amp;rsquo;s make train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Until the infrastructure engineer builds GitLab and makes CI/CD work</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/until-the-infrastructure-engineer-builds-gitlab-and-makes-ci-cd-work-6ec0f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/until-the-infrastructure-engineer-builds-gitlab-and-makes-ci-cd-work-6ec0f/</guid>
      <description># Background  Since joining the company as an infrastructure engineer and working on AWS projects, I have been writing more Python for CloudFormation and Lambda. The name of Git/GitHub/GitLab was at a level I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about, but the version control mentioned above is mandatory, and you will be using your own GitLab. Although I was an amateur, I immediately felt the convenience, and I thought that it would be better if I could establish GitLab after studying Docker on ESXi at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF beginner tried building a problem server (web) [problem]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ctf-beginner-tried-building-a-problem-server-web-problem-a1830/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ctf-beginner-tried-building-a-problem-server-web-problem-a1830/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Do you know CTF (Capture The Flag)? Through the CTF, you can experience and learn about security issues. If so, I will try to explain the problem by making a vulnerable server myself. I have created a server for CTF rudimentary problems.
important point By nature, the server is vulnerable, so Please do not implement the contents of this article as it is in a production environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Kaggle API inside Docker container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</guid>
      <description># things to do   Start container using Kaggle official image (kaggle/python) Download csv file with kaggle ~ command Download public notebook with kaggle ~ command  First summary  DL kaggle.json (kaggle.com &amp;gt;My Account &amp;gt;Create New API Token button) 2.$ docker run -it --rm --mount type=bind,src=pwd,dst=/root/dev kaggle/python $ pip install kaggle $ mkdir ~/.kaggle $ cp /root/dev/kaggle.json ~/.kaggle 6.$ chmod 600 ~/.kaggle/kaggle.json $ kaggle competitions download -c titanic -p input/titanic $ unzip input/titanic/titanic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Django in 3 minutes using docker-compose</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deploy-django-in-3-minutes-using-docker-compose-d3a56/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deploy-django-in-3-minutes-using-docker-compose-d3a56/</guid>
      <description>I have created docker-compose in a form that can be used even for projects that have already been created, so I will summarize the specifications in an article.  ** Please see How to Use on GitHub → GitHub**
(I&amp;rsquo;m sorry if you change the DB from the default sqlite&amp;hellip;
The deployment environment is Django＋Nginx＋Gunicorn.
Overview Please refer to the README on GitHub for how to use the link provided above.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>