<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> electronic work on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/electronic-work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  electronic work on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/electronic-work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a washing and drying timer using RaspberryPi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/make-a-washing-and-drying-timer-using-raspberrypi-b61d4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/make-a-washing-and-drying-timer-using-raspberrypi-b61d4/</guid>
      <description>Make a washing and drying timer using # RaspberryPi  Introduction (purpose of production)  Because I work for a company, I am often absent during the day, and I can not take in the laundry when it rains. For this reason, laundry is basically dried indoors. However, since the clothes drying room is not sunny and the drying does not proceed as expected in winter, the timing of taking in may be missed, and the laundry accumulates in a snow dharma fashion, creating a vicious cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I couldn&#39;t escape from the futon, so I made a fully automatic futon peeler.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-couldnt-escape-from-the-futon-so-i-made-a-fully-automatic-futon-peeler.-bef57/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-couldnt-escape-from-the-futon-so-i-made-a-fully-automatic-futon-peeler.-bef57/</guid>
      <description># Overview  It is known that escaping from the futon by itself on a cold winter morning is accompanied by a great deal of mental distress, and a decline in activity in the morning in the winter brings a great loss to the Japanese economy. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is the case, but for the time being, if I leave home early in the morning, my graduation will be jeopardized, so I decided to take measures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>