<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> seaborn on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/seaborn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  seaborn on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/seaborn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous visualization of data and understanding of correlation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simultaneous-visualization-of-data-and-understanding-of-correlation-649cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simultaneous-visualization-of-data-and-understanding-of-correlation-649cf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When analyzing data, I think you will visualize the data using graphs. At that time, it would be convenient if the statistics showing the correlation between two variables could be displayed at the same time. Therefore, we made it possible to display the appropriate statistics on the appropriate graph according to the content of the variable (category or numerical value).
Review so far I will summarize the appropriate graphing methods by content of variables and the statistics that show the correlation, which have been described so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Calendar-type heat map (with holiday display)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-calendar-type-heat-map-with-holiday-display-06a80/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-calendar-type-heat-map-with-holiday-display-06a80/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article  Create a heat map in calendar format with holidays as shown below.
By the way, in the data, the post date of @yaotti&amp;rsquo;s post acquired using Qiita API is used as 1 post = 1 event.
Similar visualization method  Contributions Calendar Contribution Graph Grass grass  Although it is called with various names, the following figure on GitHub is also simple and good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of basic drawing method of Plotly Express, the de facto standard of Python drawing library in the Reiwa era</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-basic-drawing-method-of-plotly-express-the-de-facto-standard-of-python-drawing-library-in-the-reiwa-era-d8cbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-basic-drawing-method-of-plotly-express-the-de-facto-standard-of-python-drawing-library-in-the-reiwa-era-d8cbe/</guid>
      <description># at first  A library called Plotly Express (official site) that allows you to easily draw interactive operations based on javascript was released a while ago. I found. Since I felt a potential of a dimension that was clearly different from the static drawing that I have used so far, I have summarized the method of drawing a basic visualization method also as a memo. For reference, I am comparing it with the pattern that I wrote a similar figure in matplotlib+seaborn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>