<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Competition on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Competition on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Recommended competition sites for data scientists</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/bd7a6f9bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/bd7a6f9bb/</guid>
      <description>We have gathered competition sites to help career development of those who aim to be data scientists.  #Kaggle It is a famous site in the data scientist community. It is written as Kaggle and read as &amp;ldquo;Kaguru&amp;rdquo;. Data scientists from all over the world compete here every day. Google acquired it on March 8, 2017. I want to request an analysis Major companies are winning the prize money, and in the past, competitions were held by Mercari and Recruit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I participated in Kaggle&#39;s NFL competition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/cf01bf10f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/cf01bf10f/</guid>
      <description>## Competition overview   Held from October 10, 2019 to November 27, 2019 (https://www.kaggle.com/c/nfl-big-data-bowl-2020/ ) Predict the number of yards the attacker will advance in an American football run play  Available data  General information and player-specific information is given for each run play -General information: -Weather, temperature, wind speed, wind direction -Stadium, location, turf condition - Start time -Home/away score -Number of downs (attack ends after 4 times *1) -Number of yards required to continue the attack -Number of yards advanced ← Predict this -etc&amp;hellip; -Information by player *2 -NFL ID -Location information (X, Y) -Movement information (S: speed, A: acceleration) -Orientation (Dir: Body orientation, Orientation: Face orientation) - Birthday - height, weight -Home/away -Jersey number -Position -etc&amp;hellip;  *1: If you advance 10 yards or more within 4 downs, you will continue to attack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>