<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> chatbot on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/chatbot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  chatbot on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/chatbot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If not, let&#39;s create one, something like AWS Chatbot for Microsoft Teams</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-not-lets-create-one-something-like-aws-chatbot-for-microsoft-teams-239c9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-not-lets-create-one-something-like-aws-chatbot-for-microsoft-teams-239c9/</guid>
      <description>## What is AWS Chatbot  https://aws.amazon.com/jp/chatbot/
Roughly speaking, you can notify Slack and Amazon Chime of events that occurred on AWS, and operate with slash commands.
At the time of writing this article, it is a beta version, so 1.10 Beta of this document In accordance with Service Participation, we will not make any further reference.
background At the moment, it&amp;rsquo;s only for Slack and Amazon Chime, so we&amp;rsquo;re going to make something like AWS Chatbot for Microsoft Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a chatbot that supports free input with Word2Vec</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</guid>
      <description>This article is the first day article of [Zeals Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/zeals).  Nice to meet you. This is Tamaki, who will join Zeals from the next fiscal year. Zeals operates a chatbot technology called chat commerce. Also, I am currently researching natural language processing at university. There are conversations in which bots do not have natural language processing, but I thought it would be interesting to add natural language processing technology to them, so I decided to make this the subject of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>