<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> LSTM on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/lstm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  LSTM on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/lstm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Nikkei Prediction with Pytorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/nikkei-prediction-with-pytorch-c398a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/nikkei-prediction-with-pytorch-c398a/</guid>
      <description>I am a graduate student studying Pytorch recently.  I started studying neural networks by dreaming about stock price forecasts and horse racing forecasts.
At last, it is in shape, so I will write it as a memorandum. I hope it will be helpful for a beginner like me.
References, cited articles and books Overview of LSTM network This is an article about the network structure and mechanism of LSTM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] College students who don&#39;t want to read English papers (python)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/college-students-who-dont-want-to-read-english-papers-python-dff79/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/college-students-who-dont-want-to-read-english-papers-python-dff79/</guid>
      <description># I want to read English papers easily! !! !!  Since I am not good at English and I can&amp;rsquo;t go on to learn more, I thought there would be a way to have fun. The idea I came up with would be something like a summary and translate that English sentence&amp;hellip;
Operation confirmation environment  Windows10 Powershell (even cmd is OK) Google Colaboratory Python 3.7.3  What is Colaboratory Colaboratory is a Jupyter notebook environment that runs entirely in the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to predict the deterioration of the lithium ion battery using Qore SDK</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-the-deterioration-of-the-lithium-ion-battery-using-qore-sdk-0066d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-the-deterioration-of-the-lithium-ion-battery-using-qore-sdk-0066d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hi everyone, this is kon2 :sunny::sunny: I am a student who usually studies negative electrode materials for lithium batteries at university.
Lithium-ion batteries are widely used in everyday life such as mobile phones and electric vehicles. Since you recently won the Nobel Prize, you often hear the name.
Although lithium-ion batteries have been in commercial use for more than 40 years, they are still an active research field, and the use of machine learning has recently been drawing attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I checked the output specification of PyTorch Bidirectional LSTM</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-checked-the-output-specification-of-pytorch-bidirectional-lstm-78a51/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-checked-the-output-specification-of-pytorch-bidirectional-lstm-78a51/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  As stated in LSTM Reference,whenhandlingBidirectionalLSTMwithPyTorch,whendeclaringLSTMIt&amp;rsquo;sOKtospecifybidirectional=Trueinthe,anditisveryeasytohandle(KerascanjustsurroundtheLSTMwithBidrectional). However, even if I look at the reference, I don&amp;rsquo;t think much about the output when LSTM is set to Bidirectional. I didn&amp;rsquo;t quite understand the output specifications of Bidirectional LSTM in PyTorch even after a quick google, so I will briefly summarize here.
#Reference
 Bidirectional recurrent neural networks Understanding Bidirectional RNN in PyTorch   Bidirectional LSTM output question in PyTorch Understanding LSTM-along with recent trends  Specification check As you can see from References 1 and 2, you can see that the bidirectional RNN and LSTM are simple because the front and rear RNNs and LSTMs overlap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Sine curve estimation with self-made deep learning module (python) &#43; LSTM</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/sine-curve-estimation-with-self-made-deep-learning-module-python-lstm-ff31b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/sine-curve-estimation-with-self-made-deep-learning-module-python-lstm-ff31b/</guid>
      <description>2017.9.16 Added.  Recently I upgraded a little. https://github.com/uyuutosa/Optimizer_with_theano
Also, I made it possible to try neural style by copy and paste. http://qiita.com/uyuutosa/items/09557f2f99e77a1b9cc2 For reference only.
I made my own deep learning module in Python (on the way). For my own study. The name is Optimizer with no twist. We aim to establish a network with a small number of keystrokes. I use theano internally, but I think that Define by Run chainer is upward compatible, so May change to chainer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>