<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lambda on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/lambda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lambda on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/lambda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] When creating Lambda Layers, docker-lambda and yumda are convenient</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/when-creating-lambda-layers-docker-lambda-and-yumda-are-convenient-a6fd8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/when-creating-lambda-layers-docker-lambda-and-yumda-are-convenient-a6fd8/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  A layer corresponding to each runtime version can be created with the docker-lambda build image!
$ docker run --rm -v $(pwd):/var/task lambci/lambda:build-python3.8 \ &amp;gt; pip install -r requirements.txt -t python/lib/python3.8/site-packages/ Software packages that you want to run on AWS Lambda can be layered with yumda!
$ docker run --rm -v $(pwd)/git-layer:/lambda/opt lambci/yumda:2 yum install -y &amp;lt;package&amp;gt; Preparing the environment from scratch is quite difficult A common caveat with AWS Lambda and Lambda Layers is the handling of native binaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try automating Qiita&#39;s likes monitoring with Lambda&#43;DynamoDB&#43;CloudWatch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-automating-qiitas-likes-monitoring-with-lambda-dynamodb-cloudwatch-a545a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-automating-qiitas-likes-monitoring-with-lambda-dynamodb-cloudwatch-a545a/</guid>
      <description>This article is a relay of &amp;quot;[2020 New Year Advent Calendar TechConnect!](https://qiita.com/dgkz/items/5131349d56354b33ee97)&amp;quot;of[LinkInformationSystem](https://www.lis.co.jp/) This is an article.  TechConnect! is a self-starting advent calendar relayed by a self-made group called engineer.hanzomon. (From the link information system Facebook here)
This article is for Wednesday, January 15th on the 7th day.
 Past articleI&amp;rsquo;mdoingit,butitwaslikeapersoninchargeofcountingthenumberoflikesofouradcurry.(Ididnotwritetheadadarebeforethat,butIcollectitbyshellart) Well, if you want to automate it anyway, if you notify it like a Qiita milestone when the number exceeds a certain amount ~~ It will be fun ~~ I decided to let it run with AWS Lambda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [AWS SAM] Create API with DynamoDB&#43;Lambda&#43;API Gateway</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/aws-sam-create-api-with-dynamodb-lambda-api-gateway-119ec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/aws-sam-create-api-with-dynamodb-lambda-api-gateway-119ec/</guid>
      <description># Content  Build an API that fetches DynamoDB data with AWS SAM
In short, from a table like this&amp;hellip;
   group(Hash) name(Range)     group1 name1   group1 name2   group2 name3    I want to make it look like this.
curl https://hogehoge/Prod/dynamo-api/v1/?group=group1&amp;amp;name=name1 { &amp;#34;result&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;group1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;group&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;name1&amp;#34; } ] } #Environment
 macOS Mojave -10.14 python3.7.4 sam 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Notify the chat of new articles of Qiita Organization to improve learning efficiency of the organization!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/notify-the-chat-of-new-articles-of-qiita-organization-to-improve-learning-efficiency-of-the-organization-fbebd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/notify-the-chat-of-new-articles-of-qiita-organization-to-improve-learning-efficiency-of-the-organization-fbebd/</guid>
      <description>We are promoting the output activity of Qiita articles in-house. It&#39;s G-awa. The learning method using output is highly recommended and is highly recommended. However, on the other hand, it is difficult for one person to continue alone, so it is important for the team and organization to support each other. If you are alone, you tend to break your heart.  &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-b_wxsoyflcs/WZP38JpI0LI/AAAAABGDA/troMJOw1KGUpq7yueRTgIdPc85o_kexXQCLcBGAs/s400/tamashii_nukeru_man.png&amp;rdquo; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; //2.bp.blogspot.com/-aIs9YKfGlEk/Vy2v2rXYgjI/AAAAAAAA6b0/PuaALahZfJsIluEeFOKgfgOy43qrc8bBQCLcB/s450/enjin_circle_wakamono.png&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;40%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;
I read yesterday&amp;rsquo;s article and it was very helpful :thumbsup: It&amp;rsquo;s a great environment for engineers to grow when there is an environment in which they can encourage each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The first step to get rid of slow queries! I tried to notify Chatwork of a slow query of RDS for MySQL using Lambda and AWS CLI v2</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-first-step-to-get-rid-of-slow-queries-i-tried-to-notify-chatwork-of-a-slow-query-of-rds-for-mysql-using-lambda-and-aws-cli-v2-4f370/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-first-step-to-get-rid-of-slow-queries-i-tried-to-notify-chatwork-of-a-slow-query-of-rds-for-mysql-using-lambda-and-aws-cli-v2-4f370/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hello. I am in charge of infrastructure at Mikatus Co., Ltd., and I am in charge of infrastructure construction, operation and maintenance centering on AWS. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll write about the case where the slow query of MySQL is notified to Chatwork.
Our system uses Amazon RDS for MySQL, and we used a monitoring tool to monitor the occurrence status for slow queries, but Chatwork will be able to make continuous improvements by sending notifications in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A story of making an anonymous channel with Slack from zero knowledge</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-of-making-an-anonymous-channel-with-slack-from-zero-knowledge-85611/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-of-making-an-anonymous-channel-with-slack-from-zero-knowledge-85611/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  A memorandum when I struggled to create an anonymous channel on Slack without any knowledge of AWS, Lambda, or Python.
#Trigger When I was thinking that I had to write something on Qiita after being invited by the Advent Calendar
 Talk about creating a VIP channel for in-house slack https://qiita.com/peisuke/items/80984db8b47cd8243019  After reading this article, this looks interesting! I would like to introduce it to Slack where I participate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Rewriting Lambda to restart Workspaces of UNHEALTHY with python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/rewriting-lambda-to-restart-workspaces-of-unhealthy-with-python-f7ffa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/rewriting-lambda-to-restart-workspaces-of-unhealthy-with-python-f7ffa/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll do Hands Lab Advent Calendar this year as well  Overview We use Workspaces, a service that provides virtual desktops for AWS, Sometimes it’s unhealthy
\ Broken without doing anything /
Most of the time, it is possible to manage by restarting due to a temporary load drop. So there is Lambda that restarts for the time being It&amp;rsquo;s written in Node.js, so it supports frequent version upgrades&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s simple code, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d rewrite it to python anyway</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s create a web chat using WebSocket with AWS serverless (Python)!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-create-a-web-chat-using-websocket-with-aws-serverless-python-d8095/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-create-a-web-chat-using-websocket-with-aws-serverless-python-d8095/</guid>
      <description>This article is the second day of NTT Technocross [Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/ntt-tx).  Hello. My name is Yasuda. I am in charge of new AI-related product development at NTT Technocross. It&amp;rsquo;s a gap from the main subject immediately, but drawing a manga is a recent break, and I&amp;rsquo;m drawing the following manga.
Data link understood by manga Enterprise architecture in the AI era understood with manga IT strategy understood by manga &amp;hellip; Well, in this article, I&amp;rsquo;d like to see how to do &amp;ldquo;WebSocket&amp;rdquo; without AWS server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try AWS Lambda Destinations</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-aws-lambda-destinations-efcb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-aws-lambda-destinations-efcb2/</guid>
      <description>AWS has announced a great feature.  Introducing AWS Lambda Destinations https://aws.amazon.com/jp/blogs/compute/introducing-aws-lambda-destinations/
![Screenshot 2019-11-27 6.51.44.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/102769/8dcc8bb4-f376-17ae-1ccf-(b64739c3289b.png)
The following actions (AWS services) can be specified according to the execution result of Lambda. If you want to control the flow with success / failure conditions, you can now complete it only with Lambda without using Step Functions.
Try immediately.
Define the calling Lambda appropriately Write Python like this. (Using Python 3.7)
import json import logging logger = logging.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>