<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>40-32/2=4!</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/40-32-24-fe791/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/40-32-24-fe791/</guid>
      <description>I think I saw it about 10 years ago...  Let&amp;rsquo;s verify this as the subject.
Brute force First of all, it will be exhausted by brain death. You will have the following loop.
from math import factorial for a in range(1,100): for b in range(1,a): for c in range(1,100): if (a-b)%c != 0: continue d = int((a-b)/c) if a-b/c == factorial(d): print(&amp;#34;{}-{}/{}={}!&amp;#34;.format(a,b,c,d)) Output.
2-1/1=1! 3-1/1=2! 3-2/1=1! 4-2/1=2! 4-3/1=1! 5-3/1=2! 5-4/1=1!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect date displayed in matplotlib.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/incorrect-date-displayed-in-matplotlib.-fed85/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/incorrect-date-displayed-in-matplotlib.-fed85/</guid>
      <description>#1 Description of this article  When a time series graph is drawn using Python&amp;rsquo;s plot, date conversion does not work properly. For example, 2020-01-01 is displayed incorrectly as 0051-01-01.
#2 Code showing incorrect date on horizontal axis For the data frame generated by Pandas, display the graph with the command &amp;ldquo;data frame.plot(&amp;hellip;・)&amp;rdquo;, and in &amp;ldquo;mdates.DateFormatter(&#39;%Y-%m-%d&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo;, select &amp;ldquo;Format YMD.&amp;rdquo; I found that the date is not displayed correctly when I set it to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story that update of calendar.day_abbr fails on admin screen of django</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/story-that-update-of-calendar.day_abbr-fails-on-admin-screen-of-django-fcfc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/story-that-update-of-calendar.day_abbr-fails-on-admin-screen-of-django-fcfc2/</guid>
      <description># I can no longer add or update models from the admin screen of django  Although the screen can be displayed and operated, the following exception occurs when the update button is pressed.
&amp;quot;AttributeError:&#39;calendar&#39; object has no attribute&#39;day_abbr&#39;&amp;quot; #Cause of application name calendar
The bottom line is that there was an application named calendar.
This seems to have failed because it caused batting with the existing calendar.
I know if it fails with the class name, but I did not anticipate the failure with the application name, so it took a while to find out the cause&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Automation] Read mail (msg file) with Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/automation-read-mail-msg-file-with-python-fa0cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/automation-read-mail-msg-file-with-python-fa0cf/</guid>
      <description>In a previous article, I showed you how to load folder and email information from Outlook.  Read Outlook emails with Python https://qiita.com/konitech913/items/8a285522b0c118d5f905
Even without doing so, I think there are cases where you want to read individual mail data (msg file) and read the information in the mail.
For example, you may want to save an &amp;ldquo;inquiry email&amp;rdquo; as a msg file in a folder on your PC and extract the information from that file and copy it to Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django 5 Beginners Make Simple Apps</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/django-5-beginners-make-simple-apps-fc6b0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/django-5-beginners-make-simple-apps-fc6b0/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Django A continuation of 4 for beginners to create simple apps. The purpose is to remove complicated things and troublesome things as much as possible, create a simplified web application, and learn the mechanism of Django. Only understand what is connected and how it moves around the backend. Implement CRUD (Create, Read, Update, Delete) as you go, and score if you move safely. Last time I rewrote Class-based-view into Function-view and compared how the two compare to track how Django works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Format when to_csv with pandas</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-format-when-to_csv-with-pandas-f9102/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-format-when-to_csv-with-pandas-f9102/</guid>
      <description>I googled the same thing over and over again, so make a note of it yourself. Used when storing data in pandas and saving to a file as to_csv. It is used when you want to make the format nice to publish and want to arrange the number of digits.  Format the float  To specify the whole float, you can set the argument of to_csv as float_format=&amp;quot;%10.4f&amp;quot; You can use round().</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a lightweight FastAPI development environment using Docker</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/build-a-lightweight-fastapi-development-environment-using-docker-fcd38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/build-a-lightweight-fastapi-development-environment-using-docker-fcd38/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I often use FastAPI recently, and I wanted to quickly build it with Docker and dispose of it. As a memo, I&amp;rsquo;d like to leave a lightweight construction method.
Preparation  Environment that can use Docker and Docker Compose  $ docker --version Docker version 19.03.8, build afacb8b7f0  The file structure looks like this  . ├── Dockerfile ├── docker-compose.yml ├── main.py └── requirements.txt Source You can clone from here https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An introduction to class platform GUI software made with Python/Tkinter! (and many Try and Error)! (during writing)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/an-introduction-to-class-platform-gui-software-made-with-python-tkinter-and-many-try-and-error-during-writing-fd22b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/an-introduction-to-class-platform-gui-software-made-with-python-tkinter-and-many-try-and-error-during-writing-fd22b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction...  The title is long and Sumimasen!!!!! It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to summarize what you want to write&amp;hellip; Someone please give me a summary&amp;hellip; (By the way, it will be long after this. Please use the table of contents.) Also, please be aware that it is being written.
What is #Python/Tkinter?
Source: Free encyclopedia &amp;quot;Wikipedia&amp;quot; Tkinter is a standard library (widget toolkit) for building and operating GUI from Python. The Tk part of Tcl/Tk is made available to Python, and the usage is designed to match Tcl/Tk as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CUM_plot often seen at the manufacturing site did not fall on the net, so I made it with python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/cum_plot-often-seen-at-the-manufacturing-site-did-not-fall-on-the-net-so-i-made-it-with-python-fa323/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/cum_plot-often-seen-at-the-manufacturing-site-did-not-fall-on-the-net-so-i-made-it-with-python-fa323/</guid>
      <description>0. In the beginning  ============ CUM_plot is often used when performing failure analysis at the production site. If it is a normal distribution, it becomes a straight line, and it is easy to understand whether it is an outlier or a mixture of multiple normal distributions. When I suddenly want to create it with python, the CUM in Figure 1 comes out, but the CUM in Figure 2 does not come out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 095 Review</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-095-review-fe2c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-095-review-fe2c6/</guid>
      <description>#Time required  #Impression
I was regrettable that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve problem D before, but I was relieved because I could solve it this time. I think that more speed will be required in the future, so I will try to acquire the typical ideas firmly.
#A problem
The number of toppings corresponds to the number of ○, so you can count and output.
s=input() print(700+s.count(&amp;#34;o&amp;#34;)*100) #B Problem
It is problem B, but it requires a little attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCC: coding crash course (4) Histogram of numbers appearing in pi 3.141562....</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/ccc-coding-crash-course-4-histogram-of-numbers-appearing-in-pi-3.141562....-f8747/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/ccc-coding-crash-course-4-histogram-of-numbers-appearing-in-pi-3.141562....-f8747/</guid>
      <description># 3.141562.... frequency distribution of numbers  Make a histogram of the numbers that appear after the decimal point of the pi.
Try it out for beginners, not for efficiency.
First, obtain the decimal point of PI at http://www.eveandersson.com/pi/digits/pi-digits?n_decimals_to_display=500&amp;amp;breakpoint=500.
char_pi = &amp;#34;14159265358979323846264338327950288419716939937510582097494459230781640628620899862803482534211706798214808651328230664709384460955058223172535940812848111745028410270193852110555964462294895493038196442881097566593344612847564823378678316527120190914564856692346034861045432664821339360726024914127372458700660631558817488152092096282925409171536436789259036001133053054882046652138414695194151160943305727036575959195309218611738193261179310511854807446237996274956735188575272489122793818301194912&amp;#34; For example, to check the number of occurrences of &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rdquo;:
count_0 = 0 for i in range(500): s = char_pi[i] if (s == &amp;#34;0&amp;#34;): count_0 = count_0 +1 print( count_0) Similarly, you can find out how many times each number appears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✨ Easy with Python ☆ Estimated elapsed time after death ✨</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/easy-with-python-estimated-elapsed-time-after-death-f89d4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/easy-with-python-estimated-elapsed-time-after-death-f89d4/</guid>
      <description># What if there was a corpse in front of you?  (quoted;DetectiveConan&amp;quot;SweetColdCourier&amp;rdquo;) When Conan finds his body, he thinks about the post-mortem time at the very beginning, right? If you know the estimated time of death, you can narrow down the suspects greatly (^o^)/ Therefore, this time we will introduce how to obtain more details about the elapsed time after death!
#Example There was a man&amp;rsquo;s body in a refrigerated car set at room temperature of 16°C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is your Tanimoto coefficient?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-your-tanimoto-coefficient-fac29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-your-tanimoto-coefficient-fac29/</guid>
      <description>A famous index for talking about compound similarities is the &amp;quot;Tanimoto coefficient.&amp;quot; However, there are quite a few people who just say &amp;quot;Tanimoto coefficient&amp;quot;, and there is a good chance to writhe, &amp;quot;Isn&#39;t that enough explanation?&amp;quot;  For example, use the following compound set The number of compounds is 10.
smiles = [ &amp;#39;C1=CC=C2C3CC(CNC3)CN2C1=O&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;CN1c2c(C(N(C)C1=O)=O)[nH0](CC(CO)O)c[nH0]2&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;CN1C2CC(CC1C1C2O1)OC(C(c1ccccc1)CO)=O&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;CN1C2CC(CC1C1C2O1)OC(C(c1cccnc1)CO)=O&amp;#39;, # Similar to the compound above &amp;#39;CN(C=1C(=O)N(c2ccccc2)N(C1C)C)C&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;CN(C=1C(=O)N(C2CCCCC2)N(C1C)C)C&amp;#39;, # Similar to the compound above &amp;#39;OCC1C(C(C(C(OCC2C(C(C(C(OC(c3ccccc3)C#N)O2)O)O)O)O1)O)O)O&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;OCc1ccccc1OC1C(C(C(C(CO)O1)O)O)O&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;OCc1cc(N)ccc1OC1C(C(C(C(CO)O1)O)O)O&amp;#39;, # Similar to the compound above &amp;#39;[nH0]1c(OC)c2c([nH0]cc[nH0]2)[nH0]c1&amp;#39;, ] Generate compounds with RDKit from #SMILES notation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Excel VBA macro from Python using xlwings</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/call-excel-vba-macro-from-python-using-xlwings-fa273/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/call-excel-vba-macro-from-python-using-xlwings-fa273/</guid>
      <description>As a practical use of xlwings UDF, I will explain how to call Excel VBA macro from Python. For those who wonder &amp;quot;what is xlwings?&amp;quot;, I have posted the following from installation of Python to basic usage of xlwings UDF, so please see that.  Introduction to Python for VBA users -Calling Python from Excel with xlwings-
1. Background Even if we started to make in-house EUC tools in Python aiming to get rid of Excel VBA, I think that there are a ton of Excel VBA tools made by our predecessors in-house, and that we also have to use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python3] Understand the basics of file operations</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python3-understand-the-basics-of-file-operations-ff5f2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python3-understand-the-basics-of-file-operations-ff5f2/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I will summarize the basic knowledge to operate files with Python.
Target: For those who have started learning Python Operating environment: Python3.8.3 (OS is MacOS)
Read and write files Open file open method  Specify the file to open and how to open (read/write). File object is returned. After manipulating the file, it is necessary to execute the close method (to release it from memory).  f = open(&amp;#34;filename&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;mode&amp;#34;)  &amp;ldquo;mode&amp;rdquo; type  |mode | Description | |:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;|:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;| |r | Read mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implement a simple application in Python full scratch without using a web framework.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/implement-a-simple-application-in-python-full-scratch-without-using-a-web-framework.-fc0f3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/implement-a-simple-application-in-python-full-scratch-without-using-a-web-framework.-fc0f3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It&amp;rsquo;s now possible to easily develop web apps using web frameworks such as Django and Flask, but even if you only understand how to use the framework without understanding the roots, it is essentially meaningless. , I decided to understand the mechanism by implementing a simple blog application using only python&amp;rsquo;s built-in functions and standard library without using the web framework.
#Create index page Since the web server returns (displays) something by accessing it from the web browser, the index page to be displayed first is created in html.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leet Code Day 35 160. Intersection of Two Linked Lists</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-35-160.-intersection-of-two-linked-lists-f9c01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-35-160.-intersection-of-two-linked-lists-f9c01/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  It seems that a coding test is conducted in an engineer&amp;rsquo;s interview overseas, and in many cases, the main thing is to implement a specific function or class according to the subject.
As a countermeasure, it seems that the site called Leet Code will be implemented.
A site that trains the algorithm power to withstand the coding tests that are being conducted in the early days.
I think it is better to have at least as much algorithmic power as an impatient person, so I think that I will occasionally solve the problem and write down the method I thought at that time in a memo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language : ChatBot Part1 - Twitter API Corpus</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/natural-language-chatbot-part1-twitter-api-corpus-fc09c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/natural-language-chatbot-part1-twitter-api-corpus-fc09c/</guid>
      <description>#Target  I have summarized a chatbot using the Microsoft Cognitive Toolkit (CNTK).
Part 1 prepares you for training your chatbot with the Microsoft Cognitive Toolkit.
We will introduce them in the following order.
 Register Twitter Developer Collecting conversation datasets using Twitter API Pre-processing text data and creating Sentence Piece model Create a file to be read by the built-in reader provided by CNTK  #Introduction Assuming you have a Twitter account and Linux is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: Stock price forecast #1</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-stock-price-forecast-#1-fa781/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-stock-price-forecast-#1-fa781/</guid>
      <description>#Get tweets  Overview There are two methods for making investment decisions in stock investment: technical analysis and fundamentals analysis. This time we will deal with the technical analysis.
Predict the Nikkei Stock Average using Twitter. First, I will explain the general flow.
1, Get the past tweets of an account from Twitter using TwitterAPI. 2. Use the polar dictionary to analyze the sentiment of daily tweets. 3, Get the time series data of Nikkei 225.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register multiple self-made styles in Word at once</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/register-multiple-self-made-styles-in-word-at-once-f9320/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/register-multiple-self-made-styles-in-word-at-once-f9320/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s convenient, but it&#39;s easy to register Microsoft Word styles in python.  Execution image  Character style is distinguished by background color + underline type Paragraph styles are distinguished by background color + border color   The table is distinguished by the color of the outer border  code As I wrote in another article,Iusepywin32tolookatthecurrentlyopendocumentandprocessit(WordVBAconstantsarehereArticleetc.).
By default, a new style will be created based on &amp;ldquo;Formatting paragraph with cursor at runtime&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leet Code Day 33 1. Two Sum Starting from Zero</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-33-1.-two-sum-starting-from-zero-fed16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-33-1.-two-sum-starting-from-zero-fed16/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  It seems that a coding test is conducted in an engineer&amp;rsquo;s interview overseas, and in many cases, the main thing is to implement a specific function or class according to the subject.
As a countermeasure, it seems that the site called Leet Code will be implemented.
A site that trains the algorithm power to withstand the coding tests that are being conducted in the early days.
I think it is better to have at least as much algorithmic power as an impatient person, so I think that I will occasionally solve the problem and write down the method I thought at that time in a memo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use os.getenv to get environment variables in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/use-os.getenv-to-get-environment-variables-in-python-f8a10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/use-os.getenv-to-get-environment-variables-in-python-f8a10/</guid>
      <description>Up until now, this has been the point when it comes to getting environment variables in Python.  import os dsn = os.environ.get(&amp;#39;DATABASE_URL&amp;#39;) But recently I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that there is a method called os.getenv.
Reference: Difference between os.getenv and os.environ.get in Python-Qiita
Since os.getenv is equivalent to os.environ.get, the above code can be rewritten as follows.
from os import getenv dsn = getenv(&amp;#39;DATABASE_URL&amp;#39;) Officially, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem that either is recommended, but I think it&amp;rsquo;s better because os.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numpy 2-D matrix calculation and performance comparison with for</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/numpy-2-d-matrix-calculation-and-performance-comparison-with-for-fde10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/numpy-2-d-matrix-calculation-and-performance-comparison-with-for-fde10/</guid>
      <description>How does this article write the following two-dimensional matrix calculation in Python numpy? That is.  for i in range(0, ni-1): for j in range(0, nj-1): y[i, j] = x[i, j] + x[i+1, j]-x[i+1, j+1] * x[i, j+1] Later, we will compare the performance. The Python version is 3.7.4. You are using anaconda3-2019.10.
Preface COVID-19 + With the change of job, I decided to learn a new language because I had a lot of spare time as I was stuck in my home in Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to collect specific files scattered in each folder in one place</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-i-want-to-collect-specific-files-scattered-in-each-folder-in-one-place-fdef0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-i-want-to-collect-specific-files-scattered-in-each-folder-in-one-place-fdef0/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Qiita&amp;rsquo;s first post. I&amp;rsquo;ve always taken care of me, so I&amp;rsquo;m about to publish what I&amp;rsquo;ve finished.
I want to collect specific files scattered in each folder in one place Won&amp;rsquo;t this happen often? All Folders have the same folder structure, and I want to collect sleeping files (this time mdb files) in sub-sub-folder somewhere.
##Code execution I will forget it every time, so I will leave it below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning: Speed up Value Iteration</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/reinforcement-learning-speed-up-value-iteration-fe140/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/reinforcement-learning-speed-up-value-iteration-fe140/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In recent years, the field of model-free deep reinforcement learning has been actively studied due to the success of AlphaGo and DQN. These algorithms are one of the effective approaches when the state-action space is very large or when mathematical modeling of dynamics is difficult. However, in many of the problems encountered in reality, mathematical modeling of the environment is relatively easy, and the state-action space can be reduced by devising it in many cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Recognize characters from images with OpenCV and pyocr</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-recognize-characters-from-images-with-opencv-and-pyocr-f9a70/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-recognize-characters-from-images-with-opencv-and-pyocr-f9a70/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When I was looking for articles using Selenium, I found an article about automated sushi batting. The method basically looks like the following ・Continue entering all keys after starting the game ・After starting the game, take a screenshot and enter the character string obtained by OCR *Sushi Uchi cannot get the character string directly because the game screen is drawn on the Canvas element.
This time I tried simple image processing using OCR part and OpenCV as pre-processing #Advance preparation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read system environment variables with python-part 2</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/read-system-environment-variables-with-python-part-2-f83da/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/read-system-environment-variables-with-python-part-2-f83da/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Create a python program that acquires system environment variables by applying Reading system environment variables with python-Part 1.
Constitution  EnvironWrapper.py&amp;mdash;A python class that encapsulates system environment variables  import os class EnvironWrapper: &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; class:EnvironWrapper Overview: A class that holds startup parameters read from environment variables &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; # Environment variable defaultenv_context = { &amp;#34;SECRET_KEY&amp;#34; :&amp;#39;naishokey&amp;#39;, # SECRET_KEY &amp;#34;DEBUG_FLG&amp;#34; :&amp;#39;true&amp;#39;, # DEBUG_FLG &amp;#34;ALLOWED_HOSTS&amp;#34;: None, # ALLOWED_HOSTS } # Environment variable getenv_context = {} def __init__(self): &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; constructor read environment variables from os.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Causal reasoning using machine learning (arrangement of causal reasoning methods)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/causal-reasoning-using-machine-learning-arrangement-of-causal-reasoning-methods-fa213/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/causal-reasoning-using-machine-learning-arrangement-of-causal-reasoning-methods-fa213/</guid>
      <description># Causal reasoning using machine learning   A rough understanding and notes of when to use causal reasoning using machine learning methods that have been actively used in recent years (Memorandum) Basically, the current causal reasoning method is summarized as a flow chart.
 Introduction Causal reasoning is a series of statistical methods aimed at answering the cause of an outcome. Generally, statistical approaches such as regression analysis focus on quantifying how changes in X are related to changes in Y.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging Inkbird IBS-TH1 values with Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/logging-inkbird-ibs-th1-values-with-raspberry-pi-fcc16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/logging-inkbird-ibs-th1-values-with-raspberry-pi-fcc16/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the same as Omron Environmental Sensor (BAG type) article This article was conducted with the low-priced Inkbird IBS-TH1. The battery used for the mini used last time was bad, so I aimed to improve the endurance with this product using AAA batteries.
What is #Inkbird? It is a manufacturer in Shenzhen, China that makes various home IoT sensors. It is attractive that it has a complete set of functions such as data acquisition with smartphone apps and APIs at a low price (about 3000 yen).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notify LINE of TV appearance information of your favorite entertainer</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/notify-line-of-tv-appearance-information-of-your-favorite-entertainer-fef55/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/notify-line-of-tv-appearance-information-of-your-favorite-entertainer-fef55/</guid>
      <description>#Purpose  I miss watching my favorite idol and comedians appear on TV, so I decided to notify them via LINE. #Overview Yahoo! TV G Guide was used to obtain information on TV programs, and to notify using LINE Notify. I set the program to run on Raspberrypi every morning at 9am.
Acquisition of program information For example, in the case of a terrestrial program of &amp;ldquo;Chiaki Bimura&amp;rdquo; (Regional setting Tokyo), such a URL is used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Product Development Team Reading Party: [INSPIRED Product Management that Creates Enthusiastic Products]</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/ai-product-development-team-reading-party-inspired-product-management-that-creates-enthusiastic-products-fb315/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/ai-product-development-team-reading-party-inspired-product-management-that-creates-enthusiastic-products-fb315/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I will introduce the management method and contents of the reading event held by the &amp;quot;AI Product Development Team&amp;quot; that I lead.  The books targeted at this reading party are ** [INSPIRED Product management that creates enthusiastic products] ** https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/B0814STTHV/
is.
In Japanese, it is translated as &amp;ldquo;Product Management that creates enthusiasm products,&amp;rdquo; but in English How to Create Tech Products Customers Love is.
How to make a loved product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is very fast if you receive the Earthquake Early Warning with a strong motion monitor and handle it with JSON</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/it-is-very-fast-if-you-receive-the-earthquake-early-warning-with-a-strong-motion-monitor-and-handle-it-with-json-fc88b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/it-is-very-fast-if-you-receive-the-earthquake-early-warning-with-a-strong-motion-monitor-and-handle-it-with-json-fc88b/</guid>
      <description>## Overview   POST JSON to the Python web server from the Chrome extension &amp;ldquo;strong motion monitor&amp;rdquo; Cook the received JSON and throw it to Discord&amp;rsquo;s webhook, Slack, etc. (POST) Fast, cheap, delicious How fast it is, it is output to the channel of Discord at the moment when the breaking news is received on the strong motion monitor of the macbook  Assumptions  Operation has been confirmed with CentOS7 and Python3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Practical Beautiful Soup ~Scraping the triple odds table on the official website for boat racing~</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-practical-beautiful-soup-~scraping-the-triple-odds-table-on-the-official-website-for-boat-racing~-f8d80/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-practical-beautiful-soup-~scraping-the-triple-odds-table-on-the-official-website-for-boat-racing~-f8d80/</guid>
      <description># Purpose  Data collection is a pain. I thought that I would like to analyze boat racing in the future, so as a practice of data collection Odds table of official boat racing site.
Overview  I can only think of a convenient language = python for scraping, so I use python3.7. Python 3.7 is called beatutiful soup ~~ It seems a little erotic ~~ It seems that the library with the name is convenient for scraping By using the beautifulsoup css selector, you can specify the location of the table without deciphering the html one by one!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder JSC2019 Qual B sum and inverse of arithmetic sequence solved with Ruby and Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-jsc2019-qual-b-sum-and-inverse-of-arithmetic-sequence-solved-with-ruby-and-python-fc719/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-jsc2019-qual-b-sum-and-inverse-of-arithmetic-sequence-solved-with-ruby-and-python-fc719/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder JSC2019 Qual B-Kleene Inversion Difficulty: 797
The theme of this time, sum of arithmetic sequences + inverse element
Ruby For the first time, I&amp;rsquo;ll hear the number of falls, but let&amp;rsquo;s see what the number of falls is for the example 1 3 2.
   K 3 2 1 Total     132   1 1   132 132  4 1 5   132 132 132 7 4 1 12   One 1 3 2 is 1, two side by side 1 3 2 1 3 2 is 4 + 1, and three are 1 3 2 1 3 2 1 3 2 is 7 You can see that the sum is + 4 + 1 and the arithmetic progression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For beginners of SageMaker-Document link collection-</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/for-beginners-of-sagemaker-document-link-collection-fecb8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/for-beginners-of-sagemaker-document-link-collection-fecb8/</guid>
      <description>SageMaker, a machine learning management service of AWS, does not come out with pinpoint points, so I will summarize it.  Amazon SageMaker features When operating the ML system in the production environment, the managed function is really effective. A component for realizing MLops and MDLC. The true benefit cannot be obtained only by developing the PoC model.
Official reference Machine Learning Lens, AWS Well-Architected Framework https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/architecture/wellarchitected-Machine-Learning-Lens.pdf Guidelines for ML systems built on AWS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a Python development environment with Poetry</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/get-a-python-development-environment-with-poetry-ffb3a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/get-a-python-development-environment-with-poetry-ffb3a/</guid>
      <description>## background  Poetry reached 1.0.0 on December 12, 2019, so I tried it.
Overview Poetry is a packaging and dependency management tool for Python.
As a similar tool, There are setuptools and Pipenv, but Poetry one can cover both functions.
I am attracted to the point that &amp;ldquo;one toml file is all I need&amp;rdquo;. Or rather, I thought it was wonderful.
version poetry v1.0.5 (latest as of May 11, 2020)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implemented SIR model, a mathematical model for infectious diseases in OpenModelica (reflects mortality rate and reinfection rate)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/implemented-sir-model-a-mathematical-model-for-infectious-diseases-in-openmodelica-reflects-mortality-rate-and-reinfection-rate-fec14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/implemented-sir-model-a-mathematical-model-for-infectious-diseases-in-openmodelica-reflects-mortality-rate-and-reinfection-rate-fec14/</guid>
      <description># Add mortality and reinfection rates to the basic SIR model  Mortality rate and reinfection of the class cl_SIRbetaInput created in the previous article, &amp;ldquo;Implement the mathematical model of infectious disease &amp;ldquo;SIR model&amp;rdquo; with OpenModelica&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/nobby-n/items/48803407f67f62b2c8f9)&amp;quot; Let&amp;rsquo;s create a full version with a percentage added.
*Corrected because we found an error in the mortality formula in the first post.
   (Corrected on May 13, 2020) Revised again.    Prerequisites for this model</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[AWS] Data migration from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-data-migration-from-dynamodb-to-aurora-mysql-fe2f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-data-migration-from-dynamodb-to-aurora-mysql-fe2f9/</guid>
      <description>I have migrated data from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL, so I will write the method.  Please note that the data migration does not mean that all tables are migrated because we have migrated the data stored in one table.
Method I think there are several possible ways to migrate from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL, but I wrote the code in disposable (?) Python to make the transition quickly and reliably Even though it is disposable, there is a possibility that data may be migrated again, so we made it possible to reuse</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried morphological conversion of the image with Python &#43; OpenCV</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-morphological-conversion-of-the-image-with-python-opencv-f87cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-morphological-conversion-of-the-image-with-python-opencv-f87cc/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  With image processing, it is not always possible to prepare beautiful images. Images often contain noise. If there is noise, it may be removed using a method called &amp;ldquo;smoothing&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;morphological transformation&amp;rdquo;.
This time, we will use Python to perform morphological transformation of the image using OpenCV.
*For details on &amp;ldquo;smoothing&amp;rdquo;, refer to the following. I tried &amp;ldquo;smoothing&amp;rdquo; the image with Python + OpenCV
What is morphological conversion Morphological transformation is mainly the process of &amp;ldquo;shrink&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;expansion&amp;rdquo; for binary images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert string to list format one by one with python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/convert-string-to-list-format-one-by-one-with-python-fa37b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/convert-string-to-list-format-one-by-one-with-python-fa37b/</guid>
      <description># For a string  #Thing you want to do #&amp;#39;hello&amp;#39; ⇒ [&amp;#39;h&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;e&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;l&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;l&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;o&amp;#39;] a =&amp;#39;hello&amp;#39; print(list(a)) The execution result is as follows
[&amp;#39;h&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;e&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;l&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;l&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;o&amp;#39;] #For numbers
b = 123456789 print(list(str(b))) The execution result is as follows
[&amp;#39;1&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;2&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;3&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;4&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;5&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;6&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;7&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;8&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;9&amp;#39;] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leet Code Day 19 121. Best Time to Buy and Sell Stock</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-19-121.-best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-f89c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-19-121.-best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-f89c2/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  It seems that a coding test is conducted in an engineer&amp;rsquo;s interview overseas, and in many cases, the main thing is to implement a specific function or class according to the subject.
As a countermeasure, it seems that the site called Leet Code will be implemented.
A site that trains the algorithm power to withstand the coding tests that are being conducted in the early days.
I think it is better to have at least as much algorithmic power as an impatient person, so I think that I will occasionally solve the problem and write down the method I thought at that time in a memo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build wxPython on Ubuntu 20.04 on raspberry pi 4</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/build-wxpython-on-ubuntu-20.04-on-raspberry-pi-4-ffde9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/build-wxpython-on-ubuntu-20.04-on-raspberry-pi-4-ffde9/</guid>
      <description># Overview  When I tried to run a Python app on ubuntu 20.04 on raspberry pi 4, I was angry that there was no wx. When I wonder what wx is, it&amp;rsquo;s wxPython. So I installed wxPython.
What you did There is no corresponding package for pip itself, and the build from the source code of the wxPython main site did not work either.
[This site](https://krhb.hatenablog.com/entry/2019/04/30/234953#ImportError-No-module-named-wx%E3%81%AE%E3%82%A8%E3%83Themethodintroducedin(A9%E3%83%BC) was helpful.
Techniques introduced</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find intersection of circle and straight line (sympy matrix)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/find-intersection-of-circle-and-straight-line-sympy-matrix-f97e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/find-intersection-of-circle-and-straight-line-sympy-matrix-f97e3/</guid>
      <description>(Reference) Find the intersection of a circle and a straight line  https://qiita.com/tydesign/items/36b42465b3f5086bd0c5 (Reference) The intersection of a circle and a straight line in sympy https://qiita.com/mrrclb48z/items/2d5bd66507166913573b It&amp;rsquo;s a sequel. I feel like I can do it with one line. It&amp;rsquo;s a sequel.
Assign a value from the beginning # [Example] Find the intersection of the circle with center (3, 2) radius 5 and the line 3x+2y-16=0 from sympy import * var(&#39;x0 y0 r x1 y1 x2 y2 c s tx ty d sx sy&#39;) x0=3 y0=2 r=5 y1=0 v=solve([3*x1+2*y1-16]) x1=v[x1] x2=0 v=solve([3*x2+2*y2-16]) y2=v[y2] d=sqrt((x1-x2)**2+(y1-y2)**2) v=solve((c*0-s*0+tx-x1,s*0+c*0+ty-y1,c*ds*0+tx-x2,s*d+c*0+ty-y2 ],[c,s,tx,ty]) A=Matrix(( [v[c],-v[s],v[tx]], [v[s], v[c],v[ty]], [0, 0, 1] ]) B=Matrix(( [x0], [y0], [1] ]) AinvB=A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leet Code Day 17 169. Majority Element starting from scratch</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-17-169.-majority-element-starting-from-scratch-fac33/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-17-169.-majority-element-starting-from-scratch-fac33/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  It seems that a coding test is conducted in an engineer&amp;rsquo;s interview overseas, and in many cases, the main thing is to implement a specific function or class according to the subject.
As a countermeasure, it seems that the site called Leet Code will be implemented.
A site that trains the algorithm power to withstand the coding tests that are being conducted in the early days.
I think it is better to have at least as much algorithmic power as an impatient person, so I think that I will occasionally solve the problem and write down the method I thought at that time in a memo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTG forest drone business</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/mtg-forest-drone-business-ff0c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/mtg-forest-drone-business-ff0c2/</guid>
      <description># Why do you do drone business?  MTG Forest contributes to the fields of forestry and agriculture through machine learning.
For example
 Measure the degree of fruit growth with image authentication Identify the name of the animal Measure the number of trees in the mountain  So far, I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this with Python if I say it in a programming language. We also use machine learning, object recognition, and AI functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parametric Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/parametric-neural-network-fcc61/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/parametric-neural-network-fcc61/</guid>
      <description># About neural networks  Original flow  Pass the value of the activation function to the next node according to the input information Linearly combine all the received information based on weight $w$ and bias $b$. Input the linearly combined value to the activation function and pass the value to the next node Repeat steps 2 and 3 to output the value from the final node Compute the loss function from the final output (although the last layer has only one node in the PNN): steps 1-6 are forward propagation Next, calculate the weight at each branch using the loss function: back propagation One training is completed in steps 1-7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to build Django environment with Win10 WSL Ubuntu18.04 &#43; Anaconda &#43; Apache2</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/steps-to-build-django-environment-with-win10-wsl-ubuntu18.04-anaconda-apache2-f85f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/steps-to-build-django-environment-with-win10-wsl-ubuntu18.04-anaconda-apache2-f85f1/</guid>
      <description>I will summarize the procedure to create a development environment of Django + Apache on Ubuntu 18.04 of Windows 10 WSL  Procedure Allow apache2 to access python via mod_wsgi. Also, we will make VScode usable as a remote IDE that can be used with WSL.
 Install anaconda3 Install django Create a django project and migrate Install apache2 Install mod_wsgi Add to apache2 configuration file Enable vscode  Since WSL cannot use systemctl, the operation of apache changes a little, when using anaconda, you need to change the reference setting by yourself unless you install mod_wsgi with pip, it is hard to understand the setting of apache2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leet Code Day 14 “136. Single Number” Starting from Zero</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-14-136.-single-number-starting-from-zero-fd12c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-14-136.-single-number-starting-from-zero-fd12c/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  It seems that a coding test is conducted in an engineer&amp;rsquo;s interview overseas, and in many cases, the main thing is to implement a specific function or class according to the subject.
As a countermeasure, it seems that the site called Leet Code will be implemented.
A site that trains the algorithm power to withstand the coding tests that are being conducted in the early days.
I think it is better to have at least as much algorithmic power as an impatient person, so I think that I will occasionally solve the problem and write down the method I thought at that time in a memo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Difference between keras and tf.keras and compatibility verification #1</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/difference-between-keras-and-tf.keras-and-compatibility-verification-#1-fcfbf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/difference-between-keras-and-tf.keras-and-compatibility-verification-#1-fcfbf/</guid>
      <description>#Keras development end  It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I posted. As you can see on github, it seems that development of the multi-backend Keras ended in April 2020. It will be replaced by Keras in Tensorflow in the future. keras-team (For convenience, the multi-backend Keras is expressed as mb-keras, and the Tensorflow Keras is expressed as tf-keras.) I would like to compare and verify mb-keras and tf-keras in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s reproduce the math teaching tool Jamaica ❗️ vol.01 Memorandum for displaying images in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/lets-reproduce-the-math-teaching-tool-jamaica-%EF%B8%8F-vol.01-memorandum-for-displaying-images-in-python-fd0b4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/lets-reproduce-the-math-teaching-tool-jamaica-%EF%B8%8F-vol.01-memorandum-for-displaying-images-in-python-fd0b4/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This series is about Math teaching tool Jamaica It is a record struggling to achieve the following goals.
▶︎ 1. *** &amp;ldquo;Jamaica&amp;rdquo; game can be run by a program that uses image display. *** 2. *** Create a program that searches for and presents the existence of solutions and their contents for any combination of dice in Jamaica. ***
Q1. What is arithmetic tool &amp;quot;Jamaica&amp;quot;? A1. &amp;ldquo;Jamaica / Jamaica&amp;rdquo; is sold as a mathematics teaching tool based on &amp;ldquo;number play&amp;quot; using dice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Chapter 4] Introduction to Python with 100 knocks</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/chapter-4-introduction-to-python-with-100-knocks-fc4ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/chapter-4-introduction-to-python-with-100-knocks-fc4ad/</guid>
      <description>This article is a sequel to my book [Introduction to Python with 100 knocks](https://qiita.com/hi-asano/items/8e303425052781d95f09).[100knocksChapter4](https://nlp100.github.io/ja/ch04.html) will be explained.  First, install the morphological analyzer MeCab, download neko.txt, and perform morphological analysis to check the contents.
$ mecab &amp;lt;neko.txt&amp;gt; neko.txt.mecab It is &amp;ldquo;I am a cat&amp;rdquo; from Aozora Bunko.
MeCab&amp;rsquo;s default dictionary system is similar to school grammar, but adjective verbs are nouns + auxiliary verbs, and Sa verbs are nouns + verbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[pip3] ImportError occurs</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/pip3-importerror-occurs-fb0d0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/pip3-importerror-occurs-fb0d0/</guid>
      <description>An error occurs when executing the # `pip3` command.  ImportError: cannot import name&amp;rsquo;pkg_resources&amp;rsquo; from&amp;rsquo;pip._vendor&amp;rsquo;
Cause pkg_resources is not in the pip._vendor package
When I checked with the CLI whether the package actually existed, it was found to exist. And when I checked the location of the file, I found that it did not exist in the directory managed by pip.
 Confirm existence of file  Python 3.7.7 (default, Mar 10 2020, 15:43:33) [Clang 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 165 Review, E-question (Python)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-165-review-e-question-python-fd675/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-165-review-e-question-python-fd675/</guid>
      <description>This is a review article for beginners of competitive professionals.  The solution I write here is written while looking at the commentary and the submissions of other people. It may not be what you actually submitted.
A-We Love Golf It is a question to answer whether K is in the range from A to B inclusive.
From the constraint of $1\leq A \leq B \leq 1000$, $1\leq K \leq 1000$, it is no problem if you simply search for a value that satisfies the condition in the range from $A$ to $B$ .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For those who have installed janome properly with Python but get an error</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/for-those-who-have-installed-janome-properly-with-python-but-get-an-error-fc055/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/for-those-who-have-installed-janome-properly-with-python-but-get-an-error-fc055/</guid>
      <description>Janome, a python package for natural language processing.  pip install janome Then install it as usual and execute! When………
ModuleNotFoundError: No module named&amp;#39;janome.tokenizer&amp;#39;;&amp;#39;janome&amp;#39; is not a package Such an error. I installed it properly&amp;hellip;
To those who
Maybe you didn&amp;rsquo;t name the file with that code &amp;ldquo;janome.py&amp;rdquo;?
I just changed it to another letter and it worked without error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to set variables that can be used for the entire Django app ~ convenient for templates ~</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-set-variables-that-can-be-used-for-the-entire-django-app-~-convenient-for-templates-~-fda84/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-set-variables-that-can-be-used-for-the-entire-django-app-~-convenient-for-templates-~-fda84/</guid>
      <description>I think it is often useful to have constants (variables) that can be used throughout the site when creating apps with Django.  For example, the text that is displayed on the entire site, such as the app name and version.
Django uses the Context Processor to retrieve the constants you define. Of course, you can set more than one.
#Environment | Software | Version | |&amp;mdash;|&amp;mdash;| | Nginx | 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: unsupervised learning: non-hierarchical clustering</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-unsupervised-learning-non-hierarchical-clustering-f98bf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-unsupervised-learning-non-hierarchical-clustering-f98bf/</guid>
      <description># Clustering techniques  Hierarchical clustering Hierarchical clustering is to find the most similar combination in the data It is a method of making clusters in order, and is characterized by having a hierarchical structure during the process.
See the figure below for a concrete example. There are 5 data points A,B,C,D,E. The closest of these 5 data We will make one cluster.
A, B, C, D, E → (A,B), C,D,E In this case, the two points A and B are the closest points in this combination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a calculation drill print</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/make-a-calculation-drill-print-fd6c0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/make-a-calculation-drill-print-fd6c0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I made a calculation drill generation program to make a self-study print for elementary school lower grades. Randomly create mathematical formulas with python and convert to pdf with A4 paper size. Print the created file at home or at a convenience store, and if the child learns for himself, the purpose is achieved.
environment  Ubuntu 18.04 [Using WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux) on Windows 10] python3.6  Install ReportLab In order to print the generated formula, use the library for Report PDF, ReportLab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If you create a file with the same name as the imported module, an AttributeError will occur</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-if-you-create-a-file-with-the-same-name-as-the-imported-module-an-attributeerror-will-occur-fe18e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-if-you-create-a-file-with-the-same-name-as-the-imported-module-an-attributeerror-will-occur-fe18e/</guid>
      <description>I just wanted to check the operation of the library, but I fell in love with it unexpectedly.  For example, suppose you create a file called json.py to try out the json module.
import json obj = { &amp;#34;id&amp;#34; :1, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34; :&amp;#34;hoge&amp;#34;, } str = json.dumps(obj) print(str) The code looks fine, but&amp;hellip;
This gives an error when run.
$python3 json.py ... AttributeError: module&amp;#39;json&amp;#39; has no attribute&amp;#39;dumps&amp;#39; I have been told that the json module does not have dumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django URL settings</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/django-url-settings-fb9c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/django-url-settings-fb9c3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Here, we will explain the settings related to the URL of django.
Project urls.py settings First, edit urls.py under the project directory as follows.
from django.contrib import admin from django.urls import path, include urlpatterns = [ path(&#39;admin/&#39;, admin.site.urls), path(&#39;&#39;, include(&#39;application name.urls&#39;)), ] The place where it becomes admin/ shows the URL to the management screen. For other pages, we use include in the sense that it is described in urls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leet Code Day 6 “1342.Number of Steps to Reduce a Number to Zero”</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-6-1342.number-of-steps-to-reduce-a-number-to-zero-fb274/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/leet-code-day-6-1342.number-of-steps-to-reduce-a-number-to-zero-fb274/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  It seems that a coding test is conducted in an engineer&amp;rsquo;s interview overseas, and in many cases, the main thing is to implement a specific function or class according to the subject.
As a countermeasure, it seems that the site called Leet Code will be implemented.
A site that trains the algorithm power to withstand the coding tests that are being conducted in the early days.
I think it is better to have at least as much algorithmic power as an impatient person, so I think that I will occasionally solve the problem and write down the method I thought at that time in a memo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Basic - Pandas, Numpy -</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-basic-pandas-numpy-fc9e2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-basic-pandas-numpy-fc9e2/</guid>
      <description># 0. Introduction of Numpy  NumPy is a Python package. It stands for &amp;lsquo;Numerical Python&amp;rsquo;, and Numpy is a linear algebra library to work with dimensional arrays, which contains useful linear algebra routines and random number capabilities.
1. Numpy arrange() method The arange() method in the Numpy module in Python is used to generate linear sequence of numbers. If does it on the basis of the pre-provide starting and ending points along with a constant step size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use the company name recognition dictionary JCLdic for MeCab</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/use-the-company-name-recognition-dictionary-jcldic-for-mecab-fca1f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/use-the-company-name-recognition-dictionary-jcldic-for-mecab-fca1f/</guid>
      <description># About this article  This article introduces how to use the company name dictionary (JCLdic).
Dictionary introduction  &amp;ldquo;JCLdic&amp;rdquo; public page  JCLdic contains over 8 million company names and their aliases. It is a dictionary created to solve the problem that the coverage of company names is low in conventional dictionaries and it is difficult to recognize due to fluctuations in notation.
#Getting a dictionary
 JCLdic Download Page  Download JC_slim as an example and download MeCab Dic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does the last () of a function mean in Python?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-does-the-last-of-a-function-mean-in-python-fe293/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-does-the-last-of-a-function-mean-in-python-fe293/</guid>
      <description>(Because this is a question that I have had little experience with, there may be some inconvenience in asking the question... Please understand.)    Question content In Python, for example, rgs=linear_model.LinearRegression() Is the understanding that declares an object called rgs. What does the last () mean?
  Background
  from sklearn import linear_model rgs=linear_model.LinearRegression rgs.fit(train_X, train_Y) print(rgs.coef_) print(rgs.intercept_)
I wrote the following code and got the following error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command for current directory Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/command-for-current-directory-python-fa229/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/command-for-current-directory-python-fa229/</guid>
      <description>#Command for current directory  Since all os modules are used
 import os  Strike first.
  Get pathname of current directory
 path = os.getcwd() print(path)    Display folders and files in the current directory
 ls = os.listdir(os.getcwd()) print(ls)    Move directory
 os.chdir(&amp;quot;Desctop&amp;quot;) # This is all you need to move curdir = os.getcwd() print(curdir)    Get the directory name of the current directory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(WIP) Verify Bresenham&#39;s algorithm for drawing line segments</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/wip-verify-bresenhams-algorithm-for-drawing-line-segments-fc890/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/wip-verify-bresenhams-algorithm-for-drawing-line-segments-fc890/</guid>
      <description># Status  For now, up to drawing and proof by human power. Next, I would like to prove it with a theorem proof system such as TLA+ or Coq. By the way, the vertical position of MathJax is too misaligned, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Overview The Bresenham algorithm is an algorithm for drawing a line segment on a screen expressed in pixels. Pixel coordinates can only have integer values, so an approximation algorithm is needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&#39;t know the valueerror</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-dont-know-the-valueerror-f869f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-dont-know-the-valueerror-f869f/</guid>
      <description>raise ValueError(&#39;Unable to configure handler &#39;  ValueError: Unable to configure handler&amp;rsquo;mail_admins&amp;rsquo; How can I fix this error?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>python setup.py test code that uses multiprocess</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-setup.py-test-code-that-uses-multiprocess-f8229/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-setup.py-test-code-that-uses-multiprocess-f8229/</guid>
      <description># wrap up   Running unittest including multiprocess module in setup.py results in infinite loop Apparently it is a specification of the multiprocess module Temporarily rewrite &amp;ldquo;__main__&amp;rdquo; as a workaround  Premise In python it uses the &amp;ldquo;multiprocess&amp;rdquo; module to run functions in multiprocess.
The formula is easy to understand how to use and sample code. https://docs.python.org/ja/3/library/multiprocessing.html
Now look at the following code
from multiprocessing import Pool def f(x): return x*x def main(): with Pool(5) as p: print(p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>concurrent.futures</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/concurrent.futures-fd6e0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/concurrent.futures-fd6e0/</guid>
      <description>#processにする場合は、threadの部分をprocessに書き換えてください。  import concurrent.futures import logging import time logging.basicConfig(level=logging.DEBUG, format=&amp;#39;%(threadName)s: %(message)s&amp;#39;) def worker(x, y): logging.debug(&amp;#39;start&amp;#39;) r = x * y logging.debug(r) logging.debug(&amp;#39;end&amp;#39;) return r def main(): with concurrent.futures.ThreadPoolExecutor(max_workers=5) as executor: f1 = executor.submit(worker, 2, 5) f2 = executor.submit(worker, 2, 5) logging.debug(f1.result()) logging.debug(f2.result()) #下記でも同じ #args = [[2, 2], [5, 5]] #r = executor.map(worker, *args) #logging.debug(r) #logging.debug([i for i in r]) if __name__ == &amp;#39;__main__&amp;#39;: main() ThreadPoolExecutor-0_0: start ThreadPoolExecutor-0_0: 10 ThreadPoolExecutor-0_0: end ThreadPoolExecutor-0_0: start ThreadPoolExecutor-0_0: 10 ThreadPoolExecutor-0_0: end MainThread: 10 MainThread: 10 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hit the ISE ERS API with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/hit-the-ise-ers-api-with-powershell-ff856/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/hit-the-ise-ers-api-with-powershell-ff856/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  If you want to operate the API easily, I think that you often use cURL, Postman, HTTP Client provided in various programming languages, etc., but there are cases where such an environment cannot be prepared due to various restrictions. Is it not?
In this post, we will introduce the API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) as a minimum to operate the REST API with a Windows terminal (PowerShell).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to automatically send the new coronavirus literature to LINE with Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-automatically-send-the-new-coronavirus-literature-to-line-with-python-fcfe5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-automatically-send-the-new-coronavirus-literature-to-line-with-python-fcfe5/</guid>
      <description># Overview  In this article, we will deal with the method of extracting documents related to the new coronavirus newly registered on the previous day from the medical literature database and automatically transmitting them to LINE. The main content is to extract documents that match a certain keyword from a database called PubMed.
When there is a new paper, you will be notified like this. Without it it looks like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every day in Python AtCoder #44</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#44-f967b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#44-f967b/</guid>
      <description>### Introduction  Last time Solve 5 boot camp problems
#44 ABC056-C
Thoughts The sum of non-negative integers up to i is $\frac{1}{2}n(n+1)$}}. This sum becomes $X$ when $\frac{1}{2}n(n+1)=X$, and when solving for $n$, $n=\frac{-1\pm{ It will be \sqrt{8X+1}}}{2}$. If you add the ceil symbol to the solution of this equation, it becomes $\lceil \frac{-1\pm{\sqrt{8X+1}}}{2} \rceil$. This is the answer.
import math x = int(input()) f = (-1+math.sqrt(8*x+1)) / 2 print(math.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical puzzles to train programmer brains Q05 Still paying cash?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/mathematical-puzzles-to-train-programmer-brains-q05-still-paying-cash-f7f6c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/mathematical-puzzles-to-train-programmer-brains-q05-still-paying-cash-f7f6c/</guid>
      <description># Problem overview  Exchange 1000 yen into a combination of 500 yen coin, 100 yen coin, 50 yen coin and 10 yen coin. However, the total number of coins is 15 or less.
#Code Solve without thinking
#Q05 Still cash payment? combinations = [] # list of combinations for c500 in range(3): for c100 in range(11): for c50 in range(16): for c10 in range(16): if c500 + c100 + c50 + c10 &amp;lt;= 15: if c500 * 500 + c100 * 100 + c50 * 50 + c10 *10 == 1000: combinations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Released the Corona Candlestick Chart App for Hyogo Prefecture.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/released-the-corona-candlestick-chart-app-for-hyogo-prefecture.-fdd23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/released-the-corona-candlestick-chart-app-for-hyogo-prefecture.-fdd23/</guid>
      <description># Published service  https://covid19-candle-hyogo.ml The source code of GitHub is here
#Motivation The published daily graph of infected persons and the cumulative graph Those who have recovered and those who have died are not deducted I think it only gives the feeling that we are constantly expanding.
As I am What I would like to know is rather the “trend” Is it expanding, is it ending, or is it in a balanced state?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every day in Python AtCoder #41</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#41-f9a60/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#41-f9a60/</guid>
      <description>### Introduction  Last time I have ABC today so I have only one question.
#41 Problem
Thoughts It&amp;rsquo;s a long-standing problem. When I tried to solve this time, I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand why I was having a difficult time. Since the range of the solution is small, check all with for. I have placed a flag to check if the M conditions are met.
n, m = map(int,input().split()) sc = [list(map(int,input().</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Google Colaboratory</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-use-google-colaboratory-fc1d7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-use-google-colaboratory-fc1d7/</guid>
      <description>![image.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/587891/ed416201-d330-975f-0707-cea8dd90ab29.png)  Purpose Google Colaboratory can be used.
Please see How to use Google Colaboratory for detailed explanation and code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use python multiprocessing (cont. 3) apply_async in a class that has Pool as a member</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-use-python-multiprocessing-cont.-3-apply_async-in-a-class-that-has-pool-as-a-member-ff80f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-use-python-multiprocessing-cont.-3-apply_async-in-a-class-that-has-pool-as-a-member-ff80f/</guid>
      <description>### Purpose  I have been studying since yesterday, but I feel that I have finally come close to the shape I want to use, so I will write it down again here.
 For input that comes asynchronously, I want to move the processing without blocking in a separate process I want to catch the end properly  I wanted to realize that. I made a note yesterday, but it feels like I&amp;rsquo;ve settled down here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Since it&#39;s free time, the front-end engineer tried Python (v3.7.5) for the first time.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/since-its-free-time-the-front-end-engineer-tried-python-v3.7.5-for-the-first-time.-f9aaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/since-its-free-time-the-front-end-engineer-tried-python-v3.7.5-for-the-first-time.-f9aaf/</guid>
      <description>#Greeting  Hello. My name is Steve.T and I am a front-end engineer. I usually do Vue.js, React, and Angular. I wrote Python because I wanted to study something because it was completely full remote and I was free. Backend knowledge is stopped in PHP, I can not write Ruby or Python, it was a little &amp;hellip; and I heard that Python is standard equipment for information processing tests, so I have to do this finally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Linear regression] Number of explanatory variables and coefficient of determination (adjusted for degrees of freedom)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/linear-regression-number-of-explanatory-variables-and-coefficient-of-determination-adjusted-for-degrees-of-freedom-fab7d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/linear-regression-number-of-explanatory-variables-and-coefficient-of-determination-adjusted-for-degrees-of-freedom-fab7d/</guid>
      <description># at first  For the explanatory variables of linear regression, &amp;ldquo;It is better not to use variables unrelated to the objective variable for learning&amp;rdquo; (*1) I have the image. However, while studying linear regression analysis, I have learned that the coefficient of determination has the following properties.
&amp;ldquo;When an explanatory variable is added, the coefficient of determination cannot fall below that before addition. (So, for accuracy comparison of models with different numbers of explanatory variables, use the &amp;ldquo;coefficient of determination with adjusted degrees of freedom&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No module named&#39;_ctypes&#39; occurs when installing pipenv</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/no-module-named_ctypes-occurs-when-installing-pipenv-f8a1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/no-module-named_ctypes-occurs-when-installing-pipenv-f8a1a/</guid>
      <description>## 環境  OS: Amazon Linux 2 Python: 3.8.1
事象 pyenvでpython3.8.1をinstall後、pip install pipenvを実行すると以下のエラーが発生し、installできない。
 ERROR: Command errored out with exit status 1: command: /root/.pyenv/versions/3.8.1/bin/python3.8 -c &#39;import sys, setuptools, tokenize; sys.argv[0] = &#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;/tmp/pip-install-shwfwhga/distlib/setup.py&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;; __file__=&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;/tmp/pip-install-shwfwhga/distlib/setup.py&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;;f=getattr(tokenize, &#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;open&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;, open)(__file__);code=f.read().replace(&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;\r\n&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;, &#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;\n&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;);f.close();exec(compile(code, __file__, &#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;exec&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;&amp;quot;&#39;))&#39; egg_info --egg-base pip-egg-info cwd: /tmp/pip-install-shwfwhga/distlib/ Complete output (11 lines): Traceback (most recent call last): File &amp;quot;&amp;lt;string&amp;gt;&amp;quot;, line 1, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; File &amp;quot;/root/.pyenv/versions/3.8.1/lib/python3.8/site-packages/setuptools/__init__.py&amp;quot;, line 20, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; from setuptools.dist import Distribution, Feature File &amp;quot;/root/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 115 Review</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-115-review-fed4f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-115-review-fed4f/</guid>
      <description>#Time required  #Impression I forgot to write my impressions (2020/04/18). When I was solving while taking classes, the results were halfway&amp;hellip; After all, I should imagine it as a production contest and usually do it&amp;hellip;
#A problem
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a smart way to change the number of Eve depending on how many days before Christmas, but I decided to divide it because it is not troublesome to divide it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pandasのto_datetimeで「TypeError: Unrecognized value type: &lt;class &#39;str&#39;&gt;」</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/pandas%E3%81%AEto_datetime%E3%81%A7typeerror-unrecognized-value-type-class-str-fa2a0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/pandas%E3%81%AEto_datetime%E3%81%A7typeerror-unrecognized-value-type-class-str-fa2a0/</guid>
      <description>This error occurs when a character string that cannot be recognized as a date is included.  I am addicted to it, so I have summarized it in an article.
When creating a DataFrame, if a &amp;ldquo;value that is not a date&amp;rdquo; is entered between date strings, it will be read as an object. (Note that if it consists of all strings that can be interpreted as a date, it can be read as datetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You will become an engineer in 100 days-Day 28-Python-Python language basics 4</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/you-will-become-an-engineer-in-100-days-day-28-python-python-language-basics-4-f9324/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/you-will-become-an-engineer-in-100-days-day-28-python-python-language-basics-4-f9324/</guid>
      <description>Today is the continuation of the basics of Python.  Last time here
You will become an engineer in 100 days-Day 27-Python-Python Exercise 1
list 
Special programming forms can be handled in programming languages. That is the data structure such as dictionary or list.
Use [ ] square brackets to create list type data. Enter the data in the form of the data you want to store inside the square brackets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Price Prediction by Machine Learning Numerai</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The general public may not have heard about it, but there is a hedge fund called &amp;ldquo;Numerai&amp;rdquo;. It is a hedge fund that has been known a little in the neighborhood by being covered by media such as Wired and Forbes from the latter half of 2016 to the first half of 2017. This hedge fund is a so-called crowdsourcing type fund that operates based on the forecast results of stock prices by an unspecified number of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use KNP as a Universal Dependency parser in spaCy</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/use-knp-as-a-universal-dependency-parser-in-spacy-ff7ea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/use-knp-as-a-universal-dependency-parser-in-spacy-ff7ea/</guid>
      <description>The other day, we released spaCy plugin [Camphr version 0.5.20](https://github.com/PKSHATechnology-Research/camphr/releases/tag/0.5.20).  The feature of this time is [universal dependency] from the analysis result of KNPimplementedbyProfessorKoichiYasuokaofKyotoUniversity.Itisafunctiontooutputthelabelof(https://universaldependencies.org/). In this article, I will briefly introduce how to use it.
Install  Install knponthesystemorKNPdockerimage $ pip install camphr[juman]  #Analysis
import camphr import spacy nlp = camphr.load(&amp;#34;knp&amp;#34;) doc = nlp (&amp;#34;Taro went to Mt. Fuji while eating an apple and a mandarin orange.&amp;#34;) spacy.displacy.render(doc) &amp;ldquo;Apple&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Mikan&amp;rdquo; are connected by conj(conjunct), which is a wonderful analysis result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move the turtle to the place where the mouse is clicked with Python turtle</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/move-the-turtle-to-the-place-where-the-mouse-is-clicked-with-python-turtle-fddcf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/move-the-turtle-to-the-place-where-the-mouse-is-clicked-with-python-turtle-fddcf/</guid>
      <description>Move the turtle to the place where the mouse is clicked with #Python turtle  Execution image Sample program import turtle kame = turtle.Turtle(&amp;#34;turtle&amp;#34;) def moveKame(x, y): kame.goto(x, y) kame.screen.onclick(moveKame) turtle.done() Explanation # load the turtle module import turtle Generate and store a Turtle in the turtle module in a variable named # kame kame = turtle.Turtle(&amp;#34;turtle&amp;#34;) Define a function named #moveKame #def means to generate a function # moveKame can be any name # x, y contains the numerical value of the coordinates clicked with the mouse def moveKame(x, y): # Move the turtle kame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do when (base) is displayed at the beginning of the Mac terminal</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-to-do-when-base-is-displayed-at-the-beginning-of-the-mac-terminal-f9c19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-to-do-when-base-is-displayed-at-the-beginning-of-the-mac-terminal-f9c19/</guid>
      <description>After launching the Mac terminal,  The familiar (base) characters at the Anaconda prompt start. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Anaconda lately.
(base)username:~$ Cause Since the setting that automatically enables the virtual environment built with Anaconda may be effective, I ran the following command to check.
$ conda config --show | grep auto_activate_base Now that we have a True returned, we know we need to change the settings.
auto_activate_base: True Environment ・MacOS Catalina 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing logistic regression with NumPy</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/implementing-logistic-regression-with-numpy-fb4cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/implementing-logistic-regression-with-numpy-fb4cd/</guid>
      <description>It is a moment if you use scikit-learn, but you can also implement it yourself as a study.  In the original article, multi-class classification and train_test_split were out of scope, so
It is simplified to a 2-class problem and evaluated with the same data as the training data.
Please refer to the following article for details. Machine learning starting from scratch #4 &amp;ldquo;Logistic regression&amp;rdquo;
from sklearn.datasets import load_iris import numpy as np iris = load_iris() X_org = iris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 162 復習</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-162-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-ff5b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-162-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-ff5b1/</guid>
      <description>#This grade  #This impression
It&amp;rsquo;s not bad in performance (although it took 1 hour), I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve either E or F, so I&amp;rsquo;m very sorry. For the time being, I would like to review what E and F were missing and review.
#A problem
Whether or not 7 is included can be handled as a character string. Why are you converting it to a list? My head is too bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7rep - Insert Dataframe To Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/7rep-insert-dataframe-to-elasticsearch-fe1b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/7rep-insert-dataframe-to-elasticsearch-fe1b5/</guid>
      <description>#TSV(CSV) code sample to insert into Elasicsearch  from elasticsearch import Elasticsearch from elasticsearch import helpers import pandas as pd import datetime import time import json import random from pandas.io.json import json_normalize # Elasticsearch es = Elasticsearch(&amp;#34;{ES_IP}&amp;#34;) INDEX = &amp;#34;{ES_Index_Name}&amp;#34; fname=&amp;#34;{FileName}&amp;#34; reader = pd.read_csv(fname, chunksize=1000, sep=&amp;#39;\t&amp;#39;,low_memory = False) df_all = reader.get_chunk() # chunk the dataframe # json df_lines = df_all.to_json(force_ascii=False, orient=&amp;#39;records&amp;#39;, lines=True) # Bulk inser actions = [] for i in iter(df_lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I created an actuarial library</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-created-an-actuarial-library-f9058/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-created-an-actuarial-library-f9058/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It&amp;rsquo;s a certain virus or crap, it seems that it is about to grow moss on my body due to my self-control. By the way, I was studying the actuary exam recently, and I thought that &amp;ldquo;I might have a library for actuarial science in Python.&amp;rdquo; ――
#Development motive ・To deepen the understanding of actuarial science. ・To simplify numerical calculations using actuarial science.
 I&amp;rsquo;ve never given my own library to PyPI in Python, so let&amp;rsquo;s try it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let me know by voice when an article you are interested in is posted</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/let-me-know-by-voice-when-an-article-you-are-interested-in-is-posted-ff518/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/let-me-know-by-voice-when-an-article-you-are-interested-in-is-posted-ff518/</guid>
      <description>You can detect updates of blogs that you are interested in through RSS feeds, but sometimes you see the title and say, &amp;quot;Isn&#39;t it necessary to read it?&amp;quot;  It&amp;rsquo;s a hassle to read the titles one by one, so I decided to ask Itako Tohoku of Voiceroid to read the article when I was interested in it.
Extracting articles that may be of interest Classification of articles using Flair Flair is a library that can easily execute the latest natural language processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQLAlchemy&#43;SQLite3でOperationalError</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/sqlalchemy-sqlite3%E3%81%A7operationalerror-fa7f2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/sqlalchemy-sqlite3%E3%81%A7operationalerror-fa7f2/</guid>
      <description># Thing you want to do   I want to use SQLite3 with SQLAlchemy I want to specify the DB file with an absolute path  Environment Python3.8.1 on alpine linux 3.11 on Docker
What happened I wrote the following code, hoping that a DB file will be created in /var/data
engine = create_engine(&amp;#34;sqlite:///var/data/project.sqlite3&amp;#34;) ... When I ran it, I was angry that the database file could not be opened</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Miniconda</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/use-miniconda-fcd03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/use-miniconda-fcd03/</guid>
      <description># Miniconda  A lightweight version of Anaconda. While Anaconda includes many libraries and IDEs, Miniconda focuses on conda, Python, and the minimum required libraries.
What is good Lightweight compared to Anaconda At the time of installation, since various Anaconda is included, it will be about several GB. In that respect Miniconda contains only the minimum required, so it will be several hundred MB.
conda can be used conda is a tool for managing Python packages and versioning Python itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to display the condition of coronavirus infection on the heat map of seaborn</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-display-the-condition-of-coronavirus-infection-on-the-heat-map-of-seaborn-f81c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-display-the-condition-of-coronavirus-infection-on-the-heat-map-of-seaborn-f81c4/</guid>
      <description># I tried to display the condition of infection of corona on the heat map of seaborn  ##Purpose Visualize the spread of corona in each prefecture The goal is this. ##Method Use python&amp;rsquo;s seaborn. Click here for data on the number of infected people (up to 4/5). https://toyokeizai.net/sp/visual/tko/covid19/ Click here for prefecture data. https://gist.github.com/mugifly/d6e68a516de4a008687c Here is a summary of various things. https://github.com/kyasby/colona.git
Import library import numpy as np import pandas as pd import matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regression analysis in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/regression-analysis-in-python-f9028/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/regression-analysis-in-python-f9028/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is Motty.  This time, I wrote about regression analysis using Python.
#Regression
Regression analysis is a method of predicting target data using the data at hand. At that time, the structure of quantitative relationships is applied to the data (regression model). If the regression model is a straight line, it is called a regression line, and if an n-order function is applied by polynomial regression, it is called a regression curve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried fitting exponential function and logistics function to the number of COVID-19 positive patients in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-fitting-exponential-function-and-logistics-function-to-the-number-of-covid-19-positive-patients-in-tokyo-fb8d7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-fitting-exponential-function-and-logistics-function-to-the-number-of-covid-19-positive-patients-in-tokyo-fb8d7/</guid>
      <description>#Background  There was a person who fitted the trend of the number of COVID-19 infected people in the world to an exponential function and a logistic function and calculated the doubling period (https://github.com/aatishb/covid), so I cloned it. I applied it to the data on the number of patients published by Tokyo.
When it comes to Tokyo, the difference in the situation depending on the region is mixed into one distribution if it is national data, so it is easier to fit it to an ideal infection explosion model in a limited area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create matplotlib color list</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/create-matplotlib-color-list-f8af8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/create-matplotlib-color-list-f8af8/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Recently, most of my hobby and work calculations are done in Python, and graphing is done in Python matplotlib. In order to improve the distinctiveness of the graph, colors are used, but I wanted to keep the color list of matplotlib at hand, and created an image of the color list.
#Sample
#How to make Get the list of colors that matplotlib can handle by referring to the following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to automatically upload a .gpx file to Strava</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-automatically-upload-a-.gpx-file-to-strava-fe1a7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-automatically-upload-a-.gpx-file-to-strava-fe1a7/</guid>
      <description>## 1. Find out which version of Google Chrome you are using  Image is from https://www.iijmio.jp/thissite/version
2. Download the &amp;ldquo;chromedriver&amp;rdquo; software that matches Google Chrome   Download it from here.
  The downloaded file is in .zip format, so put the unpacked executable file into your directory.
  3. Open the terminal and run the following in the terminal pip install beautifulsoup4 selenium requests 4. Rewrite the &amp;ldquo;email address&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;password&amp;rdquo; of the following source code according to your strava account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REAPER time sorting and labeling</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/reaper-time-sorting-and-labeling-f939e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/reaper-time-sorting-and-labeling-f939e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I originally used a script to change the item names in batch with REAPER, so I used it,
When the tracks were separated, it felt like the name was poured into each track. I wish it was a single track, but&amp;hellip;
When I noticed it, it was divided into tracks.
So I wrote a script to fill in the names in chronological order.
(Also, if there are too many numbers, it seems that the letters are over, so it only worked halfway)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a web application with Django</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-made-a-web-application-with-django-fa7a6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-made-a-web-application-with-django-fa7a6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was written as a memorandum when I created a web application in Djnago.
#Prerequisite
 The OS environment is CentOS 8.1 running on Virtualbox. Below is the detailed OS information.  # cat /etc/centos-release CentOS Linux release 8.1.1911 (Core)  In this article, Django implements the creation of the TOP page using AdminLTE and the access restriction only for logged-in users. I have summarized it in an article for all five chapters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Basic pattern of if statement and usage (comparison operator and Boolean operator)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-basic-pattern-of-if-statement-and-usage-comparison-operator-and-boolean-operator-f9742/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-basic-pattern-of-if-statement-and-usage-comparison-operator-and-boolean-operator-f9742/</guid>
      <description># [Python] Basic pattern of if statement and usage (comparison operator and Boolean operator)  A review of the if statement pattern.
** ■ Table of contents **  Basic syntax of if statement  No conditional branch Conditional branch (else only) 2 or more conditional branches (without else) Two or more conditional branches (with else)   Condition expression operator List of operators Example of comparison operator  &amp;ldquo;==&amp;rdquo; equal “!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After changing the account name on Mac, I could not use pip or ipython, so I re-installed python and it was cured</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/after-changing-the-account-name-on-mac-i-could-not-use-pip-or-ipython-so-i-re-installed-python-and-it-was-cured-fcccf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/after-changing-the-account-name-on-mac-i-could-not-use-pip-or-ipython-so-i-re-installed-python-and-it-was-cured-fcccf/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  When I changed my mac account name, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use pip or ipython installed by pyenv, so I could use python again. #environment macOS Catalina 10.15.4 Homebrew 2.2.11 pyenv 1.2.17 python 3.8.0 #Background I used brew on mac to install pyenv, and then pyenv was used to install python. After that, I changed my mac account name (and home directory name) for various reasons. Follow the official description to change the account name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannot import modules in parent directory even with sys.path.append(&#39;..&#39;)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/cannot-import-modules-in-parent-directory-even-with-sys.path.append..-ffc3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/cannot-import-modules-in-parent-directory-even-with-sys.path.append..-ffc3b/</guid>
      <description>## Question   I want to use module1.py from main.py in Python. Execute python scripts/main.py in the project directory.  project/ ├ module/ │ └ module1.py └ scripts/ └ main.py import sys sys.path.append(&amp;#39;..&amp;#39;) from module import module1 If this is the case, ModuleNotFoundError will appear.
answer .. indicates the parent directory as seen from the working directory. Not the directory where the executable is located. That is, it refers to the parent directory for the project directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning/Softmax function</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/deep-learning-softmax-function-fc805/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/deep-learning-softmax-function-fc805/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  This time, I will briefly summarize the softmax function.
#2. What is the softmax function? Convert the output of the neural network into a total probability of 1. ![Screenshot 2020-03-28 16.31.12.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/209705/1297a7fb-d2fc-4cee-babe-(4ff1aa6198bb.png)
#3.Specific calculation If the output $y_1$-$y_3$ is as follows,
The result of passing the softmax function is ![Screenshot 2020-03-28 16.25.28.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/209705/d8bbcd6a-8a78-86f6-ba13-(16bc42ec5b12.png)
#4. Code
import numpy as np def softmax(z): y = np.exp(z) / np.sum(np.exp(z)) return y z = np.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python string delete specific character by replacement</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-string-delete-specific-character-by-replacement-fdbc9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-string-delete-specific-character-by-replacement-fdbc9/</guid>
      <description>## background  It is a memorandum. When dealing with character strings, it is necessary to delete it if it contains unnecessary characters. As I looked it up, there wasn&amp;rsquo;t much that fits well. Therefore, it is easy to process by replacing the character string so that the specific character is eliminated.
# Replace the disturbing characters @,% with &amp;#34;&amp;#34; Replace #: with. (Comma) str_ = &amp;#34;@14@:@30@@%%%&amp;#34; str_ = str_.replace(&amp;#39;@&amp;#39;, ``) str_ = str_.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sy wave prediction (regression) with Pytorch</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/sy-wave-prediction-regression-with-pytorch-fe2d3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/sy-wave-prediction-regression-with-pytorch-fe2d3/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  Hello. A new employee of an IT company. Here, I described a sine wave prediction regression model learning program as a sample using Pytorch which is an open source machine learning library. (It&amp;rsquo;s not a time series forecast&amp;hellip; I also want to do a time series forecast.)
By moving chainer to pytorch, I was late, but I wrote it because I am trying to catch up this time. It also describes what I felt the difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Processing with PIL</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/image-processing-with-pil-fcb12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/image-processing-with-pil-fcb12/</guid>
      <description>In this project, we&#39;ll load and process the image with PIL.   PIL This library provides extensive file format support, an efficient internal representation, and fairly powerful image processing capabilities. The core image library is designed for fast access to data stored in a few basic pixel formats. It should provide a solid foundation for a general image processing tool.
Image Processing The library contains basic image processing functionality, including point operations, filtering with a set of built-in convolution kernels, and colour space conversions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>python selenium chromedriver beautifulsoup</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-selenium-chromedriver-beautifulsoup-f8946/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-selenium-chromedriver-beautifulsoup-f8946/</guid>
      <description>#### Sample code 1 (simple display only)  import time from selenium import webdriver import chromedriver_binary driver = webdriver.Chrome() driver.get(&amp;#39;https://xxx&amp;#39;) time.sleep(2) # 2 second wait driver.close() driver.quit() Sample code 2 (headless mode: Do not display &amp;amp; parse with beautiful soup) from bs4 import BeautifulSoup import time from selenium import webdriver import chromedriver_binary from selenium.webdriver.chrome.options import Options option = Options() option.add_argument(&amp;#39;--headless&amp;#39;) driver = webdriver.Chrome(options=option) driver.get(&amp;#39;https://xxx&amp;#39;) time.sleep(2) # 2 second wait # If you want to parse soup = BeautifulSoup(driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] ABC159D (College Mathematics nCr) [AtCoder]</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-abc159d-college-mathematics-ncr-atcoder-f9f1e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-abc159d-college-mathematics-ncr-atcoder-f9f1e/</guid>
      <description>Competitive professionals will prepare notebooks and pens! ! !  (Especially if a mathematical formula comes out)
#ABC159D Difficulty:417 This time I will explain the explanation w First, quote from Explanation.
 ① Number of methods to select two different balls with the same written integer from N balls (2) Number of methods to select a ball in which the same integer as the kth ball is written from the N-1 balls excluding the kth ball Can be obtained by subtracting the latter from the former.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete tweets for specified period</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/delete-tweets-for-specified-period-fe277/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/delete-tweets-for-specified-period-fe277/</guid>
      <description>## I want to say that there was no black history  There are already various tools in the world, According to the specifications of Twitter, only the latest 3200 can be deleted, There is a charge for mass deletion. Very troubled.
There are over 100,000 tweets like garbage that have accumulated since 2010.
There is also a source that erases all tweets in Qiita if you search for it. But everything is in trouble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What do you do for visualization of 4 variables or more?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-what-do-you-do-for-visualization-of-4-variables-or-more-fb41c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-what-do-you-do-for-visualization-of-4-variables-or-more-fb41c/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article  What if you want to check the relationship of many variables at once in data analysis? I think pairplot is the typical one, but it&amp;rsquo;s more! I thought I could summarize it, but recently I learned something like Sankey Diagram, so I drew it.
Added: Please read the additional part at the end of the article first.
How to use # Plotly Sankey Diagram</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculate AUC by groupBy of PySpark DataFrame (Define aggregation function in pandas_udf)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/calculate-auc-by-groupby-of-pyspark-dataframe-define-aggregation-function-in-pandas_udf-fd299/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/calculate-auc-by-groupby-of-pyspark-dataframe-define-aggregation-function-in-pandas_udf-fd299/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When calculating AUC with PySpark, you can easily obtain it by using the BinaryClassificationEvaluator class. However, as it is, it is not possible to meet the need to calculate the AUC for each segment rather than the entire test data in order to understand the differences between the models.
As a workaround for this, I defined an aggregate function that calculates AUC using pandas_udf and calculated it using the agg method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Established a mechanism to download a large zip file by aws with Basic authentication</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/established-a-mechanism-to-download-a-large-zip-file-by-aws-with-basic-authentication-fd79d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/established-a-mechanism-to-download-a-large-zip-file-by-aws-with-basic-authentication-fd79d/</guid>
      <description># Article content in three lines   Let&amp;rsquo;s use EC2 and framework It can not be assembled without server (it can be assembled but NG due to capacity limitation) API Gateway convenient (difficult)  Overview When sharing a large file, if it exceeds about 8MB for mail, it will be blocked because it is a mail server. Even if it is not blocked, I think that it is quite annoying to send a large file by mail to the server in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS tracking with Raspberry Pi 4B&#43;BU-353S4 (Python)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/gps-tracking-with-raspberry-pi-4b-bu-353s4-python-ff917/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/gps-tracking-with-raspberry-pi-4b-bu-353s4-python-ff917/</guid>
      <description>#Raspai 4 + BU-353S4 + Python GPS tracking  Get GPS information using Raspberry Pi I use Raspberry Pi 4B, but I think the same applies to 3 and so on.
Items to prepare  GLOBALSAT BU-353S4 =&amp;gt; USB connected GPS sensor Raspberry Pi 4  Procedure Install required packages
sudo apt-get upgrade sudo apt-get install gpsd gpsd-clients python-gps cu Insert BU-353S4 into USB and confirm the connection with the following command</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python inexperienced person try 100 knocks of language processing 00～04</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-inexperienced-person-try-100-knocks-of-language-processing-0004-fe1d3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-inexperienced-person-try-100-knocks-of-language-processing-0004-fe1d3/</guid>
      <description>[Addition]  Click here for 05-06 Python inexperienced person try 100 language processing knock 05-06 https://qiita.com/earlgrey914/items/e772f1b7e5efea114e1d Click here for 07-09 Python inexperienced person try 100 knocks of language processing 07～09 https://qiita.com/earlgrey914/items/a7b6781037bc0844744b
 #Click here to try
&amp;lt;Language processing 100 knocks 2015&amp;gt; https://repository.kulib.kyoto-u.ac.jp/dspace/handle/2433/245698
** Author profile (important) ** No basic learning experience with Python. A level where you can copy and move the sample lying on the net. I&amp;rsquo;ve touched Java a little during university exercises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get pull request info by calling github api with python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/get-pull-request-info-by-calling-github-api-with-python-fe89a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/get-pull-request-info-by-calling-github-api-with-python-fe89a/</guid>
      <description>#Background  I want to create a function that automatically notifies me when there is a schema change in the repository of the service that is the data source of the data infrastructure. I made it by pulling the Pull Request information with github api, so a memo at that time. Authentication uses a personal access token ↓
Create a personal access token for the command line Implementation import requests #Get only PR that has been closed URL =&amp;#39;https://api.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Digest authentication using Python @Lambda</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/setting-up-digest-authentication-using-python-lambda-fe83c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/setting-up-digest-authentication-using-python-lambda-fe83c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There was almost no information when I searched for Digest authentication, so I wrote it as a sequel to Basic authentication setting @ Lambda using Python. I have barely touched Digest authentication itself, and I also learned the mechanism.
#Code
import os import ctypes import json import base64 import time import hashlib import copy from Crypto.Cipher import AES accounts = [ { &amp;#34;user&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;user1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;pass&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;pass1&amp;#34; }, { &amp;#34;user&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;user2&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;pass&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;pass2&amp;#34; } ] realm = &amp;#34;sample@test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning record (5th day) #Set default values to function arguments #Specify multiple return values #Map method #Numeric expression #List and tuple</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/learning-record-5th-day-#set-default-values-to-function-arguments-%23specify-multiple-return-values-%23map-method-%23numeric-expression-%23list-and-tuple-fe656/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/learning-record-5th-day-#set-default-values-to-function-arguments-%23specify-multiple-return-values-%23map-method-%23numeric-expression-%23list-and-tuple-fe656/</guid>
      <description># content of study    Python basic grammar
 Specify default value for function argument Specify multiple return values map method Numeric representation of a number Lists and tuples    Python basic grammar Specify default value for function argument Default value can be set in the argument. In the following example, default values are set in two of the three arguments of the showName() method, and the method can be called by specifying only one or two arguments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math memorandum #3 to keep up with the scene</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/math-memorandum-#3-to-keep-up-with-the-scene-fa46e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/math-memorandum-#3-to-keep-up-with-the-scene-fa46e/</guid>
      <description>## Set again this time  In the third lesson, we will perform permutations and combinations of sets. Is it useful when making a matrix in a program?
Number of cases When you roll the dice, the number of rolls is 6, and if you make a coin toss, the number of sides In two ways, the number that can occur like this is called the number of cases __.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Tello_Video environment on Windows</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/build-tello_video-environment-on-windows-fb142/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/build-tello_video-environment-on-windows-fb142/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This page is
Run Tello-Python sample &amp;ldquo;Tello_Video&amp;rdquo;
This is a supplementary page of.
Or not only for &amp;ldquo;Tello_Video&amp;rdquo;, If you want to do &amp;ldquo;Tello-Python&amp;rdquo; on Windows, you need to do this first, including installing Python.
#Overview
Of the DJI official Python sample program for Tello &amp;ldquo;Tello-Python&amp;rdquo;, Tello_Video In order to try
 Installation of various dependent libraries  Should do
git Tello-Python page
・Windows Go to the &amp;quot;install\Windows&amp;quot; folder,select and run the correct &amp;quot;windows_install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A module summary that automates and assists the installation of WebDriver with Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/a-module-summary-that-automates-and-assists-the-installation-of-webdriver-with-python-f895e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/a-module-summary-that-automates-and-assists-the-installation-of-webdriver-with-python-f895e/</guid>
      <description>#Summary of modules that help install WebDriver with Python  When scraping with Selenium etc., it may not work if the version of WebDriver is different, so I searched for a module that arbitrarily matches the version and summarized it.
#For Chrome
chromedriver-autoinstaller  License: MIT Compatible OS: Widows/Mac/Linux  How to install pip install chromedriver-autoinstaller How to use Add to the code to do the following
from selenium import webdriver import chromedriver_autoinstaller chromedriver_autoinstaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to remove duplicate element in list in Python 3</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-remove-duplicate-element-in-list-in-python-3-fdfef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-remove-duplicate-element-in-list-in-python-3-fdfef/</guid>
      <description>### Remove duplicate elements from the list  The reason I wanted to write this list was that when I created a list with no duplicate elements, I used remove() to remove the elements. I used to think that if you use remove(), all the specified values will be deleted.
l = [1, 2, 3, 4, 1] l.remove(1) print(l) #[2, 3, 4, 1] In this way, the specified value that appears at the very beginning can be deleted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get pdf and png from Tableau server using TSC (Tableau Server Client).</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/get-pdf-and-png-from-tableau-server-using-tsc-tableau-server-client.-fb1bd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/get-pdf-and-png-from-tableau-server-using-tsc-tableau-server-client.-fb1bd/</guid>
      <description># Introduction  Use python 3.8.0. TSC requires installation. github (https://github.com/tableau/server-client-python) PyPI (https://pypi.org/project/tableauserverclient/)
pip install tableauserverclient import tableauserverclient as TSC For username, password, siteid, serverurl enter the account and server information used. Also, I want to use the latest version, so I set the user_server_version option to True.
tableau_auth = TSC.TableauAuth(&amp;#39;username&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;password&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;siteid&amp;#39;) server = TSC.Server(&amp;#39;serverurl&amp;#39;, use_server_version=True) Run the following code to see if the view exists on your site. Also, be sure to execute all_views because it will be used later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made Django&#39;s Middleware and made it possible to access request information from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-made-djangos-middleware-and-made-it-possible-to-access-request-information-from-anywhere-fab9f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-made-djangos-middleware-and-made-it-possible-to-access-request-information-from-anywhere-fab9f/</guid>
      <description>I started thinking about whether the login user could be stored in the user_created (creator) and user_updated (updater) of the model by common processing.  Until then, I wrote the process to pass user information from view to form and store it in user_created or user_updated.
What is Django middleware? From Official
 Middleware is a framework for adding hooks to Django&amp;rsquo;s request/response handling.
 You can define the process to be performed when sending a request or before returning a response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Pandas 1.0.1 Memorial] Fierce battle with Cookbook</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/pandas-1.0.1-memorial-fierce-battle-with-cookbook-faf24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/pandas-1.0.1-memorial-fierce-battle-with-cookbook-faf24/</guid>
      <description>#Background   Every time there is a Google search, it is bloody and not flesh due to temporary understanding. Fragmental knowledge alone is not enough to apply when it is difficult to apply. In order to overcome the weakened memory, it is necessary to move it, understand it, and explain it to the brain. I would like to carry out a dictum from the predecessors, &amp;ldquo;Please read the official manual&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A memorandum of python character string deletion processing</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/a-memorandum-of-python-character-string-deletion-processing-fd7a9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/a-memorandum-of-python-character-string-deletion-processing-fd7a9/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  Described as a reminder because I was a bit crazy when deleting strings in Python You may find that you are casually using rstrip,lstrip.
Phenomenon You may find it tempting to use lstrip or rstrip when removing filename prefixes or suffixes, like this:
fileName=&amp;#39;test_output file_20191217_001.xlsx&amp;#39; Remove the # prefix print(fileName.lstrip(&amp;#39;test_&amp;#39;)) # Output file_20191217_001.xlsx # Remove suffix print(fileName.rstrip(&amp;#39;.xlsx&amp;#39;)) # test_output file_20191217_001 It seems that there is no problem as an output result, but here the problem occurs when the character string is as follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First deep learning in C#-imitation of Python implementation-</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/first-deep-learning-in-c#-imitation-of-python-implementation-f87bf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/first-deep-learning-in-c#-imitation-of-python-implementation-f87bf/</guid>
      <description>Deep learning with #C# (matrix calculation)  This time, I created only the program that calculates the matrix necessary for deep learning. The book I referred to is &amp;ldquo;Making Deep Learning (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly)&amp;rdquo; from scratch. This book is very easy to understand and I think it is a good book, so I recommend it. It&amp;rsquo;s not a manga, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop&amp;hellip;I was so interested. Since I have only read about half of it, there are many things I do not understand well, but this time, I made a matrix calculation program in C#.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Tkinter template</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-tkinter-template-fe9b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-tkinter-template-fe9b5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  We will organize the standard method for classifying Tkinter, a Python GUI tool.
This is an introduction article of the procedure to create an Image Viewer using this template. (Addition) Create Image Viewer with Tkinter
#Classification template
 Application class Widget setting &amp;amp; placement, Callback function defined main function  import tkinter as tk from tkinter import ttk class Application(tk.Frame): def __init__(self,master): super().__init__(master) self.pack() self.master.geometry(&amp;#34;300x300&amp;#34;) self.master.title(&amp;#34;Tkinter with Class Template&amp;#34;) self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a clean DB for testing with FastAPI and perform unit test of API with pytest</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/create-a-clean-db-for-testing-with-fastapi-and-perform-unit-test-of-api-with-pytest-ff9c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/create-a-clean-db-for-testing-with-fastapi-and-perform-unit-test-of-api-with-pytest-ff9c8/</guid>
      <description>## things to do   implementation of a simple CRUD application using sqlite3 with FastAPI [Create a DB for each test case and perform unit test of API with pytest without affecting other test cases or production DB](#CreateaDBforeachtestcaseandcreateanothertestcase(UnittestofAPIisperformedwithpytestwithoutaffectingtheproductionDB.)  1. Implementing a simple CRUD application using sqlite3 with FastAPI CRUD application Create a CRUD app for user account. Since the test method is mainly introduced, only the following simple functions will be implemented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predict from various data in Python using Facebook Prophet, a time series prediction tool</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/predict-from-various-data-in-python-using-facebook-prophet-a-time-series-prediction-tool-f8a74/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/predict-from-various-data-in-python-using-facebook-prophet-a-time-series-prediction-tool-f8a74/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article is [Greg Rafferty](https://towardsdatascience.com/@raffg?source=post_page-----29810eb57e66----------------------)Translatedfrom&amp;quot;[ForecastinginPythonwithFacebookProphet](https://towardsdatascience.com/forecasting-in-python-with-facebook-prophet-29810eb57e66)&amp;quot; published in November 2019 by Mr. ..  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
I&amp;rsquo;m Greg Rafferty, a data scientist in the Bay Area. You can also check the code used in this project from my github.
In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to use the Facebook Prophet prediction library to make a variety of predictions, and some advanced techniques to use your expertise to handle trend inconsistencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problems when shaping data</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/problems-when-shaping-data-ff539/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/problems-when-shaping-data-ff539/</guid>
      <description>This article is a memorandum of the processing that I did when the data type I was scraping was various.  #Check the data type
df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].dtype #DataFrame np.dtype() #numpy array Change data type df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].astype(int) converted to #int df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].dtype(float) converted to #float df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].dtype(str) # convert to string #Check for missing values
df.isnull() #Remove missing values
df.dropna() #pandas line deletion
df.drop (number of lines) Add columns to #pandas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Tips</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-tips-f838b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-tips-f838b/</guid>
      <description>#docstring  Lines enclosed in &amp;quot;&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; are commented out. Also,
print(__doc__) The contents enclosed in are output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to call PyTorch in Julia</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-call-pytorch-in-julia-fda27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-call-pytorch-in-julia-fda27/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Create a virtual environment with Conda, enable PyTorch in Python in that virtual environment, make PyCall recognize that Python, and call it with Julia.
 Conda https://conda.io/en/latest/ Python https://docs.python.org/3/ PyTorch https://pytorch.org/docs/stable/index.html PyCall https://github.com/JuliaPy/PyCall.jl Julia https://docs.julialang.org/en/v1/  The procedure is as follows.
 Install Conda in a shell. Create a virtual environment with Conda. Make PyTorch available in the virtual environment. Install Julia. Install PyCall to reference Python in the virtual environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to build PyTorch 1.5 for CUDA 10.2 on Windows</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/steps-to-build-pytorch-1.5-for-cuda-10.2-on-windows-fd1fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/steps-to-build-pytorch-1.5-for-cuda-10.2-on-windows-fd1fa/</guid>
      <description>Here are the steps to build PyTorch 1.5 for CUDA 10.2 on Windows 10. (As of March 1, 2020)  It also contains the torchvision build instructions that are often used with PyTorch. Detailed explanations are omitted here, so if you need more detailed explanations, also refer to Blog-dev.infohub.cc. I hope you will.
#Build environment
 hardware -CPU: AMD Threadripper 3960X -GPU: nVIDIA TITAN RTX Software -Windows 10 Pro Version 1909 (x64) -Microsoft Visual Studio Community 2019 – Ver 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Expand escape sequences in here-docs</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-expand-escape-sequences-in-here-docs-f8218/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-expand-escape-sequences-in-here-docs-f8218/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m addicted to it  Even if the escape sequence (\) is written in the here-document as it is, it is not expanded as an escape sequence.
It can be expanded by writing two consecutive characters like \\ or using a raw string.
&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; import json &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; json_dict1 = json.loads(&amp;#39;&amp;#39;&amp;#39; ... { ... &amp;#34;id&amp;#34;: 1, ... &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;hoge&amp;#34;, ... &amp;#34;discription&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Houji \&amp;#34;Hojo \ &amp;#34;Hoge&amp;#34; ...} ...&amp;#39;&amp;#39;&amp;#39;) Traceback (most recent call last): File &amp;#34;&amp;lt;stdin&amp;gt;&amp;#34;, line 7, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; File &amp;#34;C:\Program Files\WindowsApps\PythonSoftwareFoundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 language processing knocks-38 (using pandas): histogram</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/100-language-processing-knocks-38-using-pandas-histogram-f9e48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/100-language-processing-knocks-38-using-pandas-histogram-f9e48/</guid>
      <description>[100 language processing knocks 2015](http://www.cl.ecei.tohoku.ac.jp/nlp100/)[&amp;quot;Chapter4:Morphologicalanalysis&amp;quot;](http://www.cl.ecei.tohokuItisa[38th&amp;quot;histogram&amp;quot;](http://www.cl.ecei.tohoku.ac.jp/nlp100/#sec38)recordof.ac.jp/nlp100/#ch4).  It&amp;rsquo;s easy as long as you&amp;rsquo;ve overcome the tofu from the previous knock. If you don&amp;rsquo;t put out a label, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to deal with &amp;ldquo;tofu&amp;rdquo;.
Reference link    Links Remarks     038.Histogram.ipynb Answer Program GitHub Link   [Amateur language processing 100 knocks: 38 Copy and paste source of many source parts   MeCab Official MeCab page to check first    #Environment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Udemy Python 3 introduction &#43; application] 22. Tuple unpacking</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/udemy-python-3-introduction-application-22.-tuple-unpacking-fa882/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/udemy-python-3-introduction-application-22.-tuple-unpacking-fa882/</guid>
      <description>**This article is from Udemy  &amp;ldquo;Introducing Python3 + application + application + Silicon Valley style code styles in the US taught by active Silicon Valley engineers&amp;rdquo; This is a notebook for yourself after taking the course. It is open to the public after obtaining permission from the lecturer Jun Sakai. **
■ Tuple unpacking ◆ Break tuples num_tuple = (10, 20) print(num_tuple) x, y = num_tuple print(&#39;x =&#39;, x, type(x)) print(&#39;y =&#39;, y, type(y)) (10, 20) x = 10 &amp;lt;class&#39;int&#39;&amp;gt; y = 20 &amp;lt;class&#39;int&#39;&amp;gt; Elements of tuples can be separated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flask introduction ~ Blueprint application note</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/flask-introduction-~-blueprint-application-note-fb7d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/flask-introduction-~-blueprint-application-note-fb7d1/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s try the title as easily as possible.  Blueprint allows you to implement the functionality of your application in pieces. Blueprint is officially recommended as a way to organize bloated projects.
Install Flask $ sudo pip3 install flask Directory structure $ cd ~/workspace/sample-flask/ $ls server.py from flask import Flask app = Flask(__name__) @app.route(&amp;#39;/&amp;#39;) def func_1(): return&amp;#39;Hello world&amp;#39; @app.route(&amp;#39;/test&amp;#39;) def func_2(): return&amp;#39;Test&amp;#39; if __name__ ==&amp;#39;__main__&amp;#39;: app.run(host=&amp;#39;0.0.0.0&amp;#39;, port=80, debug=True) Execution command $python3 server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pandas series part 1</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/pandas-series-part-1-fc2b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/pandas-series-part-1-fc2b7/</guid>
      <description>Series is a one-dimensional data structure.  import pandas as pd series = pd.Series([3, 6, 9]) print(series) Execution result of ```:1 0 3 1 6 2 9 dtype: int64
 There is an index in the leftmost column. To change the index, write as follows ```py:2 import pandas as pd names = [&amp;quot;Tanaka&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Yamada&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Takahashi&amp;quot;] series1 = pd.Series(names) series2 = pd.Series(names, index=[&#39;a&#39;,&#39;b&#39;,&#39;c&#39;]) print(series1) print(series2) Execution result of ```:2 0 Tanaka 1 Yamada 2 Takahashi dtype: object a Tanaka b Yamada c Takahashi dtype: object</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make anaconda environment available on windows from command prompt</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/make-anaconda-environment-available-on-windows-from-command-prompt-fd6f8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/make-anaconda-environment-available-on-windows-from-command-prompt-fd6f8/</guid>
      <description># First, install Anaconda   Download the distribution of python3.7 from Anaconda. When you run the downloaded one, a GUI installer will appear, but if you are not particular about it, it will stick with the default and complete the installation  If you use PyCharm or Jupyter, pass path to the anaconda interpreter individually with them, so this is the end story. But you should get an error even if you try python -v with cmd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 155 復習</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-155-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-fec2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-155-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-fec2d/</guid>
      <description>#This grade  #This impression
(I had no motivation for a competition professional because I was soaked in skis for 3 weeks, but I would like to resume from today (2/26)) I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve up to C this time. I felt the importance of devotion because the assumed solution of D was not difficult as an idea when I saw the solution by binary search. For E, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do a good job of distinguishing whether to carry or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract class</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/abstract-class-fa4cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/abstract-class-fa4cc/</guid>
      <description>```py  import abc
class Car(metaclass=abc.ABCMeta): def init(self,model=None): self.model = model
 @abc.abstractmethod def run(self): pass  class ToyotaCar(Car): def init(self, model,enable_auto_run=False): super().init(model) self.enable_auto_run = enable_auto_run
 #If you do not override it in the inherited class, an error will occur when you create an object def run(self): print(&#39;fast fun&#39;)  toyota_car = ToyotaCar(&amp;lsquo;Lexus&amp;rsquo;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When a local variable with the same name as a global variable is defined in the function</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/when-a-local-variable-with-the-same-name-as-a-global-variable-is-defined-in-the-function-fb01f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/when-a-local-variable-with-the-same-name-as-a-global-variable-is-defined-in-the-function-fb01f/</guid>
      <description>Variable `bar` in the function definition below is interpreted as a global variable because `bar` is not defined in the function block.  def foo(): print(bar) The code below succeeds because the global variable bar is defined before calling foo.
bar = 4 def foo(): print(bar) foo() # =&amp;gt; 4 The global variable of foo can be confirmed by the attribute co_names of the code object of foo.
foo.__code__.co_names # =&amp;gt; (&amp;#39;print&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;bar&amp;#39;) By the way, Python&amp;rsquo;s official documentsaysthatco_namesisthelocalvariablenametuple,but(localvariablenameAnd(excludingfreevariables)misnamed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Machine learning] Use WordNet to mechanically extract similar words</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/machine-learning-use-wordnet-to-mechanically-extract-similar-words-f82e9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/machine-learning-use-wordnet-to-mechanically-extract-similar-words-f82e9/</guid>
      <description>#Outline of natural language processing  Before touching on WordNet, let me briefly touch on natural language processing. In order for a machine to understand sentences in natural language processing, the following morphological analysis, syntactic analysis, semantic analysis, and contextual analysis are required in order.
Morphological analysis It is the work of dividing from natural language text data without annotations of information into columns of morphemes (the smallest unit that has meaning in the language) based on information such as the grammar of the target language and the part of speech of words called a dictionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried using the BigQuery Storage API</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-using-the-bigquery-storage-api-fa93d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-using-the-bigquery-storage-api-fa93d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Basic machine learning procedure: ②Let&amp;rsquo;s prepare data In the Pytohn environment, the process of importing the table created by BigQuery in Pandas Dataframe format has been started. It was
However, if the size of the table becomes large, it will take a long time. Probably, there were many people who had such troubles. Then, a new service called BigQuery Storage API came out.
I heard that it is 7 to 8 times faster, but what is it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build environment of LaTeX and R (Slightly Python) with Sublime Text3 (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/build-environment-of-latex-and-r-slightly-python-with-sublime-text3-windows-ff53d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/build-environment-of-latex-and-r-slightly-python-with-sublime-text3-windows-ff53d/</guid>
      <description># Sublime Text3 makes LaTeX and R (a little Python) easier to use  Introduction For your own notes. Unexpectedly, I thought that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t see the site about TeX in Sublime, I thought I would write about the environment I set up (Friend J&amp;rsquo;s Maru Pakuri).
In SublimeText3, I will describe a series of setting procedures to make LaTeX and R (a little Python) easy to use. Make sure to restart Sublime accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Twitter Data | Trend Analysis編</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/analyzing-twitter-data-trend-analysis%E7%B7%A8-fee64/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/analyzing-twitter-data-trend-analysis%E7%B7%A8-fee64/</guid>
      <description>This article is a trend analysis of Twitter Data analysis. I will deepen this series later. Since this is my first article, I will explain this case in detail after briefly analyzing Twitter Data. Because Japanese is tight, I will change it to English. [Git Repository](https://github.com/Bing-Violet/Real-Time-insights-from-social-media/blob/master/notebook.ipynb)   ###Why Analyze Twitter Data? Twitter data analysis is used in a wide range of areas including but not restricted to analyzing the mentions of each political party in an election, detecting the reactions to the introduction of a new product, understanding the geographical scope of discussion of a news story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Python execution environment Google Colaboratory memo</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/free-python-execution-environment-google-colaboratory-memo-f9f5e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/free-python-execution-environment-google-colaboratory-memo-f9f5e/</guid>
      <description># What is Google Colaboratory  Jupyter notebook environment running on Google&amp;rsquo;s cloud. https://colab.research.google.com/notebooks/welcome.ipynb
It&amp;rsquo;s free to use and no environment is required, so it&amp;rsquo;s convenient for learning Python.
In addition, GPU and TPU can be used to reduce machine learning execution time.
usage limit It is available free of charge, but there is a 12 hour continuous usage limit.
Be careful when using machine learning for a long time because the virtual machine will be disconnected after 12 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python description of a parent killed literally</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-description-of-a-parent-killed-literally-fe71b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-description-of-a-parent-killed-literally-fe71b/</guid>
      <description>@Raclett3&#39;s  Python programming whose parents were killed by literals of strings, numbers and truth values I think it&amp;rsquo;s very interesting :raised_hands:, but at the same time I couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand what was happening, so I looked into it. It&amp;rsquo;s a commentary or my own study.
I mainly write &amp;ldquo;small numerical values&amp;rdquo;. If you make a mistake, throw Masakari.
#0
int() # 0 This is as per @Raclett3&amp;rsquo;s link.
 or return 0 if no arguments are given</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note for when pip3 has been installed with python2.7 for some reason</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/a-note-for-when-pip3-has-been-installed-with-python2.7-for-some-reason-fb510/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/a-note-for-when-pip3-has-been-installed-with-python2.7-for-some-reason-fb510/</guid>
      <description>I want to install a package using pip3 for python3, but for some reason, the python version of pip3 is python2.7 and I get an error that the package cannot be installed by python3.  ~:python3 -V Python 3.7.4 ~/program/scrape: pip3 -V pip 20.0.2 from /Users/eijikudo/Library/Python/2.7/lib/python/site-packages/pip (python 2.7) python3.7 -m pip install package name It was done after specifying the python version and installing. You can do this. .. ..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I read PEP-593 (Flexible function and variable annotations)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-read-pep-593-flexible-function-and-variable-annotations-fa103/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-read-pep-593-flexible-function-and-variable-annotations-fa103/</guid>
      <description>In a certain discussion flow, I decided to read [PEP-593 (Flexible function and variable annotations)](https://www.python.org/dev/peps/pep-0593/), so I wrote down my understanding. Leave it in.  Overview  PEP-3107 (Function Annotations) introduced annotations into the Python syntax. At that time, the type hints, DB query mapping, and RPS marshalling information were mentioned as the uses of annotations. PEP-484 (Type Hints) introduced a method to implement type hints using annotation notation. It can be said that this is the main usage of annotations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube live It analyzes the sentiment of the comment and judges the emo part from Youtube LIve.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  It is a suggestion and experiment that it is possible to extract &amp;ldquo;emo&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;highlight&amp;rdquo; with better accuracy than just the number of comments per hour by performing sentiment analysis of comments on Youtube live. ..
In fact, we were able to get the result that the accuracy is likely to improve compared to just looking at the number of comments.
#Introduction
Last time, I borrowed COTOHA API and tried to think freely, not practical Article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When you want to adjust the axis scale interval with APLpy</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/when-you-want-to-adjust-the-axis-scale-interval-with-aplpy-fa0aa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/when-you-want-to-adjust-the-axis-scale-interval-with-aplpy-fa0aa/</guid>
      <description>Note that I was a little addicted to the method of adjusting the axis scale interval with APLpy.  For example, if you want to adjust the display interval of the main scale on the x-axis,
fig.ticks.set_xspacing(0.0005) You can do it. However, the argument here must be a multiple of the minimum unit of label format. Now
fig.ticklabels.set_xformat(hh:mm:ss.ss) If so, the minimum unit is 0.001s or 0.015 arcsec, and therefore 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put Ubuntu in Raspi, put Docker on it, and control GPIO with python from container</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/put-ubuntu-in-raspi-put-docker-on-it-and-control-gpio-with-python-from-container-feda9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/put-ubuntu-in-raspi-put-docker-on-it-and-control-gpio-with-python-from-container-feda9/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It became a confusing title, but it is this image #environment Development PC: Mac Mojave RaspBerry Pi4 Memory 4GB SD card 16GB
Write #Ubuntu 19.10 to SD https://ubuntu.com/download/raspberry-pi I downloaded the 64-bit version from and wrote it using balenaEtchar.
Install #docker on Ubuntu Enter ssh or something in Ubuntu
sudo apt-get install docker-ce You can install it with.
sudo usermod -aG docker ubuntu You can use docker without using sudo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand the number of input and output parameters of convolutional neural network</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/understand-the-number-of-input-and-output-parameters-of-convolutional-neural-network-ff1af/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/understand-the-number-of-input-and-output-parameters-of-convolutional-neural-network-ff1af/</guid>
      <description>Basically learning with keras and python  What I learned  Understand the number of input and output parameters of layers Understand data processing after processing convolutional layer and pooling layer  Code used for learning mnist cnn code from keras documentation.
from __future__ import print_function import keras from keras.datasets import mnist from keras.models import Sequential from keras.layers import Dense, Dropout, Flatten from keras.layers import Conv2D, MaxPooling2D from keras import backend as K batch_size = 128 num_classes = 10 epochs = 12 # input image dimensions img_rows, img_cols = 28, 28 # the data, split between train and test sets (x_train, y_train), (x_test, y_test) = mnist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A site that converts curl commands into requests</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/a-site-that-converts-curl-commands-into-requests-f85cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/a-site-that-converts-curl-commands-into-requests-f85cf/</guid>
      <description>It was convenient so I took notes  https://curl.trillworks.com/
If you have the following curl
curl -X POST&#39;https://example.com/&#39; \ - H&#39;Content-Type: application/json&#39; \ - d&#39;{&amp;quot;key1&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;value1&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;key2&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;value2&amp;quot;}&#39; If you put this, it will be converted to the following
import requests headers = { &amp;#39;Content-Type&amp;#39;:&amp;#39;application/json&amp;#39;, } data =&amp;#39;{&amp;#34;key1&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;value1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;key2&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;value2&amp;#34;}&amp;#39; response = requests.post(&amp;#39;https://example.com/login&amp;#39;, headers=headers, data=data) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display image after Data Augmentation with Pytorch</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/display-image-after-data-augmentation-with-pytorch-feb9f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/display-image-after-data-augmentation-with-pytorch-feb9f/</guid>
      <description>##background  **I want to display the image after data augmentation! **
I decided to implement it.
Data Augmentation is a technology to inflate one image, and the following operations are added.
 Random Crop Random Horizontal Flip (the image is horizontally flipped with a certain probability) Random Erasing (randomly add noise to a part of the image) Random Affine (scales images randomly)  There are many other things.
##Implementation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[DynamoDB] [Docker] Build a development environment for DynamoDB and Django with docker-compose</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/dynamodb-docker-build-a-development-environment-for-dynamodb-and-django-with-docker-compose-fca2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/dynamodb-docker-build-a-development-environment-for-dynamodb-and-django-with-docker-compose-fca2c/</guid>
      <description># Build a development environment for DynamoDB and Django with docker-compose  Introduction DynamoDB is cheap and fast. Did you know that there is a Docker Image for developing such DynamoDB locally? We will inquire about an example of development environment construction using such Docker Image.
Environment The following image versions are used according to the production environment. Use dynamodb-admin for DynamoDB GUI operation. Node is used to build the environment together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even now, let&#39;s try face recognition with Chainer (learning phase)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/even-now-lets-try-face-recognition-with-chainer-learning-phase-fa93c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/even-now-lets-try-face-recognition-with-chainer-learning-phase-fa93c/</guid>
      <description>###Overview  It is full of feeling that face recognition is announced after the end of development of Chainer is announced, I will spell it here as a memorandum.
This series will be sent in two parts. This time, I will explain how to implement the learning phase (learning face images). Next time, I will explain the implementation of prediction phase(facerecognitionusingcamera).
Since I am a ML first-year student and a high school student at the time, some of the information may be incorrect or there may be a bug in the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get the source of the page to be loaded infinitely with python.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/get-the-source-of-the-page-to-be-loaded-infinitely-with-python.-f949b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/get-the-source-of-the-page-to-be-loaded-infinitely-with-python.-f949b/</guid>
      <description># Overview  In this article, I created an infinite loading page. You can&amp;rsquo;t get the source from curl or requests, which is a common usage for such pages, so you need to do something special. This time I will write the code to get the contents of this page.
#Environment *python 3.8.1
#Code Get the source for the page created by the code of This article. When the time and the number of acquired bytes are reached, the code acquired up to that point is output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUI creation in python using tkinter 2</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/gui-creation-in-python-using-tkinter-2-fff78/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/gui-creation-in-python-using-tkinter-2-fff78/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  Continued from last time Last time I confirmed that the application started up for the time being, but I tried adding various missing parts such as prevention of double startup
Things necessary  python 3.7.2 pandas numpy  Location It is available on github. https://github.com/snowpff14/etcresource/tree/master/pythonGui
Processing content See previous for the rough part.
 I called a thread to move the process, but it was in a state where I could call it many times because there was no lock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice actor network analysis (using word2vec and networkx) (2/2)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/voice-actor-network-analysis-using-word2vec-and-networkx-2-2-ff265/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/voice-actor-network-analysis-using-word2vec-and-networkx-2-2-ff265/</guid>
      <description>### Rough flow of analysis introduced this time  ・Create and visualize female voice actor network ・Try clustering similar voice actors using network information. ・Visualize the categorized results with Cytoscape
Hi, this is bamboo-nova. Qiita mainly throws in material analysis.
If you are interested in my serious stories and analysis, please refer to this (evacuation site)
Bamboo shoot blog
Also, I have put the source code that summarizes the series of steps so far on Github, so please refer to it if you like!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continue making stock price forecasting AI for 10 hours a day Third month</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/continue-making-stock-price-forecasting-ai-for-10-hours-a-day-third-month-fae42/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/continue-making-stock-price-forecasting-ai-for-10-hours-a-day-third-month-fae42/</guid>
      <description>[Previous previous article: 1st month](https://qiita.com/Lulu_die_Zweite/items/8e5cb713073982353ac3)  Previous article: Second month
Third month By the second month I&amp;rsquo;ve faced quite a few problems. There seems to be a limit to maximizing the prediction accuracy of one AI. Therefore, I came up with a method that may improve the prediction accuracy, so I will write it here.
##AI majority theory The method is simple, first create some good AI, preferably an odd number of AIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast calculation by increasing dimension with np.newaxis</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/broadcast-calculation-by-increasing-dimension-with-np.newaxis-faf38/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/broadcast-calculation-by-increasing-dimension-with-np.newaxis-faf38/</guid>
      <description>This is an article where I wrote down my own understanding from the question that the image of the three-dimensional np.array is grabbed and what is np.newaxis. [Here](https://qiita.com/yoshi_san/items/4cbe3abb7d46c5252fdd) for the first half article that wrote the basics of np.array image and np.newaxis.  In this article, I will explain how to use np.newaxis. Specifically, when the two-dimensional array in which two or more two-dimensional vectors are lined up is first mentioned in the first half of the article, the calculation of the square of the distance between the vectors included in both is performed by brute force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not changed from Python 2 to 3</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/not-changed-from-python-2-to-3-fe0f3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/not-changed-from-python-2-to-3-fe0f3/</guid>
      <description># python2から3に変更されない...  $ python --version Python 2.7.15 $ brew install python3 $ python3 --version - bash: python3: command not found あれ、python3がインストールされてない&amp;hellip;
解決？ # python3をインストール $ brew install python3 Ignoring bindex-0.5.0 because its extensions are not built. Try: gem pristine bindex --version 0.5.0 Ignoring bootsnap-1.3.1 because its extensions are not built. Try: gem pristine bootsnap --version 1.3.1 Ignoring byebug-10.0.2 because its extensions are not built. Try: gem pristine byebug --version 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips to conveniently use models utils.Choices</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tips-to-conveniently-use-models-utils.choices-fbbda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/tips-to-conveniently-use-models-utils.choices-fbbda/</guid>
      <description># model_utils.Choices  Django, DRF users Are you using model_utils.Choices? We use it conveniently, but basically we often use it for status management.
Is it like this?
class News(models.Model): STATUS = Choices( (&amp;#39;DRAFT&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;draft&amp;#39;), (&amp;#39;CHECK&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;waiting for review&amp;#39;), (&amp;#39;PUBLISHED&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;Public&amp;#39;), ) status = StatusField( choices_name=&amp;#39;STATUS&amp;#39;, help_text=&amp;#34;Status&amp;#34;, default=STATUS.DRAFT, ) title = models.CharField( max_length=1024, null=False, blank=False, default=&amp;#34;&amp;#34;, help_text=&amp;#34;News title&amp;#34; ) body = models.TextField( null=False, blank=False, default=&amp;#34;&amp;#34;, help_text=&amp;#34;News Details&amp;#34; ) What is the explanation (VALUE) of Choice used for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You are shown a plot such as principal component analysis, and the distributions of these two data do not differ greatly?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/you-are-shown-a-plot-such-as-principal-component-analysis-and-the-distributions-of-these-two-data-do-not-differ-greatly-f90b4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/you-are-shown-a-plot-such-as-principal-component-analysis-and-the-distributions-of-these-two-data-do-not-differ-greatly-f90b4/</guid>
      <description>When I was shown a plot from a principal component analysis, etc. and received an explanation that the distributions of these two data did not differ greatly, I had the opportunity to think &amp;quot;Is this really true?&amp;quot; It was.  #Create data
Create two kinds of data data1 and data2 consisting of three dimensions of x, y and z as follows.
import numpy as np x = np.random.normal(50,10, size=(500)) y = np.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python3 Getting Started Day 21] Chapter 10 System (10.1 ~ 10.5)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python3-getting-started-day-21-chapter-10-system-10.1-~-10.5-fb945/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python3-getting-started-day-21-chapter-10-system-10.1-~-10.5-fb945/</guid>
      <description>#10.1 file  ##10.1.1 Create by open()
 The open() function not only opens a file, but creates a new file when you request a file that does not exist.  &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; fout=open(&amp;#34;oops.txt&amp;#34;,&amp;#34;wt&amp;#34;) &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; print(&amp;#34;Oops,I created a file.&amp;#34;,file=fout) &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; fout.close() ##10.1.2 Check for existence of file by exists()
&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; import os &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; os.path.exists(&amp;#34;oops.txt&amp;#34;) True &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; os.path.exists(&amp;#34;./oops.txt&amp;#34;) True &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; os.path.exists(&amp;#34;aaa.txt&amp;#34;) False &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; os.path.exists(&amp;#34;.&amp;#34;) True &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; os.path.exists(&amp;#34;..&amp;#34;) True ##10.1.3 Checking file type with isfile()</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extract string from file in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/extract-string-from-file-in-python-fdf2f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/extract-string-from-file-in-python-fdf2f/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  What to explain in this article Sample code for the following features.
 Create a list of files under the specified directory Find out if the text in a file contains a certain string Extract text within a file from a range enclosed by a specific string  Development environment
 python 2.7 or above  Create a list of files under the specified directory code def generate_file_list(dirpath_to_search): file_list = [] for dirpath, dirnames, filenames in os.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a script to greet you at my Koshien</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-made-a-script-to-greet-you-at-my-koshien-ff45b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-made-a-script-to-greet-you-at-my-koshien-ff45b/</guid>
      <description>I tried to automate a certain task in a browser game called &amp;quot;My Koshien&amp;quot; using Python.  I don&amp;rsquo;t use Python at all, so it&amp;rsquo;s a beginner level code. Please note.
What is my Koshien High school baseball simulation game. Although it is a baseball game, the actual game is played by the CPU, and the main player is coaching and coaching. Points are required for this instruction, and among some points there is a Passion PT, which can be increased by greeting another school (other player).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaggle:Introduction to Manual Feature Engineering その1</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/kaggleintroduction-to-manual-feature-engineering-%E3%81%9D%E3%81%AE1-fcbd2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/kaggleintroduction-to-manual-feature-engineering-%E3%81%9D%E3%81%AE1-fcbd2/</guid>
      <description>https://www.kaggle.com/willkoehrsen/introduction-to-manual-feature-engineering  I thought it was better to take a note of what I was doing. Qiita says that memos are OK, so write it down here.
It&amp;rsquo;s complicated to think of combining various tables in this Notebook,
Just group by client_id and count, and add that line to application_train to increase the feature quantity, It&amp;rsquo;s easy to think.
But I wonder if this KDE plot is useful in many places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical statistics from the basics Random variables</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/mathematical-statistics-from-the-basics-random-variables-fb901/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/mathematical-statistics-from-the-basics-random-variables-fb901/</guid>
      <description>#Random variables and dice  First of all, let&amp;rsquo;s consider an example of 1 to 6 dice: game_die: which has no distortion.
The dice rolls from 1 to 6 are equally likely (there is no bias in their appearance), so the appearance of each die can be given with the following probabilities.
$ P (probability of getting 1) = \frac{1}{6}\qquad P (probability of getting 2) = \frac{1}{6}\qquad P (probability of getting 3) = \frac{1}{6}\</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Introduction to Docker] I tried to summarize various findings of Docker obtained by studying (Windows/Python)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/introduction-to-docker-i-tried-to-summarize-various-findings-of-docker-obtained-by-studying-windows-python-f7eea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/introduction-to-docker-i-tried-to-summarize-various-findings-of-docker-obtained-by-studying-windows-python-f7eea/</guid>
      <description>There was a person in charge of specialized infrastructure related things in the company, and he was kind to the environment, but it would be bad if I had to study Docker around myself as soon as possible. I&#39;ve finally been introduced to Docker recently, so I&#39;ll try to put together and try what I have learned as a memorandum.  Since I have been working on unfamiliar work such as infrastructure around my career, please forgive me for things that are rough (shallow) in terms of knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The story that seemed to be a trap for rounding off</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-the-story-that-seemed-to-be-a-trap-for-rounding-off-ffd7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-the-story-that-seemed-to-be-a-trap-for-rounding-off-ffd7b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When I was implementing a trial calculation using Python in my work, it was a story that was almost caught in a trap.
#I just wanted to round&amp;hellip;
&amp;ldquo;Oh, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you what happened right now!&amp;rdquo;
** &amp;ldquo;I thought I was rounding &amp;ldquo;2.5&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;3&amp;rdquo;, but before I knew it, it was &amp;ldquo;2&amp;quot;&amp;quot; **
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you&amp;rsquo;re saying, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what you were doing&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>python parallel/asynchronous execution memorandum</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-parallel-asynchronous-execution-memorandum-f8572/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-parallel-asynchronous-execution-memorandum-f8572/</guid>
      <description>#  A lot of Python asynchronous execution material was similar (official translation/re-editing?). It&amp;rsquo;s tough for Ojisan, who has become hard-headed, so I searched for examples and looked at sites in multiple languages, and after trial and error I finally moved, so I just summarized the liver.
Overview The examples are all patterns of external command execution on Windows Almost no commentary.
Check by PID Easy and nice. This is what Ojisan came up with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect the contents of the list into a string</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-connect-the-contents-of-the-list-into-a-string-fb88e/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-connect-the-contents-of-the-list-into-a-string-fb88e/</guid>
      <description># How to connect the contents of a list into a string  Since there was no way to make an unexpected character string, it is elementary
l = [&#39;a&#39;,&#39;b&#39;,&#39;c&#39;,&#39;d&#39;,&#39;e&#39;] a =&#39;&#39;.join(l) print(a) Output result
&#39;a b c d e&#39; **The string to combine must be (str type). ** If the element is a numeric value, it must be converted to str type using the map() function, for example.
b =&#39;_&#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning record Part 27 (31st day)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/learning-record-part-27-31st-day-fc1bc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/learning-record-part-27-31st-day-fc1bc/</guid>
      <description># Learning record (31st day)  Start of study: 12/7 (Sat) ~
Teaching materials: ・Miyuki Oshige “Details! Python3 Introductory Note&amp;rdquo; (Sotec, 2017): Dec 7 (Sat) to Dec 19 (Thurs) ・Progate Python course (5 courses in total): 12/19 (Thurs) to 12/21 (Sat) ・Andreas C. Müller, Sarah Guido &amp;ldquo;(Japanese title) Machine learning started with Python&amp;rdquo; (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Japan, 2017): December 21 (Sat)-December 23 (Sat) ・Kaggle :Real or Not? NLP with Disaster Tweets ：Posted on Saturday, December 28th until Friday, January 3rd Adjustment ・Wes Mckinney &amp;ldquo;(Japanese title) Introduction to data analysis using Python&amp;rdquo; (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Japan, 2018): 1/4 (Wed) to 1/13 (Mon) read ・Yasuyuki Saito “Deep Learning from Zero” (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Japan, 2016): 1/15 (Wed)-1/20 (Mon) ・**François Chollet “Deep Learning with Python and Keras” (Quepe, 2018): 1/21 (Tue) ~ **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using LiquidTap Python Client ①</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/using-liquidtap-python-client-ff676/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/using-liquidtap-python-client-ff676/</guid>
      <description># table of contents   Introduction Get &amp;ldquo;Order Book&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;Liquid by Quoine&amp;rdquo;  #Introduction
The API of &amp;ldquo;Liquid by Quoine&amp;rdquo; is open to the public, so I will try various hits. First, from the WebSocket service.
#Get &amp;ldquo;Order Book&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;Liquid by Quoine&amp;rdquo;
Let&amp;rsquo;s install the library and get BTC/JPY. (2020.01.22)
Install library $ pip3 install liquidtap Writing code based on the sample of the head family Home: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[#1] Make Minecraft with Python. -Survey and design-</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/#1-make-minecraft-with-python.-survey-and-design-fd9ff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/#1-make-minecraft-with-python.-survey-and-design-fd9ff/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;font color=&amp;quot;grey&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Part of pictures, articles, images on this page are copyrighted by Mojang AB.&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;  #Overview This project reproduces the world-famous sandbox game &amp;ldquo;Minecraft&amp;rdquo; in the programming language &amp;ldquo;Python&amp;rdquo;.
Next article: [#2] Make Minecraft with Python. -Model drawing and player implementation-
##Trigger My first exposure to programming came from “Minecraft”.
That was over 4 years ago. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in so-called remodeling contents called &amp;ldquo;MOD&amp;rdquo; in Minecraft, and entered the world of programming, &amp;ldquo;I want to make it myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get RGB and HSV histogram with OpenCV</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-get-rgb-and-hsv-histogram-with-opencv-ff4a0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-get-rgb-and-hsv-histogram-with-opencv-ff4a0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;m working with images, and I wanted to use the RGB and HSV histogram information as features. So I tried to extract the histogram using OpenCV. Leave it as a memo.
#histogram
You can think of a histogram as a graph or plot to know the overall distribution of pixel values in an image. Generally, it is a plot with pixel value on the horizontal axis and frequency of pixel value on the vertical axis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try the book Introduction to Natural Language Application Development in 15 Steps-Chapter 2 Step 03 Memo Morphological Analysis and Wakachi</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/try-the-book-introduction-to-natural-language-application-development-in-15-steps-chapter-2-step-03-memo-morphological-analysis-and-wakachi-fb592/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/try-the-book-introduction-to-natural-language-application-development-in-15-steps-chapter-2-step-03-memo-morphological-analysis-and-wakachi-fb592/</guid>
      <description># Content  This is a memo for yourself when reading Introduction to Natural Language Processing Application. This time in Chapter 2, Step 03, I will write down my point.
#Preparation
 Personal Mac PC: MacOS Mojave version 10.14.6 docker version: Both Client and Server version 19.03.2  Chapter overview Understand the operation of MeCab and try tuning. We will also check morphological analyzers other than MeCab.
#03.1 MeCab
dictionary Written by MeCab is based on a dictionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 66 [Introduction to Kaggle] The easiest Titanic forecast</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/day-66-introduction-to-kaggle-the-easiest-titanic-forecast-fbc03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/day-66-introduction-to-kaggle-the-easiest-titanic-forecast-fbc03/</guid>
      <description>I tried to challenge &amp;quot;[Titanic: Machine Learning from Disaster](https://www.kaggle.com/c/titanic/notebooks)&amp;quot; of #Kaggle.  Kaggle is like a fighting party where you compete for machine learning. When I entered, there was content for beginners, so I will watch the guidance video at once.

Very fast English! ! ! The contents were an outline of the Titanic accident, explanation of the dataset, tutorial, how to use Kaggle, etc.
I can&amp;rsquo;t hear it because it&amp;rsquo;s too fast to speak, so [Japanese] Titanic sinking accident (https://ja.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For the time being, try using FireBase Cloud Firestore with Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/for-the-time-being-try-using-firebase-cloud-firestore-with-python-f8a2e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/for-the-time-being-try-using-firebase-cloud-firestore-with-python-f8a2e/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  &amp;ldquo;For the time being, I want to use Cloud Firestore of FireBase with Python!&amp;rdquo;, While following FireBase&amp;rsquo;s official document, write the basic procedure for &amp;ldquo;data input/output&amp;rdquo; I will.
##First&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s create a &amp;ldquo;project&amp;rdquo;
 A &amp;ldquo;project&amp;rdquo; is a &amp;ldquo;collective&amp;rdquo; for using services such as Firestore, Cloud Functions, Authentication, and Hosting. Projects created with FireBase are also common with GCP.
 Now let&amp;rsquo;s create a project.
First, go to FireBase Console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language processing 100 knocks-88: 10 words with high similarity</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/language-processing-100-knocks-88-10-words-with-high-similarity-fa498/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/language-processing-100-knocks-88-10-words-with-high-similarity-fa498/</guid>
      <description>[Language Processing 100 Knock 2015](http://www.cl.ecei.tohoku.ac.jp/nlp100/) 88th record &amp;quot;10 words with high similarity&amp;quot; is recorded.  Extract similar words from all words. This is also the process I want to do from my mailbox and minutes. Technically it is almost the same as the previous content.
Reference link    Links Remarks     088. 10 words with high similarity.ipynb Answer program GitHub link   Amateur language processing 100 knocks: 88 I have always taken care of 100 language processing knocks    #Environment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probability prediction of imbalanced data</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/probability-prediction-of-imbalanced-data-fe87b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/probability-prediction-of-imbalanced-data-fe87b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When classifying by machine learning, it is sometimes desirable to obtain the probability of belonging to those classes as well as the classification result. When the number of data for positive cases is extremely small compared to the number of data for negative cases (such data is called imbalanced data), if the prediction model is constructed using all of those data, the prediction result will also be negative. Often, it tends to be difficult to accurately classify positive data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books on data science to read in 2020</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Przemek Chojecki](https://towardsdatascience.com/@pchojecki),[[DataScienceBooksyoushouldreadin2020](https://towardsdatascience.com/data-science-books-you-should-read-in-2020-358f70e1d9b2)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
Data science is arguably one of the hottest markets right now. Almost all companies are looking for or considering a data science role.
So it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to become a data scientist. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re already a data scientist and want to promote to a senior position, it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to hone your skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Production of thermal management system with Raspberry Pi and ESP32 (2) Transmission device production</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/production-of-thermal-management-system-with-raspberry-pi-and-esp32-2-transmission-device-production-fd465/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/production-of-thermal-management-system-with-raspberry-pi-and-esp32-2-transmission-device-production-fd465/</guid>
      <description>Creating a device that sends temperature and humidity data to a Raspberry Pi.  Overall layout Parts are soldered to the universal board. ##circuit Connect SHT31 and ssd1306 in parallel with i2c. That said, just connect the four lines in parallel. Easy easy.
Confirm i2c address Once the wiring is decided, check the address on the breadboard. Code referenced this page.
Run the code and note the address that came out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flask-Create Web Service with SQLAlchemy &#43; PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/flask-create-web-service-with-sqlalchemy-postgresql-fa599/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/flask-create-web-service-with-sqlalchemy-postgresql-fa599/</guid>
      <description># Flask-Create a web service with SQLAlchemy + PostgreSQL  Introduction We will introduce using a sample application (Feedback).
This article is for Mac environment, but the procedure is the same for Windows environment. Please read the environment-dependent part and try again. 
Purpose After reading this article, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to:
| No. | Overview | Keywords | | :&amp;mdash; | :&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; | :&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; &amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | | 1 | Flask-SQLAlchemy Development | Flask-SQLAlchemy, psycopg2 | | 2 | PostgreSQL settings | psql, Flask-Migrate |</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupyter Learning Note_005</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/jupyter-learning-note_005-ff08c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/jupyter-learning-note_005-ff08c/</guid>
      <description>## How to clone GitHub repository to [google colab](https://colab.research.google.com/)  Follow the steps below.
 mount google drive  from google.colab import drive drive.mount(&amp;#39;/content/drive&amp;#39;)  create a repository in the location specified by git clone  import shutil import os # Change current directory os.chdir(&amp;#39;/content/drive/My Drive&amp;#39;) cur_dir = os.getcwd() git_name =&amp;#39;/MongoDB_PyMongo_Tutorial&amp;#39; git_folder = cur_dir + git_name #Delete if it exists if os.path.exists(git_folder): shutil.rmtree(git_folder) #Clone !git clone https://github.com/Giffy/MongoDB_PyMongo_Tutorial.git  Implementation result   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiita API Oauth with Django</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/qiita-api-oauth-with-django-f8279/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/qiita-api-oauth-with-django-f8279/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There is a convenient API called QiitaAPI for handling Qiita. https://qiita.com/api/v2/docs
Here is a sample to try it out with Django.
Only Oauth is dealt with in this article (other than that, it&amp;rsquo;s just a request)
Register the application from the following URL. https://qiita.com/settings/applications
You will get a Client ID and a Client Secret.
Around authentication ##GET /api/v2/oauth/authorize
Display the authorization screen for the user. If the user authorizes, code is added to the Callback URL specified in the application registration above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python open and io.open are the same</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-open-and-io.open-are-the-same-fac0d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-open-and-io.open-are-the-same-fac0d/</guid>
      <description>Python&#39;s `open` and `io.open` are the same. I did not know.  &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; import io &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; io.open == open True </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach explanation for beginners who are in the top 1.5% (0.83732) in Kaggle Titanic_2</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/approach-explanation-for-beginners-who-are-in-the-top-1.5-0.83732-in-kaggle-titanic_2-fb6aa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/approach-explanation-for-beginners-who-are-in-the-top-1.5-0.83732-in-kaggle-titanic_2-fb6aa/</guid>
      <description>[Last time](https://qiita.com/shiroino11111/items/bc3889fa38ff32d46c13),followedby[KaggleTitanic](https://www.kaggle.com/c/titanic/submissions)totop1.5%(0.83732) I will explain the approach of.  The code used is titanic(0.83732)_2 from Github. This time, we will extend the submission score to 0.81339 and prepare for the next time it will be 0.83732. Also, before forecasting, we will visualize the data used in Last time and analyze the data.
###1. Import the required library and read the CSV.
import pandas as pd import numpy as np import matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GET/POST communication with Flask (and for CORS support)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/get-post-communication-with-flask-and-for-cors-support-fa72c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/get-post-communication-with-flask-and-for-cors-support-fa72c/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Since the content of POST communication in Flask was ambiguous, both GET/POST communication are summarized here. ▽ There are &amp;ldquo;Communication in form&amp;rdquo;/&amp;ldquo;Communication in Json format&amp;rdquo; as contents. When you search for &amp;ldquo;Flask POST&amp;rdquo;, the information is messed up. By the way, it is Python 3.7.
#GET communication
from flask import Flask, request, jsonfy app = Flask(__name__) @app.route(&amp;#34;/&amp;#34;, methods=[&amp;#34;POST&amp;#34;]) def test(): data = request.args.get(&amp;#39;hoge&amp;#39;, ``) # Get value of hoge=value return data # Return as it is for sample POST communication Communication in Json format from flask import Flask, request, jsonfy import json app = Flask(__name__) @app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Blue Prism process using Python (SOAP)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/run-blue-prism-process-using-python-soap-fae08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/run-blue-prism-process-using-python-soap-fae08/</guid>
      <description>Introduction   With Blue Prism, a process (robot) can be exposed as a WebService and can be executed externally. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll write a client in Python and call a Blue Prism process.
There are two prerequisites for running the process exposed as a WebService. Another article and set the preconditions.
  A. Blue Prism server service is running B. public There is a runtime resource started by the switch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Until the API made with Flask&#43;MySQL is converted to Docker</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/until-the-api-made-with-flask-mysql-is-converted-to-docker-fe666/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/until-the-api-made-with-flask-mysql-is-converted-to-docker-fe666/</guid>
      <description>## this is?  I want to make an API. I want to make it with Flask+MySQL. And I want to make it Docker. Make a note of this procedure. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know where to use Docker, so concentrate on this.
things to do  Create a simple API with Flask alone. Convert 2.1 to Docker. Prepare MySQL. Enable the integration of Flask and MySQL with docker-compose.  1. Create a simple API with Flask alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a LINEBot with Django</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/create-a-linebot-with-django-f9aa5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/create-a-linebot-with-django-f9aa5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I summarized the article about using LINEBot with Django because it was a little researched and it was old.
For the time being, I will create an Omukai Bot that returns the text sent as an introduction to LINE Bot.
Here article uses SDK, but I&amp;rsquo;m a Python beginner ~~ I can&amp;rsquo;t even throw an HTTP request with Python ~~ I want to do it.
I&amp;rsquo;m a Django beginner with less than a week of Django history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python memorandum-points of personal interest-</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-memorandum-points-of-personal-interest-fdb0a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-memorandum-points-of-personal-interest-fdb0a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I was at a loss because I had a lot of use of Python 1, and I am currently learning with the goal of passing the &amp;ldquo;Python 3 Engineer Certification Basic Exam 2&amp;rdquo; @daikikatsuragawa is. In this article, I will introduce the points of personal interest as a reminder through learning Python. We will update and edit it at will. Please note.
Personally interested Command to terminate the interpreter quit() Command to exit the activated state deactivate Power calculation 3 ** 2 Multibyte characters (double-byte characters) can be used as variables However, it is not recommended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualize Go&#39;s internal package relationships for each commit</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/visualize-gos-internal-package-relationships-for-each-commit-fe077/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/visualize-gos-internal-package-relationships-for-each-commit-fe077/</guid>
      <description>![call-aimation.gif](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/479931/3ec1a7e5-ce6a-92cd-0a86-8ace5e944941.gif)  Program used: bxcodec/go-clean-arch
Overview  It is difficult to understand programs that have complicated Go internal package relationships.   I want to visualize Since it&amp;rsquo;s a big deal, I visualize it for each commit and make it an animation  #Preparation
 Go Python3 Graphviz ImageMagick  #Code
 st34-satoshi/for-each-commit  What you did  Get the commit log Execute command for each commit Output the internal package relations of Go to dot faril and create a gif Align the gif size for each commit and create an animation  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Control Engineering] Calculation of transfer function and state space model by Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/control-engineering-calculation-of-transfer-function-and-state-space-model-by-python-f9914/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/control-engineering-calculation-of-transfer-function-and-state-space-model-by-python-f9914/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I decided to do robot control at work, so I summarized it to know the following. ・Review of basic knowledge of control engineering ・How to draw a control system or PID control with python ・To understand the Kalman filter and self-localization by understanding the state space model
References Hiroki Minami, Ohmsha, &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Control Engineering with Python&amp;rdquo;
#Content Contents of Chapter 3 of &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Control Engineering with Python&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Introduction to Python] Basic usage of lambda expression</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/introduction-to-python-basic-usage-of-lambda-expression-fd429/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/introduction-to-python-basic-usage-of-lambda-expression-fd429/</guid>
      <description># Article purpose #  The same Python introductory person as myself should understand the basic usage of lambda expression.
The other day, my senior asked me about the use of lambda expressions, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t use them very much and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t answer them well, so I investigated and summarized them. At that time, I referred to the following sites. Or rather, this article is for organizing my thoughts, so I think it is easier to see the linked article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C language to see and remember Part 5 Call C language from Python (argument) array</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/c-language-to-see-and-remember-part-5-call-c-language-from-python-argument-array-fdd3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/c-language-to-see-and-remember-part-5-call-c-language-from-python-argument-array-fdd3d/</guid>
      <description>Pythonからfloatの配列を渡し、タプルで合計と平均を返す。  import myModule as capi import random x=[random.uniform(0, 100) for x in range(100)] s=0.0 for a in x: s=s+a print(&amp;#34;c &amp;#34;,s,s/len(x)) a=capi.fsum_avr(x) print(&amp;#34;py&amp;#34;,a) 実行すると &amp;gt;python capi.py py 5025.24247203747 50.252424720374705 c (5025.24247203747, 50.252424720374705) #include &amp;lt;Python.h&amp;gt;static PyObject* fsum_avr(PyObject* self, PyObject* args) { long n; double sum=0.0,avr,a; PyObject* c_list, *item; if (!PyArg_ParseTuple(args, &amp;#34;O&amp;#34;, &amp;amp;c_list)) return NULL; // Check list  if PyList_Check(c_list) n = PyList_Size(c_list); else return NULL; for (int i = 0; i &amp;lt; n; i++){ item = PyList_GetItem(c_list, i); a = PyFloat_AsDouble(item); // Increment the reference count  sum = sum + a; Py_DECREF(item); // Decrement the reference count  } avr=sum/n; return Py_BuildValue(&amp;#34;(dd)&amp;#34;,sum,avr); } static PyMethodDef myMethods[] = { { &amp;#34;fsum_avr&amp;#34;,fsum_avr, METH_VARARGS, &amp;#34;sum avr&amp;#34;}, { NULL } }; static struct PyModuleDef myModule = { PyModuleDef_HEAD_INIT,&amp;#34;myModule&amp;#34;,&amp;#34;C API Module&amp;#34;,-1,myMethods }; PyMODINIT_FUNC PyInit_myModule(void){ return PyModule_Create(&amp;amp;myModule); } 注目ポイント 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision : Object Detection - Non Maximum Suppression</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/computer-vision-object-detection-non-maximum-suppression-fbf3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/computer-vision-object-detection-non-maximum-suppression-fbf3b/</guid>
      <description>#Target  Implement Non Maximum Suppression used in object detection.
#Introduction This section introduces Intersection over Union and Non Maximum Suppression used in Computer Vision: Object Detection Part2-Single Shot Multi Detector.
##Non Maximum Suppression (NMS) In object detection, multiple candidate regions that are presumed to exist may be obtained for one recognized object, as shown in the figure below.
The part surrounded by the colored rectangle indicates the candidate area, and the display at the upper left of each candidate area indicates the category and the certainty factor of the object existing in that candidate area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XAI : AdvImg - Adversarial Images</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/xai-advimg-adversarial-images-fdc7a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/xai-advimg-adversarial-images-fdc7a/</guid>
      <description>#Target  I tried to generate a hostile image using Microsoft Cognitive Toolkit (CNTK).
It is assumed that CNTK and NVIDIA GPU CUDA are installed.
#Introduction
What is a hostile image? A very interesting model in the field of deep learning is the Adversarial Generating Network (GAN) [1].AdversarialExamples[2][3] influenced the birth of GAN. We will focus on the images here, so we will be dealing with hostile images.
Adversarial images are known to be a very effective way to deceive trained image recognition models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install dlib for Python (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/install-dlib-for-python-windows-fd84f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/install-dlib-for-python-windows-fd84f/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m stumbled upon soberly, so I will explain with a lot of images.  There may be unnecessary steps, but I will introduce the method that will definitely be tried after various trials. I would like to gradually edit to reduce waste.
0. Assumption The environment is as follows. ・Windows 10 Home 64 bit
1. Install Python You can download it from the following. https://www.python.org/downloads/windows/
This time, install &amp;ldquo;Python 3.8.1 64bit&amp;rdquo; On the installation screen, check &amp;ldquo;Add Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Model construction] Using the data set of Reuters communication, create a model (MLP) that classifies news into topics with keras (TensorFlow 2 system)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/model-construction-using-the-data-set-of-reuters-communication-create-a-model-mlp-that-classifies-news-into-topics-with-keras-tensorflow-2-system-ff9e0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/model-construction-using-the-data-set-of-reuters-communication-create-a-model-mlp-that-classifies-news-into-topics-with-keras-tensorflow-2-system-ff9e0/</guid>
      <description>## Last pre-processing!  This article is a sequel to [Pre-processing]. [Pre-processing] Creating a model (MLP) for classifying news into topics using Reuters communication data set (TensorFlow 2 series)
Please refer to the pre-processing section for the operating environment.
Model learning Create a model using the preprocessed news article text x_train and the news label y_train.
This time, we will use a two-layer MLP (Multilayer Perceptron) as a simple model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of differences between Ruby on rails and Django ~Basics~</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/summary-of-differences-between-ruby-on-rails-and-django-~basics~-ffae0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/summary-of-differences-between-ruby-on-rails-and-django-~basics~-ffae0/</guid>
      <description>##1.First of all  I am a beginner who has been programming for 4 months! Since I am studying Ruby on rails and Django, As output, I&amp;rsquo;d like to write the basic code difference! ! :pencil2::beginner: Since I started learning from rails, What about Django in terms of basic rails? It is written from the perspective of: smile: We hope you find it helpful. (Since I am studying, I plan to add and correct it at any time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting when introducing MongoDB with python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/setting-when-introducing-mongodb-with-python-fe050/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/setting-when-introducing-mongodb-with-python-fe050/</guid>
      <description>It records how to set up the popular MongoDB database for data analysis.  Download Download link → https://www.mongodb.com/download-center/community
Installation settings Set the path to C:\mongodb (not C:\Program Files)
Installation is set to Custom instead of Complete, and a new folder is created under C drive. ↓ 
Installation takes about 5 minutes.
After installation, create a C:\mongodb\data folder.
How to start the server Move the directory with cd C:\mongodb\bin, (If you often use it from now on, you may register C:\mongodb\bin as an environmental coefficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using anaconda&#39;s virtual environment with Zsh (defect support)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/using-anacondas-virtual-environment-with-zsh-defect-support-fbcb5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/using-anacondas-virtual-environment-with-zsh-defect-support-fbcb5/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Using Jupyter Notebook of anaconda installed with pyenv with zsh (defect support), following trial and error as a memorandum for using Jupyter Notebook with Zsh Keep.
Defect status  $ conda info -e can confirm the virtual environment, but cannot activate it with $ conda activate &amp;lt;virtual environment name&amp;gt;  #Environment Mac OS Mojave
Method 1. Try running the virtual environment $ conda activate &amp;lt;virtual environment name&amp;gt; Error message returned</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can try it with copy and paste! Let&#39;s draw a cool network diagram with Python&#39;s networkx</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/you-can-try-it-with-copy-and-paste-lets-draw-a-cool-network-diagram-with-pythons-networkx-fe9b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/you-can-try-it-with-copy-and-paste-lets-draw-a-cool-network-diagram-with-pythons-networkx-fe9b8/</guid>
      <description>## Let&#39;s draw a network diagram with networkx that can draw a cool network diagram during winter vacation  Do you all have a good winter vacation? Our company has been taking a day off from 28th to 5th and is really thankful to the mice.
But I think engineers should refrain from Mac refugees and improve their skills at such times.
Today we will introduce a library called networkx that can draw network diagrams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About 02/02/2020 *This is a Python article.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/about-02-02-2020-this-is-a-python-article.-fb8cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/about-02-02-2020-this-is-a-python-article.-fb8cc/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  One day 2019 I came across a wonderful article.
About April 5, 2013 *This is a Ruby article. TECHSCORE BLOG
The following is a summary of the contents.
 There is no overlap in the numbers that make up April 5, 2013. Wow! When was the last time? Next time Survey by Ruby program! The last time was &amp;ldquo;○○○○○○○○○○&amp;rdquo; and the next time was &amp;ldquo;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&amp;rdquo;!  I personally read it and enjoyed it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Function review</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/function-review-fe052/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/function-review-fe052/</guid>
      <description>Function that determines whether the specified number is positive or negative  def discri(a): if a&amp;gt; 0: return str(a) +&amp;#39;is a positive number. &amp;#39; elif a == 0: return str(a) +&amp;#39;is zero. &amp;#39; else: return str(a) +&amp;#39;is a negative number. &amp;#39; print(discri(15)) print(discri(0)) print(discri(-24)) Judge 15 and 0 and -24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips [Replace/Replace/Convert/Change/Update/Replace] Replacing the Placeholder of INPUT in FreezeGraphed .pb file of Tensorflow</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tips-replace-replace-convert-change-update-replace-replacing-the-placeholder-of-input-in-freezegraphed-.pb-file-of-tensorflow-fed7e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/tips-replace-replace-convert-change-update-replace-replacing-the-placeholder-of-input-in-freezegraphed-.pb-file-of-tensorflow-fed7e/</guid>
      <description>**`[1, ?, ?, 3]`** The **`Placeholder`** of the .pb file defined with the input size of **`[1, 513, 513, 3]`** Sample program that regenerates .pb by forcibly replacing it with **`Placeholder`**.  For the name=&#39;image&#39; part, freely specify the name of the placeholder after replacement. The placeholder name of the model before conversion is specified in the image:0 part of input_map={&#39;image:0&#39;: inputs}.
import tensorflow as tf from tensorflow.tools.graph_transforms import TransformGraph with tf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half a year when the Gori Gori literary school almost learned AI</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</guid>
      <description># Half-year when the Gori Gori literary system (deviation value 40 first half) learned AI  Hi, it&amp;rsquo;s a rugged ~~ macho~~ humanities. After graduating from commercial high school, I went to the Faculty of Humanities, so it&amp;rsquo;s different from other humanities. It is a thoroughbred world of humanities.
Although it is a vital math skill, I only studied math A up to high school, and just started math at university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For those who look at the log while learning with machine learning ~ Muscle training with LightGBM ~</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</guid>
      <description>What do you guys do when learning models with machine learning?  Did you just look at the log output to the console? &amp;ldquo;Oh, it was lower than I expected!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oh, the accuracy is getting worse, do your best!!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly fun to think, though.
But when I cheered up, the model doesn&amp;rsquo;t do its best, and there is no dramatic development, so it&amp;rsquo;s a waste of time to look at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried touching Wagtail (1), let&#39;s override the save method.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-touching-wagtail-1-lets-override-the-save-method.-fe9c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-touching-wagtail-1-lets-override-the-save-method.-fe9c6/</guid>
      <description>#### INTRODUCTION  Hello
I was developing using Wagtail a while ago. Wagtail&amp;rsquo;s Japanese literature is not very large, so reading English literature is required.
As an engineer, the ability to read English literature is very important, I wish there were references written in Japanese I think many people should think that. I think
So I&amp;rsquo;ll write the code using Wagtail and output it. This is the first of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Send and receive data with MQTT via Watson IoT Platform</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/send-and-receive-data-with-mqtt-via-watson-iot-platform-fbdfd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/send-and-receive-data-with-mqtt-via-watson-iot-platform-fbdfd/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Watson IoT Platform (Internet of Things Platform, WIOTP) is a platform for IoT based on IBM Cloud. We provide various functions such as collection, storage, and visualization of data obtained from devices such as sensors. An official SDK for connecting devices and applications is provided, and you can send and receive data via MQTT. This article explains how to do this.
Watson IoT Platform concept First, I will explain the concept of &amp;ldquo;things&amp;rdquo; handled by WIOTP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of Excel operation using OpenPyXL in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/summary-of-excel-operation-using-openpyxl-in-python-fd3ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/summary-of-excel-operation-using-openpyxl-in-python-fd3ab/</guid>
      <description>https://www.yuyagishita.com/tech/python/openpyxl/  Moved to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision : Object Detection Part1 - Bounding Box preprocessing</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/computer-vision-object-detection-part1-bounding-box-preprocessing-f94eb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/computer-vision-object-detection-part1-bounding-box-preprocessing-f94eb/</guid>
      <description>#Target  Summary of object detection using Microsoft Cognitive Toolkit (CNTK).
Part 1 prepares for object detection using Microsoft Cognitive Toolkit. As a training data set for object detection, Microsoft Common Objects in Context (COCO) provided by Microsoft is used.
We will introduce them in the following order.
 Object detection by neural network Pretreatment of bounding box Dimension Clustering for creating Anchor Box Create a file to be read by the built-in reader provided by CNTK  #Introduction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradation image generation with Python [1]｜np.linspace</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/gradation-image-generation-with-python-1np.linspace-ff031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/gradation-image-generation-with-python-1np.linspace-ff031/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This time, I will try to generate a gradient image with python, referring to this article.
#Gradation image generation This time we will generate an image using two functions.
def gradation_2d_color(start, stop, size, is_horizontal): if is_horizontal: return np.tile(np.linspace(start, stop, size[1]), (size[0], 1)) else: return np.tile(np.linspace(start, stop, size[0]), (size[1], 1)).T Use np.linspace to create a one-dimensional array of length height (or width) that stores the values of the arithmetic progression obtained by dividing the range from start to stop by the number of height (or width).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn while making! Deep reinforcement learning_1</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/learn-while-making-deep-reinforcement-learning_1-fc266/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/learn-while-making-deep-reinforcement-learning_1-fc266/</guid>
      <description># Deep Reinforcement Learning-Practical Programming with Pytorch-  I am Harima, a 1st year master of science graduate student. I will summarize my learning contents in a memo. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry it&amp;rsquo;s hard to see. I would like to know what you do not understand.
 Implementation code (GitHub) https://github.com/YutaroOgawa/Deep-Reinforcement-Learning-Book
 Chap.2 Let&amp;rsquo;s implement reinforcement learning for maze tasks 2.1 How to use Python 2.2 Implement mazes and agents import numpy as np import matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notify the chat of new articles of Qiita Organization to improve learning efficiency of the organization!</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/notify-the-chat-of-new-articles-of-qiita-organization-to-improve-learning-efficiency-of-the-organization-fbebd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/notify-the-chat-of-new-articles-of-qiita-organization-to-improve-learning-efficiency-of-the-organization-fbebd/</guid>
      <description>We are promoting the output activity of Qiita articles in-house. It&#39;s G-awa. The learning method using output is highly recommended and is highly recommended. However, on the other hand, it is difficult for one person to continue alone, so it is important for the team and organization to support each other. If you are alone, you tend to break your heart.  &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-b_wxsoyflcs/WZP38JpI0LI/AAAAABGDA/troMJOw1KGUpq7yueRTgIdPc85o_kexXQCLcBGAs/s400/tamashii_nukeru_man.png&amp;rdquo; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; //2.bp.blogspot.com/-aIs9YKfGlEk/Vy2v2rXYgjI/AAAAAAAA6b0/PuaALahZfJsIluEeFOKgfgOy43qrc8bBQCLcB/s450/enjin_circle_wakamono.png&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;40%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;
I read yesterday&amp;rsquo;s article and it was very helpful :thumbsup: It&amp;rsquo;s a great environment for engineers to grow when there is an environment in which they can encourage each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice actor history Scraping Wikipedia to see how many years ago I became a voice actor in the Aikatsu! series</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/voice-actor-history-scraping-wikipedia-to-see-how-many-years-ago-i-became-a-voice-actor-in-the-aikatsu-series-f803a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/voice-actor-history-scraping-wikipedia-to-see-how-many-years-ago-i-became-a-voice-actor-in-the-aikatsu-series-f803a/</guid>
      <description>This article is [Aikatsu! Advent Calendar 2019](https://adventar.org/calendars/4521) This is the 18th day article.  Yesterday was gecko655&amp;rsquo;s article &amp;ldquo;[Aikatsu! Ask Spotify to tell us about the musical characteristics of the song]&amp;rdquo; (https://gecko655.hatenablog.com/entry/aikatsu_adc_2019_17)&amp;quot;.
Thing you want to do I think the voice actor is one of the elements that supports the &amp;ldquo;Aikatsu!&amp;rdquo; series. Aikatsu! To become a voice actor, I scraped Wikipedia to get what year it was cast for some role in the &amp;ldquo;Aikatsu!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Completely understood Chapter 3 of Create and Move ALife</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/completely-understood-chapter-3-of-create-and-move-alife-ff98a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/completely-understood-chapter-3-of-create-and-move-alife-ff98a/</guid>
      <description># Emergence   How the pieces are defined &amp;ldquo;Open and close&amp;rdquo; is required for each individual -Open to receive changes in the environment and lock in changes to sustain yourself &amp;ldquo;Opening and closing&amp;rdquo; is a structure that recursively refers to itself and is necessary for emergence of a lifelike individual A system that has the mechanism of &amp;ldquo;the smallest unit of life&amp;rdquo; that can create and maintain itself is called &amp;ldquo;autopoiesis&amp;rdquo;  SCL model  One of the models that creates the concept of autopoiesis is the &amp;ldquo;SCL (Substrate Catalyst Link)&amp;rdquo; model This question of &amp;ldquo;what is emergence?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display and analyze only some columns in CASTable</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/display-and-analyze-only-some-columns-in-castable-fcbe4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/display-and-analyze-only-some-columns-in-castable-fcbe4/</guid>
      <description>[SAS Viya](https://www.sas.com/ja_jp/software/viya.html)isanAIplatform.ItisavailablethroughlanguagessuchasPython,JavaandR.AtableobjectcalledCASTableisusedinSASViya(CASstandsforCloudAnalyticServices). This time, I will introduce a method to display information by extracting only some columns from CAS Table.  Get table from database First, connect to SAS Viya.
import swat conn = swat.CAS(&amp;#39;server-name.mycompany.com&amp;#39;, 5570,&amp;#39;username&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;password&amp;#39;) Then get the CASTable. This time I use CSV of IRIS data.
tbl = conn.loadtable(&amp;#39;data/iris.csv&amp;#39;, caslib=&amp;#39;casuser&amp;#39;).casTable Get column You can retrieve columns by specifying the key with tbl as a dict.
col = tbl[&amp;#39;sepal_width&amp;#39;] col The output looks like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(For lawyers) Extract behavior of Office software from .evtx file</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/for-lawyers-extract-behavior-of-office-software-from-.evtx-file-f8fb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/for-lawyers-extract-behavior-of-office-software-from-.evtx-file-f8fb4/</guid>
      <description>About a year ago, I wrote an article [Parsing .evtx files with Python](https://qiita.com/kasanma3104/items/6971d3e7d09de134da37), but roughly speaking, it is called its application. Or?  Regardless of whether a lawyer uses it to prove working hours in a court&amp;hellip; wondering if you might want to work and extract that data from an EVTX (Windows XML Event Log) file that records the Windows system log? think. (The EVTX file seems to be in Win7 format, but it may be different format depending on the OS version, but I think the idea will not change so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airtest, one question one answer. Unity app E2E test starting with Airtest and Poco</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/airtest-one-question-one-answer.-unity-app-e2e-test-starting-with-airtest-and-poco-f83d5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/airtest-one-question-one-answer.-unity-app-e2e-test-starting-with-airtest-and-poco-f83d5/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 12/20 article of [Sumzap Advent Calendar 2019 #1](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/sumzap1).  What is # Airtest
https://airtest.netease.com/ Cross platform UI automation IDE developed and published by NetEase. Here we will refer to the generic name of IDEs and projects for automated testing of mobile applications that use image recognition. By using this, you can create test code without knowing the code on the project directly. You can mass-produce the test as if it were an E2E test, or repeat the same action endlessly as an aging test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to create a model with the sample of Amazon SageMaker Autopilot</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-create-a-model-with-the-sample-of-amazon-sagemaker-autopilot-fb4c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-create-a-model-with-the-sample-of-amazon-sagemaker-autopilot-fb4c8/</guid>
      <description>What is #SageMaker Autopilot?  AWS provides automatic preprocessing, algorithm selection, and hyperparameter optimization. It&amp;rsquo;s AutoML that runs on SageMaker. This time, I have an Autopilot sample, so I&amp;rsquo;d like to actually run it. →Autopilot sample
Try running the sample First, create the required libraries and Session.
import sagemaker import boto3 from sagemaker import get_execution_role region = boto3.Session().region_name session = sagemaker.Session() bucket = session.default_bucket() prefix =&#39;sagemaker/autopilot-dm&#39; role = get_execution_role() sm = boto3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a compatibility judgment program with python&#39;s random module.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/make-a-compatibility-judgment-program-with-pythons-random-module.-fb10f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/make-a-compatibility-judgment-program-with-pythons-random-module.-fb10f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is a game for beginners. Please feel free to read it.
This time, I made a program to judge compatibility with that child that I often see on the net.
#Program creation Let&amp;rsquo;s make it.
The goal this time is to enter the names of the two people you want to judge and to express the compatibility of those two as a percentage.
The random module is used for the% display part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Crawling &amp; Scraping Chapter 4 Summary</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-crawling-scraping-chapter-4-summary-fdecf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-crawling-scraping-chapter-4-summary-fdecf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Learning summary of &amp;ldquo;Python crawling &amp;amp; scraping [enhanced and revised version] Practical development guide for data collection and analysis&amp;rdquo; The fourth chapter of this time was mainly about the points to note when making a crawler under the theme of &amp;ldquo;methods for practical use&amp;rdquo;.
#4.1 Crawler characteristics ##4.1.1 Crawler with state
  Create a crawler that supports cookies when crawling sites that require login -Python&amp;rsquo;s Requests library automatically sends cookies to the server by using Session object</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MacBook Pro でOpenPose</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/macbook-pro-%E3%81%A7openpose-fccb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/macbook-pro-%E3%81%A7openpose-fccb4/</guid>
      <description>While studying machine learning and Deep Leaning articles on MacBook Pro, I posted an article that you can detect posture on Mac  I found some and tried variously, but it worked, so I will write it as a memorandum.
#environment
 MacBook Pro 15in 2018 2.2 GHz Core i7 32GB Memory Mojave 10.14.6 python 3.7.5 Install python, virtualenv and wget with homebrew  Setup steps Preparation In preparation, set up a Python virtual environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultra simple case k-means python code</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/ultra-simple-case-k-means-python-code-fa856/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/ultra-simple-case-k-means-python-code-fa856/</guid>
      <description>## python code for super simple case of k-means method  In the humanities of statistical application of the statistical test 1st grade in 2019, there was a problem about the initial value dependence of the k-means method, but here, in order to confirm that k-means actually depends on the initial value, I wrote the python code for a super simple case.
The situation setting is as follows. Classifying set: a set whose elements are (finite number) real numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[AWS] I made a reminder BOT with LINE WORKS (implementation)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-i-made-a-reminder-bot-with-line-works-implementation-ff5a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-i-made-a-reminder-bot-with-line-works-implementation-ff5a2/</guid>
      <description>It is the 14th day of LINEWORKS Advent Calendar.  This time, we will introduce the implementation of the reminder BOT introduced in LINEWORKS Advent Calendar Day 7.
[Repost] BOT screen and overall structure The reminder BOT consists of three Lambda, and is implemented with Python3.7.
①. Processing of messages sent from LINE WORKS and notification to SQS ②. Poll the events stored in the table and notify SQS ③. Notify the LINEWORKS server of the message received from SQS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>09. Typoglycemia</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/09.-typoglycemia-fb353/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/09.-typoglycemia-fb353/</guid>
      <description>## 09. Typoglycemia  Create a program that leaves the leading and trailing characters of each word in a word string separated by spaces and rearranges the order of the other characters randomly. However, words with a length of 4 or less are not sorted. Give an appropriate English sentence (for example, &amp;ldquo;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe that I could actually understand what I was reading :the phenomenal power of the human mind .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My os (Python)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/my-os-python-f9eba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/my-os-python-f9eba/</guid>
      <description>Summary for yourself  Update from time to time
Sometimes the terms are wrong because I know myself
! View
#command # Optional argument description What is #os used for? Is it a folder operation?
 Module loading import os #glob is a bonus import glob Frequent operations Get folder/file #Get current directory os.getcwd() #Get file name os.basename() #Get absolute path os.path.abspath() __file__ # path of the file being executed #Get folder name os.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report from the site. What I think is necessary to utilize AI/IoT in the manufacturing industry</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/report-from-the-site.-what-i-think-is-necessary-to-utilize-ai-iot-in-the-manufacturing-industry-f90b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/report-from-the-site.-what-i-think-is-necessary-to-utilize-ai-iot-in-the-manufacturing-industry-f90b1/</guid>
      <description>I will post Qiita for the first time. ‥  I&amp;rsquo;m always indebted to you, but I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for not posting.
Introduction As is said to be the &amp;ldquo;cliff of 2025,&amp;rdquo; digital transformation is an urgent issue for the manufacturing industry. While emerging countries are chasing after quality and cost, I feel the harshness of Japan at the factory. I wonder, &amp;ldquo;Is Japanese quality really good?&amp;rdquo; (Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just my factory!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-python-ffb51/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-python-ffb51/</guid>
      <description>Today is a favorite  Post about Python.
What is Python A programming language developed by Dutch Guido Van Rossum in 1991.
Easy programming with less code Moreover, the code is easy to read.
The use of &amp;ldquo;artificial intelligence (AI)&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;web development&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;education field&amp;rdquo; is spreading.
Advantages of Python As a basic merit
 Simple and easy to remember Offside rules with indentation No compilation required Large library  These include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try to write aggregation processing for a certain period using pandas × groupby × Grouper</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/try-to-write-aggregation-processing-for-a-certain-period-using-pandas-groupby-grouper-fafc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/try-to-write-aggregation-processing-for-a-certain-period-using-pandas-groupby-grouper-fafc1/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this article from the motivation &amp;quot;I want to write a process to create a feature amount that aggregates a certain column for N days in pandas, what should I do?&amp;quot;  Sample code is excerpted from Google Colabratory linked below. GoogleColab-pandas × groupby × Grouper sample
In addition, the data here (kaggle Datasets-Bitcoin Historical Data) is used.
First of all, from the pre-processing of data, convert the Timestamp column to datetime type for the previous processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast automated test creation using pyATS|Genie&#39;s hidden move Blitz</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/fast-automated-test-creation-using-pyatsgenies-hidden-move-blitz-fa008/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/fast-automated-test-creation-using-pyatsgenies-hidden-move-blitz-fa008/</guid>
      <description>This article was posted as the 11th day of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by volunteers from Cisco.  2017 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco
#Introduction
Hello. pyATS|GenieI&#39;m@tahigash3fromthedevelopmentteam.Inthisarticle,I&amp;rsquo;llshowyouaneasywaytocreateanetworktestusingpyATS|Genie.
Please refer to the previous article for a brief introduction and installation of pyATS|Genie. Easily check multi-vendor networks with pyATS/Genie and Robot Framework
Worries about network automation I have enumerated the worries of those who have not done network automation yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feature generation with pandas group by</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/feature-generation-with-pandas-group-by-fa15c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/feature-generation-with-pandas-group-by-fa15c/</guid>
      <description>I want to create features with group by #pandas  When you want to add a statistic for each attribute of a column to a feature, you may not need to create a dict with collections or groupby and merge it. Although it is easy to simply output statistics, I left it as a memo because I struggled with how to use pandas.DataFrame.groupby when I wanted to add it to a record as a feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lark basic explanation (Python, Lark makes a shell-like guy)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/lark-basic-explanation-python-lark-makes-a-shell-like-guy-fccd4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/lark-basic-explanation-python-lark-makes-a-shell-like-guy-fccd4/</guid>
      <description>## First  I&amp;rsquo;m a programming beginner and a pretty ignorant man, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know various names and ambiguous expressions like &amp;ldquo;*** Natsu&amp;rdquo; are used, but please forgive me.
Things to do I want to make something that works in a bash-like way of writing (I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I say)! I made it.
The created program parses and executes the following script and returns the result.
rand -s3 a b c + say def | replace e E (The result will be something like b a cd Ef)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn python gestures</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/learn-python-gestures-fccd5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/learn-python-gestures-fccd5/</guid>
      <description>I wrote in the last article that I used Visual Studio and Fortran, but rufiyaa has been a little bit programming so far. I also like using VBA at work, and I often repeat elaborate automation and make minor changes that make it useless.  In other words, I understand the basic parts such as programs and algorithms. Then, all that is needed to freely walk around the world of python is the expression method in python = python gesture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morphological analysis tool installation (MeCab,Juman&#43;&#43;,Janome,GiNZA)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/morphological-analysis-tool-installation-mecabjuman-janomeginza-fdd58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/morphological-analysis-tool-installation-mecabjuman-janomeginza-fdd58/</guid>
      <description>A morphological analysis tool is indispensable for Japanese text processing, but it was troublesome to check the installation method of the tool each time, so the following 4 installations are summarized.   MeCab Juman++ Janome GiNZA  Installation environment: Ubuntu 18.04
MeCab Quoted from official site
 MeCab is an open source morphological analysis engine developed through the Joint Research Unit Project of Kyoto University Graduate School of Informatics-Nippon Telegraph and Telephone Corporation, Communication Science Laboratories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python standard library: First half (Python learning memo ⑧)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-standard-library-first-half-python-learning-memo-f82e2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-standard-library-first-half-python-learning-memo-f82e2/</guid>
      <description>## OS interface  Functions that interact with the operating system
import os os.getcwd() # get current directory os.system(&amp;#39;mkdir today&amp;#39;) # Execute command in system shell The shutil module is useful for managing files and directories
import shutil shutil.copyfile(&amp;#39;data.db&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;archive.db&amp;#39;) shuti.move(&amp;#39;/build/executables&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;installdir&amp;#39;) File wildcard The glob module returns a list of files with a wildcard search in a directory
import glob glob.glob(&amp;#39;*.py&amp;#39;) A list of files ending with #.py is returned Command line arguments Arguments passed when executing python command are stored in sys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert cubic mesh code to WKT with Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/convert-cubic-mesh-code-to-wkt-with-python-fa2a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/convert-cubic-mesh-code-to-wkt-with-python-fa2a2/</guid>
      <description>Although it is a memorandum level, I created a function to convert the 3rd mesh code to WKT with python.  It&amp;rsquo;s plain, but it tends to be impossible to calculate when it is needed &amp;hellip;
def toWKTfromMeshCode3(mcode3:&amp;#39;mesh code(str)&amp;#39;):-&amp;gt;&amp;#39;wkt(str)&amp;#39; south = (int(mcode3[0:2]) * 80 + int(mcode3[4:5]) * 10 + (int(mcode3[6:7]))) * 30/3600 west = (int(mcode3[2:4]) * 80 + int(mcode3[5:6]) * 10 + (int(mcode3[7:8]))) * 45/3600 + 100 north = south + 30/3600 east = west + 45/3600 wkt =&amp;#39;POLYGON(({e} {n},{w} {n},{w} {s},{e} {s},{e} {n}))&amp;#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>get rid of heavy pyls in vim-lsp</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/get-rid-of-heavy-pyls-in-vim-lsp-f8b85/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/get-rid-of-heavy-pyls-in-vim-lsp-f8b85/</guid>
      <description># vim-lsp and pyls  I tried switching Vim&amp;rsquo;s Python input completion from jedi-vim to vim-lsp, but the operation is heavy. And after a while after editing a Python file, there are frequent automatic downloads of .py files on OneDrive that have nothing to do with the file you&amp;rsquo;re editing.
Looking at the process, pylint was a sub process of pyls.exe and it was running with CPU full open and eating up memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use a command to upload data to s3 of aws and update it, and delete the used data (on the way)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/use-a-command-to-upload-data-to-s3-of-aws-and-update-it-and-delete-the-used-data-on-the-way-fb390/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/use-a-command-to-upload-data-to-s3-of-aws-and-update-it-and-delete-the-used-data-on-the-way-fb390/</guid>
      <description>[Install AWS CLI version 1](https://docs.aws.amazon.com/ja_jp/cli/latest/userguide/install-cliv1.html)  Install the latest version of the AWS CLI pip3 install awscli --upgrade --user
It seems that you can install it, but aws --version Then, zsh: command not found: aws Will appear&amp;hellip; Add AWS CLI version 1 executable to macOS command line path Based on the above article, &amp;ldquo;Add aws program to PATH environment variable of operating system&amp;rdquo;. →But after all zsh: command not found: aws Will it come out&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pyenv simply the point</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/pyenv-simply-the-point-f96ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/pyenv-simply-the-point-f96ba/</guid>
      <description>#Development environment  Linux kernel 4.15.0-54-generic
#Reference
This was helpful! 
Get #pyenv This time, put pyenv in the home directory, but you can put it anywhere as long as you pass the path correctly.
Get ```terminal:pyenv from git git clone https://github.com/pyenv/pyenv.git ~/.pyenv
 ```terminal: anything else that makes you happy sudo apt install -y make build-essential libssl-dev zlib1g-dev libbz2-dev libreadline-dev libsqlite3-dev wget curl llvm libncurses5-dev libncursesw5-dev xz-utils libffi-dev #Pass through the path to use I don&amp;rsquo;t use echo&amp;gt;&amp;gt;, so I recommend the first method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clustering G-means that automatically determines the number of clusters</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/clustering-g-means-that-automatically-determines-the-number-of-clusters-fae8a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/clustering-g-means-that-automatically-determines-the-number-of-clusters-fae8a/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 6th day entry for [Advent Calendar 2019 for Freee People](https://adventar.org/calendars/4414).  I started writing in the middle of the night the day before and I was writing while saying hi-hee.
#Introduction Do you all know the library PyClustering?PyClusteringisaclustering-specificlibraryavailablefromPythonandC++.ThealgorithmcalledG-meansisnewlyimplementedinsuchPyClusteringv0.9.2. I saw the name G-means for the first time + I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find an article in Japanese, so I looked it up and put it together. The algorithm itself is simple, so it may be easiest to read Paper directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rewriting Lambda to restart Workspaces of UNHEALTHY with python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/rewriting-lambda-to-restart-workspaces-of-unhealthy-with-python-f7ffa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/rewriting-lambda-to-restart-workspaces-of-unhealthy-with-python-f7ffa/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll do Hands Lab Advent Calendar this year as well  Overview We use Workspaces, a service that provides virtual desktops for AWS, Sometimes it’s unhealthy
\ Broken without doing anything /
Most of the time, it is possible to manage by restarting due to a temporary load drop. So there is Lambda that restarts for the time being It&amp;rsquo;s written in Node.js, so it supports frequent version upgrades&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s simple code, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d rewrite it to python anyway</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>エラー：pyenv: no such command `sh-activate&#39;</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/%E3%82%A8%E3%83%A9%E3%83%BCpyenv-no-such-command-sh-activate-fdf12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/%E3%82%A8%E3%83%A9%E3%83%BCpyenv-no-such-command-sh-activate-fdf12/</guid>
      <description># エラー  pyenv: no such command `sh-activate&amp;#39; 解決策 brew install pyenv-virtualenv 環境  pyenv 1.2.15 Mac
ProductName: Mac OS X
ProductVersion: 10.15.1
BuildVersion: 19B88  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 questions to check before web scraping</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/10-questions-to-check-before-web-scraping-ff0ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/10-questions-to-check-before-web-scraping-ff0ca/</guid>
      <description>With [Web scraping](https://www.octoparse.jp/), you can get the information you need in seconds and the great value behind it. But before we do that, there are 10 questions to ask.  #1.Is Web scraping illegal?
[robot.txt](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robots_exclusion_standard If you are allowed to crawl according to the terms of the file, we recommend that you read the Terms of Service (ToS) of the target website in advance to assess the legal feasibility of your data project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make an interactive LINE BOT 004 (answer the closing date of listed companies)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-make-an-interactive-line-bot-004-answer-the-closing-date-of-listed-companies-fcebc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-make-an-interactive-line-bot-004-answer-the-closing-date-of-listed-companies-fcebc/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  Last time, I implemented the function to acquire stock price information, but as a real problem, &amp;ldquo;I did not bother to ask BOT, I used the stock application It&amp;rsquo;s only a matter of time before I get the tsukumi saying, ``It&amp;rsquo;s more convenient&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;, and I&amp;rsquo;m probably using a certain portfolio management app on a daily basis without fail, so I would like BOT to pinpoint the stock price now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Search Tweets: Full Archive / Sandbox in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/using-search-tweets-full-archive-sandbox-in-python-f7f31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/using-search-tweets-full-archive-sandbox-in-python-f7f31/</guid>
      <description>I started Python for my thesis in [previous article](https://qiita.com/johnsakagami/items/7202368fe11e570e060e) and tried various things with Twitter API.  Python is no more than 10 days old. Well, my skill hasn&amp;rsquo;t improved so much&amp;hellip;
Premise of this time: Are all the searches on the Twitter official website displayed? After all, the data collection of graduation thesis was a search on the Twitter official website that has full access to past tweets. Primitive. By the way, I was taking the number of data in that way, but the number of search results with that keyword decreases ** unexpectedly ** as I go back in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mayungo&#39;s Python learning episode 7: I tried printing with if, elif, else</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/mayungos-python-learning-episode-7-i-tried-printing-with-if-elif-else-fccb7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/mayungos-python-learning-episode-7-i-tried-printing-with-if-elif-else-fccb7/</guid>
      <description>This time we will work on if, elif, and else.  The same content is also shown in the video, so please see it if you like. 
When writing a program, there are situations where you want to make different actions depending on the conditions.
Now put 1 in the variable num.
If num is 1, 1 is output. When they are the same, they are written as ==.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nested comprehensions in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/nested-comprehensions-in-python-fa64b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/nested-comprehensions-in-python-fa64b/</guid>
      <description>Conclusion: If you forget which one of the nested comprehensions is the inner, remember it is the same as when you wrote it down in the for loop. I forgot how many times I forgot so I took a note  Single comprehension First a basic example.
&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; [x * 2 for x in [1,2,3,4,5]] [2, 4, 6, 8, 10] You can create a list by applying an expression to each element of the list by doing &amp;ldquo;[Expression using variable for variable in list]`.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[LINE Messaging API] Create parrot return BOT in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/line-messaging-api-create-parrot-return-bot-in-python-fd865/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/line-messaging-api-create-parrot-return-bot-in-python-fd865/</guid>
      <description>##チュートリアル  ####【メッセージを受信する場合】 WebhookHandlerを下記の様に設定 @handler.add(MessageEvent, message=TextMessage)
from flask import Flask, request, abort from linebot import ( LineBotApi, WebhookHandler ) from linebot.exceptions import ( InvalidSignatureError ) from linebot.models import ( MessageEvent, TextMessage, TextSendMessage, ) app = Flask(__name__) line_bot_api = LineBotApi(&amp;#39;YOUR_CHANNEL_ACCESS_TOKEN&amp;#39;) handler = WebhookHandler(&amp;#39;YOUR_CHANNEL_SECRET&amp;#39;) @app.route(&amp;#34;/callback&amp;#34;, methods=[&amp;#39;POST&amp;#39;]) def callback(): # get X-Line-Signature header value signature = request.headers[&amp;#39;X-Line-Signature&amp;#39;] # get request body as text body = request.get_data(as_text=True) app.logger.info(&amp;#34;Request body: &amp;#34; + body) # handle webhook body try: handler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginners want to make a Rubik&#39;s Cube style thing in UE4 and make it a library for reinforcement learning #6</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/beginners-want-to-make-a-rubiks-cube-style-thing-in-ue4-and-make-it-a-library-for-reinforcement-learning-#6-fb445/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/beginners-want-to-make-a-rubiks-cube-style-thing-in-ue4-and-make-it-a-library-for-reinforcement-learning-#6-fb445/</guid>
      <description>Continuing from the previous article, this article is about how beginners can make various Python libraries that involve UE4 (almost as a memorandum for themselves...).  First: #1 Last time: #5
Observation We will implement around I will write the control processing around the observed value. Basically, it is necessary to perform processing such as saving after the action, and the column of the action ID is prepared in the prepared SQLite table, so we will add the place to connect with BP to the action module ( I also thought about adding a module that uses PyActor for Observation separately, but I will add it to the action because cooperation with action relations becomes useless and complicated).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I want to be notified of the connection environment when the RaspberryPi connects to the network</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-want-to-be-notified-of-the-connection-environment-when-the-raspberrypi-connects-to-the-network-ffadd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-want-to-be-notified-of-the-connection-environment-when-the-raspberrypi-connects-to-the-network-ffadd/</guid>
      <description>I bought a Raspberry Pi 4. So I put ArchLinux in the SD card.  This time, I do not buy LEDs separately, but it will be operated in a bare state, but there is one problem,
** Checking where is connected is troublesome **
Basically, DHCP is used and there is no monitor, so it is troublesome to check the IP address whether it is a wired connection or a wireless connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A memorandum when acquiring area information / prefecture information / route information / station information / nearest station information with HeartRails Express API (python)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/a-memorandum-when-acquiring-area-information-prefecture-information-route-information-station-information-nearest-station-information-with-heartrails-express-api-python-ff25c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/a-memorandum-when-acquiring-area-information-prefecture-information-route-information-station-information-nearest-station-information-with-heartrails-express-api-python-ff25c/</guid>
      <description># Purpose  A memorandum when acquiring area information / prefecture information / route information / station information / nearest station information with HeartRails Express API (python)
 http://express.heartrails.com
 #Preparation
Install request transmission module
pip install requests #Test
Area information acquisition API Get default area
#!/usr/bin/env python3 # -*- coding: utf-8 -*- import json import requests url =&amp;#39;http://express.heartrails.com/api/json?method=getAreas&amp;#39; ret = requests.get(url) ret_json = json.loads(ret.text) print(ret_json) $python sample1.py {&#39;response&#39;: {&#39;area&#39;: [&#39;Hokkaido&#39;,&#39;Tohoku&#39;,&#39;Kanto&#39;,&#39;Chubu&#39;,&#39;Kinki&#39;,&#39;China&#39;,&#39;Shikoku&#39;,&#39;Kyushu&#39;]}} Prefecture information acquisition API Get default prefecture name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Difference between return and print-Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/difference-between-return-and-print-python-ff839/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/difference-between-return-and-print-python-ff839/</guid>
      <description>I did not understand the difference between return and print, so I will summarize here. However, I haven&#39;t grasped the difference completely, so I hope to understand the difference clearly.  return = In a function, return the value to the caller. I was confused, but since return returns a value, you have to use print if you want to output the value. print = Just print a string. It is used not only at the time of function but also in various situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try to solve a function minimization problem using particle swarm optimization</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/try-to-solve-a-function-minimization-problem-using-particle-swarm-optimization-fee23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/try-to-solve-a-function-minimization-problem-using-particle-swarm-optimization-fee23/</guid>
      <description># Particle swarm optimization  Particle Swarm Optimization (PSO) is a type of swarm intelligence used as a solution search method for combinatorial optimization problems. By repeating the update of the two information of particle velocity and position, the process proceeds with the search. The figure below is an image of particle swarm optimization. ##algorithm The algorithm for particle swarm optimization is as follows. Update formula The particle velocity and position are updated using the following update formula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried sending Raspberry Pi data to GCP (free)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-sending-raspberry-pi-data-to-gcp-free-fc564/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-sending-raspberry-pi-data-to-gcp-free-fc564/</guid>
      <description>#I sent the data of Raspberry Pi to GCP (free)  I wanted to create a mechanism to store Raspberry Pi data in MySQL and check it on the Web. For people who want to set up a server in VPS and exchange data.
*This article is intended to acquire and send temperature data on the Rasberry Pi.
Development environment  Windows10 Pro Powershell Windows Subsystem for Linux (Ubuntu)  About GCP Abbreviation for Google Cloud Platform, which is a cloud computing service provided by Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Plot data for each prefecture on a map (number of cars owned nationwide)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-plot-data-for-each-prefecture-on-a-map-number-of-cars-owned-nationwide-fa2c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-plot-data-for-each-prefecture-on-a-map-number-of-cars-owned-nationwide-fa2c4/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article  Draw a prefecture-level color-coded map like this in Python For municipal level, go to here
By the way, the data used the number of passenger cars owned nationwide.
At the end of the page is Code List.
Commentary Use the library japanmap to create a colored map
pip install japanmap Other library preparation
import numpy as np import pandas as pd import cv2 from PIL import Image import matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People who want to clear the D problem at ABC of AtCoder scratched the foot</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/people-who-want-to-clear-the-d-problem-at-abc-of-atcoder-scratched-the-foot-f9ae5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/people-who-want-to-clear-the-d-problem-at-abc-of-atcoder-scratched-the-foot-f9ae5/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction   An amateur writer tried AtCoder Beginner Contest several times. Language is python However, after the D problem, I have no teeth. For these problems, it is required to estimate the amount of calculation + how to use algorithms or libraries to improve processing speed or mathematical knowledge. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult and seems to vomit, but it&amp;rsquo;s funny. If you don&amp;rsquo;t solve it  Purpose  Learn how to solve AtCoder&amp;rsquo;s D-rank problem (400 points).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything for beginners to be able to do machine learning</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/everything-for-beginners-to-be-able-to-do-machine-learning-fcd09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/everything-for-beginners-to-be-able-to-do-machine-learning-fcd09/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is for the purpose of enabling machine learning while doing what was presented as a &amp;ldquo;knowledge necessary for doing machine learning&amp;rdquo; **, which was issued as a subject for an internship destination. is. You will only become a Apprentice Machine Learning Engineer by doing all of this article. On the contrary, you can easily expose the basics of machine learning simply by doing all of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert latitude, longitude and GPS altitude to 3D Cartesian coordinates</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/convert-latitude-longitude-and-gps-altitude-to-3d-cartesian-coordinates-fa0c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/convert-latitude-longitude-and-gps-altitude-to-3d-cartesian-coordinates-fa0c8/</guid>
      <description>There are quite a few situations where you want to convert latitude/longitude to a position in a Cartesian coordinate system, or obtain a linear distance from latitude/longitude** (not available).  In fact, I think many other people have written this kind of article. However, I think that the coordinate system you want to use may differ depending on the purpose. So, since I learned how to convert it into a non-moving three-dimensional Cartesian coordinate system with the center of gravity of the earth as the origin, I would like to summarize here with the meaning of memorandum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precautions when using string for TmeStampType of PySpark</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/precautions-when-using-string-for-tmestamptype-of-pyspark-fcecc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/precautions-when-using-string-for-tmestamptype-of-pyspark-fcecc/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is a story that there is a pattern that behaves unintentionally when the character string type of date format is carelessly used when calculating TimeStampType of PySpark.
Therefore, it is possible to operate on TimeStampType with string, but it is safer to use datetime.
#Example
A specific example will be described.
The example shown here is from PySPark 2.4.4.
Verification data With the following code, create a Spark DataFrame with date data of 2000/1/1 to 2000/1/5 and try the conditional processing for this date data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is machine learning?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-machine-learning-fe6f2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-machine-learning-fe6f2/</guid>
      <description>## Differences between machine learning, statistics and data science  Machine Learning (ML), Statistics, Data Science. All of these words are often heard due to the rapid spread of AI in recent years, but what is the difference between them? There is no definite answer, but to put it simply, firstly Data Science is a field that combines specialized fields such as statistics, computer science, and business. I think it will be easier to understand if you look at the figure below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried VS Code Jupyter notebook</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-vs-code-jupyter-notebook-fd079/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-vs-code-jupyter-notebook-fd079/</guid>
      <description>I tried #VSCode&#39;s Jupyter notebook.  There was an article of VS Code Jupyter notebook in the magazine, so I tried it. I made a Jupyter notebook experience very easily, so I will make a note of my footsteps.
Assumption  Tried on Mac. Homebrew has python installed as python3. When I put python3, pip3 is also included  ###python3
$ which python3 /usr/local/bin/python3 $python3 --version Python 3.7.5 ###pip3
$ which pip3 /usr/local/bin/pip3 $ pip3 --version pip 19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translated by: PEP 20-The Zen of Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/translated-by-pep-20-the-zen-of-python-fea95/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/translated-by-pep-20-the-zen-of-python-fea95/</guid>
      <description># 概要  英語  Long time Pythoneer Tim Peters succinctly channels the BDFL&amp;rsquo;s guiding principles for Python&amp;rsquo;s design into 20 aphorisms, only 19 of which have been written down.
 日本語  長い間PythoneerであるTim PetersがPythonの設計に対するBDFLの基本理念を20の格言を19の文章に簡潔にまとめました。
 The Zen of Python 英語  Beautiful is better than ugly. Explicit is better than implicit. Simple is better than complex. Complex is better than complicated. Flat is better than nested. Sparse is better than dense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>``First time learning&#39;&#39; that even university students with no knowledge can do-AWS SageMaker</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</guid>
      <description># My background  Amazon? Ah, you know, you know, a mail order app. Not long ago, knowledge about Amazon was that much. Of course, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know AWS.
I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed as an information undergraduate student. 
However, as a 3rd year university student, I was introduced to the lab and learned about AWS. In addition, I am addicted to the topic &amp;ldquo;Atsuhiko Nakata&amp;rsquo;s YouTube University&amp;rdquo;, which is a hot topic in this street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Boolean with Flask request</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/get-boolean-with-flask-request-fcd45/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/get-boolean-with-flask-request-fcd45/</guid>
      <description>#Environment   python 3.7.0 Flask 1.0.2  #First SOURCE API that only receives and returns bool type is_hoge with request
from flask import Flask, request app = Flask(__name__) @app.route(&amp;#34;/&amp;#34;, methods=[&amp;#39;GET&amp;#39;]) def hello(): is_hoge = request.args.get(&amp;#39;is_hoge&amp;#39;, type=bool) return f&amp;#39;{ is_hoge }&amp;#39; if __name__ == &amp;#34;__main__&amp;#34;: app.run() Expected value  True if you send true False if you send false False if you send 0  Execution result  if you send true  if you send false  If you send 0   What do you say?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recognize the board surface of Othello board with OpenCV</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/recognize-the-board-surface-of-othello-board-with-opencv-fe6b9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/recognize-the-board-surface-of-othello-board-with-opencv-fe6b9/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This year, Othello Advent Calendar was planned and invited, so I decided to write an article. Actually, I wrote another article on Day 1, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what I was doing and I suddenly entered the article, so this time It is a little self-introduction.
I&amp;rsquo;m developing an app for iOS called Goki Box. As one of its functions, we have incorporated a function that images the Othello board with a camera and overlays the evaluation value on the board with AR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Python regularly with Heroku Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/run-python-regularly-with-heroku-scheduler-fac20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/run-python-regularly-with-heroku-scheduler-fac20/</guid>
      <description>#Run Python regularly with Heroku Scheduler   Perform Python periodically with Heroku Scheduler -Introduction -Purpose -Related Article -Execution environment -Source Code -Scenario and Assumptions -Preparation -Create FX Rate API -Scheduler setup -Scheduler Registration  Introduction This article is for Mac environment, but the procedure is the same for Windows environment. Please read the environment-dependent part and try again.
Purpose After reading this article, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to:
 Run Python regularly with Heroku Scheduler  Scheduler settings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make random numbers with NumPy&#39;s random module</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-make-random-numbers-with-numpys-random-module-fc349/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-make-random-numbers-with-numpys-random-module-fc349/</guid>
      <description>NumPy can generate random numbers with the np.random module.   Np.random.rand() that generates a uniform random number between 0 and 1 Generate random numbers for the number of integers specified in ().  ・Np.random.randint(x, y, z) that generates z integers between x and less than y Note that it will generate an integer between x and y. Furthermore, if you specify an argument such as (2,3) for z, you can generate a 2×3 matrix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement learning 11 Try OpenAI acrobot with ChainerRL.</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/reinforcement-learning-11-try-openai-acrobot-with-chainerrl.-ff53c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/reinforcement-learning-11-try-openai-acrobot-with-chainerrl.-ff53c/</guid>
      <description>It is a prerequisite that you have achieved up to 10 reinforcement learning.  If you google with openai acrobot, Acrobot-v1 will come out. I do not know v1 or v0 well, so I will investigate before the magic modification. userfolder/anaconda3/envs/chainer/lib/python3.7/site-packages/gym With VS Code. A full search with CartPole found CartPole-v0 and CartPole-v1. Mumu? For acrobot, only Acrobot-v1. In CartPole created earlier, I tried to replace CartPole-v0 with CartPole-v1. The difficulty level seems to have increased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic login to ServiceNow with Selenium Web Driver</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/automatic-login-to-servicenow-with-selenium-web-driver-fdd5f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/automatic-login-to-servicenow-with-selenium-web-driver-fdd5f/</guid>
      <description># ◆Overview   Using Selenium WebDriver, which is used for automation of Web UI tests, I tried to log in ServiceNow automatically.  ◆Operating environment  OS: Windows10 Python version: 3.8.0  Preparation Creating an instance of ServiceNow  You can create a developer instance by registering an account from the ServiceNow Developers page. Make sure to write down the instance URL and the initial information of the admin account when the creation is completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a machine learning environment from scratch with Winsows10</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/create-a-machine-learning-environment-from-scratch-with-winsows10-fa354/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/create-a-machine-learning-environment-from-scratch-with-winsows10-fa354/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Do you guys do it?
Machine learning
He has been touted for the last three years as the third AI boom. Artificial intelligence, machine learning, neural networks, deep learning I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying silently these days, but it&amp;rsquo;s kind of difficult&amp;hellip;
This time, let&amp;rsquo;s leave that area and create a machine learning environment quickly. It&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly easy to make. (I think there are many reference articles, but I also use them as notes for myself)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to speed up Pandas apply method with just one sentence (with verification calculation)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-speed-up-pandas-apply-method-with-just-one-sentence-with-verification-calculation-fc4d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/how-to-speed-up-pandas-apply-method-with-just-one-sentence-with-verification-calculation-fc4d2/</guid>
      <description>#Conclusion  Just add swifter method before Pandas apply method
Concrete example import pandas as pd import numpy as np import swifter # Create a suitable DataFrame df = pd.DataFrame({&amp;#39;col&amp;#39;: np.random.normal(size=10000000)}) # Add swifter method before apply method. %time df[&amp;#39;col2&amp;#39;] = df[&amp;#39;col&amp;#39;].swifter.apply(lambda x: x**2) # Wall time: 50 ms # For comparison (normal pandas apply method) %time df[&amp;#39;col2&amp;#39;] = df[&amp;#39;col&amp;#39;].apply(lambda x: x**2) # Wall time: 3.48 s How to install $ pip install -U pandas # upgrade pandas $ pip install swifter In case of ```terminal:conda $ conda update pandas # upgrade pandas $ conda install -c conda-forge swifter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find maximum value python (improved)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/find-maximum-value-python-improved-f9959/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/find-maximum-value-python-improved-f9959/</guid>
      <description>I got some advice about the article I wrote last time ([Let&#39;s find the maximum value python (correct ver)](https://qiita.com/banana19980702/items/06db0f8fdb1ac175651c)), so I tried to refactor it further. This time, I focused on readability and modified the code.  ##change point -How to set variables when looping for statements
 The code is as follows.
num = int(input(&amp;#34;How many number values do you want to substitute?&amp;#34;)) value_list = [] # prepare an array to store numbers for i in range(num): value = int(input(&amp;#34;substitute a number&amp;#34;)) value_list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens to the access log when accessing the website automatically with selenium-webdriver</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-happens-to-the-access-log-when-accessing-the-website-automatically-with-selenium-webdriver-fe2ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-happens-to-the-access-log-when-accessing-the-website-automatically-with-selenium-webdriver-fe2ce/</guid>
      <description>#Purpose  Actually, I was secretly automating part of the internal work, but I suddenly looked into the server log and thought that it would be obvious that it was automated, so I verified it.
Verification environment  Use PaizaCloud as a web server Use Selenium-webdriver and headless-chrome as an automatic access method Use Python as a program to automate  What you did Introducing Selenium and Headless Chrome There are many articles about this, so I will omit it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construction of environment for using CaboCha on google cola borboratory</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/construction-of-environment-for-using-cabocha-on-google-cola-borboratory-fb890/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/construction-of-environment-for-using-cabocha-on-google-cola-borboratory-fb890/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Language processing 100 knocks Chapter 5 of 2015: I made a lot of trouble to use CaboCha necessary for dependency analysis, so I will summarize it.
About #google colabratory Mainly used as a python cloud environment, but shell commands can be used.
!{Shell command} !pip install library name You can use shell commands like this.
The OS you are using seems to be Ubuntu, so check it with a command</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to get data from AS/400 quickly using pypyodbc</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-get-data-from-as-400-quickly-using-pypyodbc-fad9a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-get-data-from-as-400-quickly-using-pypyodbc-fad9a/</guid>
      <description>For a long time (about 3 months), I was using the &amp;quot;execute SQL script&amp;quot; of IBM client solution to issue SQL and acquire data, but since the number of data exceeded 5000, to acquire all Since it has become troublesome to scroll endlessly, I tried an experiment of batch acquisition using Python and ODBC.  Since it is an experimental code, I do not care about error checking and output format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculation of mutual information (continuous value) with numpy</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/calculation-of-mutual-information-continuous-value-with-numpy-ffaab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/calculation-of-mutual-information-continuous-value-with-numpy-ffaab/</guid>
      <description>#Motivation  I want to calculate the mutual information $I(X;Y)$ of continuous random variables $X$ and $Y$ with Python. $$ I(X;Y) = \int_Y \int_X p(x, y) \log \frac{p(x,y)}{p(x)p(y)} dx dy $$
#Code
import numpy def mutual_information(X, Y, bins=10): # Compute joint probability distribution p(x,y) p_xy, xedges, yedges = np.histogram2d(X, Y, bins=bins, density=True) #p(x)p(y) calculation p_x, _ = np.histogram(X, bins=xedges, density=True) p_y, _ = np.histogram(Y, bins=yedges, density=True) p_x_y = p_x[:, np.newaxis] * p_y #dx and dy dx = xedges[1]-xedges[0] dy = yedges[1]-yedges[0] # Integral element elem = p_xy * np.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to summarize the string operation of Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-summarize-the-string-operation-of-python-fe55c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-tried-to-summarize-the-string-operation-of-python-fe55c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;m coding in Python, and I had a built-in method that I could use when working with strings, so I&amp;rsquo;ve put it together as a memorandum. As for the method of dividing the system, we have systematized it on an individual basis, so don&amp;rsquo;t worry.
#Orthopedics
format method The value in the string can be described later using index It becomes easy to edit the character string when used together with the variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[For beginners] I tried using the Tensorflow Object Detection API</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/for-beginners-i-tried-using-the-tensorflow-object-detection-api-fd99b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is IchiLab from RHEMS Giken.
This time using the Object Detection API of TensorFlow, Let me detect the object I want to recognize, I finally tried it on an Android device.
Many helpful sites have helped me, Still, I had a lot of points that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve with just one or two pages.
In this article, I will pick up the parts that I stumbled upon to make a difference, I hope that the number of people who do the same will be reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can programs started using cron be made interactive?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/can-programs-started-using-cron-be-made-interactive-fcca8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/can-programs-started-using-cron-be-made-interactive-fcca8/</guid>
      <description>## I wanted to run an interactive program with cron  I&amp;rsquo;m running a project to track the lending history of books at a certain place, and want to use the Raspberry Pi as feedback and whether the barcode was read correctly or not. I plan to manage based on ISBN, so I created a program in Python that receives the input of the barcode reader and returns the feedback &amp;ldquo;OK if it is OK, NG otherwise&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I want to upload the Django app to heroku</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-want-to-upload-the-django-app-to-heroku-fe79c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-want-to-upload-the-django-app-to-heroku-fe79c/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your help.  【environment】 Surface Laptop2 Windows 1809 Python 3.7.4 (the one running on the command line) Django 2.2.6
[What you want to achieve] I want to publish an app made with Django using heroku
【Situation】 The Django app on Heroku doesn&amp;rsquo;t deploy well and the build doesn&amp;rsquo;t succeed.
Procedure (1) https://qiita.com/frosty/items/66f5dff8fc723387108c Https://qiita.com/RyuSA/items/0cbc7d5b0145585861a8 I rewrote settings.py with reference to the two sites Was rewritten as from socket import gethostname # It is possible to get the hostname by doing this ***A import django_heroku import os import dj_database_url</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[The Road to Intermediate Python] Article Link Summary</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/the-road-to-intermediate-python-article-link-summary-fb3f3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/the-road-to-intermediate-python-article-link-summary-fb3f3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I need to make better use of Python used in my research, so I will compile my personal writing.
Article link  [Route to Intermediate] Understanding Python Properties [Road to Intermediate] Python seems to be all objects [Road to Intermediate] What are Python&amp;rsquo;s *args and **kwargs?  [Route to Intermediate] Utilizing Python&amp;rsquo;s built-in function vars [Route to Intermediate Python] Dynamically specify execution method by variable name [Road to Intermediate Python] Enable comparison operation of original class [Route to Intermediate Python] Call a class instance with call like a function [Road to Python intermediate] define in in original class [Route to Intermediate Python] Use ternary operator [Path to Intermediate Python] using if statement in list comprehension [Route to Intermediate Python] Use lambda expression [Path to Python Intermediate] Install packages in batch with pip [Route to Intermediate Python] Define getattr function in class  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaggle Related Summary</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/kaggle-related-summary-fc867/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/kaggle-related-summary-fc867/</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of information that will help you capture Kaggle.  (Will be updated at any time)
▪︎website https://naotaka1128.hatenadiary.jp/entry/kaggle-compe-tips
◼︎ Mechanism Curry&amp;rsquo;s commentary http://www.currypurin.com/entry/2018/02/21/011316
◾️ Book Data Analysis Technology Wins at Kaggle https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/B07YTDBC3Z/
◾️Booth kaggle tutorial 4th edition https://booth.pm/ja/items/1567594
■ slack https://kaggler-ja.herokuapp.com
■ discord Curry&amp;rsquo;s
■ wiki http://kaggler-ja-wiki.herokuapp.com/
■ coursera https://ja.coursera.org/learn/competitive-data-science
◾️ Summary article kaggle api related https://qiita.com/uni-3/items/f1fdbeeddd08ca22c80f
https://qiita.com/shunkakinoki/items/1f58e218f8f6b31ad0bf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best practices for data manipulation with pandas</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/best-practices-for-data-manipulation-with-pandas-f7ed4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/best-practices-for-data-manipulation-with-pandas-f7ed4/</guid>
      <description>After preprocessing the data with machine learning, with a hypothesis,  Play with data? Play with? I think there are phases, At that time, how to control pandas freely is I think it will be important.
I myself have a little programming experience and database knowledge,
***pandas DataFrame [] ← This is too complicated! ! ***
Especially, it is difficult to narrow down by conditions.
train[train[&amp;#34;company_id&amp;#34;] == 1088][&amp;#34;meter_reading&amp;#34;] It&amp;rsquo;s confusing at this point, but if this is train_weather_df, it will be ruined</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freecad&#39;s memorandum (for yourself)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/freecads-memorandum-for-yourself-fc558/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/freecads-memorandum-for-yourself-fc558/</guid>
      <description>A memorandum for yourself.  Create a primitive sphere and export with iges (specify radius and position) import FreeCAD as APP import Part freecad = APP.newDocument(&amp;#34;model&amp;#34;) comp_1 = Part.Sphere() comp_1.Radius=10 myPart = freecad.addObject(&amp;#34;Part::Feature&amp;#34;,&amp;#34;comp_1&amp;#34;) myPart.Shape= comp_1.toShape() myPart.Placement = App.Placement(App.Vector(100,0,0),App.Rotation(App.Vector(0,0,1),0)) freecad.recompute() myPart.Shape.MatrixOfInertia freecad.saveAs(&amp;#34;comp_1.FCStd&amp;#34;) Part.export([freecad.Objects[0]],&amp;#34;comp_1.iges&amp;#34;) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Python on Mac from 2 to 3</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</guid>
      <description># Overview  This article is a step-by-step article on how a beginner himself developed a coupon distribution service for iPhone with RESTful API and swift. It was a very detouring implementation because we implemented it while examining the technical elements one by one.
Python is originally installed on the Mac, but the version is old as of OS 10.15. When actually writing Python, everyone seems to have been updated to 3 series.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>