<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> data science on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/data-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  data science on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I created an actuarial library</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/i-created-an-actuarial-library-f9058/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/i-created-an-actuarial-library-f9058/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It&amp;rsquo;s a certain virus or crap, it seems that it is about to grow moss on my body due to my self-control. By the way, I was studying the actuary exam recently, and I thought that &amp;ldquo;I might have a library for actuarial science in Python.&amp;rdquo; ――
#Development motive ・To deepen the understanding of actuarial science. ・To simplify numerical calculations using actuarial science.
 I&amp;rsquo;ve never given my own library to PyPI in Python, so let&amp;rsquo;s try it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books on data science to read in 2020</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Przemek Chojecki](https://towardsdatascience.com/@pchojecki),[[DataScienceBooksyoushouldreadin2020](https://towardsdatascience.com/data-science-books-you-should-read-in-2020-358f70e1d9b2)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
Data science is arguably one of the hottest markets right now. Almost all companies are looking for or considering a data science role.
So it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to become a data scientist. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re already a data scientist and want to promote to a senior position, it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to hone your skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best practices for data manipulation with pandas</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/best-practices-for-data-manipulation-with-pandas-f7ed4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/best-practices-for-data-manipulation-with-pandas-f7ed4/</guid>
      <description>After preprocessing the data with machine learning, with a hypothesis,  Play with data? Play with? I think there are phases, At that time, how to control pandas freely is I think it will be important.
I myself have a little programming experience and database knowledge,
***pandas DataFrame [] ← This is too complicated! ! ***
Especially, it is difficult to narrow down by conditions.
train[train[&amp;#34;company_id&amp;#34;] == 1088][&amp;#34;meter_reading&amp;#34;] It&amp;rsquo;s confusing at this point, but if this is train_weather_df, it will be ruined</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>