<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> api on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  api on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>To people who are offered but not recruited</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/to-people-who-are-offered-but-not-recruited-0f811/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/to-people-who-are-offered-but-not-recruited-0f811/</guid>
      <description>** [Twitter](https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)introducesartificialintelligenceandarticleswritteninothermedia**,soifyouwanttoknowmoreaboutartificialintelligence,**Pleasefeelfreetofollowus(https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)! **  ** Add Shinjiro Koizumi syntax [Add](https://qiita.com/omiita/items/0f811f15e569bf2539b8#6-%E7%95%AA%E5%A4%96%E7%B7%A8%E5%B0%8F%E6%B3%89%E9%80%B2%E6%AC%A1%E9%83%8E%E6%A7%8B%E6%96%87) Did. ** -- 1. I teach, but I don&amp;rsquo;t explain Prime Minister Abe&amp;rsquo;s Remark &amp;ldquo;I am recruiting but not recruiting&amp;rdquo; I was inspired and created a program that automatically converts the input sentence into a sentence &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m recruiting but not recruiting&amp;rdquo;**!
If you enter &amp;ldquo;Recruit people&amp;rdquo;, it will be converted into the sentence &amp;ldquo;We are recruiting people but not recruiting&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it still exhausted by MVC? ~ SPA development started with Django x React ~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</guid>
      <description>Recently, sites using JS framework are increasing.  In particular, JS frameworks such as React and Vue are often used for application development called SPA and bring many benefits not only to users of the site but also to developers.
Assumed readers  Web development experience People who have developed web applications using API Someone who knows JavaScript a lot and Python a little I know a little about Django People who have developed using MVC or MTV  There is an article written in more detail in another article, so please see here if you feel that this article is difficult or if you want to learn more deeply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Youtube data in Python using Youtube Data API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-youtube-data-in-python-using-youtube-data-api-7c98e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-youtube-data-in-python-using-youtube-data-api-7c98e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Recently, I am investigating whether various data can be acquired using API. Since I investigated and practiced how to get information such as the number of video views and likes using the Youtube Data API, I wrote a memorandum. #reference I have referred to the following when using the Youtube Data API.
 Youtube video search with Python Outline of YouTube Data API Youtube Data API Reference  #Preparing to use API ##Youtube Data API registration You need a Google account to get Youtube Data API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple network operation by linking Cisco DNA Center and Tact Switch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simple-network-operation-by-linking-cisco-dna-center-and-tact-switch-6cc65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simple-network-operation-by-linking-cisco-dna-center-and-tact-switch-6cc65/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the eighth day of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by volunteers from Cisco.
 2017 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco  What do you want to do?  Network operation that anyone can do Cisco&amp;rsquo;s best-selling controller for Cisco DNA Center ~~ Stema ~~ Tips demo Balancing work and material Common cool topics ~~ Policy, AI or Assurance ~ ~, but rather quiet operation that is often heard Reuse of goods bought in 2017  What is this?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>