<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> material on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/material/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  material on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/material/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] That&#39;s right, let&#39;s eat Bubu-zuke. [Natural language processing starting with Kyoto dialect]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a81d547fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a81d547fe/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I will do natural language processing for the first time. Excited. This article is [Qiita x COTOHA API present project] Let&amp;rsquo;s do text analysis with COTOHA API! ](https://zine.qiita.com/event/collaboration-cotoha-api/?utm_source=qiita&amp;amp;utm_medium=banner) ~~ I want more prizes! ~~ The post was in time.
Immediately the main subject. What to do now First, I will briefly explain what to do. I could do the following ↓
python3 bubuduke.py &amp;quot;Getta&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Do not be good&amp;quot; I will make a Kyoto dialect translator like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A program that automatically corrects Takenoko no Sato to Mushroom Mountain</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a8c7ba2c5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a8c7ba2c5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction-Introduction of wonderful sweets and the existence of late-deteriorated products-  As you probably know, there is a wonderful sweets called &amp;ldquo;Mushroom Mountain&amp;rdquo;1. A chocolate snack made and sold by Meiji Co., Ltd. since 1975. It has a cute mushroom-like shape with crackers on the stem and chocolate on the umbrella. It was said that the best combination was tried and errored over a development period of 5 years, and while it was easy to hold and functional, it had plenty of chocolate and a moderately salty and crispy feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The winner of the one with the highest degree of similarity to the original story in The Most Stupid Hototogisu Won&#39;t Winner</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/33b6989f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/33b6989f9/</guid>
      <description># Overview  A long time ago, there was a story that said, &amp;ldquo;The most stinky hottogigisu who won the championship 1&amp;rdquo;. If it&#39;s a crow, invite me to nothingness (Izanae) Totogi (Hototogisu) It&amp;rsquo;s like Growing my jet black flame, Firetogisu.
I like all the works, but it&amp;rsquo;s useless even if this kind of hand is too far from the original material, and the best taste is to keep the shape and meaning similar to the original material and to have a sense of jerk I wonder if it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Can AI distinguish Carlos Ghosn and Mr. Bean (Face recognition using face landmark)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d1b29fe29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d1b29fe29/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The news is about the news that Carlos Ghosn, the former chairman of Nissan Motor Co., Ltd., broke bail conditions and traveled to Lebanon. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking for a long time, but it&amp;rsquo;s similar to Mr. Bean&amp;hellip; Left: [Carlos Ghosn](https://www.google.com/search?q=Carlos+Ghosn&amp;amp;sxsrf=ACYBGNS1gsNQxqfqi7GRWUUeSSZ6CRix8w:1577813710879&amp;amp;source=lnms&amp;amp;tbm=isch&amp;amp;Ah&amp;amp;EqjQAQBQ&amp;amp;QAQBQBQ&amp;amp;QAQBQ&amp;amp;QB Right: [Mr. Bean (Rowan Atkinson)](https://www.google.com/search?q=rowan+atkinson&amp;amp;biw=1386&amp;amp;bih=710&amp;amp;sxsrf=ACYBGNTsdddnLF7jgPr9RTePeEMGgREpyA:1577813660092&amp;amp;source=lnms&amp;amp;tbm=isch&amp;amp;saQ&amp;amp;isch&amp;amp;saq
It was a year-end and New Year holiday, so I made a little classifier using a neural network. If you google it, a lot of images of the two people will appear, so it was good for CNN, but This time, as another approach, I would like to perform classification based on the position of landmarks on the face.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>