<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Muscle training on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/muscle-training/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Muscle training on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/muscle-training/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Check your squat form with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/check-your-squat-form-with-deep-learning-bd59e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/check-your-squat-form-with-deep-learning-bd59e/</guid>
      <description>**The video used in this article was recorded a long time ago, and I currently refrain from exercising at the gym. **  #Introduction This is the second edition of &amp;ldquo;Muscle Training x Deep Learning&amp;rdquo;. The first is here (Deep learning made it easier to see the time-lapse of physical changes). &amp;ldquo;Form check&amp;rdquo; that many trainees (people who love muscle training) have become habitual. You can fix your smartphone during the training, take a selfie, and look back later to know the habit of your form and improve the quality of your training afterwards!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning made it easy to see the time-lapse of physical changes</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-made-it-easy-to-see-the-time-lapse-of-physical-changes-f0e60/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-made-it-easy-to-see-the-time-lapse-of-physical-changes-f0e60/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  &amp;ldquo;Self-portraits (body)&amp;rdquo; that many trainees (people who love muscle training) have become accustomed. It&amp;rsquo;s blissful to take a picture of your pumped body after training and look back later. In addition, if you display the captured image in animation like a time lapse, you can understand that muscle growth is more like a hand! This article uses deep learning to drastically make it easier to see the timelapse of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For those who look at the log while learning with machine learning ~ Muscle training with LightGBM ~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</guid>
      <description>What do you guys do when learning models with machine learning?  Did you just look at the log output to the console? &amp;ldquo;Oh, it was lower than I expected!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oh, the accuracy is getting worse, do your best!!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly fun to think, though.
But when I cheered up, the model doesn&amp;rsquo;t do its best, and there is no dramatic development, so it&amp;rsquo;s a waste of time to look at it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>