<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EdgeTPU on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/edgetpu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EdgeTPU on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/edgetpu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning with Raspberry Pi 4 and Coral USB Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/12affbf81/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/12affbf81/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article summarizes the installation procedure of Raspberry Pi 4 and Coral USB Accelerator as a method of machine learning with edge device.
Raspberry Pi 4 is the latest generation of the current model. The CPU and memory performance have been greatly improved, and USB 3.0 is also supported.
Coral USB Accelerator is Google&amp;rsquo;s dedicated ASIC developed by Google for machine learning on edge devices.
This dedicated ASIC is called Edge TPU, and you can use TensorFlow Lite&amp;rsquo;s flake work specialized for inference at the edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build RaspberryPi for Python and machine learning study (RaspberryPi4 &amp; Buster version (RaspberryPi3 is also available))</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d370a3b3f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d370a3b3f/</guid>
      <description>## [Content]   ** 2020/02/19 We reviewed some contents and confirmed the operation with Raspberry Pi 3 model B. ** ** Added Node-RED environment construction. **  Finally the Raspberry Pi 4 model B has started selling in Japan. In order to use it immediately, I rewrote the previously posted [Building Raspberry Pi for Python and machine learning study] to the Raspberry Pi 4th edition. In addition to the hardware, I have the latest version of Raspbian (Buster 20200213).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>