<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Anomaly detection on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/anomaly-detection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Anomaly detection on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/anomaly-detection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Dimension curse] Can the number of sensors be changed to ∞ to detect anomalies?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/dimension-curse-can-the-number-of-sensors-be-changed-to-to-detect-anomalies-1a800/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/dimension-curse-can-the-number-of-sensors-be-changed-to-to-detect-anomalies-1a800/</guid>
      <description>Since the IOT became popular, efforts have been made to increase the number of sensors in order to predictively maintain machinery.  Is being done.
Rumor has it that there are cases where 100 sensors are attached to one machine.
The question is, is it justified to increase the number of sensors? In other words, does **adding extra sensors not affect the anomaly detection performance? When That is it.
In this paper, we focus on the curse of dimension, “When we increase the number of extra sensors, we detect anomalies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make an Anpanman painter discrimination machine</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-an-anpanman-painter-discrimination-machine-30a44/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-an-anpanman-painter-discrimination-machine-30a44/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I thought about learning AI and making a simple application with the technology I learned, I tried to make something like the following. The reason why I chose Anpanman was because it was a cartoon character that I could easily write. I wanted to handle GAN as a model, and that it is possible to detect abnormalities by learning only normal images I thought I would make it ANOGAN, but when I looked it up, it was called EfficientGAN in the high-speed version of ANOGAN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Detect image distortion by deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-detect-image-distortion-by-deep-distance-learning-54585/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-detect-image-distortion-by-deep-distance-learning-54585/</guid>
      <description>There is a lot of research being done on image anomaly detection using deep learning.  As an approach for detecting abnormal products using only normal data for industrial products, For now, @daisukelab&amp;rsquo;s Learning with self-teaching is the most powerful. In this research, As a problem, the accuracy of some images was sluggish, and we tried to make an error class data by trial and error ** There was a comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Abnormality detection] Try the latest method of deep distance learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-try-the-latest-method-of-deep-distance-learning-d2a3a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/abnormality-detection-try-the-latest-method-of-deep-distance-learning-d2a3a/</guid>
      <description>Previously, using **deep distance learning** [&amp;quot;image anomaly detection&amp;quot;](https://qiita.com/shinmura0/items/06d81c72601c7578c6d3#%E3%83%99%E3%83%B3%E3%83%81%E3%83%9E%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AF).  After that, The latest method of deep distance learning &amp;ldquo;AdaCos&amp;rdquo; appeared.
In this article, I would like to apply AdaCos to &amp;ldquo;anomaly detection&amp;rdquo; and do a simple benchmark. The entire code is here
*This is the presentation material of Python Data Analysis Study Group #15.
#From the conclusion By applying AdaCos to anomaly detection, we found the following:
 Same accuracy as ArcFace Thank you for not tuning parameters  #AdaCos AdaCos is said to be the latest method of deep distance learning, but as of January 2020, more than half a year has passed since the paper was published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Time series data abnormality detection for beginners</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/time-series-data-abnormality-detection-for-beginners-8dfa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/time-series-data-abnormality-detection-for-beginners-8dfa0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the sixth day of Cisco Advent Calendar 2019 by Cisco Systems LLC.
Seven years have passed since the SuperVision team at the University of Toronto, Canada won the ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Challenge (ILSVRC) 2012 in 2012. At this time, by using a model using deep learning, modeling in machine learning and deep learning is often done in the third AI boom, and it is common sense nowadays to use machine learning/deep learning for AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try extracting features from sensor data with CNN</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-extracting-features-from-sensor-data-with-cnn-fd392/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-extracting-features-from-sensor-data-with-cnn-fd392/</guid>
      <description># I tried convolution with sensor data (1 dimensional vector)  The convolutional neural network is generally used in image processing, but this time, I tried using a one-dimensional vector as seen in sensor data. The point is to convert the data structure using reshape to make it pseudo-three-dimensional (RGB, X, Y), which is the same as the image. I think that convolution can extract features even if there are few learning parameters, and is effective in detecting anomalies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>