<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Vtuber on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/vtuber/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Vtuber on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/vtuber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Try running wav2pix, which creates a face image from audio (there is also an anime face generator)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-running-wav2pix-which-creates-a-face-image-from-audio-there-is-also-an-anime-face-generator-159ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-running-wav2pix-which-creates-a-face-image-from-audio-there-is-also-an-anime-face-generator-159ce/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The world of deep learning, especially Generative Adversarial Networks (GAN), has grown dramatically in recent years, and I think that research is progressing in various fields such as text-to-image, voice conversion, and sound source separation.
In this talk, I will loosely write about wav2pix, which generates face images from voice.
Paper: WAV2PIX: SPEECH-CONDITIONED FACE GENERATION USING GENERATIVEADVERSARIAL NETWORKS
#Overview https://imatge-upc.github.io/wav2pix/
The proposed model consists of the following three modules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a chatbot that supports free input with Word2Vec</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</guid>
      <description>This article is the first day article of [Zeals Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/zeals).  Nice to meet you. This is Tamaki, who will join Zeals from the next fiscal year. Zeals operates a chatbot technology called chat commerce. Also, I am currently researching natural language processing at university. There are conversations in which bots do not have natural language processing, but I thought it would be interesting to add natural language processing technology to them, so I decided to make this the subject of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>