<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> R on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  R on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Causal reasoning using machine learning (arrangement of causal reasoning methods)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fa2135a81/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fa2135a81/</guid>
      <description># Causal reasoning using machine learning   A rough understanding and notes of when to use causal reasoning using machine learning methods that have been actively used in recent years (Memorandum) Basically, the current causal reasoning method is summarized as a flow chart.
 Introduction Causal reasoning is a series of statistical methods aimed at answering the cause of an outcome. Generally, statistical approaches such as regression analysis focus on quantifying how changes in X are related to changes in Y.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 5 Data Science Masterpieces You Can Learn for Free [Japanese books are not scared if you can speak English even if they are expensive]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5e5a7f3f5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5e5a7f3f5/</guid>
      <description>#Let&#39;s study by this time  There are many generous organizations overseas, or there are many specialized books that can be read for free.
There are other summary articles of this series, I would like to display translated Japanese books and original books side by side. Especially introduced only in the field of data science.
Maybe that expensive original book is actually free?
(As of May 2020)
#1
Japanese: Basics of statistical learning (15,000 yen) It&amp;rsquo;s commonly called a &amp;ldquo;castella book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I have read 10 books related to time series data, so I write a book review.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/58c3e1135/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/58c3e1135/</guid>
      <description>#About the standing position of each book  I&amp;rsquo;m worried about what kind of axis to explain the standing position, but this time I tried to position it as &amp;ldquo;arbitrary and prejudiced&amp;rdquo; on the two axes of &amp;ldquo;target reader level&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;relationship with time series&amp;rdquo;.
#Introduction At work, I use various methods for various data regarding data analysis, but when I analyze it, there are surprisingly many time series data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to insert NEologd dictionary in Windows relatively easily-system dictionary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e491f1712/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e491f1712/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I used WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux)+Ubuntu to install the NEologd dictionary for MeCab morphological analysis, but it was relatively easy to install with git for Windows and 7-zip.
Since I wrote about user dictionaries in the previous article ↓, this time it is the system dictionary. https://qiita.com/zincjp/items/c61c441426b9482b5a48
#environment Windows10 64bit Language: Japanese MeCab 0.996-32bit
What to introduce git for Windows 2.20.1 64-bit 7-Zip 18.06 64-bit #Introduction procedure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to learn newbies before they get into Bayesian statistics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d02a81766/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d02a81766/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article and target audience  This article provides a guide to those who have barely studied statistics before being able to speak brilliantly about Young&amp;rsquo;s statistics in the now known Bayesian stats.
The goal of this article is to be able to tell correct things about Bayesian statistics with a doya face, and to be able to argue with people who are familiar with statistics.
Please note that studying this article will not make you familiar with Bayesian statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [You can see from the photo] In 10 minutes, how to start kaggle from initial status (novice) to Contributor.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/22954bb7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/22954bb7b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Nikkei xTECH Business AI Advent Calendar 2019 I will be in charge of the 4th day of the road to AI Dojo &amp;ldquo;Kaggle&amp;rdquo;.
#kaggle&amp;rsquo;s say depends on status
Users are ranked in kaggle. It is called Progression. It&amp;rsquo;s a progress level or something like a title.
Depending on this rank, the degree of attention to the posted script and the degree of influence of the statement differ.
When you register, you will be given the title novice, and if you meet certain conditions, you will become Contributor, If you want to become a higher rank from there, you must make statements that collect good evaluations from others, obtain medals, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s seriously think about the definition of data scientists and skill sets</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f9bf14a75/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f9bf14a75/</guid>
      <description>## What is a data scientist?  As the subject of the title, let&amp;rsquo;s think about the profession of being a data scientist, which is being said variously these days. Even in the industry, the definition of this occupation is vague and there is no unified view.
Well, honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s a story that &amp;ldquo;a data scientist wants to give a name to a person who wants to give it a name&amp;rdquo;, but since it&amp;rsquo;s a big deal, I&amp;rsquo;ll write my personal thoughts during this period.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>