<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> scipy on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/scipy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  scipy on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/scipy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross the walls of the left-hand and right-hand coordinate systems.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/cross-the-walls-of-the-left-hand-and-right-hand-coordinate-systems.-05089/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/cross-the-walls-of-the-left-hand-and-right-hand-coordinate-systems.-05089/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is a completely personal memo at that time because I needed to convert the rotation in the left-handed coordinate system (often used in computer vision and Unity) and the rotation in the right-handed coordinate system (often used in robots and physics). Since many libraries are created in the right-handed coordinate system, I have summarized how to convert at that time.
4 things that represent rotation To express rotation in the first place</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Fluid simulation: Incompressible Navier-Stokes equation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-fluid-simulation-incompressible-navier-stokes-equation-9d2a9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-fluid-simulation-incompressible-navier-stokes-equation-9d2a9/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  While studying Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD), I would like to summarize the knowledge necessary for constructing a computational fluid dynamics analysis code. It seems that there are many mistakes, so please feel free to contact us if you find it.
Target audience  People who can use Python People who are interested in numerical calculation People who are interested in fluid mechanics Those who understand basic university physics and mathematics (simple differential equations and linear algebra?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to predict the number of domestic infections of the new corona with a mathematical model</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-the-number-of-domestic-infections-of-the-new-corona-with-a-mathematical-model-a6632/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-the-number-of-domestic-infections-of-the-new-corona-with-a-mathematical-model-a6632/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  Since I found The Lancet&amp;rsquo;s paper 1 that predicts the number of infected people with a mathematical model, I implemented a mathematical model to predict the number of infected people in Japan and compared it with other infectious diseases.
Summary  The number of infected people was predicted by the SEIR model. The basic reproduction number of the new Corona is about 2.9, which is slightly higher than that of influenza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Article that enables high-speed sparse matrix calculation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-article-that-enables-high-speed-sparse-matrix-calculation-e5500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-article-that-enables-high-speed-sparse-matrix-calculation-e5500/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  **A sparse matrix is a matrix in which most of the elements of the matrix are 0. It is used in a wide range of fields such as numerical calculation, machine learning, and graph theory (I think). Since most of the matrix is 0, if you devise to ignore 0, you can perform matrix calculation at high speed. For example, if you use a large-scale sparse matrix (nearly 90% is 0) (1 million rows x 1 million columns) and only use non-zero parts, the calculation time will be about 1/10 and the calculation can be completed quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The SEIR model was used to predict the behavior of the new coronavirus.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-seir-model-was-used-to-predict-the-behavior-of-the-new-coronavirus.-ed28f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-seir-model-was-used-to-predict-the-behavior-of-the-new-coronavirus.-ed28f/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  The number of new corona pneumonia (Covid-19) that occurred in Wuhan, Hubei Province, China in December 2019 is increasing in Japan. Understanding how infectious diseases such as influenza, AIDS, and SARS spread through human populations through the process of confirming the effects of health policies such as setting vaccinations and isolation of infected persons. Is also important. In the previous article, I explained the SIR model, but I will introduce the SEIR model that considers the latency of infectious diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of infectious disease mathematical prediction model (SIR model)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-infectious-disease-mathematical-prediction-model-sir-model-3078f/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-infectious-disease-mathematical-prediction-model-sir-model-3078f/</guid>
      <description>#1. At the beginning  The number of people infected with the new coronavirus (Convid-19) in Wuhan, China in December 2019 in Japan is increasing. Understanding how wrestling infectious diseases such as influenza, AIDS, and SARS spread in human populations is essential to confirm the effects of health policies such as setting vaccinations and isolating infected people. Is also important. Here, we will introduce the SIR model, which is the basis of the infectious disease mathematical prediction model, and the process of calculating this model in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics with python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/statistics-with-python-25022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/statistics-with-python-25022/</guid>
      <description># Total and average  numpy.sum(data) # sum numpy.mean(data) # mean #Maximum, minimum, and median
numpy.amax(data) numpy.amin(data) numpy.median(data) #dispersion
An index that indicates how far the data is from the average
\sigma^2=\frac{1}{N}\sum_{i=1}^{n} (x_i-\mu)^2 numpy.var(data, ddof = 0) Unbiased distribution The sample variance is a value obtained by further calculating the variance using the sample mean, but this value causes an underestimate bias. Therefore, the one without bias becomes the universal variance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carefully understand Poisson distribution and draw with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/carefully-understand-poisson-distribution-and-draw-with-python-83682/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/carefully-understand-poisson-distribution-and-draw-with-python-83682/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The Poisson distribution that always appears when studying statistics, but the formula for the probability distribution did not come into my mind at all, so I tried to understand it carefully from the derivation of the probability distribution. I also draw in Python to grab the image.
##reference I have referred to the following to understand the Poisson distribution and draw the distribution.
 [University Mathematics] Poisson distribution (specific examples and their meanings, Poisson&amp;rsquo;s limit theorem) [Probability Statistics]  Introduction to Statistics (Basic Statistics I) What is Poisson distribution?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to sparse matrix with scipy.sparse</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-sparse-matrix-with-scipy.sparse-60322/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-sparse-matrix-with-scipy.sparse-60322/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 22nd day article of [Furukawa Laboratory Advent Calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/flab).  I am an OB of Furukawa Laboratory, but I was invited by a student to participate. Thank you.
#Introduction This time, I would like to explain the sparse matrix and its representation format while also describing the implementation by scipy.sparse. This article is intended for people who have become accustomed to numpy to some extent, but haven&amp;rsquo;t dealt with sparse matrix-related&amp;hellip; I just want to know a little about what it is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to sample from any probability density function in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-sample-from-any-probability-density-function-in-python-93626/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-sample-from-any-probability-density-function-in-python-93626/</guid>
      <description>~~MCMC should be done! Onegacious without the tsukkomi  As you know, many probability density functions are predefined in scipy, and by using them, you can easily perform sampling and plotting of probability density functions.
For example,
stats.norm.rvs(loc=50, scale=20, size=1000) Then you can get 1000 samples from a normal distribution with mean 50 and standard deviation 20, and
x = np.linspace(0, 100, 100) px = stats.norm.pdf(x, loc=50, scale=20) plt.plot(x, px) Then we can also plot the normal distribution at $0&amp;lt;x&amp;lt;100$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Dynamic Mode Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-dynamic-mode-decomposition-702f6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-dynamic-mode-decomposition-702f6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I could only think of Fourier transform or wavelet transform as the method of investigating temporal changes, but I learned that there is a good method called dynamic mode decomposition (DMD) that can extract modes in both temporal and spatial directions. I will record it here in order to deepen my understanding.
The content is almost the same as the reference site, but I will write a slightly translated Google translation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>