<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> artificial intelligence on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  artificial intelligence on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Challenges for large-scale models such as BERT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e72d82635/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e72d82635/</guid>
      <description># Breakthrough model of natural language processing-BERT  BERT[BidirectionalEncoderRepresentationsfromTransformers]wasannouncedtoGoogle&amp;rsquo;steaminthefallof2018.Thisistheresultoflearningamodelinarevolutionarywayforaverylargenetworkwithalargeamountofdatausingatransformerarchitecture.PleaserefertoThisarticle for learning method and accuracy.
In the field of machine learning where open source and free exchange of information are important, new ideas are published as papers at arxiv.org, and models are shared on github. Doing is the basic way. As soon as new ideas are published, they can be referenced and reused by machine learning researchers and development teams around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] There are many books on machine learning, but which should I buy? Recommended by level! ! &lt;For beginners&gt;</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a2f649aa5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a2f649aa5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There are many books on machine learning, but I recommend you to buy one by level.
There are 5 levels from Level 1 to Level 5. Please choose a book from the level that suits you. It will be best if you read the books introduced here in 3 to 4 months. I don&amp;rsquo;t cover studying methods in this note, but there are some very good online courses, such as Cousera&amp;rsquo;s machine learning courses, so please try using services other than books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I installed the IoT platform Rimotte</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/392782870/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/392782870/</guid>
      <description>### What is Limotte  Rimotte is an All-In-One platform for always-on apps such as IoT. It is used by using the “Station” that is installed and used on Windows and a web browser that runs on Android, iOS, Windows, MacOS, Linux, etc. Not limited to IoT, it can be used for applications that are used without being connected to the Internet, and applications such as measurement, monitoring, automation, and AI can be easily realized.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>