<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Workflow on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/workflow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Workflow on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/workflow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Predict Titanic survival using Kedro, a machine learning workflow management tool</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/predict-titanic-survival-using-kedro-a-machine-learning-workflow-management-tool-42067/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/predict-titanic-survival-using-kedro-a-machine-learning-workflow-management-tool-42067/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In this article, I will build a Titanic survival prediction workflow using a library called Kedro.
Recently, there are many types of machine learning workflow management tools and construction support tools. Just what I&amp;rsquo;ve heard,
 Apache Airflow luigi -gokart Dagster Metaflow DataBolt(d6t) Kedro  And so on.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare the performance of these tools through a common prediction project! That is the origin of this article.
As a common project, we chose Titanic survival prediction, which is a path that anyone should go through once they start data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the ETL processing framework cliboa?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-is-the-etl-processing-framework-cliboa-503fd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-is-the-etl-processing-framework-cliboa-503fd/</guid>
      <description>What is #ETL processing?  ETL is a term that connects the initials of extract, transform, and load. Extract, transform, and load are translated into Japanese for extraction, processing, and loading. The ETL processing is to perform processing indicated by ETL on some data (text file, csv file, etc.).
What is #cliboa BrainPad We designed and implemented the common base part of the ETL processing function that was developed and operated in-house as an application framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried Metaflow, an ML workflow tool developed by Netflix [Overview]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-metaflow-an-ml-workflow-tool-developed-by-netflix-overview-925c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-metaflow-an-ml-workflow-tool-developed-by-netflix-overview-925c8/</guid>
      <description>Netflix has released [Metaflow](https://metaflow.org), a Python library for managing machine learning workflows.  With this,
 Data processing/model building process can be described in a uniform format, making it easy to follow the overall flow Version control of model and pretreatment process is possible Distributed processing is possible on AWS environment  There are advantages such as.
If you are curious, let&amp;rsquo;s go through the official documentationwhilerunningthetutorial. .. For Tutorial, after inserting the library with pip install metaflow,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>