<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> neural network on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/neural-network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  neural network on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/neural-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Neural network super introduction that can be understood even by cats</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/489a4158b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/489a4158b/</guid>
      <description>![IMG_0489.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/458623/93e891ee-1dc8-fa4e-7bb5-5a1922ffe589.png)  Written  What is a neural network? a unit? weight? bias? Activation function Overview of NN Summary  The goal is to get a general idea of the neural network. I don&amp;rsquo;t use mathematical formulas, so people who are allergic to mathematics should also check it.
#1.What is a neural network?
A neural network is something like the one below. When written in English, it is Neural Network, so it is often abbreviated as NN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I passed the 1st AI implementation test [A grade], so I tried collecting various things</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/437ae52fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/437ae52fe/</guid>
      <description>[JDLA Certification Program](https://www.jdla.org/business/forE-qualificationssponsoredbytheJapanDeepLearningAssociation)(https://www.jdla.org/business/certificate/?id=certificate_No01)Certificate-?id=certificate_No04)Study-AICo.,Ltd.establishedanAIimplementationcertificationexecutivecommittee,andasaqualificationtoacquiretheskilltochallengeEqualification,``[AIimplementationOfficialtest](http://kentei.ai/)&amp;quot; has started. When I took the test: cherry_blossom: Passed successfully: cherry_blossom: I did. Therefore, I will dump the information such as the test measures that I actually worked on before I remembered it.  Pass notification email that actually arrived It seems that you have made a careless mistake about the problem of Python. .. ..
 This qualification was taken from past article&amp;lsquo;sarticleby[@kazzy0099][scheduledupdate]Datascience/machinelearningrelatedqualificationsummary and took the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Transform a real ferocious crocodile image into a 100 crocodile-smiling neural style with Keras</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5fed6bf9d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5fed6bf9d/</guid>
      <description>#What is neural style conversion?  Neural style conversion is one of the machine learning techniques that transforms a target image into the style (texture) of another image to generate a new image. It&amp;rsquo;s a technology used in apps that change Van Gogh&amp;rsquo;s image of a city or people. Now, let&amp;rsquo;s try using this technology to see if this time we can transform a real, ferocious crocodile image that seems to eat humans into a gentle crocodile crocodile by transforming its style into a crocodile style that will die 100 days later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Super introduction] Machine learning using Python-From environment construction to simple perceptron implementation-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/365f33e34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/365f33e34/</guid>
      <description># First of all  This article is from the 7th day of the DMM WEBCAMP Advent Calendar. This time it&amp;rsquo;s a super introduction, so I created it for those who have never tried machine learning but want to start **.
The purpose is to get a rough idea of machine learning and try to implement a basic simple perceptron for the time being, so I&amp;rsquo;ve written a lot about the explanation of machine learning etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>