<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SQLite3 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/sqlite3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SQLite3 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/sqlite3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simulate temperature measurement with Raspberry Pi &#43; Flask &#43; SQLite &#43; Ajax</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f3530677d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f3530677d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is convenient to be able to debug with software alone when measuring temperature with Raspberry Pi and acquiring sensor status with GPIO. Therefore, we created a debug environment that simulates temperature measurement and acquisition of sensor status with GPIO, and displays it on a website (created with Flask). Save the simulated temperature and sensor state in SQLite and refresh the page via Ajax. The temperature and sensor values are hard to understand, so it looks as if the living room temperature and sensor had changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Easy to understand Python web application (Django) for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fbd235008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fbd235008/</guid>
      <description>#Composition of commentary articles     No. Title      1 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (1) [Environment]    2 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (2) [Project creation]    3 Python web application (Django) is easy to understand even for beginners (3) [Application creation/DB setting]    4 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (4) [Introduction to routing settings and MTV design patterns] ←   5 Python Web application (Django) is easy to understand for beginners (5) [Introduction to DB operation with Django shell]    6 Explanation of Python Web application (Django) for beginners (6) [MTV design pattern completion]     Development environment  OS: Mac OS Sierra (10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>