<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Unity on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/unity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Unity on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/unity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Cross the walls of the left-hand and right-hand coordinate systems.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/cross-the-walls-of-the-left-hand-and-right-hand-coordinate-systems.-05089/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/cross-the-walls-of-the-left-hand-and-right-hand-coordinate-systems.-05089/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is a completely personal memo at that time because I needed to convert the rotation in the left-handed coordinate system (often used in computer vision and Unity) and the rotation in the right-handed coordinate system (often used in robots and physics). Since many libraries are created in the right-handed coordinate system, I have summarized how to convert at that time.
4 things that represent rotation To express rotation in the first place</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Airtest, one question one answer. Unity app E2E test starting with Airtest and Poco</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/airtest-one-question-one-answer.-unity-app-e2e-test-starting-with-airtest-and-poco-f83d5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/airtest-one-question-one-answer.-unity-app-e2e-test-starting-with-airtest-and-poco-f83d5/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 12/20 article of [Sumzap Advent Calendar 2019 #1](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/sumzap1).  What is # Airtest
https://airtest.netease.com/ Cross platform UI automation IDE developed and published by NetEase. Here we will refer to the generic name of IDEs and projects for automated testing of mobile applications that use image recognition. By using this, you can create test code without knowing the code on the project directly. You can mass-produce the test as if it were an E2E test, or repeat the same action endlessly as an aging test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [ML-Aents] I tried machine learning using TensorFlow of Unity and Python (v0.11β compatible)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ml-aents-i-tried-machine-learning-using-tensorflow-of-unity-and-python-v0.11%CE%B2-compatible-687f0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ml-aents-i-tried-machine-learning-using-tensorflow-of-unity-and-python-v0.11%CE%B2-compatible-687f0/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any Japanese article about v0.11.0, so please take a note.
This article is for beginners. Unity beginners mimic one of ML-Agents official tutorials do it It is one of the machine learning, __ which I tried __ Reinforcement Learning.
I will make something like this. :arrow_up:__
For those who know how to operate Unity easily, but who have not done machine learning yet. Rather than focusing on theory, I introduce you to Zakuri so that you can experience while moving your hands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>