<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitHubActions on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/githubactions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitHubActions on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/githubactions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Prepare a pseudo API server using GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/prepare-a-pseudo-api-server-using-github-actions-e7021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/prepare-a-pseudo-api-server-using-github-actions-e7021/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Perhaps recently, a feature called GitHub Actions has been added. This is the one that can fire certain Actions (shell script executions) for certain events. For example, it is a function for so-called CI/CD that builds when PR of dev branch is merged and pushes it to dev-pages branch.
At this time, I participated in the COVID-19 countermeasure site Hokkaido version, which is currently a big move, and developed using this function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried a visual regression test on GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-a-visual-regression-test-on-github-pages-80026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-a-visual-regression-test-on-github-pages-80026/</guid>
      <description>#Motivation  Hello @glassmonkey. CI is Github Action. Since I wanted to try using images if I did CI, I tried a visual regression test easily. I made it in a rush, so I would appreciate any feedback.
#What is a visual regression test?
The explanation on Astamuse-sama&amp;rsquo;s blog was easy to understand, so I will quote it.
 The visual regression test is a visual regression test, specifically a test that takes a screenshot and extracts the differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Automated test of Pipenv &#43; Pytest with Github Actions</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/automated-test-of-pipenv-pytest-with-github-actions-e74c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/automated-test-of-pipenv-pytest-with-github-actions-e74c6/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Last time, I performed an automatic test using Travis CI in “I did an automated test of Pipenv + Pytest with Travis CI”,but[GithubActions]((https://help.github.com/ja/actions/automating-your-workflow-with-github-actions/about-github-actions) is now available, so I tried it here as well. The repositories that I actually tried are as follows. https://github.com/doara-developer/weatherlib
Github Actions CI/CD tool on Github. It&amp;rsquo;s still in beta now, but soon will be standard support. Available by sending Beta Participation Request. In my case, I went there a few days after applying.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>