<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> GoogleColaboratory on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/googlecolaboratory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  GoogleColaboratory on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/googlecolaboratory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Introduction] Satellite data analysis using Python (Google Colab environment)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-satellite-data-analysis-using-python-google-colab-environment-97b2e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-satellite-data-analysis-using-python-google-colab-environment-97b2e/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction-What is satellite data-   Artificial satellite data refers to data acquired by &amp;ldquo;remote sensing&amp;rdquo; using artificial satellites. Until now, satellite data required specialized tools and a large-capacity data processing platform, so the available organizations were limited to university institutions and some specialized institutions, but the spread of open source libraries and data By using the processing infrastructure cloud, an external environment has been set up in which general organizations can easily handle satellite data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to easily draw the structure of neural network on Google Colaboratory using convnet-drawer</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-easily-draw-the-structure-of-neural-network-on-google-colaboratory-using-convnet-drawer-d2b6d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-easily-draw-the-structure-of-neural-network-on-google-colaboratory-using-convnet-drawer-d2b6d/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img width=&amp;quot;498&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;nn-draw.png&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/81919/087786b6-8954-4811-b377-f781f3fe7881.png&amp;quot;&amp;gt;  What is &amp;ldquo;convnet-drawer&amp;rdquo;? It is a software that visualizes the structure of the neural network created by @yu4u. I knew it existed before, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t tried it yet, so I tried it. It felt good to run on Google Colaboratory (Google Colab), so I also created a notebook that you can try easily.
Please refer to the following blog article for explanations about Google Colab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried SARS analysis before coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-sars-analysis-before-coronavirus-62138/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-sars-analysis-before-coronavirus-62138/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;m bored of the coronavirus lately and I&amp;rsquo;m bored staying at home, so I want to go out early, so In order to know the trend of Navirus, I analyzed from the same type of SARS virus.
Future outlook  With the epidemic of coronavirus, SARS virus of the same classification is analyzed After that, we also analyze coronavirus Compare the two ##First First of all, I started searching for data because there is no data even if I say to analyze it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easily learn 100 language processing knocks 2020 with Google Colaboratory</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/easily-learn-100-language-processing-knocks-2020-with-google-colaboratory-e4694/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/easily-learn-100-language-processing-knocks-2020-with-google-colaboratory-e4694/</guid>
      <description># 100 language processing What is knock 2020  100 language processing knock 2020
It is a collection of problems on the above site. I quote from the site.
 100 Language Processing Knock is a collection of problems aimed at learning programming, data analysis, and research skills in a fun way while tackling practical and exciting challenges.
 I am very grateful to be able to publish such wonderful things for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free first-principles calculation using Google Colaboratory</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/free-first-principles-calculation-using-google-colaboratory-a31ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/free-first-principles-calculation-using-google-colaboratory-a31ab/</guid>
      <description>Recently, for those who can not experiment with the new corona, &amp;quot;Free first-principles calculation for physical property experimenter&amp;quot;  https://cometscome.github.io/DFT/build/ I wrote an article, but in the process I learned how to do first-principles calculation only with Google Colab, so I would like to share it here as well.
Things necessary  Browser Google account  Software to use  Quantum Espresso: First principles calculation software Atomic Simulation Environment (ASE): Python library for atomic and molecular simulations https://qiita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Data Augmentation with PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-data-augmentation-with-pytorch-9b56a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-data-augmentation-with-pytorch-9b56a/</guid>
      <description>Inflating data with #PyTorch (Data Augmentation)  I will summarize the method of padding data with PyTorch. Regarding PyTorch itself, I wrote an introductory article on the blog before, so please refer to the following if you like.
Introduction to the featured deep learning framework &amp;ldquo;PyTorch&amp;rdquo;
Please refer to the following article for the reason for implementing data padding and specific examples.
Image Augmentation Method for Improving Deep Learning Accuracy by Playing with Free Materials</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyPI package for easy use of Cotoha on Google colab</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</guid>
      <description>## 2020/04/10 PyPI package has been released!  For details, see here(I&amp;rsquo;mreallyhappytohaveastar!)
If you want to use it quickly, please refer to the code below
$ pip install cotoha_at_python from cotohacall.main import cotoha_call import os os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_ID&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Your ID&amp;#39; os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_SECRET&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Ypur Secret&amp;#39; sentence =&amp;#39;API service that enables highly accurate natural language analysis of Japanese. With the COTOHA API, you can easily use the natural language analysis technology that utilizes the research results of NTT Group for over 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning with Python, a quick and easy analysis of the weather data of the last 10 years was started.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/beginning-with-python-a-quick-and-easy-analysis-of-the-weather-data-of-the-last-10-years-was-started.-ee6a3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/beginning-with-python-a-quick-and-easy-analysis-of-the-weather-data-of-the-last-10-years-was-started.-ee6a3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I recently started studying Python. Since I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, I&amp;rsquo;d like to make a post that will be useful for those who are new to Python like me. Since I have never written Python, this time I would like to do a simple data analysis while understanding the syntax of python and what kind of library it has.
Reference book: [Immediately usable! Can be practiced in work! How to create AI/machine learning/deep learning apps with Python](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wear Instagram</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/wear-instagram-3d933/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/wear-instagram-3d933/</guid>
      <description>What kind of photos do you post when you post photos on instagram? [^1]  I think that SNS for showing to others, it is easy to unconsciously produce a fulfilling self **. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s what your actions are tied to ** your SNS&amp;rsquo;s past posts?
I would like to express such a situation.
 This article is Keio SFC Tokui Lab (Computational Creativity Lab.) Also serves as a commentary on the summer camp 2019 hackathon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the shortest path to create an image recognition model by machine learning and implement an Android application</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-the-shortest-path-to-create-an-image-recognition-model-by-machine-learning-and-implement-an-android-application-453a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-the-shortest-path-to-create-an-image-recognition-model-by-machine-learning-and-implement-an-android-application-453a2/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article   How to easily create an image recognition model and share it as an application  Execution environment  google colaboratory (Runtime: GPU)(tensorflow 2.0)(Google Chrome) win 10 Android Studio (3.5.2) android 9.0(Huawei mate 10 pro)  What to write in this article  Dataset creation method for image recognition model How to create image recognition model How to load the created image recognition model in Android Studio My failure (?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>P100-PCIE-16GB was added to the GPU of Google Colab somehow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/p100-pcie-16gb-was-added-to-the-gpu-of-google-colab-somehow-56633/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/p100-pcie-16gb-was-added-to-the-gpu-of-google-colab-somehow-56633/</guid>
      <description>* * This article is based on November 24, 2019.  While thinking that everyone may already know. .. .. ..
About Google colab GPU gacha I think it&amp;rsquo;s well known that you have a GPU gacha. See below for details. https://qiita.com/koshian2/items/d33edc963ed6cfcad77e
Trigger I thought that it was faster than usual, and when I checked the GPU, P100 was added as follows. GPU speed comparison Immediately, I compared the training speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Fully automatic connection] 90 minutes and 12 hours solved with Colaboratory file only [Use Selenium]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fully-automatic-connection-90-minutes-and-12-hours-solved-with-colaboratory-file-only-use-selenium-8869b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fully-automatic-connection-90-minutes-and-12-hours-solved-with-colaboratory-file-only-use-selenium-8869b/</guid>
      <description>Are you using Google Colaboratory? It&#39;s the best, isn&#39;t it?  Google Colaboratory is a Jupyter notebook environment that runs on a browser. Moreover, GPU and TPU machines can be used free of charge. That&amp;rsquo;s the best.
However, there were two rules about usage time (described later), and it was also a addictive point to crawl Colaboratory users.
&amp;ldquo;When I wake up in the morning, the connection will be cut&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>