<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> programming on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  programming on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Foreign Coding Interview Measures in the leetcode Era</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/foreign-coding-interview-measures-in-the-leetcode-era-9cfa3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/foreign-coding-interview-measures-in-the-leetcode-era-9cfa3/</guid>
      <description>Make a note of measures such as GAFAM or FAANG, or software engineer interview measures that tend to be similar to those (such as Indeed or PFN in Tokyo).  #Coding interview and leetcode
Foreign IT companies place great importance on coding interviews when hiring software engineers. It&amp;rsquo;s more like a programming contest problem, which is easier than business coding, and it seems common sense that American students and engineers take a few months of proactive measures when they receive an IT company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A function that makes you think that Itching is out of reach... in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-function-that-makes-you-think-that-itching-is-out-of-reach...-in-python-b24ac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-function-that-makes-you-think-that-itching-is-out-of-reach...-in-python-b24ac/</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of Python techniques, small tips and tricks useful for everyday programming.  We have confirmed the operation with Python 3.8.0.
Comparison of 3 or more values 1 == 2 == 3 # -&amp;gt; False 1 &amp;lt;2 &amp;lt;3 &amp;lt;4 # -&amp;gt; True Time (datetime/date) comparison Flexible comparisons are possible thanks to magic methods.
Reference: [Python] Allow comparison operation in original class
from datetime import date feb1 = date(2020, 2, 1) feb2 = date(2020, 2, 2) feb3 = date(2020, 2, 3) feb1 &amp;lt;feb2 &amp;lt;= feb2 &amp;lt;feb3 # -&amp;gt; True Maximum/minimum time from datetime import date # Intentionally reverse order dates = [ date(2020, 2, 3), date(2020, 2, 2), date(2020, 2, 1), ] min(dates) # -&amp;gt; datetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Minimal implementation for doing UnionFind in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/minimal-implementation-for-doing-unionfind-in-python-52fd4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/minimal-implementation-for-doing-unionfind-in-python-52fd4/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I am happy.  Sometimes I had problems with UnionFind, but I tended to use other people&amp;rsquo;s libraries, so I&amp;rsquo;ll write about it as a review. If you think that it&amp;rsquo;s like a forgetful personal note
Important example AtCoder Typical Contest 001 B-Union Find https://atcoder.jp/contests/atc001/tasks/unionfind_a
Union Find&amp;rsquo;s pure problem An explanation slide is also attached, so I will follow along with this.
https://www.slideshare.net/chokudai/union-find-49066733 Union find (primary set data structure) from AtCoder Inc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I thought about how to learn programming for free.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-thought-about-how-to-learn-programming-for-free.-97e12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-thought-about-how-to-learn-programming-for-free.-97e12/</guid>
      <description># Background  I thought about a low-cost way to learn programming from an empty situation. (Mac) Is the continuation of.
This time, I summarized how to take a smartphone and learn the program for free for those who are new to buying a PC.
OPAC-Library search system Perhaps it is OPAC that university graduates know but middle and high school graduates do not. If you are a university, you will be asked at the first orientation of your first year to search for books, magazines, papers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] By clarifying the difference between statistics and machine learning, I can see why many business companies cannot use machine learning!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</guid>
      <description>#What is the difference between statistics and machine learning? Why can&#39;t I predict from machine learning today and make money?  Perhaps everyone wonders when they start studying machine learning. And why can&amp;rsquo;t many business companies use it for their daily work today? The question also comes up. There are various documents, but I was having trouble comprehending them, so I rearranged them myself. I&amp;rsquo;m putting together a lot of information by combining information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Requirements definition-Article that can become a person who can design a system</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/requirements-definition-article-that-can-become-a-person-who-can-design-a-system-741fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/requirements-definition-article-that-can-become-a-person-who-can-design-a-system-741fc/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Have you ever experienced programming while studying programming?
** &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t make a product even after studying&amp;rdquo; ** ** &amp;ldquo;How do you do development in the first place?&amp;rdquo; ** What is the requirement definition?
In order to solve that problem, let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the overall feeling of development. See &amp;ldquo;Software development process&amp;rdquo; below
The programming I&amp;rsquo;m always studying corresponds to the &amp;ldquo;implementation&amp;rdquo; part. In other words, there are as many as four walls before you can exercise your programming skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Process huge excel files with Python to improve productivity</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/process-huge-excel-files-with-python-to-improve-productivity-33983/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/process-huge-excel-files-with-python-to-improve-productivity-33983/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Benedikt Droste](https://towardsdatascience.com/@droste.benedikt),&amp;quot;[BoostyourefficiencyandprocessExcel-fileswithPython](https://towardsdatascience.com/boost-your-efficiency-and-process-excel-files-with-python-cae650c85d6c)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
When you&amp;rsquo;re working with data, you inevitably come into contact with Excel. Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t use it for yourself, it will be needed by clients and colleagues. Excel excels in spreadsheets with small datasets.
But I always lamented when I saw an Excel sheet with tens of thousands of rows and hundreds of columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Beginner] Learn Python basic grammar in 5 hours for free!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/beginner-learn-python-basic-grammar-in-5-hours-for-free-b97b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/beginner-learn-python-basic-grammar-in-5-hours-for-free-b97b2/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  This article is available from AI Academy&amp;rsquo;s Python Syntax quick learningandPythonprogrammingintroduction This is a partial modification based on the content. You can learn the basics of Python basic grammar by reading this article. If you have finished learning Python, please use AI Academy,whereyoucanlearnAIandmachinelearningforfree(onlysomecontentsarechargedbutbasiccontentsarealmostfree). .. *For short-term AI boot camps for individuals, click here (https://aiacademy.jp/bootcamp/)
Why Python? **AI Academyhandleslearningcontentscenteredontheartificialintelligence(AI) field, and Python handles machine learning and deep learning easily in the artificial intelligence field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If you use Python, you should know! 10 convenient libraries</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-python-you-should-know-10-convenient-libraries-f76a9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-you-use-python-you-should-know-10-convenient-libraries-f76a9/</guid>
      <description>*This article is intended to be useful for everyone&#39;s learning by prosta editorial department publishing a very popular Python grammar article now.  Reference site: If you use Python, you should know! 10 handy libraries
If you use #Python you should know! 10 convenient libraries
Python has many standard and external libraries, but due to their abundance, it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to know which one to use. This time, I will introduce a Python library that is useful to know from among them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A problem study memo that asks for too much divided by 1000000007</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-problem-study-memo-that-asks-for-too-much-divided-by-1000000007-fd1fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-problem-study-memo-that-asks-for-too-much-divided-by-1000000007-fd1fc/</guid>
      <description>In programming contests, when the answer gets very large, the question often arises is to find too much divided by a prime number.  I studied the way of thinking about such problems, so I will summarize it. The sample code is basically Python 2.7. Reference: Top Coder Trends and Countermeasures 4 (C++: Counting)
What should I do? You just have to ask too much for each calculation.
In case of addition After adding, you can ask for too much.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>