<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> word2vec on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/word2vec/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  word2vec on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/word2vec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to analyze the hearing survey results with text mining</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-analyze-the-hearing-survey-results-with-text-mining-024e6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-analyze-the-hearing-survey-results-with-text-mining-024e6/</guid>
      <description>#Background  It seems that you conducted an interview with a resident in a certain area in a study by a certain university at a certain university, but there was something unconsciously aware of the people in that area based on the content of the hearing. I decided to try it because I wanted to analyze it.
Used MeCab This is also a familiar morphological analysis engine.
What is morphological analysis?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understanding Word2Vec</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understanding-word2vec-69afa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understanding-word2vec-69afa/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I have summarized what I have learned about Word2Vec, which is now a standard method for natural language processing. The outline of the algorithm is organized and the model is created using the library.
##reference I have referred to the following to understand Word2Vec.
 Deep Learning from Zero ❷-Natural Language Processing EditionK.Saito(Author) How to understand Word2vec with pictures  Efficient Estimation of Word Representations in Vector Space (Original paper) gensim API reference  #Word2Vec overview The following describes the concept of natural language processing, which is the premise of Word2Vec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Sentiment analysis with Python (word2vec)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/sentiment-analysis-with-python-word2vec-55b4e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/sentiment-analysis-with-python-word2vec-55b4e/</guid>
      <description>I recently attended a Python study group sponsored by Team Zet Co., Ltd. The theme this time is &amp;quot;text emotion using word2vec  &amp;ldquo;Analysis.&amp;rdquo; Honestly, it was a pungent theme for me who first touched Python a week ago, but maybe I&amp;rsquo;m going to experience how the grammar I&amp;rsquo;m studying now is being put into shape. I rushed into the train one day before the event.
By the way, let&amp;rsquo;s leave this foreword and go into the main subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Employee 2vec: Extract member characteristics from Slack history and visualize organizational structure</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/employee-2vec-extract-member-characteristics-from-slack-history-and-visualize-organizational-structure-05e2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/employee-2vec-extract-member-characteristics-from-slack-history-and-visualize-organizational-structure-05e2c/</guid>
      <description>It is the 7th day of [ABEJA Advent Calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/abeja).  #Introduction
Last time, I dropped a piece of information that couldn&amp;rsquo;t make a VIP channel in Slack, but it&amp;rsquo;s not good to think that ABEJA is just playing with VIP, so I decided to send it to Tech a little this time. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll try the following two stories. If it&amp;rsquo;s hard to understand, maybe you can jump to the bottom and see the graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create a chatbot that supports free input with Word2Vec</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</guid>
      <description>This article is the first day article of [Zeals Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/zeals).  Nice to meet you. This is Tamaki, who will join Zeals from the next fiscal year. Zeals operates a chatbot technology called chat commerce. Also, I am currently researching natural language processing at university. There are conversations in which bots do not have natural language processing, but I thought it would be interesting to add natural language processing technology to them, so I decided to make this the subject of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Vectorize sentences and search for similar sentences</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/vectorize-sentences-and-search-for-similar-sentences-f9bb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/vectorize-sentences-and-search-for-similar-sentences-f9bb4/</guid>
      <description>I tried searching for similar sentences with Doc2Vec, so I will introduce the implementation.  What is #Doc2Vec In order for a computer to process natural language, human words must first have a value that the computer can handle. Word2Vec exists as a method to vectorize the meaning of words. For details, the link is very easy to understand, but roughly speaking, it expresses that word in a list of n words before and after.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>