<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows10 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/windows10/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows10 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/windows10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment installation by introducing Docker Image of Kaggle on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/environment-installation-by-introducing-docker-image-of-kaggle-on-windows-66bf0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/environment-installation-by-introducing-docker-image-of-kaggle-on-windows-66bf0/</guid>
      <description>I will record as a reminder the part that was clogged up when I tried to easily build the environment on my windows notebook using Kaggle&#39;s Docker Image.  Basically, I am referring to the article of &amp;ldquo;Tenshiki Graffiti&amp;rdquo;, so please refer to here first, and OS is not Win10 Pro except windows. And if you are using Docker toolbox, I think it will be helpful.
Stumble point ① Execution of yaml of docker-compose does not work due to error of volume name After creating the docker-compose yaml file as in the above article, I got an error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python environment construction (Anaconda &#43; VSCode) @ Windows10 [January 2020 edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</guid>
      <description>#Background  When I made a Python environment with Anaconda + VS Code, I was troubled because the latest setting method did not come out, so I will publish my notes for those who will do it now. It seems that there was a VS Code specification change around 2017. Be careful when reading old commentary.
Articles referenced: @Atupon0302: Build Python environment in Windows 10 environment with Anaconda+Visual Studio Code [September 2017]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduce PyTorch (GPU) with Windows10 &#43; Pipenv</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduce-pytorch-gpu-with-windows10-pipenv-69b30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduce-pytorch-gpu-with-windows10-pipenv-69b30/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  While people around me were switching to PyTorch saying that they would like it better, Tensorflow officially made the Tensorboard available, so I decided to change it myself, so I wrote this article.
Target audience official
pip3 install torch===1.3.1 torchvision===0.4.2 -f https://download.pytorch.org/whl/torch_stable.html It can be introduced with, but this is for people who want to do it with pipenv install hogehoge So I don&amp;rsquo;t write about Python or CUDA, so if you are expecting that, please use the browser back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run toio core cube on Windows 10/macOS/Linux with Python library bleak</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/run-toio-core-cube-on-windows-10-macos-linux-with-python-library-bleak-8baa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/run-toio-core-cube-on-windows-10-macos-linux-with-python-library-bleak-8baa2/</guid>
      <description># I want to run the toio core cube on a familiar PC  The toio core cube is a &amp;ldquo;very cute&amp;rdquo; two-wheeled robot that can be controlled by BLE communication. https://toio.github.io/toio-spec/
The other day, I tried to write a story of trying to move the toio core cube directly using BLE communication with a smartphone, but this time using a personal computer I will move the toio core cube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>python3.8 jupyter notebook in venv environment</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python3.8-jupyter-notebook-in-venv-environment-f32bd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python3.8-jupyter-notebook-in-venv-environment-f32bd/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; Information as of 2019 1124. I write so lightly that I die because I am sleepy.   20191227 Addendum This article seems to be in demand
 Starting confirmation and initial setting.
python install I&amp;rsquo;m using the py launcher, so I cannot pass the path to python.
venv environment creation Environment creation. Then activate it. Console is git-bash
$ py -m venv hoge $ .hoge/scripts/activate install jupyter under venv environment Update pip and install jupyter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>