<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows10 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/windows10/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows10 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/windows10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python environment construction (Anaconda &#43; VSCode) @ Windows10 [January 2020 edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-anaconda-vscode-windows10-january-2020-edition-38e96/</guid>
      <description>#Background  When I made a Python environment with Anaconda + VS Code, I was troubled because the latest setting method did not come out, so I will publish my notes for those who will do it now. It seems that there was a VS Code specification change around 2017. Be careful when reading old commentary.
Articles referenced: @Atupon0302: Build Python environment in Windows 10 environment with Anaconda+Visual Studio Code [September 2017]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Run toio core cube on Windows 10/macOS/Linux with Python library bleak</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/run-toio-core-cube-on-windows-10-macos-linux-with-python-library-bleak-8baa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/run-toio-core-cube-on-windows-10-macos-linux-with-python-library-bleak-8baa2/</guid>
      <description># I want to run the toio core cube on a familiar PC  The toio core cube is a &amp;ldquo;very cute&amp;rdquo; two-wheeled robot that can be controlled by BLE communication. https://toio.github.io/toio-spec/
The other day, I tried to write a story of trying to move the toio core cube directly using BLE communication with a smartphone, but this time using a personal computer I will move the toio core cube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] python3.8 jupyter notebook in venv environment</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python3.8-jupyter-notebook-in-venv-environment-f32bd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python3.8-jupyter-notebook-in-venv-environment-f32bd/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; Information as of 2019 1124. I write so lightly that I die because I am sleepy.   20191227 Addendum This article seems to be in demand
 Starting confirmation and initial setting.
python install I&amp;rsquo;m using the py launcher, so I cannot pass the path to python.
venv environment creation Environment creation. Then activate it. Console is git-bash
$ py -m venv hoge $ .hoge/scripts/activate install jupyter under venv environment Update pip and install jupyter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Install Bash on Ubuntu on Windows, Ruby, Python, Jupyter etc.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/install-bash-on-ubuntu-on-windows-ruby-python-jupyter-etc.-fadbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/install-bash-on-ubuntu-on-windows-ruby-python-jupyter-etc.-fadbe/</guid>
      <description>##background  While changing the environment setting of the personal computer, I could not use gnuplot or Ruby&amp;rsquo;s Narray with Cygwin, so I decided to replace it with bash. I also installed Python and Jupyter. #Bash on Ubuntu on Windows Installation I have referred to this article. Let&amp;rsquo;s install Bash on Ubuntu on Windows!  Go to Settings&amp;gt; Update &amp;amp; Security&amp;gt; For Developers and select Developer Mode. Start the command prompt, type bash and press Enter to start the installation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>