<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cisco on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/cisco/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cisco on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/cisco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 2019 edition: Trend analysis of unauthorized access (example of general-purpose server on cloud)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a478195b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a478195b3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as day 23 of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2018 by Cisco colleagues.
2017: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco
I think that many network/infrastructure/server engineers have built a home lab. I had an actual machine at home like that for a few years, but I stopped having equipment at home about a year and a half ago and moved to multiple cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Fast automated test creation using pyATS|Genie&#39;s hidden move Blitz</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fa00872a1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fa00872a1/</guid>
      <description>This article was posted as the 11th day of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by volunteers from Cisco.  2017 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco
#Introduction
Hello. pyATS|GenieI&#39;m@tahigash3fromthedevelopmentteam.Inthisarticle,I&amp;rsquo;llshowyouaneasywaytocreateanetworktestusingpyATS|Genie.
Please refer to the previous article for a brief introduction and installation of pyATS|Genie. Easily check multi-vendor networks with pyATS/Genie and Robot Framework
Worries about network automation I have enumerated the worries of those who have not done network automation yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] First satellite data analysis with Tellus</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0bde39d88/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0bde39d88/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted on the 21st day of Cisco Advent Calendar 2019 by Cisco Systems LLC. What kind of connection does Cisco have with satellite data in the first place? I think that there is a question, so I will introduce it including that.
What you can do with this article  Know what satellite data is Find out what the satellite data platform Tellus is Know how to use Tellus development environment Satellite data can be analyzed using Tellus development environment Understanding what NDVI and NDWI are  Finally you can   Display high-definition satellite image by selecting date and position Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:42:49 GMT, North 35.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simple network operation by linking Cisco DNA Center and Tact Switch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/6cc65e6d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/6cc65e6d1/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the eighth day of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by volunteers from Cisco.
 2017 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco  What do you want to do?  Network operation that anyone can do Cisco&amp;rsquo;s best-selling controller for Cisco DNA Center ~~ Stema ~~ Tips demo Balancing work and material Common cool topics ~~ Policy, AI or Assurance ~ ~, but rather quiet operation that is often heard Reuse of goods bought in 2017  What is this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Time series data abnormality detection for beginners</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8dfa028dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8dfa028dd/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the sixth day of Cisco Advent Calendar 2019 by Cisco Systems LLC.
Seven years have passed since the SuperVision team at the University of Toronto, Canada won the ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Challenge (ILSVRC) 2012 in 2012. At this time, by using a model using deep learning, modeling in machine learning and deep learning is often done in the third AI boom, and it is common sense nowadays to use machine learning/deep learning for AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried MindMeld for the first time</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/9e9d80d24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/9e9d80d24/</guid>
      <description>This article was posted as the 10th day of the Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by Cisco colleagues.  Click here for past calendars 2017 edition: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco
 -&amp;gt; Distribute policy tag with LISP, tried TrustSec with CML/VIRL 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco -&amp;gt; I tried using Cisco&amp;rsquo;s SaaS monitoring and behavior detection tool for multi-cloud environment monitoring  This year, the 3rd year since joining the company (Advent Calendar has also participated for 3 consecutive years!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to automatically generate a port management table from Config of L2SW</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/75ec526ff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/75ec526ff/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In the previous article, I introduced an example of automatically generating Config from the port management table. I tried to automatically generate L2SW Config from the port management table + parameter table + Jinja2 template
In some cases, you may want to create a port management table from the already created Config. This time, using a Python parser library called TTP (Template Text Parser), I automatically generated a CSV format port management table from the L2SW Config file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Device monitoring with IOS-XE On-box Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2c244fd6b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2c244fd6b/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  When monitoring Cisco network equipment, you may want to see the results of show commands. This time, from the Guest Shell of IOS-XE, I would like to get the result of the show command using python and send it to Elasticsearch for visualization.
About Guest Shell Guest Shell is a Linux container environment hosted on IOx, and is implemented in products such as the Catalyst 9000 series and ISR4000 series.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>