<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> unsupervised learning on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/unsupervised-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  unsupervised learning on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/unsupervised-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple method to obtain MNIST correct rate of 97% or more by unsupervised learning (without transfer learning)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simple-method-to-obtain-mnist-correct-rate-of-97-or-more-by-unsupervised-learning-without-transfer-learning-0aa24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simple-method-to-obtain-mnist-correct-rate-of-97-or-more-by-unsupervised-learning-without-transfer-learning-0aa24/</guid>
      <description>First article posted as job hunting news.  I tried to read and implement a paper on IIC (Invariant Information Clustering), which is said to be highly accurate and has unsupervised learning. IIC is a method of clustering by maximizing mutual information. IIC paper here
 Invariant Information Clustering for Unsupervised Image Classification and Segmentation Xu Ji, João F. Henriques, Andrea Vedaldi
 The framework used is TensorFlow 2.0. The target data is familiar MNIST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to summarize the basic form of GPLVM</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-basic-form-of-gplvm-32803/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-basic-form-of-gplvm-32803/</guid>
      <description>This article is from [Furukawa Lab, Advent_calendar Day 23](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/flab).  #Introduction
GPLVM is an unsupervised learning method that uses Gaussian process (GP) and can estimate low-dimensional manifolds whose data are distributed in high-dimensional space. The main attraction of GPLVM is that the model is very simple and highly expandable, and theoretically easy to handle. In fact, it has been extended to more complex situations such as Bayesian estimation of hyperparameters, time series data analysis 1, multiview analysis 2, and tensor decomposition 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>