<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> beginner on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/beginner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  beginner on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/beginner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Machine learning] Understanding the decorrelation from mathematics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/37c0398a7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/37c0398a7/</guid>
      <description>#1.Introduction  ##(1. Purpose If you want to do machine learning, anyone can use scikit-learn etc. to implement it relatively easily. However, in order to achieve results at work or to improve your level, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand the background, but I got this result&amp;rdquo; I think it&amp;rsquo;s clearly weak.
This time, we will focus on &amp;ldquo;correlation&amp;rdquo;**.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about decorrelation, why do you do it?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;How do you use it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction] Satellite data analysis using Python (Google Colab environment)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/97b2e4ed9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/97b2e4ed9/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction-What is satellite data-   Artificial satellite data refers to data acquired by &amp;ldquo;remote sensing&amp;rdquo; using artificial satellites. Until now, satellite data required specialized tools and a large-capacity data processing platform, so the available organizations were limited to university institutions and some specialized institutions, but the spread of open source libraries and data By using the processing infrastructure cloud, an external environment has been set up in which general organizations can easily handle satellite data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Hands-on for beginners] Kaggle&#39;s Predicting house prices is read line by line (1st part: Data reading)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a7f5e4a2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a7f5e4a2c/</guid>
      <description># theme  A job that operates a real estate system as a service, a story broke out that there is no loss in doing hands-on at the field level. That&amp;rsquo;s why we decided to challenge kaggle&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;House Price&amp;rdquo; problem, which is a famous title. So, if you make a note of this properly, it will be useful for later, so I decided to post it to qiita after reading the line by line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Even beginners want to say I understand Python completely</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/10402b314/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/10402b314/</guid>
      <description>My child: &amp;quot;Oh, oh, oh, oh! Don&#39;t understand Python at all!!&amp;quot;  I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, my child who is new to Python doesn&amp;rsquo;t know Python and doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it today&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
I can&amp;rsquo;t say that Python is easy for anyone to program, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think the super-convenient features that are so boring are known to me. Moreover, when I try to use a convenient feature, it makes no sense at all. Nana no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I have read 10 books related to time series data, so I write a book review.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/58c3e1135/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/58c3e1135/</guid>
      <description>#About the standing position of each book  I&amp;rsquo;m worried about what kind of axis to explain the standing position, but this time I tried to position it as &amp;ldquo;arbitrary and prejudiced&amp;rdquo; on the two axes of &amp;ldquo;target reader level&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;relationship with time series&amp;rdquo;.
#Introduction At work, I use various methods for various data regarding data analysis, but when I analyze it, there are surprisingly many time series data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [The strongest English word book bomb ww] Automatically generate the English word book required by engineers in Python-Part 1</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5bf186787/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5bf186787/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I think that everyone has bought once If you automatically create an English word book in Python,
 You don&#39;t need to buy an English word book anymore?  I will verify the hypothesis.   **If LGTM exceeds 10,** We will make more practical ones in the second part (or the second part), so please LGTM if you find it interesting~! About the author Biography After graduating from the Department of Electrical and Information Engineering at the age of 20, at a technical trading company, translating specifications etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The end of the programming beginner who wrote the code with the motivation to bring about the result rather than the technical viewpoint of programming (my pattern)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/bc040fe63/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/bc040fe63/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Introduction&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;  First of all, the target audience for this article is &amp;ldquo;non-engineers&amp;rdquo;.
As a non-engineer, I am aiming to acquire programming skills and explain what I did in the process.
By the way, I am not studying as a programmer now, and I am still studying, and since I was writing an article in the course of studying in the first place, the teacher who was suddenly made an adviser of the Kabaddi club decided the rules of the sport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to learn machine learning from scratch (March 2020 edition)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b5992f5ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b5992f5ed/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Data science and machine learning are fun! However, do you have the experience that you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to study? By the way, I am one of them. In this article, *** What is machine learning in the first place? Even if you are a beginner who knows the word AI but do not know the details, you will learn the learning method *** to learn from the basic foundations necessary to gain knowledge and experience and be able to tackle machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] First data analysis/machine learning (Kaggle)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8d77e3d18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8d77e3d18/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  As I was about to get a job (spring break in the fourth year of university), I suddenly wanted to become a data scientist, so I started working on Kaggle for the time being.
This time, I worked on a tutorial of Kaggle&amp;quot;Titanic&amp;rdquo;.
I have experience in statistical analysis in my research, but since I do not understand machine learning at all, I decided to study with reference to the code of the incredibly excellent person!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I have no emotions... ← Try to analyze if there are no emotions using various emotion estimators</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2f70ad50d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2f70ad50d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Human communication includes not only language but also many non-verbal information such as facial expressions and gestures. When analyzing and interpreting human behavior mechanically and programmatically, more information can be obtained by adding meaning to such non-verbal information. These technologies are being researched and developed in various fields such as image processing, natural language processing, and voice recognition, and are expected to be applied in many fields such as marketing and robot interaction systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Flask introduction ~ Blueprint application note</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fb7d1d58d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fb7d1d58d/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s try the title as easily as possible.  Blueprint allows you to implement the functionality of your application in pieces. Blueprint is officially recommended as a way to organize bloated projects.
Install Flask $ sudo pip3 install flask Directory structure $ cd ~/workspace/sample-flask/ $ls server.py from flask import Flask app = Flask(__name__) @app.route(&amp;#39;/&amp;#39;) def func_1(): return&amp;#39;Hello world&amp;#39; @app.route(&amp;#39;/test&amp;#39;) def func_2(): return&amp;#39;Test&amp;#39; if __name__ ==&amp;#39;__main__&amp;#39;: app.run(host=&amp;#39;0.0.0.0&amp;#39;, port=80, debug=True) Execution command $python3 server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 8 services that even beginners can learn Python (for beginners to advanced users)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3334be951/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3334be951/</guid>
      <description>After checking on various existing sites,  Since the fee display etc. were old, I tried to summarize it again.
If you are an introduction to programming, you can learn from the basics progate progate This is the most recommended learning site for beginners who want to learn programming from now on. The programming terms are very polite and easy to understand, so You will be able to proceed with your learning without any setbacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction to Python for non-engineers</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e0d04f238/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e0d04f238/</guid>
      <description>## Following the trend of the world ~ About programming ~  Recently, &amp;ldquo;programming&amp;rdquo; has come to the forefront without even saying. Until a while ago (2010-2015), programming was something that engineers in the science field worked on, and it was unfamiliar to so-called non-mathematical people, such as those used by PC experts. However, if you look around the world, IT companies such as GAFA are listed in Top 10 in the world market capitalization ranking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python3] A//B and math.floor(A/B) are not always the same! ?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ee26e8cce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ee26e8cce/</guid>
      <description># Note  **This article contains spoilers for &amp;ldquo;Atcoder Beginner Contest 148 E-Double Factorial&amp;rdquo;. Please refrain from browsing if you plan to solve this problem yourself. **
Overview I got into a problem with the title while solving Atcoder, so I&amp;rsquo;ll post this article to keep it as a memorandum and to hear the opinions of Python experts.
Problem Atcoder Beginner Contest 148 E-Double Factorial
Define f(n) as follows for an integer n of 0 or more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Don&#39;t write Python if you want to speed it up</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/1c2c25bf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/1c2c25bf4/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I decided to give a Lightning Talk about Python at work, so I&amp;rsquo;ll write something that can be read in about 5 minutes. The talk theme is &amp;ldquo;Knowledge when trying to speed up in Python&amp;rdquo;. **This isn&amp;rsquo;t an article about Python. **
Target of this article This article is for the following people:
 Python beginner People who are interested in Python but think that it seems not to be speed  Immediate conclusion As the title says, don&amp;rsquo;t write Python (as much as possible) if you want to speed it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction to Docker] I tried to summarize various findings of Docker obtained by studying (Windows/Python)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f7eea9730/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f7eea9730/</guid>
      <description>There was a person in charge of specialized infrastructure related things in the company, and he was kind to the environment, but it would be bad if I had to study Docker around myself as soon as possible. I&#39;ve finally been introduced to Docker recently, so I&#39;ll try to put together and try what I have learned as a memorandum.  Since I have been working on unfamiliar work such as infrastructure around my career, please forgive me for things that are rough (shallow) in terms of knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Re: Competitive programming life starting from zero Chapter 1 Only C&#43;&#43; can be used</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/cea3b9c25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/cea3b9c25/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In this article, I am an aspiring engineer with a programming Wakaba mark on my chest, OT solves the problem of competitive programming given at At. It is an article. You may disappear in despair on the way, but I would like to continue until I get a job! !
#First, a simple profile Name: OT Programming history: 3 months (TECH::EXPERT63 period) Languages available: Ruby (level to make a simple website with Rails), C# (level to make a simple Othello with Unity), Python (&amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; level) Favorite celebrity: Gacky</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let Siri do the job of reading AWS bills posted by Slackbot</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d85fda007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d85fda007/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the iPhone for less than a decade and I noticed that Siri wasn&amp;rsquo;t working at all. Now that smart speakers are popular, I want my Siri to do more, so I decided to read the AWS bill posted by Slackbot.
From the results, it looks like this. When you ask for the price&amp;hellip; He read the content I posted to Slack. Then, I will introduce various ways to make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] After hitting the Qiita API with Python to get a list of articles for beginners, we will worship God articles</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/97e788317/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/97e788317/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Qiita&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Beginner&amp;rdquo; tag and &amp;ldquo;New Programmer Support&amp;rdquo; tag articles for beginners As a new QA engineer, everything is very helpful. Unfortunately, the individual tag page only shows trends and new articles, The specifications make it difficult to find good articles in the past. In this article, first use the Qiita API to write an article for beginners (:= Article with the tag &amp;ldquo;Beginner&amp;rdquo; OR &amp;ldquo;Newcomer programmer support&amp;rdquo;) After creating a program to output all, next read each article in the output list in descending order of likes I would like to introduce the God articles that I felt &amp;ldquo;This is really helpful!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Ikiri high school students will explain blockchain to beginners in 10 minutes! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f4991357e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f4991357e/</guid>
      <description>#1. About this article  ##1-1. Introduction This article was touched by me as a high school student when I received [Udemy: An Introduction to Blockchain Development from Scratch Beginning with Python Taught by Active Silicon Valley Engineers](https://www.udemy.com/share/1021OSAkIbdVdQQXo=/) , I wrote this article with the hope that everyone reading this article should attend. I completed this lesson in 2 days, so if you are already accustomed to development, I think it is sufficiently possible to understand and implement in 1 day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The story that the algorithm came out with a ridiculous conclusion when trying to solve the traveling salesman problem appropriately</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ec2e321b9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ec2e321b9/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 13th day of [Furukawa Lab Advent_calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/flab).  This article was written by a student of Furukawa Lab as part of their studies. The content may be ambiguous or the expressions may be slightly different.
#Introduction Hello everyone Do you know the traveling salesman problem? It&amp;rsquo;s a kind of common combinatorial optimization problem, but in this article I&amp;rsquo;d like to write about a sad case when I tried to solve the traveling salesman problem appropriately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Until the transcendental beginer implements 1&#43;1 using qiskit</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/65f2b91f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/65f2b91f1/</guid>
      <description>### First post  Self-introduction tax_free. I usually write about study sessions that I attended on hatena. Suffering from the day of the school final test and article I&amp;rsquo;m a first year high school student
Environment My development environment
 Mac OS Catalina 10.15.1 Python 3.7.4  Motivation I&amp;rsquo;m a high school student now, but if I wanted to study quantum computing at university, I found this advent calendar, so I joined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [You can see from the photo] In 10 minutes, how to start kaggle from initial status (novice) to Contributor.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/22954bb7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/22954bb7b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Nikkei xTECH Business AI Advent Calendar 2019 I will be in charge of the 4th day of the road to AI Dojo &amp;ldquo;Kaggle&amp;rdquo;.
#kaggle&amp;rsquo;s say depends on status
Users are ranked in kaggle. It is called Progression. It&amp;rsquo;s a progress level or something like a title.
Depending on this rank, the degree of attention to the posted script and the degree of influence of the statement differ.
When you register, you will be given the title novice, and if you meet certain conditions, you will become Contributor, If you want to become a higher rank from there, you must make statements that collect good evaluations from others, obtain medals, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python newbie tried Hello World in 30 seconds using micro framework Flask</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/44f9335fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/44f9335fa/</guid>
      <description>## What is Flask   Python micro web framework Minimal functionality provided as standard Django for full stack framework Reference -Comparison of 4 types of Python Web framework  about me Python history 3 days
Reason for doing looks fun
What I did ** ① Flask installation **
pip install Flask ** ② Make hello.py in your favorite folder ** ③ Paste the following
from flask import Flask app = Flask(__name__) @app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Object-oriented programming learned with Pokemon</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/48274b395/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/48274b395/</guid>
      <description>Pokemon Sword Shield has recently been released and is very popular.  So, taking advantage of this popularity of Pokemon, I will explain object-oriented programming using Pokemon.
What is object-oriented programming? &amp;ldquo;Object&amp;rdquo; is a direct translation of an object. In other words, we try to program as we make things.
Things should have features or parts and movements. The kind of thing is called &amp;ldquo;class&amp;rdquo;, each thing is called &amp;ldquo;instance&amp;rdquo;, and the behavior of thing is called &amp;ldquo;method&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Jupyter Notebook Magic Command My Summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/437656b8c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/437656b8c/</guid>
      <description>### Prerequisites   macOS Catalina 10.15.1 anaconda 4.17.12 jupyter-notebook 5.0.0 Python 3.6.9  What is a magic command Magic Commands is a mechanism provided by the IPython kernel. In addition to the functions related to the operation of Notebook, it provides utility functions such as directory movement and file list display.
Magic command basics Enter ``%&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; at the beginning and then enter the command. The command to output the current directory is as follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Things from building Python environment to running on Windows</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fdf02d4df/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fdf02d4df/</guid>
      <description>When building the Python environment, I went through various articles saying &amp;quot;Authentication proxy settings, coexistence environment, and execution confirmation are all necessary&amp;quot;, so I think that it would be nice to put them all together.  #Introduction
Content The contents introduced in this article are as follows. Please skip the authentication proxy and coexistence environment construction if necessary.
 Install Anaconda (Windows) Authentication proxy settings Different versions coexistence environment construction Run the program in interactive mode Run Python script  For whom For Python beginners who meet any of the following:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>