<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>math on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/math/</link>
    <description>Recent content in math on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/math/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Summary of techniques for automatically determining thresholds</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/29c02b4fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/29c02b4fa/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I often talk about talk about wanting to automatically determine the threshold, so I summarized it.  Threshold design corresponds to two-dimensional unsupervised clustering of two groups. Yes. This time, we will summarize 5 classical and useful methods, taking image binarization as an example.
Note: If the distribution system is unknown, there is no correct answer for threshold determination
Preparation This time I will use this photo taken properly. The brightness histogram of this image is as follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Draw a knot interactively with Plotly (Python)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3bf3b9630/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3bf3b9630/</guid>
      <description>Draw a knot interactively with #Plotly (Python)  1.First of all This time, I will plot a knot in Plotly on a three-dimensional space. I hope it will help you with your learning.
You can do something like ↓.
See the Pen dyoyxKW by Sota Misawa (@mitawaut) on CodePen.  Source (GitHub)
2. Review Make a minimal review of how to draw the knot.
Knot (knot) is $S^1$ embedded piecewise linearly in $S^3$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] From the party that protects the people from NHK Is the party that protects NHK from the party that protects NHK from the people a party that protects NHK from the people?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/bf94453cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/bf94453cb/</guid>
      <description># What are you saying  Please read this article first (https://qiita.com/MirrgieRiana/items/da7dade622770a04d8f7).
In this article, I will implement the &amp;ldquo;algorithm for determining whether the world is inconsistent when given a political party name&amp;rdquo; in Python, which was asked in the original article.
Formulate mathematically If NHK is 0 and the people are 1, the “party protecting the people from NHK” can be expressed as the “party protecting 0 to 1”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Pauli matrices and dual quaternions in Clifford algebra</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fafe77f9a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fafe77f9a/</guid>
      <description>The length with the direction can be expressed by a vector. Clifford algebra makes it possible to handle areas and volumes by combining vectors. We introduce a Pauli matrix as a three-dimensional Clifford algebra representation matrix and confirm that it is isomorphic to a biquaternion. The calculation by SymPy is attached.  This is a series article.
 Complex vector considered with real vector Bi-complex numbers considered by expression matrix Quaternion considered by expression matrix Pauli matrices and dual quaternions considered in Clifford algebra ← this article  This article has related articles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>