<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/twitter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Twitter on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete tweets for specified period</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/delete-tweets-for-specified-period-fe277/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/delete-tweets-for-specified-period-fe277/</guid>
      <description>## I want to say that there was no black history  There are already various tools in the world, According to the specifications of Twitter, only the latest 3200 can be deleted, There is a charge for mass deletion. Very troubled.
There are over 100,000 tweets like garbage that have accumulated since 2010.
There is also a source that erases all tweets in Qiita if you search for it. But everything is in trouble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Twitter Data | Trend Analysis編</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/analyzing-twitter-data-trend-analysis%E7%B7%A8-fee64/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/analyzing-twitter-data-trend-analysis%E7%B7%A8-fee64/</guid>
      <description>This article is a trend analysis of Twitter Data analysis. I will deepen this series later. Since this is my first article, I will explain this case in detail after briefly analyzing Twitter Data. Because Japanese is tight, I will change it to English. [Git Repository](https://github.com/Bing-Violet/Real-Time-insights-from-social-media/blob/master/notebook.ipynb)   ###Why Analyze Twitter Data? Twitter data analysis is used in a wide range of areas including but not restricted to analyzing the mentions of each political party in an election, detecting the reactions to the introduction of a new product, understanding the geographical scope of discussion of a news story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Search Tweets: Full Archive / Sandbox in Python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/using-search-tweets-full-archive-sandbox-in-python-f7f31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/using-search-tweets-full-archive-sandbox-in-python-f7f31/</guid>
      <description>I started Python for my thesis in [previous article](https://qiita.com/johnsakagami/items/7202368fe11e570e060e) and tried various things with Twitter API.  Python is no more than 10 days old. Well, my skill hasn&amp;rsquo;t improved so much&amp;hellip;
Premise of this time: Are all the searches on the Twitter official website displayed? After all, the data collection of graduation thesis was a search on the Twitter official website that has full access to past tweets. Primitive. By the way, I was taking the number of data in that way, but the number of search results with that keyword decreases ** unexpectedly ** as I go back in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>