<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/twitter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Twitter on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Humans are not so sad creatures</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/humans-are-not-so-sad-creatures-17761/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/humans-are-not-so-sad-creatures-17761/</guid>
      <description>With the birth of the Internet, the world has changed dramatically. Now with just one smartphone, you can instantly do various things such as research, shopping, communication, entertainment consumption, and information dissemination.  As efficiency went on, people&amp;rsquo;s tasks continued to diminish, and even ** began to disappear. **The everyday life is spreading, in which people act like the information recommended by AI and like the posts that everyone likes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a TwitterBot with Python!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-twitterbot-with-python-dc502/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-twitterbot-with-python-dc502/</guid>
      <description>## What is TwitterBot?  Bot is the etymology of Robot, and refers to something that automatically does something. On Twitter
 Auto Tweet Bot Auto Like Bot Auto follow bot  There are various bots.
What are the benefits of Bot? Automatic Tweets act like notifications. For example, &amp;ldquo;we tweet automatically when the live information of your favorite artist is updated&amp;rdquo;. Auto Like and Auto Follow serve as a tool to let an unspecified number of people know your account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The back side of the ring-fit adventure stock bot that eradicates resale yard</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-back-side-of-the-ring-fit-adventure-stock-bot-that-eradicates-resale-yard-6024a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-back-side-of-the-ring-fit-adventure-stock-bot-that-eradicates-resale-yard-6024a/</guid>
      <description>#2020/01/11  Ringfit Adventure Arrival bot has been renewed because it has frozen. Thank you for your continued support for Listed Dolphin @ Ringfit Adventure.
Overview Get notified when Ringfit Adventures arrives at a list price on Amazon Ringfit adventure arrival bot I made. I will introduce the back side of this bot. Eradicate the resale yard.
#Background
Ringfit Adventure is very popular. The product has been in short supply since its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginners of GoogleMaps API and Twitter API made tweet map</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/beginners-of-googlemaps-api-and-twitter-api-made-tweet-map-c4b65/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/beginners-of-googlemaps-api-and-twitter-api-made-tweet-map-c4b65/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  If I knew when and where I tweeted, I thought it would be fun to look like a life log, so I made a tweet map.
It is the first time to touch GoogleMaps API and TwtterAPI. Thanks to various sites. .. .. ..
![Screenshot 2019-11-25 14.14.55.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/445408/d4ca8dcd-e24a-ca6e-b09c-(df19ed888805.png) ⬆️ This is when riding a bicycle on the Shimanami Kaido (It&amp;rsquo;s fun to know where you were and what you were doing!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>