<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> morphological analysis on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/morphological-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  morphological analysis on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/morphological-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[The strongest English word book bomb ww] Automatically generate the English word book required by engineers in Python-Part 1</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-strongest-english-word-book-bomb-ww-automatically-generate-the-english-word-book-required-by-engineers-in-python-part-1-5bf18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-strongest-english-word-book-bomb-ww-automatically-generate-the-english-word-book-required-by-engineers-in-python-part-1-5bf18/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I think that everyone has bought once If you automatically create an English word book in Python,
 You don&#39;t need to buy an English word book anymore?  I will verify the hypothesis.   **If LGTM exceeds 10,** We will make more practical ones in the second part (or the second part), so please LGTM if you find it interesting~! About the author Biography After graduating from the Department of Electrical and Information Engineering at the age of 20, at a technical trading company, translating specifications etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morphological analysis tool installation (MeCab,Juman&#43;&#43;,Janome,GiNZA)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/morphological-analysis-tool-installation-mecabjuman-janomeginza-fdd58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/morphological-analysis-tool-installation-mecabjuman-janomeginza-fdd58/</guid>
      <description>A morphological analysis tool is indispensable for Japanese text processing, but it was troublesome to check the installation method of the tool each time, so the following 4 installations are summarized.   MeCab Juman++ Janome GiNZA  Installation environment: Ubuntu 18.04
MeCab Quoted from official site
 MeCab is an open source morphological analysis engine developed through the Joint Research Unit Project of Kyoto University Graduate School of Informatics-Nippon Telegraph and Telephone Corporation, Communication Science Laboratories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to visualize the night of the Galactic Railway with WordCloud!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-to-visualize-the-night-of-the-galactic-railway-with-wordcloud-07baa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-to-visualize-the-night-of-the-galactic-railway-with-wordcloud-07baa/</guid>
      <description># at first   I created it because I wanted to make WordCloud. Code may be wrong (sorry)  #Environment
 Python 3.7.3 Jupyter Notebook Windows  #Flow 1. Extracting text with scraping 2. Divide words using MeCab 3. WordCloud creation
#1.Scraping Here has &amp;ldquo;Galaxy Railway Night&amp;rdquo; on the site, so extract only the text from here.
 &amp;lt;div class = &amp;#34;main-text&amp;#34;&amp;gt; As you can see, if you extract the text of the lower level of this&amp;rsquo;div&amp;rsquo;, it will be ok!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>