<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Git on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/git/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Git on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/git/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Created a tool that visualizes mechanically from repository history in order to objectively know the productivity and soundness of the development team</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/created-a-tool-that-visualizes-mechanically-from-repository-history-in-order-to-objectively-know-the-productivity-and-soundness-of-the-development-team-ceece/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/created-a-tool-that-visualizes-mechanically-from-repository-history-in-order-to-objectively-know-the-productivity-and-soundness-of-the-development-team-ceece/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The productivity and soundness of a software development team can be understood as an internal sensation, but it is difficult for an external person to see it. This information asymmetry has caused problems in relationships with people outside the development team.
Also, for EMs, CTOs that bundle multiple development teams and products, and visualizing each situation with objective numbers and graphs, it is important reference information when considering the overall strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python development flow using Poetry, Git and Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-development-flow-using-poetry-git-and-docker-43efd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-development-flow-using-poetry-git-and-docker-43efd/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is a sister article of Python development flow using pipenv, Git and Docker I wrote earlier. Now that the development of Pipenv is not very active, I think that there will be occasions when Poetry is used in projects using Python. So I&amp;rsquo;ll try to summarize the development flow using Poetry again.
Overall flow  Installation of development environment Project initialization Docker  #Prerequisite environment
 Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Hypothesis/Verification (170) 11 essential skills that developers in 2020 should know → Answers → Sort → Sort items (8 items) → Add content</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hypothesis-verification-170-11-essential-skills-that-developers-in-2020-should-know-answers-sort-sort-items-8-items-add-content-39e1c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hypothesis-verification-170-11-essential-skills-that-developers-in-2020-should-know-answers-sort-sort-items-8-items-add-content-39e1c/</guid>
      <description>11 essential skills developers should know for 2020  https://qiita.com/rana_kualu/items/c79a16ff503c86b27483
11 Essential Skills Software Developers should Learn in 2020 https://dev.to/javinpaul/11-essential-skills-software-developers-should-learn-in-2020-1bio
 Top 11 Essentials Skills for Software Developers in 2020
  Containers (Docker and Kubernetes) Cloud Platform (AWS, GCP, or Azure) Data Structure and Algorithm A Version Control Tool (Git) One Text Editors (VIM) IDEs (VSCode or IntelliJIDEA) Database and SQL UNIX (Linux) An OOP Programming language (C++, Java or Python) Networking basics One Scripting language  Answer Self-assess 11 skills.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>