<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> bioinformatics on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/bioinformatics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  bioinformatics on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/bioinformatics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] ChIP-seq analysis starting from scratch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/chip-seq-analysis-starting-from-scratch-41927/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/chip-seq-analysis-starting-from-scratch-41927/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  ChIP-seq (chromatin immunoprecipitation followed by sequencing) is a method to comprehensively measure at which position on the genome the binding and histone modification of a specific transcription factor and how often it occurs. You will be able to start from the environment construction, analyze using the data of the paper, and finally see the results in the genome browser and make peak calls ~. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the environment construction immediately!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try using PHATE, a dimension reduction and visualization method for biological data</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-using-phate-a-dimension-reduction-and-visualization-method-for-biological-data-b4b95/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-using-phate-a-dimension-reduction-and-visualization-method-for-biological-data-b4b95/</guid>
      <description># Try using PHATE, a dimension reduction and visualization method for biological data  PHATE (Moon, KR, van Dijk, D., Wang, Z. et al. Nature Biotechnology 37, 1482–1492 (2019)) Try to use. There are a lot of methods of dimension reduction used in biology papers, but each method has advantages and disadvantages. The following methods are often used as typical ones.
 PCA: principal component analysis. Take out the axis of maximum dispersion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>