<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Machine Learning on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Machine Learning on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Machine learning] Understanding the decorrelation from mathematics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-understanding-the-decorrelation-from-mathematics-37c03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-understanding-the-decorrelation-from-mathematics-37c03/</guid>
      <description>#1.Introduction  ##(1. Purpose If you want to do machine learning, anyone can use scikit-learn etc. to implement it relatively easily. However, in order to achieve results at work or to improve your level, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand the background, but I got this result&amp;rdquo; I think it&amp;rsquo;s clearly weak.
This time, we will focus on &amp;ldquo;correlation&amp;rdquo;**.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about decorrelation, why do you do it?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;How do you use it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python beginner publishes web application using machine learning [Part 1] Introduction</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-beginner-publishes-web-application-using-machine-learning-part-1-introduction-52dc4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-beginner-publishes-web-application-using-machine-learning-part-1-introduction-52dc4/</guid>
      <description>### Purpose of this article  Obstetrician and Gynecologist Tomi&amp;lsquo;sarticle[[[Self-studypossible]LearningroadmapformachinelearningforPythonbeginners]](https://obgynai.Itriedtocreatetheroadmapmyselfbyreferringto(com/self-study-python-machine-learning/).
This article is the first in a series of memo articles. For readability, the article is divided into pieces! (After writing, we will publish an article that summarizes everything)
###Self-introduction My name is Tsuba Mukku. After graduating from Kyushu University, I re-entered the National University School of Medicine. While aiming to graduate from medical school and pass the national exam of doctors, I am also learning pure mathematics and computer science (I also take classes in mathematics and information science).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction to Deep Learning-Coding Preparation-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-deep-learning-coding-preparation-884c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-deep-learning-coding-preparation-884c6/</guid>
      <description># Target audience  It is a continuation of Last article. This article prepares for coding from now on. If you want to implement it yourself, but it is quite &amp;hellip; please take a look. (Basically, I can&amp;rsquo;t use complicated techniques, so don&amp;rsquo;t worry.) ** The coding environment is jupyter notebook. ** If you want to manage it at the module level elsewhere, uncomment the command such as import. If it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work please let me know in the comments&amp;hellip; Next article here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Prediction of horse racing: If I thought that the collection rate exceeded 100% in machine learning (Light GBM), I did it</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/prediction-of-horse-racing-if-i-thought-that-the-collection-rate-exceeded-100-in-machine-learning-light-gbm-i-did-it-3e099/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/prediction-of-horse-racing-if-i-thought-that-the-collection-rate-exceeded-100-in-machine-learning-light-gbm-i-did-it-3e099/</guid>
      <description>#Thank you  Note!!! This article is completely disguised
I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for the person who stocked it.
Thanks to @hal27 for pointing it out, thank you.
・What I did I made a fatal mistake from the scraping stage. I was going to get the data for the previous 3 races from the time of the race, but in fact I was getting the information for the latest 3 races from the scraping execution time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A memorandum of studying and implementing deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-memorandum-of-studying-and-implementing-deep-learning-4fb85/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-memorandum-of-studying-and-implementing-deep-learning-4fb85/</guid>
      <description># Target audience  A person who has studied machine learning and deep learning in general, but who does not know how they are related when implementing. Someone who wants to organize their mind. I will not give a detailed mathematical explanation. See the chainer tutorial for a mathematical explanation.
What became a model of deep learning Deep learning was created by imitating the mechanism of information transmission in human nerve cells.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Implementation explanation] Japanese BERT x unsupervised learning (information maximization clustering) to classify livedoor news: Google Colaboratory (PyTorch)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-japanese-bert-x-unsupervised-learning-information-maximization-clustering-to-classify-livedoor-news-google-colaboratory-pytorch-6a887/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-japanese-bert-x-unsupervised-learning-information-maximization-clustering-to-classify-livedoor-news-google-colaboratory-pytorch-6a887/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will implement and explain how clustering is performed by using the Japanese version BERT in Google Colaboratory and performing unsupervised learning information maximization clustering for livedoor news.   Using the Japanese version of BERT with Google Colaboratory, the content until vectorization of sentences, Information maximization clustering for unsupervised learning in MNIST  About this, I have explained it in the series articles so far, so please see here first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simultaneous visualization of data and understanding of correlation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simultaneous-visualization-of-data-and-understanding-of-correlation-649cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simultaneous-visualization-of-data-and-understanding-of-correlation-649cf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When analyzing data, I think you will visualize the data using graphs. At that time, it would be convenient if the statistics showing the correlation between two variables could be displayed at the same time. Therefore, we made it possible to display the appropriate statistics on the appropriate graph according to the content of the variable (category or numerical value).
Review so far I will summarize the appropriate graphing methods by content of variables and the statistics that show the correlation, which have been described so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Hands-on for beginners] Kaggle&#39;s Predicting house prices is read line by line (1st part: Data reading)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hands-on-for-beginners-kaggles-predicting-house-prices-is-read-line-by-line-1st-part-data-reading-a7f5e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hands-on-for-beginners-kaggles-predicting-house-prices-is-read-line-by-line-1st-part-data-reading-a7f5e/</guid>
      <description># theme  A job that operates a real estate system as a service, a story broke out that there is no loss in doing hands-on at the field level. That&amp;rsquo;s why we decided to challenge kaggle&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;House Price&amp;rdquo; problem, which is a famous title. So, if you make a note of this properly, it will be useful for later, so I decided to post it to qiita after reading the line by line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The relationship between brain science and unsupervised learning. Information maximization with unsupervised learning MNIST: Google Colabratory (PyTorch)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-relationship-between-brain-science-and-unsupervised-learning.-information-maximization-with-unsupervised-learning-mnist-google-colabratory-pytorch-e3c01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-relationship-between-brain-science-and-unsupervised-learning.-information-maximization-with-unsupervised-learning-mnist-google-colabratory-pytorch-e3c01/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will explain unsupervised learning and brain science, and IIC&#39;s implementation of high performance in MNIST for unsupervised learning.  The papers of interest in this article are: Invariant Information Clustering for Unsupervised Image Classification and Segmentation is.
In this paper, we utilize an index called mutual information to classify handwritten digit images by unsupervised learning clustering.
It is called IIC (Invariant Information Clustering).
In this article, we will discuss brain science and unsupervised learning, IIC points, and implementation examples in MNIST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Neural network super introduction that can be understood even by cats</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-neural-network-super-introduction-that-can-be-understood-even-by-cats-489a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-neural-network-super-introduction-that-can-be-understood-even-by-cats-489a4/</guid>
      <description>![IMG_0489.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/458623/93e891ee-1dc8-fa4e-7bb5-5a1922ffe589.png)  Written  What is a neural network? a unit? weight? bias? Activation function Overview of NN Summary  The goal is to get a general idea of the neural network. I don&amp;rsquo;t use mathematical formulas, so people who are allergic to mathematics should also check it.
#1.What is a neural network?
A neural network is something like the one below. When written in English, it is Neural Network, so it is often abbreviated as NN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Causal reasoning using machine learning (arrangement of causal reasoning methods)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/causal-reasoning-using-machine-learning-arrangement-of-causal-reasoning-methods-fa213/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/causal-reasoning-using-machine-learning-arrangement-of-causal-reasoning-methods-fa213/</guid>
      <description># Causal reasoning using machine learning   A rough understanding and notes of when to use causal reasoning using machine learning methods that have been actively used in recent years (Memorandum) Basically, the current causal reasoning method is summarized as a flow chart.
 Introduction Causal reasoning is a series of statistical methods aimed at answering the cause of an outcome. Generally, statistical approaches such as regression analysis focus on quantifying how changes in X are related to changes in Y.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Summary of Markov chain and Monte Carlo method</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-markov-chain-and-monte-carlo-method-d1089/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-markov-chain-and-monte-carlo-method-d1089/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Currently, I am learning about Bayesian statistics. From that, I will summarize the Markov chain Monte Carlo method. In this article, I will explain the outline of Markov chain and Monte Carlo method as an entrance.
Next article
Here is the book that I referred to this time.
 Bayes statistics from the basics: a practical introduction to the Hamiltonian Monte Carlo method  What is Markov chain Monte Carlo In Bayesian inference, when the observed data is $X$ and the set of unobserved variables such as parameters and latent variables is $Z$, consider the probabilistic model $P(X,Z)$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Implementation explanation] How to use Japanese version BERT in Google Colaboratory (PyTorch)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-how-to-use-japanese-version-bert-in-google-colaboratory-pytorch-e522a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implementation-explanation-how-to-use-japanese-version-bert-in-google-colaboratory-pytorch-e522a/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will explain how to use the Japanese version of BERT with Google Colaboratory.  About the BERT itself, the book I wrote last year
&amp;ldquo;Learn while making! Development deep learning with PyTorch&amp;rdquo;
Is explained in detail in.
If you want to know how BERT works, please see the above book.
Since the book only dealt with the English version, this post will explain how to use BERT in the Japanese version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 5 Data Science Masterpieces You Can Learn for Free [Japanese books are not scared if you can speak English even if they are expensive]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5-data-science-masterpieces-you-can-learn-for-free-japanese-books-are-not-scared-if-you-can-speak-english-even-if-they-are-expensive-5e5a7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5-data-science-masterpieces-you-can-learn-for-free-japanese-books-are-not-scared-if-you-can-speak-english-even-if-they-are-expensive-5e5a7/</guid>
      <description>#Let&#39;s study by this time  There are many generous organizations overseas, or there are many specialized books that can be read for free.
There are other summary articles of this series, I would like to display translated Japanese books and original books side by side. Especially introduced only in the field of data science.
Maybe that expensive original book is actually free?
(As of May 2020)
#1
Japanese: Basics of statistical learning (15,000 yen) It&amp;rsquo;s commonly called a &amp;ldquo;castella book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Understand the shortest] Python basics for data analysis</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understand-the-shortest-python-basics-for-data-analysis-7d8f5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understand-the-shortest-python-basics-for-data-analysis-7d8f5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For those who want to analyze data using Python &amp;hellip; or those who have decided to use Python for seminars and research but have never done programming &amp;hellip; Once you know this, the basics are okay for now (Maybe). I think it can be used as a review of knowledge. First, we will cover the basics of general-purpose Python syntax to a minimum, and then describe the basic tools and techniques used for data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AI engineers want to be aware of Python implementation know-how / tips summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ai-engineers-want-to-be-aware-of-python-implementation-know-how-tips-summary-c0e8a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ai-engineers-want-to-be-aware-of-python-implementation-know-how-tips-summary-c0e8a/</guid>
      <description>This article summarizes the points, tips, and know-how that data scientists and AI engineers should be aware of when implementing programs in Python.   ● May 16, 2020: Added Book: Self-propelled programmer author: Mr. Shimizukawa, provided detailed explanations to this article and answers to my questions. Click this link to move to the comment. 
 We published a book in April 2020.
[Qiita] I wrote a book that teaches a good balance between machine learning implementation and algorithms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Differences that C# engineers felt when they first learned python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/differences-that-c#-engineers-felt-when-they-first-learned-python-29944/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/differences-that-c#-engineers-felt-when-they-first-learned-python-29944/</guid>
      <description>Hi, this is [Muscle Training Clinical Engineering Engineer ken](https://twitter.com/ce_fitness_note).  This is my first post on Qiita.
I usually use C# to develop medical systems. I decided to focus on machine learning, so I started learning python.
Even though I learned about it, I went around Progate&amp;rsquo;s python course, but I will briefly summarize the differences between C# and how to write.
If you usually use C#, C++, VB and want to learn python from now on, I think that learning will be better if you know the difference between the two in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Data analysis started with python (data preprocessing-machine learning)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/data-analysis-started-with-python-data-preprocessing-machine-learning-b7dc7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/data-analysis-started-with-python-data-preprocessing-machine-learning-b7dc7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For beginners, I would like to explain from data preprocessing in python to machine learning model construction. Use gradient boosting for machine learning.
Source code https://gitlab.com/ceml/qiita/-/blob/master/src/python/notebook/first_time_ml.ipynb
Content of this article table of contents  Data preprocessing 1-1. Read data 1-2. Combine data 1-3. Compensation for missing areas 1-4. Feature creation 1-5. Data division Machine learning 2-1. Dataset creation and model definition 2-2. Model training and evaluation 2-3. Check the importance of features  About dataset ・Provided by: California Institute of Technology ・Contents: Heart disease test data ・URL: https://archive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I wrote a book that teaches a well-balanced implementation of machine learning and algorithms.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-wrote-a-book-that-teaches-a-well-balanced-implementation-of-machine-learning-and-algorithms.-db5c5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-wrote-a-book-that-teaches-a-well-balanced-implementation-of-machine-learning-and-algorithms.-db5c5/</guid>
      <description>I wrote a book that uses the scikit-learn library to teach a well-balanced implementation of machine learning and algorithms.  Introduction to machine learning for people aiming to become AI engineers, learning the algorithm flow while implementing it (Dentsu International Information Service Takuya Shimizu, Yutaro Ogawa, Technical Review) https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/4297112094/
It has already been released.
Machine learning ・Implementation of various algorithms ・Mechanism of operation of each algorithm
I wrote this for those who want to learn these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Anyway, I gathered a site where you can learn basic free Pythonmachine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/anyway-i-gathered-a-site-where-you-can-learn-basic-free-pythonmachine-learning-823e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/anyway-i-gathered-a-site-where-you-can-learn-basic-free-pythonmachine-learning-823e3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I will introduce the sites that I collected by surfing the net with only the name, link and a brief description. (Add links etc. at any time) I would be happy if you could introduce the site in the comments. We do not include famous sites such as Progate and dot installation. We also introduce a blog. Please note that the contents are not explained. Let&amp;rsquo;s go.
#Codeprep Format: Exercise Price: All free Learning scope: Basic grammar, data manipulation, NumPy, Pandas, OOP It is a fill-in-the-blank format and does not require environment construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to predict Titanic survival on PyCaret</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-titanic-survival-on-pycaret-a377f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-titanic-survival-on-pycaret-a377f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The other day, I tried using the machine learning library PyCaret that was released. Data feature analysis and performance comparison work with multiple models will be automated, and the work time of data scientists up to now will be considerably reduced.
This time, I will apply PyCaret to the Titanic survival prediction problem, submit the prediction result to Kaggle, and see the result.
**This is a follow-up article to I tried to classify wine quality with PyCaret, which I posted last time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to classify the quality of wine with PyCaret</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-classify-the-quality-of-wine-with-pycaret-c8fa7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-classify-the-quality-of-wine-with-pycaret-c8fa7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The other day, I tried using the machine learning library PyCaret that was released. Data feature analysis and performance comparison work with multiple models will be automated, and the work time of data scientists up to now will be considerably reduced.
#1. Install PyCaret
Run the following code to install. I use Anaconda, but I launched and installed a virtual environment dedicated to PyCaret. An error may occur in a virtual environment managed by an existing Conda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Free version of DataRobot! ? Introduction to library PyCaret that automates machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/free-version-of-datarobot-introduction-to-library-pycaret-that-automates-machine-learning-62151/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/free-version-of-datarobot-introduction-to-library-pycaret-that-automates-machine-learning-62151/</guid>
      <description>What is #PyCaret  I recently saw an article called Announcing PyCaret 1.0.0 .. It was an interesting library, so in this article I will explain how to use PyCaret. **PyCaret is a Python library that enables data pre-processing, visualization, and model development with a few lines of code in machine learning model development. **
PyCaret is a Python wrapper for some of the major machine learning libraries (scikit-learn, XGBoost, LightGBM, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to visualize the model with the low-code machine learning library PyCaret</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-the-model-with-the-low-code-machine-learning-library-pycaret-bdd48/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-the-model-with-the-low-code-machine-learning-library-pycaret-bdd48/</guid>
      <description># Overview   PyCaret, a library for machine learning with low-code, has finally become v1.0. Visualization of machine learning model is convenient, so let&amp;rsquo;s focus on Visualization of model and summarize.  If you check Source,youcanseeYellowbrick@HP(Yellowbrick@qiita). *In addition, it is taken up by Qiita in PyCaret tags below.  I tried using PyCaret at the fastest speed Introduction to the library &amp;ldquo;PyCaret&amp;rdquo; that automates machine learning    things to do The enumeration is as follows, but it can be executed in a few lines by automation of pycaret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning model inference web API server configuration [FastAPI implementation example available]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-model-inference-web-api-server-configuration-fastapi-implementation-example-available-9803f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-model-inference-web-api-server-configuration-fastapi-implementation-example-available-9803f/</guid>
      <description>## Purpose of this article  Introducing a typical configuration of machine learning inference web API. I think that the content can be read without necessarily having knowledge of WEB or machine learning. (Excluding implementation example) The configuration to introduce is based on my experience of making inference web APIs for some machine learning models in my work, but since it is my personal opinion, if you have any suggestions, please let me know in the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] For those who want to start machine learning with TensorFlow2</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-want-to-start-machine-learning-with-tensorflow2-7d7a2/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am currently a M2 student majoring in CS. I usually write machine learning code in PyTorch. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to write for the time being. PyTorch is said to be &amp;ldquo;Define by Run&amp;rdquo;**, and what is good at the same time when the calculation graph and data are sent is that it is easy to debug because you can check the calculation results on the way. As a PyTorch believer, I need to write code in TensorFlow this time, so I will keep a memo so that I don&amp;rsquo;t forget the know-how at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried using PyCaret at the fastest speed</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-pycaret-at-the-fastest-speed-5dd40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-pycaret-at-the-fastest-speed-5dd40/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Immediately, I tried using the machine learning library PyCaret released the other day. I realized that anyone can easily model. It was really easy! You can tune and predict from preprocessing without writing 10 lines of code! Although there are many parts that I have not understood yet such as arguments, I decided to write the article of PyCaret first. If you have any notes, please comment.
0. Environment and version  PyCaret 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Stock Price Prediction by Machine Learning Numerai</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The general public may not have heard about it, but there is a hedge fund called &amp;ldquo;Numerai&amp;rdquo;. It is a hedge fund that has been known a little in the neighborhood by being covered by media such as Wired and Forbes from the latter half of 2016 to the first half of 2017. This hedge fund is a so-called crowdsourcing type fund that operates based on the forecast results of stock prices by an unspecified number of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (3) Differentiable rendering</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-the-latest-physics-based-renderer-mitsuba2-3-differentiable-rendering-5f270/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-the-latest-physics-based-renderer-mitsuba2-3-differentiable-rendering-5f270/</guid>
      <description>What is #Mitsuba2  A free physically based renderer for academics. There are new features such as differentiable rendering and polarized rendering. Other related articles I wrote are below.
-Try the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (1) Introduction -Try to touch the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (2) Move from Python -Try the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (4) Polarization rendering -Difference between BRDF and polarized BRDF (pBRDF)
The assumption is that Mitsuba2 has been installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning on a gaming PC and comparing the differences in CPU/GPU performance with Colabo [Windows machine learning environment construction procedure definitive version. TF2.0 compatible]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-on-a-gaming-pc-and-comparing-the-differences-in-cpu-gpu-performance-with-colabo-windows-machine-learning-environment-construction-procedure-definitive-version.-tf2.0-compatible-b6fa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-on-a-gaming-pc-and-comparing-the-differences-in-cpu-gpu-performance-with-colabo-windows-machine-learning-environment-construction-procedure-definitive-version.-tf2.0-compatible-b6fa2/</guid>
      <description># In a nutshell  Purchase a cheap gaming PC (Windows), Enable to switch CPU/GPU in virtual environment of Anaconda, Tensorflow-Running the GPU (v2.0) code, With 4 patterns including CPU/GPU of Colaboratory, I compared the performance. I will summarize the performance comparison results and the Windows version environment construction procedure. Article.
*I often hear that GPU is effective for machine learning
 Gaming PCs have GPUs and are cheap these days  ⇒ ** Let&amp;rsquo;s use GPU of gaming PC for machine learning!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to learn machine learning from scratch (March 2020 edition)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-machine-learning-from-scratch-march-2020-edition-b5992/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-machine-learning-from-scratch-march-2020-edition-b5992/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Data science and machine learning are fun! However, do you have the experience that you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to study? By the way, I am one of them. In this article, *** What is machine learning in the first place? Even if you are a beginner who knows the word AI but do not know the details, you will learn the learning method *** to learn from the basic foundations necessary to gain knowledge and experience and be able to tackle machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s take a free Python introductory course for machine learning online until April 27th</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-take-a-free-python-introductory-course-for-machine-learning-online-until-april-27th-93ebf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-take-a-free-python-introductory-course-for-machine-learning-online-until-april-27th-93ebf/</guid>
      <description>Yes~mo :clap:  Today, I&amp;rsquo;m going to take &amp;ldquo;Python introductory course for machine learning **&amp;rdquo; online.
This is an online course for machine learning super beginners, developed by Skill-Up AI Co., Ltd. in cooperation with the Japan Deep Learning Association.
If it is true, it costs about 50,000 yen, but for people who are discerning with the example corona 2020/4/30By 2020/4/27 If you apply, 2020/ You can read the teaching materials until 4/30!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 9 steps to become a machine learning expert in the shortest time [Completely free]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/9-steps-to-become-a-machine-learning-expert-in-the-shortest-time-completely-free-19a32/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/9-steps-to-become-a-machine-learning-expert-in-the-shortest-time-completely-free-19a32/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I don&amp;rsquo;t think you need to do Steps 1, 2 and 7 if you don&amp;rsquo;t have time.
1. Learn statistics  Acquisition of Level 2 statistical test  2. Know the principle of ML   Machine Learning -coursera
  Outline of gradient descent optimization algorithm
  3. Learn Python  Python -Google  4. Learn the basics of ML   Machine Learning Crash Course</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning algorithms (support vector machines)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-algorithms-support-vector-machines-d17cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-algorithms-support-vector-machines-d17cb/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Step-by-step about the theory, the implementation in python, and the analysis using scikit-learn of the algorithm taken up in &amp;ldquo;Classification of machine learning&amp;rdquo; Learn with. I wrote it for personal learning, so I would like you to take a look at any mistakes.
This time about Support Vector Machine. Despite its old history, it is a popular technique in the field of machine learning. It has a high generalization performance, and was the strongest algorithm until it was broken into deep learning by ILSVRC2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [2020 version for beginners] Recommended study method for those who want to become AI engineers by themselves</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2020-version-for-beginners-recommended-study-method-for-those-who-want-to-become-ai-engineers-by-themselves-e47bf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2020-version-for-beginners-recommended-study-method-for-those-who-want-to-become-ai-engineers-by-themselves-e47bf/</guid>
      <description># Service introduction (AI Academy and AI Academy Bootcamp)  This is an AI learning service for individuals operated by us.
① AI Academy Online AI programming learning service where you can learn Python, machine learning, deep learning for almost free *About 300 types of practical content can be used for 980 yen per month.
② AI Academy Bootcamp Short-term intensive AI programming boot camp for individuals (AI programming school) Python course (50,000 yen per month) Data Scientist Course (¥120,000 for 2 months) Machine learning engineer course (120,000 yen for 2 months)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is the network since VGG really improving? The story</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-the-network-since-vgg-really-improving-the-story-16022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-the-network-since-vgg-really-improving-the-story-16022/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, AI competitions don&amp;rsquo;t produce useful models just overtraining the dataset &amp;amp; outperforming the game? The purpose of this study is to investigate the story with the wide-angle fundus dataset 1. Also, as an introduction, we will explain how to fine-turn from the learned weights of ImageNet2 using the network implemented in tf.keras.
All code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [TensorFlow 2.x supported version] TensorFlow (Keras) using TFRecord &amp; DataSet to learn a large amount of data</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-2.x-supported-version-tensorflow-keras-using-tfrecord-dataset-to-learn-a-large-amount-of-data-11140/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-2.x-supported-version-tensorflow-keras-using-tfrecord-dataset-to-learn-a-large-amount-of-data-11140/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is an updated version of the previous article. How to train a large amount of data using TFRecord &amp;amp; DataSet with TensorFlow &amp;amp; Keras-Qiita
One thing I want to do is &amp;ldquo;I want an efficient way to learn huge data that does not fit in memory.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a method that allows CPU data reading and GPU calculation to be processed in parallel. Using the DataSet API, you can efficiently learn from the data saved in a specific format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Machine learning] Understanding decision trees from both scikit-learn and mathematics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-understanding-decision-trees-from-both-scikit-learn-and-mathematics-53efe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-understanding-decision-trees-from-both-scikit-learn-and-mathematics-53efe/</guid>
      <description>#1. Purpose  If you want to do machine learning, anyone can use scikit-learn etc. to implement it relatively easily. However, in order to achieve results at work or to improve your level, The explanation &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand the background but I got this result&amp;rdquo; clearly shows the weakness.
In this article, the purpose of ** is 2-3, &amp;ldquo;I will use scikit-learn first because the theory is good,&amp;rdquo; and 4 and &amp;ldquo;understand the background from mathematics&amp;rdquo; **.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Performance verification of data preprocessing for machine learning (numerical data edition) (1)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/performance-verification-of-data-preprocessing-for-machine-learning-numerical-data-edition-1-cf176/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/performance-verification-of-data-preprocessing-for-machine-learning-numerical-data-edition-1-cf176/</guid>
      <description>First Edition: March 10, 2020 &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;  Author: Soichi Takashige, Masahiro Ito, Hitachi, Ltd.
#Introduction In this post, I will introduce the design know-how of data preprocessing and the results of performance verification of data preprocessing when designing a system incorporating a machine learning model.
The second article introduces know-how for performance improvement and verification results in data preprocessing using Python.
Post list:
 Data preprocessing for systems that use machine learning Performance Verification of Data Preprocessing for Machine Learning (Numerical Data) (Part 1) (Posted) Performance Verification of Data Preprocessing for Machine Learning (Numerical Data) (Part 2)  #About the benchmark (BigBench) referenced in the performance verification Before introducing design know-how and performance verification results, we will introduce the benchmarks that were referenced as references in verification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [With Japanese model] Sentence vector model recommended for people who will process natural language in 2020</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/with-japanese-model-sentence-vector-model-recommended-for-people-who-will-process-natural-language-in-2020-1df94/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/with-japanese-model-sentence-vector-model-recommended-for-people-who-will-process-natural-language-in-2020-1df94/</guid>
      <description>## Summary   Create and publish a Japanese model of Sentence-BERT (Papers,Implementation). did. By using this Japanese model, anyone can easily create high-quality sentence vectors. Please use it. Sentence-BERT uses pre-trained BERTmodelandSiameseNetwork , Is a method of creating a highly accurate sentence vector. Cosine similarity using accuracy evaluation of English version (STSbenchmarkandrankcorrelationcoefficientofspearmanofcorrectlabel.1Inthecaseof(closerisbetter),themethodusingtheaverageofsimplewordvectors(GloVe)is0.58,andthemodelcorrespondingtothescalecreatedthistimeisaround0.85(PapersSeeTable2). The accuracy is 0.17 when using the CLS vector of the bare BERT and 0.46 when using the average of the BERT embeddings, which is worse than the result of the average of the word vector (0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried using PIFu that generates a 3D model of a person from one image</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-pifu-that-generates-a-3d-model-of-a-person-from-one-image-ecf40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-using-pifu-that-generates-a-3d-model-of-a-person-from-one-image-ecf40/</guid>
      <description>What is #PIFu  Image quote (left): Sumire Uesaka Official Blog Nekomori Meeting
PIFu: Pixel-Aligned Implicit Function for High-Resolution Clothed Human Digitization
If you explain roughly,
A machine learning model that generates a 3D model of a person with clothes from a single image
is.
 We introduce Pixel-aligned Implicit Function (PIFu), a highly effective implicit representation that locally aligns pixels of 2D images with the global context of their corresponding 3D object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] About sklearn.preprocessing.Imputer</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-sklearn.preprocessing.imputer-19c81/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-sklearn.preprocessing.imputer-19c81/</guid>
      <description>Currently (2020/03/03), all the teaching materials of N prep schools are released free of charge due to the suspension of elementary and junior high school due to the spread of COVID-19 infection. It is said that I am also working on &amp;quot;Introduction to machine learning&amp;quot;, but a little trouble occurred in &amp;quot;12. How to handle missing values&amp;quot;.  error
 ImportError: cannot import name&amp;rsquo;Imputer&amp;rsquo; from&amp;rsquo;sklearn.preprocessing&amp;rsquo;
 The version of scikit-learn that I use is 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Data preprocessing for systems using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/data-preprocessing-for-systems-using-machine-learning-48825/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/data-preprocessing-for-systems-using-machine-learning-48825/</guid>
      <description>First Edition: March 3, 2020 &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;  Author: Soichi Takashige, Masahiro Ito, Hitachi, Ltd.
#Introduction In this post, I will introduce the design know-how of data preprocessing and the performance verification results of numerical data preprocessing when designing a system incorporating a machine learning model.
The first article introduces the data preprocessing of machine learning system and its design.
Post list:
 Data preprocessing for systems that use machine learning (this post) Performance verification of data preprocessing for machine learning (numerical data) (1) Performance Verification of Data Preprocessing for Machine Learning (Numerical Data) (Part 2)  #Outline and flow of AI projects Data analysis utilizing AI technology such as machine learning is drawing attention, and the number of projects utilizing AI is increasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Image classification with wide-angle fundus image dataset</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/image-classification-with-wide-angle-fundus-image-dataset-8c011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/image-classification-with-wide-angle-fundus-image-dataset-8c011/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  In this article, as an introduction, we aim to use TensorFlow 2.0 and perform image classification with Deep Learning for the time being. The image dataset is not so interesting as MNIST, so we will use the wide-angle fundus image dataset 1 published by Tsukazaki Hospital. The network is a simple 10-layer CNN.
All Code
2. Environment  PC specs -CPU: Intel Core i9-9900K -RAM: 16GB -GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Library -Python: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Article that enables high-speed sparse matrix calculation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-article-that-enables-high-speed-sparse-matrix-calculation-e5500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-article-that-enables-high-speed-sparse-matrix-calculation-e5500/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  **A sparse matrix is a matrix in which most of the elements of the matrix are 0. It is used in a wide range of fields such as numerical calculation, machine learning, and graph theory (I think). Since most of the matrix is 0, if you devise to ignore 0, you can perform matrix calculation at high speed. For example, if you use a large-scale sparse matrix (nearly 90% is 0) (1 million rows x 1 million columns) and only use non-zero parts, the calculation time will be about 1/10 and the calculation can be completed quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Challenges for large-scale models such as BERT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/challenges-for-large-scale-models-such-as-bert-e72d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/challenges-for-large-scale-models-such-as-bert-e72d8/</guid>
      <description># Breakthrough model of natural language processing-BERT  BERT[BidirectionalEncoderRepresentationsfromTransformers]wasannouncedtoGoogle&amp;rsquo;steaminthefallof2018.Thisistheresultoflearningamodelinarevolutionarywayforaverylargenetworkwithalargeamountofdatausingatransformerarchitecture.PleaserefertoThisarticle for learning method and accuracy.
In the field of machine learning where open source and free exchange of information are important, new ideas are published as papers at arxiv.org, and models are shared on github. Doing is the basic way. As soon as new ideas are published, they can be referenced and reused by machine learning researchers and development teams around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 8 services that even beginners can learn Python (for beginners to advanced users)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8-services-that-even-beginners-can-learn-python-for-beginners-to-advanced-users-3334b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8-services-that-even-beginners-can-learn-python-for-beginners-to-advanced-users-3334b/</guid>
      <description>After checking on various existing sites,  Since the fee display etc. were old, I tried to summarize it again.
If you are an introduction to programming, you can learn from the basics progate progate This is the most recommended learning site for beginners who want to learn programming from now on. The programming terms are very polite and easy to understand, so You will be able to proceed with your learning without any setbacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to understand (engineering) UMAP, which is stronger than t-SNE</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-understand-engineering-umap-which-is-stronger-than-t-sne-06ab8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-understand-engineering-umap-which-is-stronger-than-t-sne-06ab8/</guid>
      <description>Do you know UMAP?  I know
If you&amp;rsquo;ve heard it but don&amp;rsquo;t know it, this article will help you understand it.
#What is UMAP
It is a method to reduce and visualize dimensions faster and with higher performance than t-SNE. Compare with the commonly used t-SNE. The following figure is a visualization of Fashion MNIST.
(From Understanding UMAP)
Compared to t-SNE, UMAP seems to have distinct clusters. Similar categories are placed near each other and dissimilar categories are placed far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Stock investment by deep reinforcement learning (policy gradient method) (1)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/stock-investment-by-deep-reinforcement-learning-policy-gradient-method-1-1c160/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/stock-investment-by-deep-reinforcement-learning-policy-gradient-method-1-1c160/</guid>
      <description>I am a 4th year university student studying reinforcement learning. I have already graduated.  I started researching simply thinking that I could make money with the power of AI. Probably because it is financial related, I can not find any information even if I search &amp;hellip; So, my research this year &amp;ldquo;Acquisition of investment strategy by deep reinforcement learning&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;d like to write about it and be helpful for someone somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Story that made Mel icon generator</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/story-that-made-mel-icon-generator-cad3f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/story-that-made-mel-icon-generator-cad3f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Do you know this icon? Yes, it is the icon of the famous Melville. It is known that there are many people who have Melville draw their favorite characters, etc. and use it as a thumbnail for twitter, and it has gained great support. The icon drawn by this person is often called &amp;ldquo;Mel icon&amp;rdquo; due to its unique style. Examples of typical Mel icons
  (Those of Yukatayu and Shun, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] An amateur stumbled upon Deep Learning made from scratch Memo: Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-upon-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-7-8541c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-upon-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-7-8541c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I suddenly started to study &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning from scratch-the theory and implementation of deep learning learned with Python&amp;rdquo; It is a memo of the trip.
The execution environment is macOS Mojave + Anaconda 2019.10, and the Python version is 3.7.4. For details, please refer to Chapter 1 of this memo.
(To other chapters of this memo: Chapter 1/Chapter2/Chapter3/Chapter4/Chapter5/Chapter6/Chapter7/Chapter8)/Summary))
#7 Convolutional Neural Network
This chapter describes Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I shot Kamehameha using OpenPose</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-shot-kamehameha-using-openpose-ec501/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-shot-kamehameha-using-openpose-ec501/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I wanted to shoot Kamehameha so I made it.
You can also hide the estimation line.
The coordinates of the joint are acquired using OpenPose, the angle is calculated from that, and it is judged whether the pose looks like that.
About OpenPose How to set up I used tf pose estimation which is Tensorflow version of OpenPose. My environment was Windows10, GTX1070, etc., so I referred to the following page for setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Dimension curse] Can the number of sensors be changed to ∞ to detect anomalies?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/dimension-curse-can-the-number-of-sensors-be-changed-to-to-detect-anomalies-1a800/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/dimension-curse-can-the-number-of-sensors-be-changed-to-to-detect-anomalies-1a800/</guid>
      <description>Since the IOT became popular, efforts have been made to increase the number of sensors in order to predictively maintain machinery.  Is being done.
Rumor has it that there are cases where 100 sensors are attached to one machine.
The question is, is it justified to increase the number of sensors? In other words, does **adding extra sensors not affect the anomaly detection performance? When That is it.
In this paper, we focus on the curse of dimension, “When we increase the number of extra sensors, we detect anomalies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Why Deep Metric Learning based on the Softmax function works</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/why-deep-metric-learning-based-on-the-softmax-function-works-7ed56/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/why-deep-metric-learning-based-on-the-softmax-function-works-7ed56/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In distance learning (metric learning) using deep learning, similarities (and dissimilarities) between images are used by using Contrastive Loss and Triplet Loss.) Is widely used, but it is also known that it is difficult to combine and select learning data, and learning itself is difficult in many cases. For that reason, various improvements and ideas have been proposed so far. However, recently, metric learning, which can learn based on the Softmax function as if it is a general class classification task without the difficulty of selecting learning data like this, has been attracting attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Machine learning] Understand logistic regression from both scikit-learn and mathematics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-understand-logistic-regression-from-both-scikit-learn-and-mathematics-ee2a0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-understand-logistic-regression-from-both-scikit-learn-and-mathematics-ee2a0/</guid>
      <description>#1. Purpose  If you want to do machine learning, anyone can use scikit-learn etc. to implement it relatively easily. However, in order to achieve results at work or to improve your level, The explanation &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand the background, but I got this result&amp;rdquo; is clearly weak.
In this article, the two aims are to &amp;ldquo;use the scikit-learn first because the theory is good&amp;rdquo; and to &amp;ldquo;understand the background from mathematics&amp;rdquo; from the fourth and later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] There are many books on machine learning, but which should I buy? Recommended by level! ! &lt;For beginners&gt;</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/there-are-many-books-on-machine-learning-but-which-should-i-buy-recommended-by-level-for-beginners-a2f64/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/there-are-many-books-on-machine-learning-but-which-should-i-buy-recommended-by-level-for-beginners-a2f64/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There are many books on machine learning, but I recommend you to buy one by level.
There are 5 levels from Level 1 to Level 5. Please choose a book from the level that suits you. It will be best if you read the books introduced here in 3 to 4 months. I don&amp;rsquo;t cover studying methods in this note, but there are some very good online courses, such as Cousera&amp;rsquo;s machine learning courses, so please try using services other than books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deep Learning Association G test study method (for beginners) [2020 edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-association-g-test-study-method-for-beginners-2020-edition-001ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-association-g-test-study-method-for-beginners-2020-edition-001ed/</guid>
      <description># In this article, we will explain to beginners how to study for the Deep Learning Association G test (an example)  (Last update: February 3, 2020)
Click here for more information on the G test. What is the Deep Learning Association G Test?
*This document&amp;rsquo;s calligraphy is used with the permission of the publisher (or the image in the common database of the publishing industry from the publisher Dotcom).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 40-year-old engineer manager passed Deep Learning for ENGINEER</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/40-year-old-engineer-manager-passed-deep-learning-for-engineer-c58b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/40-year-old-engineer-manager-passed-deep-learning-for-engineer-c58b3/</guid>
      <description>## What is Deep Learning for ENGINEER  Please note that this article is current as of January 2020. Currently, the following official qualifications are available to prove AI skills in Japan.
 JDLA Deep Learning for GENERAL (G test) JDLA Deep Learning for ENGINEER (E qualification)  is.
Positioned as a test, the G test asks general education about AI-related technology. E-qualification is an exam that understands the theory of AI-related technology and asks the skills to implement AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] An amateur stumbled on Deep Learning made from scratch Memo: Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-on-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-5-8707e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/an-amateur-stumbled-on-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-5-8707e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I suddenly started studying [Deep Learning from scratch&amp;ndash;the theory and implementation of deep learning learned with Python] It is a memo of the trip.
The execution environment is macOS Mojave + Anaconda 2019.10, and the Python version is 3.7.4. For details, please refer to Chapter 1 of this memo.
(To other chapters of this memo: Chapter 1/Chapter2/Chapter3/Chapter4/Chapter5/Chapter6/Chapter7/Chapter8)/Summary))
#5 Error Back Propagation
This chapter describes the backpropagation method for speeding up the calculation of weight parameters in learning neural networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [PyTorch] How to use BERT-fine tuning Japanese pre-trained models to solve classification problem</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pytorch-how-to-use-bert-fine-tuning-japanese-pre-trained-models-to-solve-classification-problem-7f3a5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pytorch-how-to-use-bert-fine-tuning-japanese-pre-trained-models-to-solve-classification-problem-7f3a5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Although BERT is updating SOTA with various tasks of natural language processing, what is published by [Google] on Github is based on Tensorflow. It has been implemented. People who use PyTorch want to use the PyTorch version, but I have not created the PyTorch version, so please use the one made by HuggingFace,butwedevelopedAskthemformoreinformationastheyarenotinvolvedin!AndQA.
Although it is a BERT made by Hugging Face, there was no Japanese pre-trained model until December 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] By clarifying the difference between statistics and machine learning, I can see why many business companies cannot use machine learning!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</guid>
      <description>#What is the difference between statistics and machine learning? Why can&#39;t I predict from machine learning today and make money?  Perhaps everyone wonders when they start studying machine learning. And why can&amp;rsquo;t many business companies use it for their daily work today? The question also comes up. There are various documents, but I was having trouble comprehending them, so I rearranged them myself. I&amp;rsquo;m putting together a lot of information by combining information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] World Champion Mr. Satan Makeover App Made</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-world-champion-mr.-satan-makeover-app-made-216aa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-world-champion-mr.-satan-makeover-app-made-216aa/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Everyone&amp;rsquo;s yearning, world champion &amp;ldquo;Mr. Satan&amp;rdquo;. I made an application that can transform into &amp;ldquo;Mr. Satan&amp;rdquo;. Wearing the characteristic eyebrows, beard, and afro hair, you are now &amp;ldquo;Mr. Satan&amp;rdquo;!
Miscellaneous (w)! Technically, the face_recognition library is used to acquire the coordinates of various parts of the face, and the positions and sizes of the eyebrows, whiskers, and afro are calculated and drawn based on them.
What is #face_recognition</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Predict the existence of affair with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/predict-the-existence-of-affair-with-machine-learning-5182e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/predict-the-existence-of-affair-with-machine-learning-5182e/</guid>
      <description>Introduction   I used Udemy [50,000 people in the world] practice Python data science to analyze data using python. .. The data used this time is sample data contained in a library called Statsmodels, which will be the paper of a survey conducted in 1974 regarding the presence or absence of affair with married women.
Affairs dataset
The purpose of this time is Using the sample data, we will create a model that predicts the existence of affair by machine learning and predict which attribute influences the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Books on data science to read in 2020</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Przemek Chojecki](https://towardsdatascience.com/@pchojecki),[[DataScienceBooksyoushouldreadin2020](https://towardsdatascience.com/data-science-books-you-should-read-in-2020-358f70e1d9b2)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
Data science is arguably one of the hottest markets right now. Almost all companies are looking for or considering a data science role.
So it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to become a data scientist. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re already a data scientist and want to promote to a senior position, it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to hone your skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning completely understood by junior high school students [Updated daily]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-completely-understood-by-junior-high-school-students-updated-daily-0e91f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-completely-understood-by-junior-high-school-students-updated-daily-0e91f/</guid>
      <description>## 0 Foreword  My name is jp_Pythonia and I am in the 1st year of middle school. Nice to meet you. Since this article is a buzz and there is a lot of information, I have made it a divided version.
Part 1 Part 2
1 What is machine learning? What is machine learning? Tom Mitchell defines:
 Based on a performance criterion P for a task T, a computer program</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried HR Tech to develop an expert search engine by machine learning the in-house meeting information</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-hr-tech-to-develop-an-expert-search-engine-by-machine-learning-the-in-house-meeting-information-973c0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-hr-tech-to-develop-an-expert-search-engine-by-machine-learning-the-in-house-meeting-information-973c0/</guid>
      <description>## TL; DR  We will create an expert search engine by utilizing the dark data that sleeps inside the company and the data related to meetings. This guy This will help you find the in-house expert and the contact path to that expert.
1. Background. .. .. 1.1 What is work style reform? It is often said that Jitahara has work style reform.
 Jitahara: Forcing employees to leave the company, such as “Do not work overtime” and “Return on time” without specific measures to reduce overtime hours</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning Graph Convolutional Networks with PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/learning-graph-convolutional-networks-with-pytorch-42913/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/learning-graph-convolutional-networks-with-pytorch-42913/</guid>
      <description>** [Twitter](https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)introducesartificialintelligenceandarticleswritteninothermedia**,soifyouwanttoknowmoreaboutartificialintelligence,**Pleasefeelfreetofollowus(https://twitter.com/omiita_atiimo)! **  Learning with PyTorch Graph Convolutional Networks In this article, I will explain GCN, which has been attracting a lot of attention as a neural network that can vectorize (embed) graph structures in recent years, and PyTorch Geometric, a library that can easily use GCN. The fields of application range from biology to traffic jam prediction and recommender systems. This article is GCN creator&amp;rsquo;s blog articleand[PyTorchGeometricofficialtutorial](https://pytorch-geometric.readthedocs.io/en(/latest/index.html) is used as a reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to use machine learning for work? 03_Python coding procedure</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-machine-learning-for-work-03_python-coding-procedure-7f444/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-machine-learning-for-work-03_python-coding-procedure-7f444/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  So far, I&amp;rsquo;ve delivered an article with the theme &amp;ldquo;How to use machine learning for work?&amp;rdquo; In this third installment, we will introduce concrete programming under the theme of &amp;ldquo;Python coding procedure&amp;rdquo;.
If you also read the back number, you can understand the whole from machine learning basics to Python coding, so please use it.
 Part 1: Understanding the purpose of machine learning Part 2: Overview of AI development project  Since various information is also sent on SNS, please feel free to read the article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction to Style GAN] I played with A man&#39;s life ♬</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-style-gan-i-played-with-a-mans-life-5c936/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-style-gan-i-played-with-a-mans-life-5c936/</guid>
      <description>To be clear, just by using Example, the frequently played video (conversion from male to female) can be reproduced immediately, and it is really amazing when you try it.  This time, this is an introduction article by trying only the first entrance. The reference is as follows. 【reference】 ① I tried using StyleGAN ② Try to mix Yukichi Fukuzawa with StyleGan ③ Puzer/stylegan-encoder ④ NVlabs/stylegan Currently, styleGAN2 seems to be out, but first of all, I would like to try the first step of StyleGAN and have a real feeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Can AI distinguish Carlos Ghosn and Mr. Bean (Face recognition using face landmark)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/can-ai-distinguish-carlos-ghosn-and-mr.-bean-face-recognition-using-face-landmark-d1b29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/can-ai-distinguish-carlos-ghosn-and-mr.-bean-face-recognition-using-face-landmark-d1b29/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The news is about the news that Carlos Ghosn, the former chairman of Nissan Motor Co., Ltd., broke bail conditions and traveled to Lebanon. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking for a long time, but it&amp;rsquo;s similar to Mr. Bean&amp;hellip; Left: [Carlos Ghosn](https://www.google.com/search?q=Carlos+Ghosn&amp;amp;sxsrf=ACYBGNS1gsNQxqfqi7GRWUUeSSZ6CRix8w:1577813710879&amp;amp;source=lnms&amp;amp;tbm=isch&amp;amp;Ah&amp;amp;EqjQAQBQ&amp;amp;QAQBQBQ&amp;amp;QAQBQ&amp;amp;QB Right: [Mr. Bean (Rowan Atkinson)](https://www.google.com/search?q=rowan+atkinson&amp;amp;biw=1386&amp;amp;bih=710&amp;amp;sxsrf=ACYBGNTsdddnLF7jgPr9RTePeEMGgREpyA:1577813660092&amp;amp;source=lnms&amp;amp;tbm=isch&amp;amp;saQ&amp;amp;isch&amp;amp;saq
It was a year-end and New Year holiday, so I made a little classifier using a neural network. If you google it, a lot of images of the two people will appear, so it was good for CNN, but This time, as another approach, I would like to perform classification based on the position of landmarks on the face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle Kernel Method Summary [Table Time Series Data]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggle-kernel-method-summary-table-time-series-data-4c0f3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggle-kernel-method-summary-table-time-series-data-4c0f3/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I will write something like a standard for each data type in the Kaggle competition. In addition, I think it would be nice if it could be a hint when accuracy is not obtained regardless of the competition.  This time we will touch on the following competition datasets. In the case of competition, there is no Kernel, so I&amp;rsquo;ll try to put together Notebooks. Predict Future Sales Avocado Prices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle&#39;s Kernel Method Summary [Image Edition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggles-kernel-method-summary-image-edition-11bd7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggles-kernel-method-summary-image-edition-11bd7/</guid>
      <description>Click here for the previous article  Kaggle Kernel Summary [Table Time Series Data]
In this article, including myself, I would like to know something like a standard for each data type in the Kaggle competition! I will write for people like. In addition, I think it would be nice if it could be a hint when accuracy is not obtained regardless of the competition.
This time we will look at various kernels, not just the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Half a year when the Gori Gori literary school almost learned AI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</guid>
      <description># Half-year when the Gori Gori literary system (deviation value 40 first half) learned AI  Hi, it&amp;rsquo;s a rugged ~~ macho~~ humanities. After graduating from commercial high school, I went to the Faculty of Humanities, so it&amp;rsquo;s different from other humanities. It is a thoroughbred world of humanities.
Although it is a vital math skill, I only studied math A up to high school, and just started math at university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning with Pokemon</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-with-pokemon-08a1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-with-pokemon-08a1b/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  The Pokemon Sword Shield was launched last month. By the way, have you ever played Pokemon? As anyone who has played Pokemon will know, Pokemon has the ability value which consists of HP, Kogeki, Bogyo, Tokukou, Tokubo, and Quickness. It can be said that the higher the ability value is, the stronger the Pokemon is. Ability score is calculated from three values: race value, individual value and effort value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Full disclosure of methods used in machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/full-disclosure-of-methods-used-in-machine-learning-61b62/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/full-disclosure-of-methods-used-in-machine-learning-61b62/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  There are increasing opportunities for anyone to learn machine learning, such as kaggle and learning sites. On the other hand, I feel that there are many people who have too much information and don&amp;rsquo;t get the overall feeling.
Therefore, I will publish the methods used in machine learning introduced in various reference books and articles. Please refer to that link for detailed coding.
Since various information is also sent on SNS, please feel free to read the article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to use machine learning for work? 02_AI development project overview</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-machine-learning-for-work-02_ai-development-project-overview-4bbb0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-machine-learning-for-work-02_ai-development-project-overview-4bbb0/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I am writing a series on the theme &amp;ldquo;To use machine learning for work&amp;rdquo;. In this second article, I will organize how AI development projects proceed.
The chapters are as follows.
 What is the difference between AI development and machine learning? Overview of AI development Where to use machine learning in AI development? Steps to build the model  What is machine learning? If you feel that your understanding of is suspicious, you should read &amp;ldquo;Part 1: Understanding the Purpose of Machine Learning&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to summarize the basic form of GPLVM</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-basic-form-of-gplvm-32803/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-basic-form-of-gplvm-32803/</guid>
      <description>This article is from [Furukawa Lab, Advent_calendar Day 23](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/flab).  #Introduction
GPLVM is an unsupervised learning method that uses Gaussian process (GP) and can estimate low-dimensional manifolds whose data are distributed in high-dimensional space. The main attraction of GPLVM is that the model is very simple and highly expandable, and theoretically easy to handle. In fact, it has been extended to more complex situations such as Bayesian estimation of hyperparameters, time series data analysis 1, multiview analysis 2, and tensor decomposition 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] For those who look at the log while learning with machine learning ~ Muscle training with LightGBM ~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</guid>
      <description>What do you guys do when learning models with machine learning?  Did you just look at the log output to the console? &amp;ldquo;Oh, it was lower than I expected!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oh, the accuracy is getting worse, do your best!!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly fun to think, though.
But when I cheered up, the model doesn&amp;rsquo;t do its best, and there is no dramatic development, so it&amp;rsquo;s a waste of time to look at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to use machine learning for work? 01_Understand the purpose of machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-machine-learning-for-work-01_understand-the-purpose-of-machine-learning-a708e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-machine-learning-for-work-01_understand-the-purpose-of-machine-learning-a708e/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone.  I started Qiita from today.
As a machine learning engineer, I am usually involved in AI development and web application development.
In private, I became a newbie daddy. I am writing an article while holding my eldest son who will be 4 months (laugh)
As a motivation to write an article, I have been working on machine learning since 2017 when there was no reference book yet, I always feel that the experience of having a hard time learning machine learning is useful for someone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try using PHATE, a dimension reduction and visualization method for biological data</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-using-phate-a-dimension-reduction-and-visualization-method-for-biological-data-b4b95/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-using-phate-a-dimension-reduction-and-visualization-method-for-biological-data-b4b95/</guid>
      <description># Try using PHATE, a dimension reduction and visualization method for biological data  PHATE (Moon, KR, van Dijk, D., Wang, Z. et al. Nature Biotechnology 37, 1482–1492 (2019)) Try to use. There are a lot of methods of dimension reduction used in biology papers, but each method has advantages and disadvantages. The following methods are often used as typical ones.
 PCA: principal component analysis. Take out the axis of maximum dispersion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The guy who predicts the number of views from the title of Jarjar&#39;s video</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-guy-who-predicts-the-number-of-views-from-the-title-of-jarjars-video-06f6f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-guy-who-predicts-the-number-of-views-from-the-title-of-jarjars-video-06f6f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This time, I will talk about making a model that predicts the number of views from the title of Jarjar&amp;rsquo;s video. Since NLP is a complete amateur, I tried to imitate the appearance by referring to the articles of other people.
What is jar jar JALJAL is a comedy group with the most momentum*, consisting of Junpei Goto and Shusuke Fukutoku, who belong to the Yoshimoto Kogyo Tokyo headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Case where hand recognition has reached a practical level</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/case-where-hand-recognition-has-reached-a-practical-level-3e43b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/case-where-hand-recognition-has-reached-a-practical-level-3e43b/</guid>
      <description>In HandTracking of MediaPipe (Google), I will write about the gesture implementation that is being talked about in Issue.  It worked like this Seeing is believing that the picture is worth a thousand words. MediaPipe With the announcement of MediaPipe at CVPR 2019 in June this year, Hand Tracking has been released as one of the applications. MediaPipe doesn&amp;rsquo;t require you to write code called ML pipeline A framework for building ML applications using only visualization tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For beginners] Build a Python environment that you can enjoy by copying and copying, scraping, machine learning, and practical application [Look for affordable rental properties with SUUMO! ]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-build-a-python-environment-that-you-can-enjoy-by-copying-and-copying-scraping-machine-learning-and-practical-application-look-for-affordable-rental-properties-with-suumo-8ea9b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-beginners-build-a-python-environment-that-you-can-enjoy-by-copying-and-copying-scraping-machine-learning-and-practical-application-look-for-affordable-rental-properties-with-suumo-8ea9b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Everyone, do you like data analysis __?
Nice to meet you! I&amp;rsquo;m @haraso_1130 who is the mentor at DMM WEB CAMP
Suddenly, look at the image below.
What a property in 23 wards of Tokyo is 5DK 80,000 yen! ? If you are in the 23 wards, you can comfortably do 80,000 a room a month &amp;hellip;
This property is Using &amp;ldquo;Python&amp;rdquo; Collecting data by &amp;ldquo;scraping&amp;rdquo; Results of data analysis using &amp;ldquo;machine learning&amp;rdquo; It is a property that we were able to discover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Uncle SE whose brain was hardened studied machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/uncle-se-whose-brain-was-hardened-studied-machine-learning-13eea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/uncle-se-whose-brain-was-hardened-studied-machine-learning-13eea/</guid>
      <description>## [Introduction]  This article will be on the 19th day of How I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ② Advent Calendar 2019.
Here is how my uncle SE studied machine learning. The motivation was to start with the question, &amp;ldquo;Can you use machine learning?&amp;rdquo; Since I was working in the dark clouds, my honest memory is vague.
career I have been programming for nearly 30 years. Starting with MS BASIC I learned when I was in elementary school, I have touched Z80 assembler, MC68000 assembler, FORTRAN, C (UNIX), C++ (Mac), VB, Java (Android), VB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Ver 4 to make sandwich man&#39;s control by machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ver-4-to-make-sandwich-mans-control-by-machine-learning-2a164/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ver-4-to-make-sandwich-mans-control-by-machine-learning-2a164/</guid>
      <description>The fourth volume to make a sandwich man&#39;s control with deep learning! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! !  I&amp;rsquo;m in charge of Natural Language Processing Advent Calendar 2019 (I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for delaying one day!!!) https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/nlp
I want to automatically make a control like Sandwich Man, and I want to sell it to a comedy office for 4000 trillion yen. And I want to see Sandwich Man!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I made a muscle training estimation application using Qore SDK</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-muscle-training-estimation-application-using-qore-sdk-d6519/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-muscle-training-estimation-application-using-qore-sdk-d6519/</guid>
      <description>## tl;dr   I made a muscle training estimation app Qore uses an algorithm called reservoir computing Performed a task of classifying time series data from acceleration data that can be acquired with a smartphone -Code Pretty good -99.6% accuracy with test data This should make you a muscle engineer  Strategy  Collect accelerometer data with a smartphone (iphone) Time series data with three components on the x, y and z axes is available Learn with 4 types of muscle training: push-ups, abs, squats, abs You can tell what kind of muscle training you did with only your smartphone  Data collection   Do your muscle workout with your smartphone in your pants pocket -This time, in any muscle training, put the smartphone in the pocket in the same direction -It seems that it will be more difficult to estimate if it is set in a different direction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Recommended learning order for beginners of machine learning and deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/recommended-learning-order-for-beginners-of-machine-learning-and-deep-learning-25b08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/recommended-learning-order-for-beginners-of-machine-learning-and-deep-learning-25b08/</guid>
      <description># Target of this article  Purpose of writing the article The words AI and deep learning have been around for a long time, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think there are many people who really understand their meaning. I think it&amp;rsquo;s very dangerous to have a debate about what AI can do, as in Japan today.
I think the reason why there is such a debate about AI in this way is that you do not fully understand the mathematical basis of machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried Metaflow, an ML workflow tool developed by Netflix [Overview]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-metaflow-an-ml-workflow-tool-developed-by-netflix-overview-925c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-metaflow-an-ml-workflow-tool-developed-by-netflix-overview-925c8/</guid>
      <description>Netflix has released [Metaflow](https://metaflow.org), a Python library for managing machine learning workflows.  With this,
 Data processing/model building process can be described in a uniform format, making it easy to follow the overall flow Version control of model and pretreatment process is possible Distributed processing is possible on AWS environment  There are advantages such as.
If you are curious, let&amp;rsquo;s go through the official documentationwhilerunningthetutorial. .. For Tutorial, after inserting the library with pip install metaflow,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Performance study of latest ensemble learning Sklearn Stacking (Compare LBGM, RGF, ET, RF, LR, KNN models with Heamy and Sklearn)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/performance-study-of-latest-ensemble-learning-sklearn-stacking-compare-lbgm-rgf-et-rf-lr-knn-models-with-heamy-and-sklearn-61b3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/performance-study-of-latest-ensemble-learning-sklearn-stacking-compare-lbgm-rgf-et-rf-lr-knn-models-with-heamy-and-sklearn-61b3b/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  Stacking sklearn, it might be a standard because it was a very good child when I tried using it
| library | layer1 | layer2 | public score | speed | | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; | &amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | | lgbm model | lgb |-| 0.74162 |-| heamy single stacking | lbg, rgf, et, rf, lr, knn | lr | 0.76076 | 64s | heamy multiple stacking | lgb, rgf, et, rf, lr, knn | lgb, lr | 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The first Kaggle (kaggle ①)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-first-kaggle-kaggle-0290b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-first-kaggle-kaggle-0290b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This is the story of participating in the Kaggle competition for the first time. First try it out in a &amp;ldquo;Titanic&amp;rdquo; competition.
#table of contents
 What is Kaggle Register for Kaggle Participate in the Titatic competition Write the code Submit the learning results Summary reference  #1.What is Kaggle
It is read as kaguru. Kaggle is a US-based community site for people involved in data science and machine learning around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A struggle note after a machine learning amateur who changed jobs to a non-IT company was assigned to an AI project</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-struggle-note-after-a-machine-learning-amateur-who-changed-jobs-to-a-non-it-company-was-assigned-to-an-ai-project-11386/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-struggle-note-after-a-machine-learning-amateur-who-changed-jobs-to-a-non-it-company-was-assigned-to-an-ai-project-11386/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 8th day of How I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ② Advent Calendar 2019. We hope that it will be helpful for those who are new to the market.
Programming experience  School days (robot engineering, fluid mechanics):  :new: C/C++; embedded, computational fluid dynamics, research tools :new: Matlab; A little in modern control theory   Previous job (ADAS):  C/C++; embedded, in-house tool :new: Python; Algorithm prototyping and data organization *Not related to AI   Current position (construction and civil engineering construction management):  C++; built-in Python; Machine Learning/Deep Learning :new: JavaScript (Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Do Houdini with Python3! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/do-houdini-with-python3-a0194/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/do-houdini-with-python3-a0194/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The second adcare article this year. The first one was &amp;ldquo;[Verify new installation method of SideFX Labs Tool, Package function]&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/takavfx/items/d1698b89df6fb1b86f9c). So this time, let&amp;rsquo;s take a different angle.
It is Python material.
Due to various reasons, the base of my work has already moved to Python3 series, and Python3 series is regularly used. When making a stand-alone tool, it is 3 series. When you have to write Python processing because of M○y○ etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle competition process as seen from the score transition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggle-competition-process-as-seen-from-the-score-transition-49d54/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggle-competition-process-as-seen-from-the-score-transition-49d54/</guid>
      <description># Kaggle competition process from the perspective of score transition  This article is on the 6th day of Advent Calendar of Road to AI Dojo &amp;ldquo;Kaggle&amp;rdquo; by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ① Advent Calendar 2019 This is an article.
This article is for Kaggle newbies who don&amp;rsquo;t know how to get started with Kaggle. While watching the score transition of the competition, I will write an article about what the kagglers are doing at a certain time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Time series data abnormality detection for beginners</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/time-series-data-abnormality-detection-for-beginners-8dfa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/time-series-data-abnormality-detection-for-beginners-8dfa0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the sixth day of Cisco Advent Calendar 2019 by Cisco Systems LLC.
Seven years have passed since the SuperVision team at the University of Toronto, Canada won the ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Challenge (ILSVRC) 2012 in 2012. At this time, by using a model using deep learning, modeling in machine learning and deep learning is often done in the third AI boom, and it is common sense nowadays to use machine learning/deep learning for AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Use Kaggle API inside Docker container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/use-kaggle-api-inside-docker-container-88f08/</guid>
      <description># things to do   Start container using Kaggle official image (kaggle/python) Download csv file with kaggle ~ command Download public notebook with kaggle ~ command  First summary  DL kaggle.json (kaggle.com &amp;gt;My Account &amp;gt;Create New API Token button) 2.$ docker run -it --rm --mount type=bind,src=pwd,dst=/root/dev kaggle/python $ pip install kaggle $ mkdir ~/.kaggle $ cp /root/dev/kaggle.json ~/.kaggle 6.$ chmod 600 ~/.kaggle/kaggle.json $ kaggle competitions download -c titanic -p input/titanic $ unzip input/titanic/titanic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I don&#39;t want to search for high para because it is IQ1 (how to use lightgbm_tuner)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-dont-want-to-search-for-high-para-because-it-is-iq1-how-to-use-lightgbm_tuner-dee7f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-dont-want-to-search-for-high-para-because-it-is-iq1-how-to-use-lightgbm_tuner-dee7f/</guid>
      <description>This article is posted on [IQ1&#39;s 2nd Advent Calendar 2019](https://adventar.org/calendars/4711).  IQ1 machine learning For machine learning, data preprocessing and model hyper search are inevitable. However, I have an IQ of 1, so I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do it if I can do preprocessing of data and high-para search. If you put the preprocessing of data into this modern gradient boosting tree system algorithm (such as lightgbm), you can handle the missing values as they are and you do not have to preprocess the categorical variables, so it will be a world relatively friendly to IQ1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning Machine learning learned by a new graduate who has no experience in machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-machine-learning-learned-by-a-new-graduate-who-has-no-experience-in-machine-learning-4a511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-machine-learning-learned-by-a-new-graduate-who-has-no-experience-in-machine-learning-4a511/</guid>
      <description>This article is about how I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI② Advent Calendar 2019 __.  Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the steps that have taken a slightly different step from the general approach to learning machine learning. I would be happy if it could be used as a reference for as many people as possible. I usually write for individual blogs, and I was warmly thinking about writing on my blog, but I thought it was a great opportunity, so I posted it on __qiita for the first time __.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Built environment for machine learning from 0 (windows10 &#43; Anaconda &#43; VSCode &#43; Tensorflow &#43; GPU version)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/built-environment-for-machine-learning-from-0-windows10-anaconda-vscode-tensorflow-gpu-version-08d3f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/built-environment-for-machine-learning-from-0-windows10-anaconda-vscode-tensorflow-gpu-version-08d3f/</guid>
      <description>I opened the OS for a while and reinstalled the OS, so I rebuilt the environment.  It is a memorandum at that time.
Overview  Machine learning (reinforcement learning) environment built from almost 0 (GPU compatible) Environment  windows10 NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060   Build environment  Anaconda VSCode Tensorflow GPU compatible settings Cooperation between Anaconda and VS Code ChainerRL    Preparation for using Tensorflow GPU version *Not required when using the CPU version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I read and implemented the Variants of UKR</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-read-and-implemented-the-variants-of-ukr-cade1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-read-and-implemented-the-variants-of-ukr-cade1/</guid>
      <description>This article is the first day article of [Furukawa Lab Advent_calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/flab).  This article was written by a student of Furukawa Lab as part of their studies. The content may be ambiguous or the expressions may be slightly different.
Introduction In this article, I will introduce the UKR (Unsupervised Kernel Regression) that I actually made. I translated it into an unsupervised kernel regression, I read and implemented this paper.
If you are interested in manifold learning, please join us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle&#39;s initial equipment-a cell that collects frequently used codes-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggles-initial-equipment-a-cell-that-collects-frequently-used-codes-c946c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggles-initial-equipment-a-cell-that-collects-frequently-used-codes-c946c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When working on Kaggle1, which is a competition platform for data science, Python2 written in Notebook3(orJupyterNotebook[^JupyterNotebook]orGoogleColaboratory[^GoogleColaboratory])istheexecutionenvironment.]]Ithinkthereisa&amp;quot;highlyusedcode&amp;rdquo;.Inordertoreuseit,Iwillintroduceitinonecellasaformatthatiseasytocopyandpasteanyway.Wehopethatbyreusingthecontentsofthiscell,wecanimprovetheefficiencyofdataanalysisinKaggle.(Thisis“Kaggle&amp;rsquo;sinitialequipment”!)
*This article is based on the Notebook published by Kaggler (Kaggle participant) predecessors and the book [Technology of data analysis that wins at Kaggle]. However, it is the individual subjectivity as of December 2019. Therefore, please see for your reference.
#Conclusion
What is Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s initial equipment?
This cell!
#Display Notebook from IPython.core.interactiveshell import InteractiveShell InteractiveShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] P100-PCIE-16GB was added to the GPU of Google Colab somehow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/p100-pcie-16gb-was-added-to-the-gpu-of-google-colab-somehow-56633/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/p100-pcie-16gb-was-added-to-the-gpu-of-google-colab-somehow-56633/</guid>
      <description>* * This article is based on November 24, 2019.  While thinking that everyone may already know. .. .. ..
About Google colab GPU gacha I think it&amp;rsquo;s well known that you have a GPU gacha. See below for details. https://qiita.com/koshian2/items/d33edc963ed6cfcad77e
Trigger I thought that it was faster than usual, and when I checked the GPU, P100 was added as follows. GPU speed comparison Immediately, I compared the training speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle Tutorial Know-how in the top 2% of Titanic</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggle-tutorial-know-how-in-the-top-2-of-titanic-d8a1f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggle-tutorial-know-how-in-the-top-2-of-titanic-d8a1f/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  Since I started studying machine learning, I tried Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s tutorial for beginners, Titanic.
At first, I tried to play around with the feature amount on my own, referring to Japanese Web information, but even if the training data showed good accuracy, when I submitted the test data, the accuracy did not rise as expected, It was difficult to break the wall of 80% and I was in agony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] ``First time learning&#39;&#39; that even university students with no knowledge can do-AWS SageMaker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</guid>
      <description># My background  Amazon? Ah, you know, you know, a mail order app. Not long ago, knowledge about Amazon was that much. Of course, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know AWS.
I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed as an information undergraduate student. 
However, as a 3rd year university student, I was introduced to the lab and learned about AWS. In addition, I am addicted to the topic &amp;ldquo;Atsuhiko Nakata&amp;rsquo;s YouTube University&amp;rdquo;, which is a hot topic in this street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Speech recognition by Python MFCC</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/speech-recognition-by-python-mfcc-15968/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/speech-recognition-by-python-mfcc-15968/</guid>
      <description>In the [previous article](https://qiita.com/k-maru/items/4f12fd0f8344b9e093bd),vowelrecognitionwasperformedusingformantanalysis.IlearnedaboutMFCCinaninternshipat[CyceedCo.,Ltd.](http://www.sciseed.jp/), and verified the classification accuracy, so this article is a continuation of the previous article about MFCC that is often used for speech recognition. I would like to summarize.  ##table of contents
 Background What is MFCC -MFCC derivation process Implementation of MFCC derivation program -Regarding librosa -Derivation of MFCC -Phoneme class classification using MFCC Implementation of a program for continuous speech recognition -Regarding dynamic differences -Derivation of primary and secondary differences -Phoneme class classification including features of second-order differences Consideration Summary Reference  background Previous article formant analysis finds the envelope of the spectrum, and the frequencies emphasized in them are used as features from lower to F1 and F2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Beginner] Learn Python basic grammar in 5 hours for free!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/beginner-learn-python-basic-grammar-in-5-hours-for-free-b97b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/beginner-learn-python-basic-grammar-in-5-hours-for-free-b97b2/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  This article is available from AI Academy&amp;rsquo;s Python Syntax quick learningandPythonprogrammingintroduction This is a partial modification based on the content. You can learn the basics of Python basic grammar by reading this article. If you have finished learning Python, please use AI Academy,whereyoucanlearnAIandmachinelearningforfree(onlysomecontentsarechargedbutbasiccontentsarealmostfree). .. *For short-term AI boot camps for individuals, click here (https://aiacademy.jp/bootcamp/)
Why Python? **AI Academyhandleslearningcontentscenteredontheartificialintelligence(AI) field, and Python handles machine learning and deep learning easily in the artificial intelligence field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Fully automatic connection] 90 minutes and 12 hours solved with Colaboratory file only [Use Selenium]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fully-automatic-connection-90-minutes-and-12-hours-solved-with-colaboratory-file-only-use-selenium-8869b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fully-automatic-connection-90-minutes-and-12-hours-solved-with-colaboratory-file-only-use-selenium-8869b/</guid>
      <description>Are you using Google Colaboratory? It&#39;s the best, isn&#39;t it?  Google Colaboratory is a Jupyter notebook environment that runs on a browser. Moreover, GPU and TPU machines can be used free of charge. That&amp;rsquo;s the best.
However, there were two rules about usage time (described later), and it was also a addictive point to crawl Colaboratory users.
&amp;ldquo;When I wake up in the morning, the connection will be cut&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [ML-Aents] I tried machine learning using TensorFlow of Unity and Python (v0.11β compatible)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ml-aents-i-tried-machine-learning-using-tensorflow-of-unity-and-python-v0.11%CE%B2-compatible-687f0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ml-aents-i-tried-machine-learning-using-tensorflow-of-unity-and-python-v0.11%CE%B2-compatible-687f0/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any Japanese article about v0.11.0, so please take a note.
This article is for beginners. Unity beginners mimic one of ML-Agents official tutorials do it It is one of the machine learning, __ which I tried __ Reinforcement Learning.
I will make something like this. :arrow_up:__
For those who know how to operate Unity easily, but who have not done machine learning yet. Rather than focusing on theory, I introduce you to Zakuri so that you can experience while moving your hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build your own PC for deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-your-own-pc-for-deep-learning-5d31a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-your-own-pc-for-deep-learning-5d31a/</guid>
      <description>Leave a memorandum of your own PC.  Finally, I will describe up to the point where Ubuntu is installed and a deep learning environment is created with docker.
table of contents  Find out how to make your own PC Assemble the PC Environmental construction  1. Find out how to make your own PC  I referred to the following sites. -Summary by budget for own PC -How to make a deep learning PC  It seems that it is better to decide the specifications according to the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Smoother pipeline processing in Luigi! Introducing gokart</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/smoother-pipeline-processing-in-luigi-introducing-gokart-8cf0e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/smoother-pipeline-processing-in-luigi-introducing-gokart-8cf0e/</guid>
      <description># what is this?  This is a summary article about gokart, a wrapper library for Luigi.
The motivation for development and basic usage are summarized in M3&amp;rsquo;s blog very carefully, and the basic usage is It&amp;rsquo;s a story that I should read this, but I wanted to summarize it as a reverse lookup reference, so I made an article.
The functions of Luigi itself are not explained so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Score-CAM implementation with keras. Comparison with Grad-CAM</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/score-cam-implementation-with-keras.-comparison-with-grad-cam-95c51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/score-cam-implementation-with-keras.-comparison-with-grad-cam-95c51/</guid>
      <description># Overview   Implemented the method &amp;ldquo;Score-CAM&amp;rdquo; of Paper posted on arxiv on October 3, 2019 with keras. Comparison with Grad-CAM, Grad-CAM++. Implemented the independently accelerated Faster Score-CAM. Applied to the model trained on DAGM dataset. The code can be found on github.  What is # Score-CAM?
 One of the visualization methods of the basis of judgment of CNN -There is a wonderful summary on here for understanding the judgment basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Gaussian process and machine learning Gaussian process regression implemented only by numpy of Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/gaussian-process-and-machine-learning-gaussian-process-regression-implemented-only-by-numpy-of-python-cf16e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/gaussian-process-and-machine-learning-gaussian-process-regression-implemented-only-by-numpy-of-python-cf16e/</guid>
      <description>I recently read [&amp;quot;Gaussian Process and Machine Learning&amp;quot;](https://www.amazon.co.jp/GaussianProcessandMachineLearning-MachineLearningProfessionalSeries-Mochihashi-Daichi/dp/4061529269) I implemented it.  The content is &amp;ldquo;3.4.2 Gaussian Process Regression Calculation&amp;rdquo; in Chapter 3. Deer is a landmark. It is easy to understand and highly recommended.
What is the Gauss process? First of all, to explain the Gaussian process in one word,
At Y=f(X) &amp;ldquo;If input X is similar, output Y is similar.&amp;quot;
It is a tool for mathematically expressing that property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What an amateur stumbled upon in Deep Learning made from scratch Memo: Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-an-amateur-stumbled-upon-in-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-1-1945a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-an-amateur-stumbled-upon-in-deep-learning-made-from-scratch-memo-chapter-1-1945a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Suddenly, I thought &amp;ldquo;[Deep Learning from scratch-the theory and implementation of deep learning learned with Python]&amp;rdquo; (https://www.oreilly.co.jp/books/9784873117584/) and &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning from scratch ( 2)-Natural language processing&amp;rdquo; I decided to study.
However, I am very worried whether I will not be able to take the time to continue. However, when I completed [Language Processing 100 Knock 2015]2-3yearsago,Amateurlanguageprocessing100knocks I continued to post to Qiita, and thanks to everyone&amp;rsquo;s likes and comments, I was able to finish it, so again this time Qiita&amp;rsquo;s I decided to help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] (Saved version: updated from time to time) A collection of useful tutorials for doing data analysis hackathons by Team AI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/saved-version-updated-from-time-to-time-a-collection-of-useful-tutorials-for-doing-data-analysis-hackathons-by-team-ai-f8e32/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/saved-version-updated-from-time-to-time-a-collection-of-useful-tutorials-for-doing-data-analysis-hackathons-by-team-ai-f8e32/</guid>
      <description>We at Team AI hold machine learning study sessions and data analysis hackathons every day in Shibuya.  The goal is to have a community of 1 million people, mainly in Tokyo.
I hope this movement of data analysis will spread throughout Japan and around the world. We have put together a useful tutorial for doing data analysis hackathons. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun, so everyone, especially the locals, should try it out for yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Environment construction of auto-sklearn that semi-automates machine learning (Mac&amp;Docker)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/environment-construction-of-auto-sklearn-that-semi-automates-machine-learning-macdocker-ffd7f/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/environment-construction-of-auto-sklearn-that-semi-automates-machine-learning-macdocker-ffd7f/</guid>
      <description>What is # auto-sklearn  A library that can semi-automatically perform preprocessing of machine learning, algorithm selection, and hyperparameter search. See below for detailed explanation.
What is auto-sklearn? Automatic machine learning with WPython auto sklearn Data analysis with Python: Automation of machine learning
Build an environment for auto-sklearn on mac As a premise, auto-sklearn is developed on Ubuntu, and it works on Linux but may not work on Mac or Window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Statistics for programmers] There is more than one way to calculate the average value</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/statistics-for-programmers-there-is-more-than-one-way-to-calculate-the-average-value-fec65/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/statistics-for-programmers-there-is-more-than-one-way-to-calculate-the-average-value-fec65/</guid>
      <description>## table of contents  Statistics for Programmers-Table of Contents
Related article  Average, Median, Mode  Overview When calculating the average value, I generally think of adding all the values and dividing by the number of elements. However, there are several other average values, such as weighted average and geometric average, which can be used depending on the application. The commonly known method of dividing the total by the number of elements is called the arithmetic mean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 100 amateur language processing knocks: Summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/100-amateur-language-processing-knocks-summary-fb50b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/100-amateur-language-processing-knocks-summary-fb50b/</guid>
      <description>It is a summary of the challenge record of [100 language processing knock 2015](http://www.cl.ecei.tohoku.ac.jp/nlp100/).  :warning:** This is not a challenge record of 100 processing of language knock 2020.Theold2015version is the target. Please note: bangbang:**
Challenge environment Ubuntu 16.04 LTS + Python 3.5.2 :: Anaconda 4.1.1 (64-bit). (Only Problem 00andProblem01arePython2.7.)
#Chapter 1: Preparatory exercise
 Reviewing somewhat advanced programming language topics while working on materials that deal with text and strings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Translation] scikit-learn 0.18 User Guide 4.1. Pipeline and Feature Union: Combination of estimators</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/translation-scikit-learn-0.18-user-guide-4.1.-pipeline-and-feature-union-combination-of-estimators-fdfd2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/translation-scikit-learn-0.18-user-guide-4.1.-pipeline-and-feature-union-combination-of-estimators-fdfd2/</guid>
      <description>Google translated http://scikit-learn.org/0.18/modules/pipeline.html  scikit-learn 0.18 User Guide 4. Dataset conversion
 4.1. Pipeline and FeatureUnion: Estimator combination 4.1.1. Pipeline: Chain estimation Pipeline can be used to combine multiple estimators into one. I can do it. It is convenient because the steps that process the data, such as feature selection, normalization, and classification, are often fixed. The pipeline serves two purposes here.
-Convenience: To fit the whole sequence of estimators, just call fit and predict the data once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] From environment construction to deep learning tutorial</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/from-environment-construction-to-deep-learning-tutorial-ff8dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/from-environment-construction-to-deep-learning-tutorial-ff8dc/</guid>
      <description>Deep learning has become a hot topic these days,  &amp;ldquo;I want to study, but I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what I can do&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
For such people, we will introduce the methods from Mac environment construction to deep learning execution.
python environment construction Machine learning and deep learning are python. For the time being, prepare the environment construction of python. First, let&amp;rsquo;s install python. Let&amp;rsquo;s open the terminal and run it in order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understand the TensorFlow namespace and master shared variables</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understand-the-tensorflow-namespace-and-master-shared-variables-ffe99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understand-the-tensorflow-namespace-and-master-shared-variables-ffe99/</guid>
      <description>## Intro  This is the 9th day article of TensorFlow Advent Calendar 2016.
TensorFlow was released in November 2015, but the &amp;ldquo;namespace&amp;rdquo; function was supported from the beginning. This is used in graph visualization with TensorBoard, but of course it&amp;rsquo;s not the only one. Namespaces are very useful for managing identifiers. I recall C++ when it comes to strong &amp;ldquo;namespace&amp;rdquo; support, but I&amp;rsquo;ll quote it from a C++ instruction book (self-study C++).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Implemented PRML algorithm in Python (almost Numpy only)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implemented-prml-algorithm-in-python-almost-numpy-only-fc83b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implemented-prml-algorithm-in-python-almost-numpy-only-fc83b/</guid>
      <description>I will implement the method published in PRML in Python for my own study (machine learning algorithm and Python study).  As a general rule, in the algorithm part, in addition to the Python standard library, Only Numpy can be used. Machine learning packages such as scikit-learn and tensorflow are not used. Packages that show results such as matplotlib will be used unless they are related to the implementation of the algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Predict the value of the water level gauge by machine learning using open data of data city Sabae</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/predict-the-value-of-the-water-level-gauge-by-machine-learning-using-open-data-of-data-city-sabae-fe2e0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/predict-the-value-of-the-water-level-gauge-by-machine-learning-using-open-data-of-data-city-sabae-fe2e0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When I was looking for something good as an example of using open data, I found that the water level data was published on the site of Data City Sabae, so I tried machine learning using it. It was
http://data.city.sabae.lg.jp/top_page/
Download data There is the following notation in the &amp;ldquo;Disaster prevention&amp;rdquo; group on the &amp;ldquo;Open data&amp;rdquo; page on the above site.
Water level data (Sabae City, Fukui Prefecture) Nontegawa Drainage Pump Station [CSV] It is the data of the water level gauge in Sabae city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Talk to improve the bottleneck of machine learning algorithm with Cython</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/talk-to-improve-the-bottleneck-of-machine-learning-algorithm-with-cython-fe83f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/talk-to-improve-the-bottleneck-of-machine-learning-algorithm-with-cython-fe83f/</guid>
      <description>#About this article   Talk about how to make Python faster Find CPU bound processing bottlenecks by profiling Improve the bottleneck you find with Cython  #Introduction We recently implemented a recommendation algorithm called Bayesian Personalized Ranking (BPR). I tried to write the code with reference to the formula of this paper, but when I tried to execute it, it was a bit too slow and I could not use it, so I improved the processing speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deep Learning (under attendance)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-under-attendance-f8352/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-under-attendance-f8352/</guid>
      <description>Taking classes at MPS Yokohama  I am having a difficult time because I am a beginner in programming and mathematics. (We will check Markdown notation and TeX notation and rewrite later)
Motivation for attending: Ultimately, I want to customize the appropriate Deep Learning library (tensorflow) etc. and use it for work (advertisement operation tool) and play (home electronics operation from sensing??).
Textbook (learning source) MPS lecture slides Lecture video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to make face image data set used in machine learning (2: Frame analysis of moving image and acquisition of candidate image)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-make-face-image-data-set-used-in-machine-learning-2-frame-analysis-of-moving-image-and-acquisition-of-candidate-image-fdfe8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-make-face-image-data-set-used-in-machine-learning-2-frame-analysis-of-moving-image-and-acquisition-of-candidate-image-fdfe8/</guid>
      <description>[Last time](http://qiita.com/ligerbolt/items/aeaa88980030fba940b6) introduced how to collect candidate images using Bing Image Search API.  This time, I will introduce a method of frame analysis and collection of videos.
Development environment used this time  MacOS X El Capitan 10.11.4 Python 3.5 OpenCV 3.1  Merits of extracting candidate images from videos The video basically uses the same mechanism as flipbook comics, and still images are switched within a short time to express movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning beginners try out Naive Bayes (1)-theory</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-beginners-try-out-naive-bayes-1-theory-fe4c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-beginners-try-out-naive-bayes-1-theory-fe4c3/</guid>
      <description>## This page  Since I&amp;rsquo;m a machine learning beginner and a Python beginner, I think that it will be a bit like reading the pages that were basically referenced.
What is conditional probability (Bayes&amp;rsquo; theorem)? ? It&amp;rsquo;s a bit of math. Have you heard the term conditional probability? I heard a little about it in the class before, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t remember much.
P(B|A) = \frac{P(A \cap B)}{P(A)} = \frac{P(B)P(A|B)}{P(A)} P(B|A) is the probability of event B occurring when event A occurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction to Machine Learning from Simple Perceptron</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-machine-learning-from-simple-perceptron-fb369/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-machine-learning-from-simple-perceptron-fb369/</guid>
      <description>#1. What is a simple perceptron?  The input data is classified into two classes using the following linear discriminant function.
f(x)=g(w^{T}x+\theta)\\ Here, if \theta = x_0, \\ =g(\sum _{i=0}^{d}w_ix_i) Non-linear activation function: g(a) = \left\{ \begin{array}{ll} +1 &amp;amp; (a \geq 0) \\ - 1 &amp;amp; (a \lt 0) \end{array} \right. Weight: w=(w_0,w_1,...,w_{d}), \\ Input data: x=(x_0=\theta,x_1,x_2,...,x_{d}), \\d: number of dimensions, Bias: \theta (arbitrary number) When f(x) \geq 0, x\in C_{1} When f(x) \lt 0, x\in C_{2} C_1: Class 1, C_2: Class 2 Of the above, the process for determining the parameter of weight_w_ is called “learning”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] TensorFlow Deep MNIST for Experts 翻訳</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-deep-mnist-for-experts-%E7%BF%BB%E8%A8%B3-fa9cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tensorflow-deep-mnist-for-experts-%E7%BF%BB%E8%A8%B3-fa9cf/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Beforeandprevious using Beginner tutorial translation and actually using TensorFlow I did machine learning. This time I translated the tutorial for Expert.
Deep MNIST for Experts TensorFlow is a powerful library for performing large-scale numerical calculations. One of the best tasks is the training and execution of deep neural networks. In this tutorial we will learn the basic building blocks of a TensorFlow model while building a deep convolutional MNIST classifier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to compress the image using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-compress-the-image-using-machine-learning-fb6ee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-compress-the-image-using-machine-learning-fb6ee/</guid>
      <description>![original_compressed.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.amazonaws.com/0/77079/2f7e9fc7-d91a-bd40-dca9-bed85174e317.png)  #Introduction Try compressing the image using K-Means, which is a typical clustering algorithm. First, I will explain the K-Means algorithm. After that, I will explain about image compression using K-Means. For details, refer to Coursera Machine Learning.
What is clustering? Dividing a collection of data into several groups (clusters) according to the similarity between the data. K-Means algorithm Intuitive description of algorithm The K-Means algorithm is roughly divided into the following three processes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Must see OpenCV-Python Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/must-see-opencv-python-tutorials-facf9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/must-see-opencv-python-tutorials-facf9/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;quot;OpenCV-Python Tutorial Document&amp;quot; site is up.  [Welcome to the OpenCV-Python tutorial documentation page!] (http://labs.eecs.tottori-u.ac.jp/sd/Member/oyamada/OpenCV/html/index.html)
Please use the above site to read the complete translation. The following translations are inadequate as translations, and their comparison with related python libraries is somewhat unique.
 OpenCV-Python Tutorials of OpenCV 3.2 http://docs.opencv.org/3.2.0/d9/df8/tutorial_root.html It is published in. (The accuracy of Google Translate has improved recently, so it may be enough to try Google Translate rather than reading this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to classify the voice actor&#39;s voice</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-classify-the-voice-actors-voice-f785e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-classify-the-voice-actors-voice-f785e/</guid>
      <description>I tried to identify the voice actor&#39;s voice in machine learning practice. Make a note of the procedure.  ###Thing you want to do First of all, let&amp;rsquo;s learn the voice actors&amp;rsquo; original voices (voices such as radio), and check how accurately they can be identified by including the original voices as test data. Next, I would like to test whether the voices of anime can be predicted from the voice actors&amp;rsquo; original voices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to build an environment for machine learning with Python (Mac OS X)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-build-an-environment-for-machine-learning-with-python-mac-os-x-fad4c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-build-an-environment-for-machine-learning-with-python-mac-os-x-fad4c/</guid>
      <description>At the CROSS 2015 python session the other day, I thought that machine learning might be interesting, so for the time being, I tried to prepare the environment, so it is also a meme.  The article of CROSS 2015 the other day is here.
:black_square_button: Overview  Build an environment for machine learning with python I didn&amp;rsquo;t do a big deal, so I thought I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t give it to Qiita, but I was addicted to various things, so I will give it for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Tool to support machine learning in Python MALSS (Introduction)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/tool-to-support-machine-learning-in-python-malss-introduction-fe1cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/tool-to-support-machine-learning-in-python-malss-introduction-fe1cc/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;Font color=&amp;quot;red&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Support Python3 (2016.01.25)&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;  I made a tool called MALSS (Machine Learning Support System) that supports machine learning in Python (PyPI/GitHub). We would be happy if you could give us your opinions.
I&amp;rsquo;m writing the rest here.
 Tool MALSS (basic) that supports machine learning in Python Tool MALSS (application) that supports machine learning in Python  Purpose A rich open source development environment has made it really easy to use machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Calculation of support vector machine (SVM) (using cvxopt)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/calculation-of-support-vector-machine-svm-using-cvxopt-faba9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/calculation-of-support-vector-machine-svm-using-cvxopt-faba9/</guid>
      <description>Hello.  The calculation of the support vector machine (SVM) is based on the procedure (using cvxopt) of Discontinuation creation &amp;ldquo;soft margin SVM&amp;rdquo; about artificial intelligenceIfyoufollowitexactly,youwillfeelalittlelikecalculatingthesolutionyourself.Inthefollowing1,theconvergentsolutionofLagrangemultiplieralpha,tabplot,etc.arealsoplotted(```class×prediction==1``Highlightthedatathatbecomes`.prediction==0istheboundaryline).
$ ./svm.py file = classification.txt (len=200) cvxopt result status: optimal delta = 5.684342e-14 class = (&#39;-1&#39;,&#39;+1&#39;) confusion matrix: [[96 7] [34 63]] #!/usr/bin/env python # -*- coding: utf-8 -*- # support vector machine (SVM) calculation Use # cvxopt.solvers.qp (Quadratic Programming) from __future__ import print_function import numpy as np import cvxopt Ccoeff = [30, 30] # soft margin coefficients of class SIGMA = 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Calculate tf-idf with scikit-learn</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/calculate-tf-idf-with-scikit-learn-f8697/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/calculate-tf-idf-with-scikit-learn-f8697/</guid>
      <description>**This post is the fourth day article of [Reality Escape Advent Calendar 2013](http://katryo.hatenablog.com/entry/2013/12/19/001823). **  2nd dayusesthehtmlfetchedusingtheBingAPI,so[2ndday](http://qiita.com/katryo(/items/62291ba328de9d12bd30) is easier to understand if you read it first.
Put this article in 3 lines  I checked a Python library called scikit-learn Day 2 Calculated tf-idf of word in html saved Confirmed word to tfidf mapping  Reference scikit-learn formula, text feature extraction document
Calculating tfidf of words in Tweet using scikit-learn</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>