<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> machine learning on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  machine learning on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Causal reasoning using machine learning (arrangement of causal reasoning methods)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/causal-reasoning-using-machine-learning-arrangement-of-causal-reasoning-methods-fa213/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/causal-reasoning-using-machine-learning-arrangement-of-causal-reasoning-methods-fa213/</guid>
      <description># Causal reasoning using machine learning   A rough understanding and notes of when to use causal reasoning using machine learning methods that have been actively used in recent years (Memorandum) Basically, the current causal reasoning method is summarized as a flow chart.
 Introduction Causal reasoning is a series of statistical methods aimed at answering the cause of an outcome. Generally, statistical approaches such as regression analysis focus on quantifying how changes in X are related to changes in Y.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Product Development Team Reading Party: [INSPIRED Product Management that Creates Enthusiastic Products]</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/ai-product-development-team-reading-party-inspired-product-management-that-creates-enthusiastic-products-fb315/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/ai-product-development-team-reading-party-inspired-product-management-that-creates-enthusiastic-products-fb315/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I will introduce the management method and contents of the reading event held by the &amp;quot;AI Product Development Team&amp;quot; that I lead.  The books targeted at this reading party are ** [INSPIRED Product management that creates enthusiastic products] ** https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/B0814STTHV/
is.
In Japanese, it is translated as &amp;ldquo;Product Management that creates enthusiasm products,&amp;rdquo; but in English How to Create Tech Products Customers Love is.
How to make a loved product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTG forest drone business</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/mtg-forest-drone-business-ff0c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/mtg-forest-drone-business-ff0c2/</guid>
      <description># Why do you do drone business?  MTG Forest contributes to the fields of forestry and agriculture through machine learning.
For example
 Measure the degree of fruit growth with image authentication Identify the name of the animal Measure the number of trees in the mountain  So far, I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this with Python if I say it in a programming language. We also use machine learning, object recognition, and AI functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: unsupervised learning: non-hierarchical clustering</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-unsupervised-learning-non-hierarchical-clustering-f98bf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-unsupervised-learning-non-hierarchical-clustering-f98bf/</guid>
      <description># Clustering techniques  Hierarchical clustering Hierarchical clustering is to find the most similar combination in the data It is a method of making clusters in order, and is characterized by having a hierarchical structure during the process.
See the figure below for a concrete example. There are 5 data points A,B,C,D,E. The closest of these 5 data We will make one cluster.
A, B, C, D, E → (A,B), C,D,E In this case, the two points A and B are the closest points in this combination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Price Prediction by Machine Learning Numerai</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The general public may not have heard about it, but there is a hedge fund called &amp;ldquo;Numerai&amp;rdquo;. It is a hedge fund that has been known a little in the neighborhood by being covered by media such as Wired and Forbes from the latter half of 2016 to the first half of 2017. This hedge fund is a so-called crowdsourcing type fund that operates based on the forecast results of stock prices by an unspecified number of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing logistic regression with NumPy</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/implementing-logistic-regression-with-numpy-fb4cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/implementing-logistic-regression-with-numpy-fb4cd/</guid>
      <description>It is a moment if you use scikit-learn, but you can also implement it yourself as a study.  In the original article, multi-class classification and train_test_split were out of scope, so
It is simplified to a 2-class problem and evaluated with the same data as the training data.
Please refer to the following article for details. Machine learning starting from scratch #4 &amp;ldquo;Logistic regression&amp;rdquo;
from sklearn.datasets import load_iris import numpy as np iris = load_iris() X_org = iris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let me know by voice when an article you are interested in is posted</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/let-me-know-by-voice-when-an-article-you-are-interested-in-is-posted-ff518/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/let-me-know-by-voice-when-an-article-you-are-interested-in-is-posted-ff518/</guid>
      <description>You can detect updates of blogs that you are interested in through RSS feeds, but sometimes you see the title and say, &amp;quot;Isn&#39;t it necessary to read it?&amp;quot;  It&amp;rsquo;s a hassle to read the titles one by one, so I decided to ask Itako Tohoku of Voiceroid to read the article when I was interested in it.
Extracting articles that may be of interest Classification of articles using Flair Flair is a library that can easily execute the latest natural language processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problems when shaping data</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/problems-when-shaping-data-ff539/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/problems-when-shaping-data-ff539/</guid>
      <description>This article is a memorandum of the processing that I did when the data type I was scraping was various.  #Check the data type
df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].dtype #DataFrame np.dtype() #numpy array Change data type df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].astype(int) converted to #int df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].dtype(float) converted to #float df[&amp;#39;column name&amp;#39;].dtype(str) # convert to string #Check for missing values
df.isnull() #Remove missing values
df.dropna() #pandas line deletion
df.drop (number of lines) Add columns to #pandas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even now, let&#39;s try face recognition with Chainer (learning phase)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/even-now-lets-try-face-recognition-with-chainer-learning-phase-fa93c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/even-now-lets-try-face-recognition-with-chainer-learning-phase-fa93c/</guid>
      <description>###Overview  It is full of feeling that face recognition is announced after the end of development of Chainer is announced, I will spell it here as a memorandum.
This series will be sent in two parts. This time, I will explain how to implement the learning phase (learning face images). Next time, I will explain the implementation of prediction phase(facerecognitionusingcamera).
Since I am a ML first-year student and a high school student at the time, some of the information may be incorrect or there may be a bug in the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning record Part 27 (31st day)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/learning-record-part-27-31st-day-fc1bc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/learning-record-part-27-31st-day-fc1bc/</guid>
      <description># Learning record (31st day)  Start of study: 12/7 (Sat) ~
Teaching materials: ・Miyuki Oshige “Details! Python3 Introductory Note&amp;rdquo; (Sotec, 2017): Dec 7 (Sat) to Dec 19 (Thurs) ・Progate Python course (5 courses in total): 12/19 (Thurs) to 12/21 (Sat) ・Andreas C. Müller, Sarah Guido &amp;ldquo;(Japanese title) Machine learning started with Python&amp;rdquo; (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Japan, 2017): December 21 (Sat)-December 23 (Sat) ・Kaggle :Real or Not? NLP with Disaster Tweets ：Posted on Saturday, December 28th until Friday, January 3rd Adjustment ・Wes Mckinney &amp;ldquo;(Japanese title) Introduction to data analysis using Python&amp;rdquo; (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Japan, 2018): 1/4 (Wed) to 1/13 (Mon) read ・Yasuyuki Saito “Deep Learning from Zero” (O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Japan, 2016): 1/15 (Wed)-1/20 (Mon) ・**François Chollet “Deep Learning with Python and Keras” (Quepe, 2018): 1/21 (Tue) ~ **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probability prediction of imbalanced data</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/probability-prediction-of-imbalanced-data-fe87b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/probability-prediction-of-imbalanced-data-fe87b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When classifying by machine learning, it is sometimes desirable to obtain the probability of belonging to those classes as well as the classification result. When the number of data for positive cases is extremely small compared to the number of data for negative cases (such data is called imbalanced data), if the prediction model is constructed using all of those data, the prediction result will also be negative. Often, it tends to be difficult to accurately classify positive data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books on data science to read in 2020</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/books-on-data-science-to-read-in-2020-fe474/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Przemek Chojecki](https://towardsdatascience.com/@pchojecki),[[DataScienceBooksyoushouldreadin2020](https://towardsdatascience.com/data-science-books-you-should-read-in-2020-358f70e1d9b2)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
Data science is arguably one of the hottest markets right now. Almost all companies are looking for or considering a data science role.
So it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to become a data scientist. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re already a data scientist and want to promote to a senior position, it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to hone your skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half a year when the Gori Gori literary school almost learned AI</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/half-a-year-when-the-gori-gori-literary-school-almost-learned-ai-f9988/</guid>
      <description># Half-year when the Gori Gori literary system (deviation value 40 first half) learned AI  Hi, it&amp;rsquo;s a rugged ~~ macho~~ humanities. After graduating from commercial high school, I went to the Faculty of Humanities, so it&amp;rsquo;s different from other humanities. It is a thoroughbred world of humanities.
Although it is a vital math skill, I only studied math A up to high school, and just started math at university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For those who look at the log while learning with machine learning ~ Muscle training with LightGBM ~</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/for-those-who-look-at-the-log-while-learning-with-machine-learning-~-muscle-training-with-lightgbm-~-fbe57/</guid>
      <description>What do you guys do when learning models with machine learning?  Did you just look at the log output to the console? &amp;ldquo;Oh, it was lower than I expected!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oh, the accuracy is getting worse, do your best!!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly fun to think, though.
But when I cheered up, the model doesn&amp;rsquo;t do its best, and there is no dramatic development, so it&amp;rsquo;s a waste of time to look at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display and analyze only some columns in CASTable</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/display-and-analyze-only-some-columns-in-castable-fcbe4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/display-and-analyze-only-some-columns-in-castable-fcbe4/</guid>
      <description>[SAS Viya](https://www.sas.com/ja_jp/software/viya.html)isanAIplatform.ItisavailablethroughlanguagessuchasPython,JavaandR.AtableobjectcalledCASTableisusedinSASViya(CASstandsforCloudAnalyticServices). This time, I will introduce a method to display information by extracting only some columns from CAS Table.  Get table from database First, connect to SAS Viya.
import swat conn = swat.CAS(&amp;#39;server-name.mycompany.com&amp;#39;, 5570,&amp;#39;username&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;password&amp;#39;) Then get the CASTable. This time I use CSV of IRIS data.
tbl = conn.loadtable(&amp;#39;data/iris.csv&amp;#39;, caslib=&amp;#39;casuser&amp;#39;).casTable Get column You can retrieve columns by specifying the key with tbl as a dict.
col = tbl[&amp;#39;sepal_width&amp;#39;] col The output looks like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultra simple case k-means python code</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/ultra-simple-case-k-means-python-code-fa856/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/ultra-simple-case-k-means-python-code-fa856/</guid>
      <description>## python code for super simple case of k-means method  In the humanities of statistical application of the statistical test 1st grade in 2019, there was a problem about the initial value dependence of the k-means method, but here, in order to confirm that k-means actually depends on the initial value, I wrote the python code for a super simple case.
The situation setting is as follows. Classifying set: a set whose elements are (finite number) real numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything for beginners to be able to do machine learning</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/everything-for-beginners-to-be-able-to-do-machine-learning-fcd09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/everything-for-beginners-to-be-able-to-do-machine-learning-fcd09/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is for the purpose of enabling machine learning while doing what was presented as a &amp;ldquo;knowledge necessary for doing machine learning&amp;rdquo; **, which was issued as a subject for an internship destination. is. You will only become a Apprentice Machine Learning Engineer by doing all of this article. On the contrary, you can easily expose the basics of machine learning simply by doing all of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is machine learning?</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-machine-learning-fe6f2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/what-is-machine-learning-fe6f2/</guid>
      <description>## Differences between machine learning, statistics and data science  Machine Learning (ML), Statistics, Data Science. All of these words are often heard due to the rapid spread of AI in recent years, but what is the difference between them? There is no definite answer, but to put it simply, firstly Data Science is a field that combines specialized fields such as statistics, computer science, and business. I think it will be easier to understand if you look at the figure below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>``First time learning&#39;&#39; that even university students with no knowledge can do-AWS SageMaker</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</guid>
      <description># My background  Amazon? Ah, you know, you know, a mail order app. Not long ago, knowledge about Amazon was that much. Of course, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know AWS.
I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed as an information undergraduate student. 
However, as a 3rd year university student, I was introduced to the lab and learned about AWS. In addition, I am addicted to the topic &amp;ldquo;Atsuhiko Nakata&amp;rsquo;s YouTube University&amp;rdquo;, which is a hot topic in this street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaggle Related Summary</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/kaggle-related-summary-fc867/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/kaggle-related-summary-fc867/</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of information that will help you capture Kaggle.  (Will be updated at any time)
▪︎website https://naotaka1128.hatenadiary.jp/entry/kaggle-compe-tips
◼︎ Mechanism Curry&amp;rsquo;s commentary http://www.currypurin.com/entry/2018/02/21/011316
◾️ Book Data Analysis Technology Wins at Kaggle https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/B07YTDBC3Z/
◾️Booth kaggle tutorial 4th edition https://booth.pm/ja/items/1567594
■ slack https://kaggler-ja.herokuapp.com
■ discord Curry&amp;rsquo;s
■ wiki http://kaggler-ja-wiki.herokuapp.com/
■ coursera https://ja.coursera.org/learn/competitive-data-science
◾️ Summary article kaggle api related https://qiita.com/uni-3/items/f1fdbeeddd08ca22c80f
https://qiita.com/shunkakinoki/items/1f58e218f8f6b31ad0bf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best practices for data manipulation with pandas</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/best-practices-for-data-manipulation-with-pandas-f7ed4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/best-practices-for-data-manipulation-with-pandas-f7ed4/</guid>
      <description>After preprocessing the data with machine learning, with a hypothesis,  Play with data? Play with? I think there are phases, At that time, how to control pandas freely is I think it will be important.
I myself have a little programming experience and database knowledge,
***pandas DataFrame [] ← This is too complicated! ! ***
Especially, it is difficult to narrow down by conditions.
train[train[&amp;#34;company_id&amp;#34;] == 1088][&amp;#34;meter_reading&amp;#34;] It&amp;rsquo;s confusing at this point, but if this is train_weather_df, it will be ruined</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>