<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> BI on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/bi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  BI on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/bi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Data analysis Appropriate use of data analysis tools for beginners</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/data-analysis-appropriate-use-of-data-analysis-tools-for-beginners-74218/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/data-analysis-appropriate-use-of-data-analysis-tools-for-beginners-74218/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article and target audience  There are many tools for data analysis. Here, data analysis tools include Excel, programming, dashboard tools, BI tools, etc.
In this article, for those who are new to data analysis and those who are going to do data analysis, we will explain what kind of analysis tool should be used for what kind of situation.
The most important reason to decide what kind of analysis tool to use in what situation is that the right tool can make data analysis efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Knowledge and study methods required for future data analysts</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/knowledge-and-study-methods-required-for-future-data-analysts-34359/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/knowledge-and-study-methods-required-for-future-data-analysts-34359/</guid>
      <description># Target audience and content  The target audience of this article is those who are going to analyze user behavior and sales data of companies, researchers who have to do a little tedious data analysis to do with Excel, and so on.
Background of the demand for &amp;ldquo;dick&amp;rdquo; data analysts In recent years, it has become very important for IT companies to analyze data and to make detailed improvements in UI and UX and implement growth hack measures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>