<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> gensim on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/gensim/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  gensim on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/gensim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Word2Vec</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understanding-word2vec-69afa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understanding-word2vec-69afa/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I have summarized what I have learned about Word2Vec, which is now a standard method for natural language processing. The outline of the algorithm is organized and the model is created using the library.
##reference I have referred to the following to understand Word2Vec.
 Deep Learning from Zero ❷-Natural Language Processing EditionK.Saito(Author) How to understand Word2vec with pictures  Efficient Estimation of Word Representations in Vector Space (Original paper) gensim API reference  #Word2Vec overview The following describes the concept of natural language processing, which is the premise of Word2Vec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s use the distributed expression of words quickly with fastText!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-use-the-distributed-expression-of-words-quickly-with-fasttext-c26fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-use-the-distributed-expression-of-words-quickly-with-fasttext-c26fa/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we&#39;ll look at how to use fastText to get a distributed word representation. [Article on the previous day](https://qiita.com/BlueRayi/items/eb7949594839771c1b70) I thought it would be nice if I could talk about a little link.  What is #fastText
fastTextisamethodtoacquiredistributedexpressions(wordsexpressedasnumbers)announcedbyFacebook.ItisbasedonthefamiliarWord2Vec(CBOW/skip-gram). As for Word2Vec, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to be explained because it has been changed.
Paper: Enriching Word Vectors with Subword Information
The difference between Word2Vec and fastText is how to take a vector.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>