<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TouchDesigner on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/touchdesigner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TouchDesigner on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/touchdesigner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Useful when debugging with TouchDesigner</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/50228c396/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/50228c396/</guid>
      <description>## debug() instead of print()  Although print() is the output method used in Python, in TouchDesigner you can use the function debug() instead of where print() is available. The debug() can see the output as well as where and on which line of which operator it was called. This is useful in most cases when debugging with Touch Designer.
 Comparison of print and debug   Troubleshooting_in_TouchDesigner#Command:_debug
CrashAutoSave for files that cannot be opened or have initial failure Sometimes I write an infinite loop, or something I don&amp;rsquo;t know causes the file to crash or not open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Asynchronous communication only with Touch Designer</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7a3da5ea6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7a3da5ea6/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  TouchDesigner (TD) can execute python script, If a process such as HTTP communication takes a long time, it will be hardened until the process is completed. At this time, the timeline of the whole TD also stops and the drawing is not updated, so In order to prevent it, I decided to communicate asynchronously.
If you just want to get the value asynchronously, you may use node etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [TouchDesigner] Tips for for sentence by python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8ffa1d1d4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8ffa1d1d4/</guid>
      <description>## Nice to meet you  My name is ibuibu69 and I am making videos and music as a hobby! Until now, I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing instrumental bands with VJ using max and processing. .. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NswI72i6lCg
&amp;hellip;The band has disbanded and I want to do something new with Touch Designer. I live in Tokyo, so please make friends. ..
Now, let&amp;rsquo;s start posting the first Advent Calendar.
Main subject When trying to do difficult things with TouchDesigner, python control becomes essential.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>