<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> networkx on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/networkx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  networkx on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/networkx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice actor network analysis (using word2vec and networkx) (2/2)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/voice-actor-network-analysis-using-word2vec-and-networkx-2-2-ff265/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/voice-actor-network-analysis-using-word2vec-and-networkx-2-2-ff265/</guid>
      <description>### Rough flow of analysis introduced this time  ・Create and visualize female voice actor network ・Try clustering similar voice actors using network information. ・Visualize the categorized results with Cytoscape
Hi, this is bamboo-nova. Qiita mainly throws in material analysis.
If you are interested in my serious stories and analysis, please refer to this (evacuation site)
Bamboo shoot blog
Also, I have put the source code that summarizes the series of steps so far on Github, so please refer to it if you like!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can try it with copy and paste! Let&#39;s draw a cool network diagram with Python&#39;s networkx</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/you-can-try-it-with-copy-and-paste-lets-draw-a-cool-network-diagram-with-pythons-networkx-fe9b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/you-can-try-it-with-copy-and-paste-lets-draw-a-cool-network-diagram-with-pythons-networkx-fe9b8/</guid>
      <description>## Let&#39;s draw a network diagram with networkx that can draw a cool network diagram during winter vacation  Do you all have a good winter vacation? Our company has been taking a day off from 28th to 5th and is really thankful to the mice.
But I think engineers should refrain from Mac refugees and improve their skills at such times.
Today we will introduce a library called networkx that can draw network diagrams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>