<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> plotly on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/plotly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  plotly on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/plotly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Visualize coronavirus infection status with Plotly [For beginners]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/visualize-coronavirus-infection-status-with-plotly-for-beginners-507cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/visualize-coronavirus-infection-status-with-plotly-for-beginners-507cf/</guid>
      <description>Next time https://qiita.com/Naoya_Study/items/851f4032fb6e2a5cd5ed  With the spread of coronavirus infection, various organizations have released cool dashboards that visualize the infection status.
Example 1 WHO Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) Situation Example 2 Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare new coronavirus infection domestic case Example 3 Toyo Keizai ONLINE New Coronavirus Domestic Infection Status It is cool! I want to be able to make this myself. The goal is to create a dashboard like the one above using Python&amp;rsquo;s visualization-specific data frame Dash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introducing the potential of Plotly&#39;s scatter plots with practical examples</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introducing-the-potential-of-plotlys-scatter-plots-with-practical-examples-63646/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introducing-the-potential-of-plotlys-scatter-plots-with-practical-examples-63646/</guid>
      <description>Hello! This article is Kaggle&#39;s advent calendar,  Scatter plot of Python data visualization library &amp;ldquo;Plotly&amp;rdquo; I thought that it goes well with competitions such as Kaggle, so I would like to introduce it.
First of all, I would like to see a concrete example. Example 1 Plots the word&amp;rsquo;s distributed representation with 3D compression Example 2 Plot rental data for 23 wards of Tokyo on map data What do you think!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Summary of basic drawing method of Plotly Express, the de facto standard of Python drawing library in the Reiwa era</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-basic-drawing-method-of-plotly-express-the-de-facto-standard-of-python-drawing-library-in-the-reiwa-era-d8cbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-basic-drawing-method-of-plotly-express-the-de-facto-standard-of-python-drawing-library-in-the-reiwa-era-d8cbe/</guid>
      <description># at first  A library called Plotly Express (official site) that allows you to easily draw interactive operations based on javascript was released a while ago. I found. Since I felt a potential of a dimension that was clearly different from the static drawing that I have used so far, I have summarized the method of drawing a basic visualization method also as a memo. For reference, I am comparing it with the pattern that I wrote a similar figure in matplotlib+seaborn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>