<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poetry on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/poetry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Poetry on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/poetry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python development flow using Poetry, Git and Docker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-development-flow-using-poetry-git-and-docker-43efd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-development-flow-using-poetry-git-and-docker-43efd/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is a sister article of Python development flow using pipenv, Git and Docker I wrote earlier. Now that the development of Pipenv is not very active, I think that there will be occasions when Poetry is used in projects using Python. So I&amp;rsquo;ll try to summarize the development flow using Poetry again.
Overall flow  Installation of development environment Project initialization Docker  #Prerequisite environment
 Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python environment construction (pyenv&#43;poetry&#43;pipx)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-pyenv-poetry-pipx-85f21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-pyenv-poetry-pipx-85f21/</guid>
      <description># What&#39;s this?  macbook Python environment
 pyenv poetry pipx  It&amp;rsquo;s a memo because it was built in. The environment is mac OS 10.14.6 Mojave. I will proceed with the assumption that homebrew is already included. (If you don&amp;rsquo;t have homebrew, please refer to Homebrew official) I will update it as appropriate.
#Install Python3 Install python3 of system with homebrew. If you have already put it in, please skip it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried Poetry for the first time &amp; I was moved from Pipenv to poetry</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-poetry-for-the-first-time-i-was-moved-from-pipenv-to-poetry-0e5b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-poetry-for-the-first-time-i-was-moved-from-pipenv-to-poetry-0e5b8/</guid>
      <description>## Motivation  I recently tried poetry because the installation of pipenv is quite slow. I will summarize what I found after trying it all the way through. I&amp;rsquo;m using Pipenv, so compare it with that. Please refer to Official Doc,becauseIdon&amp;rsquo;tdescribethepackagerelatedcommands(build,publish&amp;hellip;) or detailed functions.
About Poetry Poetry is a Python package management tool. Like Pipenv, it resolves dependencies and installs and uninstalls packages, The poetry.lock file allows other users to install the package with the right version and dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a clean Python development environment with pyenv&#43;pipx&#43;Poetry</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-a-clean-python-development-environment-with-pyenv-pipx-poetry-a3f09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-a-clean-python-development-environment-with-pyenv-pipx-poetry-a3f09/</guid>
      <description>It is as this article that had been a hot topic before. …Because it becomes a worthless article, I will explain it a little.  My Python Development Environment, 2020 Edition
The author of this article uses WSL, but I can use it almost as it is in OS X environment.
pyenv  Why? I need to run multiple Python versions, isolated from the system Python.pyenv makes it easy to install, manage, and switch between those multiple Pythons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>