<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> sourcetrail on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/sourcetrail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  sourcetrail on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/sourcetrail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Story that tried Sourcetrail × macOS × VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/story-that-tried-sourcetrail-macos-vs-code-b2da7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/story-that-tried-sourcetrail-macos-vs-code-b2da7/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I will try it immediately because the code visualization tool called Sourcetrail has been made open source. It looks interesting.
What is Source Trail @ IT&amp;rsquo;s article (Sourcetrail, a code visualization tool for C++ and Python is open source)
 Sourcetrail combines features such as interactive dependency graphs, concise code views, and efficient code searching to provide source code overviews and details.
 By statically analyzing the source code and visualizing it, developers are freed from reading a huge amount of existing source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Analyze the source code of your own simple search engine written in Python with the code visualization tool SOURCE TRAIL</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/analyze-the-source-code-of-your-own-simple-search-engine-written-in-python-with-the-code-visualization-tool-source-trail-e4f81/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/analyze-the-source-code-of-your-own-simple-search-engine-written-in-python-with-the-code-visualization-tool-source-trail-e4f81/</guid>
      <description>![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17031124/69477854-9d62be00-0e2e-11ea-87d5-8d4da2481162.png)  I am a software engineer r2enofwhite,inc.Wearedoingconsultantworkcenteringonnewbusinessesatourcompany,andtheengineerteamusuallydevelopsFreecloudtypetooltodevelopnewbusinesses, From consulting to PoC development
I was searching for a tool that can interactively understand the source code in the succession of development from the PoC development phase to the operation phase, or in the operation of existing software, but I found SOURCETEAIL, so I touched it so I shared it let me try

Overview SOURCETEAIL is a tool that helps developers code productively by analyzing and visualizing source code so that developers do not spend too much time understanding source code written by others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The world changed when I opened a large Python project (Django) with Sourcetrail (Linux)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-world-changed-when-i-opened-a-large-python-project-django-with-sourcetrail-linux-410c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-world-changed-when-i-opened-a-large-python-project-django-with-sourcetrail-linux-410c3/</guid>
      <description>It seems that a tool called Sourcetrail has been released and it seems interesting, so I tried it.  There was an article you have already touched, but it is charming. Ubuntu.
I used it, and the big repository that I can think of was Django, so I will try it with a combination of Python and Django.
Install SourceTrail You can download it from Sourcetrail(GitHub) Release Page. Download 64-bit Linux tar file</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>