<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> titanic on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/titanic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  titanic on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/titanic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] First data analysis/machine learning (Kaggle)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-first-data-analysis-machine-learning-kaggle-8d77e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-first-data-analysis-machine-learning-kaggle-8d77e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  As I was about to get a job (spring break in the fourth year of university), I suddenly wanted to become a data scientist, so I started working on Kaggle for the time being.
This time, I worked on a tutorial of Kaggle&amp;quot;Titanic&amp;rdquo;.
I have experience in statistical analysis in my research, but since I do not understand machine learning at all, I decided to study with reference to the code of the incredibly excellent person!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predict Titanic survival using Kedro, a machine learning workflow management tool</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/predict-titanic-survival-using-kedro-a-machine-learning-workflow-management-tool-42067/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/predict-titanic-survival-using-kedro-a-machine-learning-workflow-management-tool-42067/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In this article, I will build a Titanic survival prediction workflow using a library called Kedro.
Recently, there are many types of machine learning workflow management tools and construction support tools. Just what I&amp;rsquo;ve heard,
 Apache Airflow luigi -gokart Dagster Metaflow DataBolt(d6t) Kedro  And so on.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare the performance of these tools through a common prediction project! That is the origin of this article.
As a common project, we chose Titanic survival prediction, which is a path that anyone should go through once they start data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaggle Tutorial Know-how in the top 2% of Titanic</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/kaggle-tutorial-know-how-in-the-top-2-of-titanic-d8a1f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/kaggle-tutorial-know-how-in-the-top-2-of-titanic-d8a1f/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  Since I started studying machine learning, I tried Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s tutorial for beginners, Titanic.
At first, I tried to play around with the feature amount on my own, referring to Japanese Web information, but even if the training data showed good accuracy, when I submitted the test data, the accuracy did not rise as expected, It was difficult to break the wall of 80% and I was in agony.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>