<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> colaboratory on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/colaboratory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  colaboratory on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/colaboratory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Memo about using Colab Pro for about 2 months (good point / bad point)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/memo-about-using-colab-pro-for-about-2-months-good-point-bad-point-c5822/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/memo-about-using-colab-pro-for-about-2-months-good-point-bad-point-c5822/</guid>
      <description># What is Google Colaboratory  A free Jupyter Notebook environment where you can write and run Python code in your browser. There are restrictions on use, but you can also use the GPU.
Colab Pro A paid version ($9.99/month) of Google Colaboratory. There are various advantages over the regular version. Currently US only (contract requires US address and credit card).
Since I live in the United States, I signed up for Colab Pro at the same time as Launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning on a gaming PC and comparing the differences in CPU/GPU performance with Colabo [Windows machine learning environment construction procedure definitive version. TF2.0 compatible]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-on-a-gaming-pc-and-comparing-the-differences-in-cpu-gpu-performance-with-colabo-windows-machine-learning-environment-construction-procedure-definitive-version.-tf2.0-compatible-b6fa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-on-a-gaming-pc-and-comparing-the-differences-in-cpu-gpu-performance-with-colabo-windows-machine-learning-environment-construction-procedure-definitive-version.-tf2.0-compatible-b6fa2/</guid>
      <description># In a nutshell  Purchase a cheap gaming PC (Windows), Enable to switch CPU/GPU in virtual environment of Anaconda, Tensorflow-Running the GPU (v2.0) code, With 4 patterns including CPU/GPU of Colaboratory, I compared the performance. I will summarize the performance comparison results and the Windows version environment construction procedure. Article.
*I often hear that GPU is effective for machine learning
 Gaming PCs have GPUs and are cheap these days  ⇒ ** Let&amp;rsquo;s use GPU of gaming PC for machine learning!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Landscape transformation by AI † Different world transformation †</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/landscape-transformation-by-ai-different-world-transformation-93d2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/landscape-transformation-by-ai-different-world-transformation-93d2c/</guid>
      <description># Introduction († horror transformation †)     Before conversion After conversion     !      Did you understand?
This uses GAN (Hostile Generation Network) to add &amp;ldquo;horror&amp;rdquo; features to photos and convert them.
Let&amp;rsquo;s leave the principle behind for now, and take a look at the possibilities of GAN!
Seasonal conversion, Aurora conversion, Fireworks conversion    Before conversion After conversion     !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The winner of the one with the highest degree of similarity to the original story in The Most Stupid Hototogisu Won&#39;t Winner</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-winner-of-the-one-with-the-highest-degree-of-similarity-to-the-original-story-in-the-most-stupid-hototogisu-wont-winner-33b69/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-winner-of-the-one-with-the-highest-degree-of-similarity-to-the-original-story-in-the-most-stupid-hototogisu-wont-winner-33b69/</guid>
      <description># Overview  A long time ago, there was a story that said, &amp;ldquo;The most stinky hottogigisu who won the championship 1&amp;rdquo;. If it&#39;s a crow, invite me to nothingness (Izanae) Totogi (Hototogisu) It&amp;rsquo;s like Growing my jet black flame, Firetogisu.
I like all the works, but it&amp;rsquo;s useless even if this kind of hand is too far from the original material, and the best taste is to keep the shape and meaning similar to the original material and to have a sense of jerk I wonder if it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyPI package for easy use of Cotoha on Google colab</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</guid>
      <description>## 2020/04/10 PyPI package has been released!  For details, see here(I&amp;rsquo;mreallyhappytohaveastar!)
If you want to use it quickly, please refer to the code below
$ pip install cotoha_at_python from cotohacall.main import cotoha_call import os os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_ID&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Your ID&amp;#39; os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_SECRET&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Ypur Secret&amp;#39; sentence =&amp;#39;API service that enables highly accurate natural language analysis of Japanese. With the COTOHA API, you can easily use the natural language analysis technology that utilizes the research results of NTT Group for over 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The result of having Mr. COTOHA summarize My memories of Mentos and Go. With COTOHA fastest tutorial</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-result-of-having-mr.-cotoha-summarize-my-memories-of-mentos-and-go.-with-cotoha-fastest-tutorial-16e67/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-result-of-having-mr.-cotoha-summarize-my-memories-of-mentos-and-go.-with-cotoha-fastest-tutorial-16e67/</guid>
      <description># Memories of Mentos and Go  Mentos has a deep feeling. At that time, I was participating in a Go club, Playing a Go stone to drop the opponent&amp;rsquo;s Go stone He was playing &amp;ldquo;shooting Go&amp;rdquo;. Heian nobles must have been entertaining, The club president, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand the naive play, went mad. According to him, the important go stone breaks, so stop it. Go stones cannot be fixed if they break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A story about trying magic tricks of live coding of natural language processing and dependency analysis with LT in an instant from an empty place</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-trying-magic-tricks-of-live-coding-of-natural-language-processing-and-dependency-analysis-with-lt-in-an-instant-from-an-empty-place-b0472/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-trying-magic-tricks-of-live-coding-of-natural-language-processing-and-dependency-analysis-with-lt-in-an-instant-from-an-empty-place-b0472/</guid>
      <description># wrap up  GiNZA, which carries out ultra-high-precision natural language processing and dependency analysis, is amazing, With Colaboratory, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to build an environment and you can use it easily with just a browser.
During the LT (Lightning Talk) in order to emphasize that crispness On-the-fly environment construction &amp;amp; natural code processing by writing code, Moreover, I tried the &amp;ldquo;magic trick&amp;rdquo; that says I can achieve high precision and high functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College students who don&#39;t want to read English papers (python)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/college-students-who-dont-want-to-read-english-papers-python-dff79/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/college-students-who-dont-want-to-read-english-papers-python-dff79/</guid>
      <description># I want to read English papers easily! !! !!  Since I am not good at English and I can&amp;rsquo;t go on to learn more, I thought there would be a way to have fun. The idea I came up with would be something like a summary and translate that English sentence&amp;hellip;
Operation confirmation environment  Windows10 Powershell (even cmd is OK) Google Colaboratory Python 3.7.3  What is Colaboratory Colaboratory is a Jupyter notebook environment that runs entirely in the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better than a horse race, a boat race, or a bicycle race? I think I found a way to win at the casino. .. .. This can go!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/better-than-a-horse-race-a-boat-race-or-a-bicycle-race-i-think-i-found-a-way-to-win-at-the-casino.-..-..-this-can-go-3a0d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/better-than-a-horse-race-a-boat-race-or-a-bicycle-race-i-think-i-found-a-way-to-win-at-the-casino.-..-..-this-can-go-3a0d1/</guid>
      <description># (Postscript) I&#39;m sorry!  The results of np.random.randint and random.randint are different, It turns out that you lose at the casino. For more information: https://qiita.com/mnoda/items/a75d350e1aa432eaf4f3
I think I&amp;rsquo;ve found a way to win at the casino (in Python). .. .. This can go! AI betting on horse racing has recently been talked about at Qiita, but I tried to program it from a different angle. I&amp;rsquo;m not a &amp;ldquo;professional&amp;rdquo; in programming, but I&amp;rsquo;m scared of making it myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First image classifier</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/first-image-classifier-a8902/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/first-image-classifier-a8902/</guid>
      <description>Hello. In my work, I&#39;m far from engineering and I can&#39;t write much by doing what I&#39;ve done,  I have a little time, so I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize what I learned a little. Advent calendar I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid! You can write an article that you just did a tutorial! That means one&amp;hellip;
Assumed readers I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a lot about machine learning, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t touched on implementation so much so I will touch on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyTorch super introduction PyTorch basics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pytorch-super-introduction-pytorch-basics-df87f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pytorch-super-introduction-pytorch-basics-df87f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This series is described as a summary of learning of PyTorch which is a machine learning framework of Python. This time, I have written a summary of the basics of PyTorch. It may be difficult to read as a reading material because I try to write down the main points rather than to convey it, but I hope you can use it to understand the points.
What is #PyTorch As I mentioned earlier, PyTorch is a Python machine learning framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a note of Google colaboratory that can use Spleeter easily.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-note-of-google-colaboratory-that-can-use-spleeter-easily.-65acd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-note-of-google-colaboratory-that-can-use-spleeter-easily.-65acd/</guid>
      <description># Where is it  Here Please use it. Since it uses a GPU, the processing speed is quite fast. The best Google that lends GPU for free! !
#How to use
If you get an error, restart the runtime and run the cells one by one from the preparation section. I think most errors will be resolved by doing so. If you get a network error when downloading, please execute the cell again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>