<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Kivy on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/kivy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Kivy on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/kivy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IOS application development with Python (kivy) that can be done by monkeys</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ios-application-development-with-python-kivy-that-can-be-done-by-monkeys-b06e7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ios-application-development-with-python-kivy-that-can-be-done-by-monkeys-b06e7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python, which is active in the field of machine learning and data science, has a simple GUI, and kivy used this time can make applications that can be run on desktop, Android, or iOS by building it.
This time, I will give a simple explanation for those who have not made an application but know Python to some extent. Not even a memorandum to yourself. ..
What is #kivy One of Python&amp;rsquo;s libraries that allows you to easily create a GUI (Graphical User Interface: not a black console screen).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to imitate Python × Kivy de Kinoppy (Kinokuniya bookstore application)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-imitate-python-kivy-de-kinoppy-kinokuniya-bookstore-application-5ecd9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-imitate-python-kivy-de-kinoppy-kinokuniya-bookstore-application-5ecd9/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 14th day of [Personal Development Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/private-development).  And Qiita&amp;rsquo;s first post. Begin.
I am creating a Windows app using a framework called Python x Kivy.
###background
 I cooked a paper book and made it into PDF. Refreshing! -Now read on your iPad -My child took an iPad&amp;hellip; -I bought a Surface! Let&amp;rsquo;s read on Surface -Unlike iPad, there is no good app for Windows -Kinoppy (Kinokuniya bookstore app) Good!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a drawing quiz with kivy&#43;PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/make-a-drawing-quiz-with-kivy-pytorch-75f1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/make-a-drawing-quiz-with-kivy-pytorch-75f1b/</guid>
      <description>#Summary  This article is the second day of Docomo Advent Calendar.
Do you know the drawing quiz? It is a quiz in which the questioner draws a picture and guesses what other people are drawing. There are many apps.
If you recognize the image drawn by the user and guess it, you can play it alone, so PyTorchofthemachinelearninglibrarywillcontinue.//pytorch.org/)andkivy, a library that can create apps, will be combined.
What is # kivy?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>