<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> PHP on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  PHP on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 IT Conference Summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2020-it-conference-summary-c4621/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2020-it-conference-summary-c4621/</guid>
      <description># IT conference to be held in 2020  This is a summary as of January 20. We will update it from time to time.
#language ##PyCon JP Python conference Dates: Scheduled for August 28th and 29th Place: Ota-ku Sangyo Plaza PiO Official site
##PHP conference PHP conference Date: October 11 Place: Ota-ku Sangyo Plaza PiO 2019 Official Site 2020 official website
##PHPerKaigi PHP conference Date: February 9th 16:30 ~ February 10, 10:00- February 11th 10:00~ Place: Nerima Ward Residents &amp;amp; Industries Plaza Coconeri Hall 2020 Official Site</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[January 2020] Reiwa, let&#39;s start the development container at full speed with VS Code&#39;s Remote Container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/january-2020-reiwa-lets-start-the-development-container-at-full-speed-with-vs-codes-remote-container-084a0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/january-2020-reiwa-lets-start-the-development-container-at-full-speed-with-vs-codes-remote-container-084a0/</guid>
      <description># Start a dash from &amp;quot;Development environment + container containing all projects&amp;quot; with Remote Conainer of VS Code! ?  Are you using VS Code Remote Conainer for development? You can use Remote SSH if you just enter an existing container, but let&amp;rsquo;s use Remote Container as a &amp;ldquo;part of local development environment&amp;rdquo;, rather as ** local development environment = Remote Container **. It&amp;rsquo;s Reiwa! ~~ (It&amp;rsquo;s been 2 years already&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to make my own research tool using API of law [Smart Roppo]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-my-own-research-tool-using-api-of-law-smart-roppo-0e434/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-my-own-research-tool-using-api-of-law-smart-roppo-0e434/</guid>
      <description>```   Introduction I made a product that looks like a legal tech Smart Roppo concept Main functions and features of SmartRoppo Why did you decide to make it yourself? Future tasks in conclusion   ##1. Introduction This article inherits the baton from Janku ([@jank_2525](https://twitter.com/jank_2525)),and&amp;quot;**[LegalAffairsAdventCalendar2019](https://adventar.org/calendars/3900)**[^1]” I am writing as an entry for the 14th day. Everybody&#39;s entry is wonderful and full of individuality, and I look very interesting every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 trends in 2020 software development</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7-trends-in-2020-software-development-4d9c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7-trends-in-2020-software-development-4d9c3/</guid>
      <description>The following is an article by Tiara Brown Neil ([hackernoon](https://hackernoon.com/@theneil248)),[7SoftwareDevelopmentTrends2020Revealed](https://hackernoon.com/software-development-trends-2020-revealed-spi305m) is a Japanese translation.  7 Software Development Trends 2020 Revealed Did you know? Over half of IT projects have failed. For many of us who are aware of the complexity and dynamic nature of the software development industry, it&amp;rsquo;s less shocking.
Keeping pace is essential to survive in this unpredictable industry with constant innovation and progress. The wise not only take advantage of software development services, but weigh the pros and cons of all technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20&#39;s Engineer Rating Check CODING-Special Study Session After Scheduled-Opening [In-house Study Session-Paiza]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/20s-engineer-rating-check-coding-special-study-session-after-scheduled-opening-in-house-study-session-paiza-0d319/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/20s-engineer-rating-check-coding-special-study-session-after-scheduled-opening-in-house-study-session-paiza-0d319/</guid>
      <description>Premise   My current affiliation is the system development department, and the department that refurbishes and maintains existing packages. We are active in a cycle of renovating and releasing our long-lived in-house package (LAMP configuration) once every two months. The members of the development department range from those with deep experience as engineers to employees who are new graduates.
In that situation, I checked the rating using Paiza, and it is a report and impression.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>