<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> introduction on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  introduction on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s do difficult things with COTOHA API-Learn by using Introduction to natural language processing-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0d5b5ccc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0d5b5ccc1/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the world of natural language processing (NLP) has continued to make remarkable progress. I think many people would like to enter the world of such natural language processing. However, even though it is generally natural language processing, the number of tasks contained in the word is enormous.  &amp;ldquo;What should I start with after all!?&amp;rdquo;
This article is to answer such a voice.
1.First of all This article aims to raise the level of &amp;ldquo;natural language processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction to Python with 100 language processing knocks</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/02d82cc1e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/02d82cc1e/</guid>
      <description>This article is for people who want to get started with natural language processing in Python, with little knowledge of C but little of Python. We are aiming for the shortest route that can solve Chapter 1 of [Language Processing 100 Knock 2015](http://www.cl.ecei.tohoku.ac.jp/nlp100/) which is famous as an introduction to natural language processing. ..  (4/8 postscript, Chapter 1 is the same for 2020 version)
This Qiita already has a lot of articles about 100 knocks, but I thought that it might be difficult for beginners to learn Python, so I wrote this article.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>