<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PostgreSQL on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/postgresql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PostgreSQL on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/postgresql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Rebuild Django development environment with Docker! ! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/rebuild-django-development-environment-with-docker-e345f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/rebuild-django-development-environment-with-docker-e345f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I wrote this article before. [Build Django development environment with Docker! (Docker-compose/Django/postgreSQL/nginx)]](https://qiita.com/nokonoko_1203/items/242367a83c313a5e46bf)
The original article was written a long time ago (a year or so?), but now that I have enough knowledge, I thought I could make it a little better, so I decided to try it!
I will not talk about installing Docker in detail, so if you are interested, please check the original article! (Here)willhelp.)
Also, as a clear difference from the previous article, Django thinks as an API delivery server and assumes Vue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create a new corona infection site map [FastAPI/PostGIS/deck.gl(React)] (Data processing)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-new-corona-infection-site-map-fastapi-postgis-deck.glreact-data-processing-579fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-new-corona-infection-site-map-fastapi-postgis-deck.glreact-data-processing-579fc/</guid>
      <description>New Corona... The spread of infection is not stopping...  I was thinking that I would like to put some data on a map and visualize it as a fledgling GIS shop, but I was afraid that most of the open data was collected in PDF format.
But! ! ! ! ! !
For non-profit purposes, sites that provide wonderful data with free data duplication, quotation, and reprint (https://gis.jag-japan.com/covid19jp/, so I would like to use this data to express it on the map!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build a Django development environment with Docker! (Docker-compose/Django/postgreSQL/nginx)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-a-django-development-environment-with-docker-docker-compose-django-postgresql-nginx-24236/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-a-django-development-environment-with-docker-docker-compose-django-postgresql-nginx-24236/</guid>
      <description>I tried rebuilding!  Rebuild Django development environment with Docker! ! ! ! 
#Introduction
Team development&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s very difficult to build an environment&amp;hellip; At that time, use Docker (miscellaneous).
This article is a repost of what I gave to qrunchLet&amp;rsquo;s build a Django/postgreSQL/gunicorn/nginx development environment using Docker and Docker-compose, which are very convenient for team development! !
The whole flow is based on almost the following sites, but I intend to make the article easy to understand, such as putting comments in almost all lines of the configuration file etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>