<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Go on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Go on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [January 2020] Reiwa, let&#39;s start the development container at full speed with VS Code&#39;s Remote Container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/january-2020-reiwa-lets-start-the-development-container-at-full-speed-with-vs-codes-remote-container-084a0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/january-2020-reiwa-lets-start-the-development-container-at-full-speed-with-vs-codes-remote-container-084a0/</guid>
      <description># Start a dash from &amp;quot;Development environment + container containing all projects&amp;quot; with Remote Conainer of VS Code! ?  Are you using VS Code Remote Conainer for development? You can use Remote SSH if you just enter an existing container, but let&amp;rsquo;s use Remote Container as a &amp;ldquo;part of local development environment&amp;rdquo;, rather as ** local development environment = Remote Container **. It&amp;rsquo;s Reiwa! ~~ (It&amp;rsquo;s been 2 years already&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Comparing basic syntax of Python and Go in an easy-to-understand manner</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/comparing-basic-syntax-of-python-and-go-in-an-easy-to-understand-manner-5263e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/comparing-basic-syntax-of-python-and-go-in-an-easy-to-understand-manner-5263e/</guid>
      <description>This article is on December 24 (Tue) of [DeNA Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/dena).  Introduction I usually use Perl, but I put together it for the purpose of learning Go and reviewing Python. Python&amp;rsquo;s grammar is very simple, so I thought it would be easier to learn Go by the difference. I&amp;rsquo;ve written as much as possible, but I think there are various shortages. Please note.
Comment First, how to write a comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Pythonista tells us, This is strange, Go language</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pythonista-tells-us-this-is-strange-go-language-84df0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pythonista-tells-us-this-is-strange-go-language-84df0/</guid>
      <description>[VISITS Advent Calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/visits) is also less than a week left.  Looking back, I found that articles in a very wide range of fields were written, and even the people inside the company were often surprised that &amp;ldquo;this person had this kind of technology.&amp;rdquo;
For me, this is the final article for the 2019 Advent Calendar!
TL; DR Some of our products implement API server in Go language.
The author, who has been familiar with Python for a long time, will write about Go language for about a month and a half, but I will write an article about Differences between Go language and Python that I found by writing it carefully at work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 20&#39;s Engineer Rating Check CODING-Special Study Session After Scheduled-Opening [In-house Study Session-Paiza]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/20s-engineer-rating-check-coding-special-study-session-after-scheduled-opening-in-house-study-session-paiza-0d319/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/20s-engineer-rating-check-coding-special-study-session-after-scheduled-opening-in-house-study-session-paiza-0d319/</guid>
      <description>Premise   My current affiliation is the system development department, and the department that refurbishes and maintains existing packages. We are active in a cycle of renovating and releasing our long-lived in-house package (LAMP configuration) once every two months. The members of the development department range from those with deep experience as engineers to employees who are new graduates.
In that situation, I checked the rating using Paiza, and it is a report and impression.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>