<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> physics on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/physics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  physics on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/physics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Fluid visualization BOS method at home to see invisible things</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b8250a370/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b8250a370/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Transparent gas is invisible to the naked eye. Still, there are times when I want to see. Fluid visualization technologies such as the schlieren method and shadowgraph method are useful in this regard. This time I will try to visualize this fluid at home. Basically, you only have to prepare the camera.
References I experimented with this as a reference. We recommend reading this page for detailed theory. Improvement of visualization method of density gradient based on BOS method</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] X-ray diffraction simulation with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/def7848f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/def7848f9/</guid>
      <description>It’s!  Hello. This is my second post. This time I tried to simulate X-ray diffraction with Python. The full code (I use Jupyter Notebook) is GitHub1
#X-Ray Diffraction (XRD) X-ray diffraction is a phenomenon in which X-rays are diffracted in a crystal. X-rays are electromagnetic waves with wavelengths within a certain range (about 1 nm to 1 pm), and diffraction is the propagation of something that has the properties of waves around obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>