<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Network on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Network on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simple network operation by linking Cisco DNA Center and Tact Switch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/6cc65e6d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/6cc65e6d1/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the eighth day of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by volunteers from Cisco.
 2017 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco  What do you want to do?  Network operation that anyone can do Cisco&amp;rsquo;s best-selling controller for Cisco DNA Center ~~ Stema ~~ Tips demo Balancing work and material Common cool topics ~~ Policy, AI or Assurance ~ ~, but rather quiet operation that is often heard Reuse of goods bought in 2017  What is this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to automatically generate a port management table from Config of L2SW</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/75ec526ff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/75ec526ff/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In the previous article, I introduced an example of automatically generating Config from the port management table. I tried to automatically generate L2SW Config from the port management table + parameter table + Jinja2 template
In some cases, you may want to create a port management table from the already created Config. This time, using a Python parser library called TTP (Template Text Parser), I automatically generated a CSV format port management table from the L2SW Config file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Execute commands by automatically detecting the type of network device with netmiko</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/feff470e0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/feff470e0/</guid>
      <description>What is #netmiko  netmiko is a Python library that helps you login and operate network devices with SSH. Currently, it supports Cisco IOS, Juniper JunOS, Palo Alto PAN-OS, etc. Login, configuration mode transition, logout, etc. are abstracted as methods, and each command is a type of library that directly specifies a command. This is less abstract than NAPALM. It can be installed with pip intall netmiko etc.
  GitHub repository   ktbyers/netmiko: Multi-vendor library to simplify Paramiko SSH connections to network devices</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>