<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> COVID-19 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/covid-19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  COVID-19 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction to infectious disease model] All over Japan is ending...♬</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/bc4079546/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/bc4079546/</guid>
      <description>Today, it is announced that the extension of the emergency declaration will be announced, but for the time being, I would like to suppress the current situation nationwide.  Last time, we predicted the peak number of infections based on the SIR model, but this time we would like to use the SIHR model to predict the termination. .. This article is also written by an amateur, so please handle the contents at your own risk The SIHR model is an extension of the SIR model in order to reproduce the delay in the healing number, and is as follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If Tokyo citizens become severely ill with the new coronavirus, they may be taken to a hospital in Kagoshima prefecture.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b639177f0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b639177f0/</guid>
      <description>#table of contents  Introduction Current status of medical collapse risk Whether or not to secure beds for severely ill persons Severely ill transport model Delivery destination of severely ill Conclusion
#Introduction
 Background Infectious disease designated medical institutions are tight, and it is extremely difficult to secure sufficient beds to accommodate severely ill persons. In various places, measures have been taken to treat patients with mild illness at hotels, homes, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simple simulation of virus infection</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/993638570/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/993638570/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  The following article was published in the Washington Post of March 14, 2020.
 ***Why outbreaks like coronavirus spread exponentially, and how to “flatten the curve”***
https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2020/world/corona-simulator/  The Japanese version is below.
*** Why outbreaks such as coronaviruses can grow so fast and how to &amp;ldquo;flatten the curve&amp;rdquo; ***
https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2020/health/corona-simulation-japanese/
Using the simple principle of contact between balls, In an article that introduced how the number of people infected with the virus will increase and decrease, I think it was very easy to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Introduction to SIR Model] COVID-19 data fitting to predict the end of life in each country ♬</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2bcc7f3c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2bcc7f3c2/</guid>
      <description>In the previous SEIR model, values such as $lp \fallingdotseq 1e^{-23}$ were obtained among the obtained parameters. In such a case, be careful because the digit cancellation or the differential equation may not work in the first place.  So, this time, I will change this part and try fitting with the simplest model.
what you did ・A little theory ・Code explanation ・End of Japan ・End of each country ・A little discussion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s calculate the transition of basic reproduction number of new coronavirus by prefecture</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e68b34b60/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e68b34b60/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The center of infection with the new coronavirus infectious disease (COVID-19) is already shifting from mainland China to Europe and the United States, and urgent situations such as restricting free border movement within the EU region and issuing curfew It&amp;rsquo;s happening. In Japan, the threat of the new coronavirus began to be recognized on February 3, 2020, when the Diamond Princess entered Yokohama Port, on February 25, when the government announced its basic policy, and on February 28, in Hokkaido.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is the New Corona really a threat? Verified with Stan (was)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/894dd3b5c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/894dd3b5c/</guid>
      <description>[Notice] [Sequel](https://qiita.com/akeyhero/items/a8aa2d3db2c32c867ff6) is used to determine the lethality rate of COVID-19.  Purpose  Verify if COVID-19&amp;rsquo;s lethality is really high Try the stochastic programming language Stan  What is a probabilistic programming language? It is a programming language that solves nicely by describing statistical relationships (models). As an implementation, it seems to sample by Markov chain Monte Carlo method.
It is not a replacement for the procedural programming language because it has a completely different role and method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understanding by Bayes&#39; theorem Significance of narrowing down the target of PCR test for new coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ee345ba45/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ee345ba45/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The number of people infected with the novel coronavirus infection (COVID-19) spread from China to the world, and as of March 14, 2020, the number of infected people was 145,637 and 5,436 dead, which is a very high number. However, looking at the situation in Japan, the number of infected people was 734, 9.1% of Korea&amp;rsquo;s 8086 and 4.2% of Italy&amp;rsquo;s 17,660. It has been pointed out that the reason for this apparent difference is that Japan is limiting the number of PCR tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] COVID-19 Hokkaido Data Edition (2) Toward Open Data &#43; Automatic Update</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8f0768708/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8f0768708/</guid>
      <description>## Table of contents  COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition (1) Initial data creation by scraping etc. COVID-19 Hokkaido Data Edition (2) To open data + automatic update ←This article! COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition ③ Fully automated
![Screenshot 2020-03-10 17.37.10.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/73197/cfee968c-cffb-cc29-67c0-(76b076fa30cd.png)
In ①, we have summarized V0 in the above figure, but this article will summarize the use of external APIs such as open data portal.
Issues with V0 In V0, data acquisition relied on (1) scraping from the road website and (2) static CSV files provided by Sapporo City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] COVID-19 Hokkaido Data Edition (1) Initial data creation by scraping</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b47984fbf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b47984fbf/</guid>
      <description>## Table of contents  COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition (1) Initial data creation by scraping etc. ←This article! COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition ②Open data + automatic update COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition ③ Fully automated
![Screenshot 2020-03-10 17.25.46.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/73197/db6e9de7-3071-9836-9aba-(be5d04c240d3.png)
Introduction Tokyo official corona virus protection sitewasreleasedbyTokyoandCodeforJapan,anditssourcecodewasreleasedonGitHubunderMITlicense&amp;hellip;Inotherwords,eveninotherprefectures,youcancreateawebapplicationthatvisualizesinthesameway(ifyoucanpreparesimilardata)(althoughyouactuallyneedserverresourcesetc.). This is a groundbreaking initiative.
Well, that&amp;rsquo;s why the movements around the country have become more active, and in Hokkaido, volunteers with diverse backgrounds such as Code for Sapporo, IT companies in Hokkaido, and local government employees JUST Road IT was formed, and a project that was forked from Tokyo on March 6 was released at noon on March 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Hypothesis of why the new coronavirus is not so many infected in urban areas such as Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/72286382b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/72286382b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  If you check the transition of the number of people infected with the new coronavirus infectious disease (COVID-19) with Map of new coronavirus infected people by prefecture, etc. As of March 7, 2020, there are 98 people in Hokkaido, 21 people in Sagamihara City, etc., while there are a considerable number of people locally, 73 people in Tokyo, 41 people in Osaka, 8 people in Kyoto and 8 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The SEIR model was used to predict the behavior of the new coronavirus.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ed28fb723/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ed28fb723/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  The number of new corona pneumonia (Covid-19) that occurred in Wuhan, Hubei Province, China in December 2019 is increasing in Japan. Understanding how infectious diseases such as influenza, AIDS, and SARS spread through human populations through the process of confirming the effects of health policies such as setting vaccinations and isolation of infected persons. Is also important. In the previous article, I explained the SIR model, but I will introduce the SEIR model that considers the latency of infectious diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction of infectious disease mathematical prediction model (SIR model)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3078f4095/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3078f4095/</guid>
      <description>#1. At the beginning  The number of people infected with the new coronavirus (Convid-19) in Wuhan, China in December 2019 in Japan is increasing. Understanding how wrestling infectious diseases such as influenza, AIDS, and SARS spread in human populations is essential to confirm the effects of health policies such as setting vaccinations and isolating infected people. Is also important. Here, we will introduce the SIR model, which is the basis of the infectious disease mathematical prediction model, and the process of calculating this model in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>