<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> RaspberryPi on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/raspberrypi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  RaspberryPi on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/raspberrypi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] RaspberryPi sensor sample file distribution URL summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/raspberrypi-sensor-sample-file-distribution-url-summary-c0e65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/raspberrypi-sensor-sample-file-distribution-url-summary-c0e65/</guid>
      <description>#RaspberryPi sensor sample file distribution URL summary  The company that sells the sensors collectively records the sample files on a CD and sells them as a set, but I summarized the companies that publish the files on the Web.
##OSOYOO OSOYOO Raspberry Pi Learn electronic work kit Beginners&amp;rsquo; practice parts set Rasppie 11 actual example Circuit wiring diagram and sample sketch programming Raspberry Pi super introduction starter learning kit LED control switch I2C LCD temperature/humidity sensor micro servo human sensor A/D converter Buzzer Atmospheric pressure sensor Relay module control Infrared remote control etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Raspberry Pi] Stepping motor control with Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/raspberry-pi-stepping-motor-control-with-raspberry-pi-0c7f6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/raspberry-pi-stepping-motor-control-with-raspberry-pi-0c7f6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I bought a Razz pie, thinking that I might find a new hobby indoors during lockdown. I wondered if it would be useful for experiments later if I could control the motor, so I bought a stepper motor together, so I will control it. It is interesting just to rotate it at a constant speed, but the goal was to be able to do arbitrary movements. I started from almost zero knowledge of electric and electronic circuits, but it was easy to do because various information was dropped on the net.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] With VS Code&#39;s SSH connection function, edit and debug the code in Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/with-vs-codes-ssh-connection-function-edit-and-debug-the-code-in-raspberry-pi-26ab9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/with-vs-codes-ssh-connection-function-edit-and-debug-the-code-in-raspberry-pi-26ab9/</guid>
      <description>What is #VSCode?  Abbreviation for source code editor &amp;ldquo;Visual Studio Code&amp;rdquo; developed by Microsoft. As a free, lightweight, and multifunctional editor, it is rapidly gaining popularity.
From 2019/10 edition, SSH connection function to RaspberryPi (ARM v8) is officially supported, so I wrote the result of trying remote editing of Python code in Raspberry Pi.
** In conclusion, we were able to achieve debugging with breakpoints and a comfortable remote development environment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Making an autonomous driving robot car with Raspberry Pi3 B&#43; and ultrasonic distance sensor HC-SR04</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/making-an-autonomous-driving-robot-car-with-raspberry-pi3-b-and-ultrasonic-distance-sensor-hc-sr04-64cec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/making-an-autonomous-driving-robot-car-with-raspberry-pi3-b-and-ultrasonic-distance-sensor-hc-sr04-64cec/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The elements that make up a self-driving car in the real world are vehicle position estimation, object recognition, action judgment, and vehicle body control. It is possible to implement all four of these elements on the basis of radio control, but it is not easy to easily estimate the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s position, and this time the target is low-speed driving, so there is almost no need for body control. Therefore, this time, I would like to use an ultrasonic distance sensor to recognize an object in front of me and make a simple action decision to avoid it with a radio-controlled robot car that operates automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deep learning of Raspberry Pi 3 B&#43; &amp; PyTorch for real-time classification of multiple objects in camera images</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-of-raspberry-pi-3-b-pytorch-for-real-time-classification-of-multiple-objects-in-camera-images-a09b4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-of-raspberry-pi-3-b-pytorch-for-real-time-classification-of-multiple-objects-in-camera-images-a09b4/</guid>
      <description>I got Razpai 3B+ and picamera because of university class. Since I&#39;m free, I decided to let Razpai classify using deep learning. However, instead of classifying the pictures taken in advance, it classifies the objects in the real-time image from picamera and displays them in a nice way.  It may be at the student level, but I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it if you can refer to even a part of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction to electronic paper module</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-electronic-paper-module-04162/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-electronic-paper-module-04162/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Combining ready-made products in the shortest possible time, The purpose is to create a prototype that allows you to customize the content displayed on the electronic paper. It&amp;rsquo;s just a prototype, so I don&amp;rsquo;t think about costs or operation costs.
Things to prepare Raspberry Pi WH Zero WH 1 A similar product is the Raspberry Pi Zero W. Raspberry Pi Zero WH is a model with pin header mounted on Raspberry Pi Zero W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Machine learning with Raspberry Pi 4 and Coral USB Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-with-raspberry-pi-4-and-coral-usb-accelerator-12aff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/machine-learning-with-raspberry-pi-4-and-coral-usb-accelerator-12aff/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article summarizes the installation procedure of Raspberry Pi 4 and Coral USB Accelerator as a method of machine learning with edge device.
Raspberry Pi 4 is the latest generation of the current model. The CPU and memory performance have been greatly improved, and USB 3.0 is also supported.
Coral USB Accelerator is Google&amp;rsquo;s dedicated ASIC developed by Google for machine learning on edge devices.
This dedicated ASIC is called Edge TPU, and you can use TensorFlow Lite&amp;rsquo;s flake work specialized for inference at the edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Insert ROS melodic into Raspberry Pi 4/Buster</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/insert-ros-melodic-into-raspberry-pi-4-buster-063d9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/insert-ros-melodic-into-raspberry-pi-4-buster-063d9/</guid>
      <description>![SS 192.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/565043/a41cd967-f549-8677-1efa-2e99bf69518d.png) First post on Qiita To do. I&#39;m Ninagawa_Izumi. Hope it helps.  ##things to do Let&amp;rsquo;s make ROS melodic work with Raster Pi 4 Buster. While referring to various places, I tried to write it in a way that is OK if you continue to type shell commands. I&amp;rsquo;m sure anyone can introduce the latest ROS environment as of January 2020.
What is ROS? An open source platform aimed at promoting joint development of robot software on a global scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simulate temperature measurement with Raspberry Pi &#43; Flask &#43; SQLite &#43; Ajax</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simulate-temperature-measurement-with-raspberry-pi-flask-sqlite-ajax-f3530/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simulate-temperature-measurement-with-raspberry-pi-flask-sqlite-ajax-f3530/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is convenient to be able to debug with software alone when measuring temperature with Raspberry Pi and acquiring sensor status with GPIO. Therefore, we created a debug environment that simulates temperature measurement and acquisition of sensor status with GPIO, and displays it on a website (created with Flask). Save the simulated temperature and sensor state in SQLite and refresh the page via Ajax. The temperature and sensor values are hard to understand, so it looks as if the living room temperature and sensor had changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I couldn&#39;t escape from the futon, so I made a fully automatic futon peeler.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-couldnt-escape-from-the-futon-so-i-made-a-fully-automatic-futon-peeler.-bef57/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-couldnt-escape-from-the-futon-so-i-made-a-fully-automatic-futon-peeler.-bef57/</guid>
      <description># Overview  It is known that escaping from the futon by itself on a cold winter morning is accompanied by a great deal of mental distress, and a decline in activity in the morning in the winter brings a great loss to the Japanese economy. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is the case, but for the time being, if I leave home early in the morning, my graduation will be jeopardized, so I decided to take measures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Raspai? What? Level of hardware inexperienced I made a system to understand if there are people in the office</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/raspai-what-level-of-hardware-inexperienced-i-made-a-system-to-understand-if-there-are-people-in-the-office-8c747/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/raspai-what-level-of-hardware-inexperienced-i-made-a-system-to-understand-if-there-are-people-in-the-office-8c747/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hello. I am currently working as an intern at an IT company while being a university student in Nagoya.
However, when I spend most of my time, I want to work and work on days other than the default workday. After taking a lecture at university, go to work. On such a day, I come to work around 6pm and work until there are no more employees (the office is closed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Christmas Classic (?) Lighting a Christmas Tree with Raspberry Pi and Philips Hue</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/christmas-classic-lighting-a-christmas-tree-with-raspberry-pi-and-philips-hue-67701/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/christmas-classic-lighting-a-christmas-tree-with-raspberry-pi-and-philips-hue-67701/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; This article is the 25th day article of [North Detail Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/northdetail).   2020/04/02 Addendum This article is also posted on the NorthDetail blog. https://www.northdetail.co.jp/blog/455/
 Merry Christmas! Advent Calendar is Christmas on the last day, and Speaking of Christmas, it&amp;rsquo;s Razpai!
So, at the end of North Detail Advent Calendar 2019, I would like to make a mechanism to control the lights that illuminate the Christmas tree with Raspberry Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s make a cycle computer with Raspberry Pi Zero (W, WH)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-make-a-cycle-computer-with-raspberry-pi-zero-w-wh-46619/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-make-a-cycle-computer-with-raspberry-pi-zero-w-wh-46619/</guid>
      <description>github repository is here  https://github.com/hishizuka/pizero_bikecomputer
(2020/4/30) The article structure was reviewed and the &amp;ldquo;latest update&amp;rdquo; was added to the original article &amp;ldquo;[The story that when I made a cycle computer with Gachi, I was able to make it fairly]&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita .com/hishi/items/8f77fd4655027fac7c7d)”.
It will be the 22nd day of Road Bike Advent Calendar 2019. This is a technically unusual post, but I would appreciate your favor.
The author has been working on making a cycle computer from scratch for several years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Since IBM MAX supports ARM, it runs on Raspberry Pi.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/since-ibm-max-supports-arm-it-runs-on-raspberry-pi.-93f30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/since-ibm-max-supports-arm-it-runs-on-raspberry-pi.-93f30/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  Do you know IBM MAX? It is provided by IBM and you can use the service that can connect the deep-learned model with REST API as a container compatible with Docker. It can also be called from Node-RED. From around November 2019, it became compatible with IoT devices equipped with ARM CPUs including Raspberry Pi, embedded devices, and PCs equipped with ARM CPU, so in this article, I will use IBM MAX with Raspberry Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Observing Gemini meteor shower with RaspberryPi4</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/observing-gemini-meteor-shower-with-raspberrypi4-9efed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/observing-gemini-meteor-shower-with-raspberrypi4-9efed/</guid>
      <description># Overview  I have purchased Raspberry Pi 4, so I will talk about making a shooting star radio observation system with Raspberry Pi. Also, since 12/12~15 is the Gemini meteor shower every year, I tried to see if I could actually observe it.
It will be a long story because it will be explained from the principle.
#Observation principle A shooting star appears when dust floating in the universe plunges into the Earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere, collides violently, and emits plasma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The story that the guards were confined when the laboratory became IoT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-story-that-the-guards-were-confined-when-the-laboratory-became-iot-b623c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-story-that-the-guards-were-confined-when-the-laboratory-became-iot-b623c/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 20th day of Retty Advent Calendar 2019.  Yesterday, Mr. Hirano&amp;rsquo;s “Retty Data Analysis Team-Review of the 2nd year after launch ~Data platform/data democratization/statistical model~”.
Nice to meet you. My name is Koda and I&amp;rsquo;m currently an intern at Retty as a 20-year-old engineer.
For the time being, I was wondering what to write after registering for participation, but I made my own entry/exit management system (electronic lock) that is used in the laboratory of the university I am attending, so I will talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simple network operation by linking Cisco DNA Center and Tact Switch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simple-network-operation-by-linking-cisco-dna-center-and-tact-switch-6cc65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simple-network-operation-by-linking-cisco-dna-center-and-tact-switch-6cc65/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the eighth day of Cisco Systems Japan Advent Calendar 2019 by volunteers from Cisco.
 2017 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2017/cisco 2018 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2018/cisco 2019 version: https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/cisco  What do you want to do?  Network operation that anyone can do Cisco&amp;rsquo;s best-selling controller for Cisco DNA Center ~~ Stema ~~ Tips demo Balancing work and material Common cool topics ~~ Policy, AI or Assurance ~ ~, but rather quiet operation that is often heard Reuse of goods bought in 2017  What is this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/raspberry-pi-863fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/raspberry-pi-863fe/</guid>
      <description>#00 Introduction  *This article is the 7th day of Kinki University Advent Calendar 2019. *Basically, it is written for college students.
 This time, I will write on the assumption that RaspberryPi ZeroW which is cheap and suitable for trying is used, but you can do it with the same procedure for other RaspberryPi. *I rushed into some of the guys who were carrying a classmate who loves JavaScript. Gomenne  By the way, haven&amp;rsquo;t you heard of RaspberryPi?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I got an error when I put opencv in python3 with Raspberry [Workaround]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-got-an-error-when-i-put-opencv-in-python3-with-raspberry-workaround-48463/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-got-an-error-when-i-put-opencv-in-python3-with-raspberry-workaround-48463/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&#39;t install and uninstall opencv well, so I was able to install it somehow, so I will write the history.  Error situation pi@raspberrypi:~ $python3 Python 3.7.3 (default, Apr 3 2019, 05:39:12) [GCC 8.2.0] on linux Type &amp;quot;help&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;credits&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;license&amp;quot; for more information. &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; import cv2 Traceback (most recent call last): File &amp;quot;&amp;lt;stdin&amp;gt;&amp;quot;, line 1, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; File &amp;quot;/home/pi/cv2/__init__.py&amp;quot;, line 3, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; from .cv2 import * ImportError: /home/pi/cv2/cv2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to be notified of the connection environment when the RaspberryPi connects to the network</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-be-notified-of-the-connection-environment-when-the-raspberrypi-connects-to-the-network-ffadd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-want-to-be-notified-of-the-connection-environment-when-the-raspberrypi-connects-to-the-network-ffadd/</guid>
      <description>I bought a Raspberry Pi 4. So I put ArchLinux in the SD card.  This time, I do not buy LEDs separately, but it will be operated in a bare state, but there is one problem,
** Checking where is connected is troublesome **
Basically, DHCP is used and there is no monitor, so it is troublesome to check the IP address whether it is a wired connection or a wireless connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Handling GPS with Raspberry Pi 3 Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/handling-gps-with-raspberry-pi-3-python-fff54/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/handling-gps-with-raspberry-pi-3-python-fff54/</guid>
      <description>This is a memo of GPS module in Raspberry Pi 3 Python. The OS version of Raspberry Pi 3 is  Raspbian GNU/Linux 8.0 (jessie) Raspbian GNU/Linux 9.4 (stretch) (Corrected on October 5, 2018)
is. GPS module For the GPS module, I used Akizuki Denshi&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;[GPS receiver kit 1PPS output with &amp;ldquo;Michibiki&amp;rdquo; compatible]&amp;rdquo; (http://akizukidenshi.com/catalog/g/gK-09991/)&amp;quot;.
This GPS module sends out the received GPS data serially. There are two methods for serial communication with Raspberry Pi3: using a USB port and using a GPIO pin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Read FeliCa IDm with raspberrypi3 (pasori RC-S380 version)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/read-felica-idm-with-raspberrypi3-pasori-rc-s380-version-f735b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/read-felica-idm-with-raspberrypi3-pasori-rc-s380-version-f735b/</guid>
      <description>Click here to read FeliCa IDm on pasori RC-S320 (http://qiita.com/t114/items/819a9cdfe90ea98dd4d3)  Basically it is exactly what is written in Official of nfcpy It was.
#Environment Hard: raspberrypi3 OS: raspbian Leader: pasori RC-S380
#nfcpy installation In the case of nfcpy version 0.10, IDm could not be read well when reading FeliCa of Osaifu-Keitai or license, so 0.9 is installed below.
$ sudo apt-get install python-usb $ sudo apt-get install bzr $ mkdir nfcpy $ cd nfcpy $ bzr branch lp:nfcpy/0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>