<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> OpenAPI on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/openapi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  OpenAPI on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/openapi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying to make a typed web application with Python&#39;s web framework ``FastAPI&#39;&#39; and TypeScriptOpenAPI-technology stack for machine learning webapp</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/trying-to-make-a-typed-web-application-with-pythons-web-framework-fastapi-and-typescriptopenapi-technology-stack-for-machine-learning-webapp-9278f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/trying-to-make-a-typed-web-application-with-pythons-web-framework-fastapi-and-typescriptopenapi-technology-stack-for-machine-learning-webapp-9278f/</guid>
      <description># Intro  Introducing FastAPI+TypeScript+OpenAPI as a technology stack for creating web applications with machine learning and image processing implemented in Python as the back end.
#Motivation
 I want to set up a web server (API server) quickly with Python -Uses like using Flask until now &amp;ldquo;In Python&amp;rdquo; -Because it is a machine learning / image processing service &amp;ldquo;Crispy&amp;rdquo; -I want to enjoy validation I want type assurance for both server and client -Machine learning and image processing apps tend to have many parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema-driven development with Responder: Try displaying Swagger UI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/schema-driven-development-with-responder-try-displaying-swagger-ui-6ad57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/schema-driven-development-with-responder-try-displaying-swagger-ui-6ad57/</guid>
      <description>#What is Schema Driven Development  Simply put, it is a development method that first decides the schema of API (definition of request and response types and field names), systematically generates documents and mocks accordingly, and then implements the internal implementation. (Reference: Schema Driven Development Optimization &amp;amp; Implementation Example for Optimizing Team Web API Development)
I would like to try schema driven development with responder which is a python web framework.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>