<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> iOS on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/ios/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  iOS on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/ios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [IOS] First Pyto</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e1172d250/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e1172d250/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I think Pythonista is the most famous Python environment for iOS. Personally Pythonista
 It has not been updated for more than 2 years (as of 2020/2/24) (Added 2020/3/9: Pythonista v3.3 was released) There are few supported libraries (Pandas cannot be used)  That was the reason why I was postponed from purchasing. One day, an application called &amp;ldquo;Pyto&amp;rdquo; was introduced in Nikkei Software, and when I searched it, the following points were attractive compared to Pythonista, so I purchased it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let Siri do the job of reading AWS bills posted by Slackbot</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d85fda007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d85fda007/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the iPhone for less than a decade and I noticed that Siri wasn&amp;rsquo;t working at all. Now that smart speakers are popular, I want my Siri to do more, so I decided to read the AWS bill posted by Slackbot.
From the results, it looks like this. When you ask for the price&amp;hellip; He read the content I posted to Slack. Then, I will introduce various ways to make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] IOS application development with Python (kivy) that can be done by monkeys</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b06e76cf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b06e76cf2/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python, which is active in the field of machine learning and data science, has a simple GUI, and kivy used this time can make applications that can be run on desktop, Android, or iOS by building it.
This time, I will give a simple explanation for those who have not made an application but know Python to some extent. Not even a memorandum to yourself. ..
What is #kivy One of Python&amp;rsquo;s libraries that allows you to easily create a GUI (Graphical User Interface: not a black console screen).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Looking Back on iOS&#39;Healthcare App&#39; 2019</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0a3ccb3c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0a3ccb3c6/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 9th day of the Docomo Advent Calendar.  It is Yamamoto of DoCoMo. In my work, I am engaged in R&amp;amp;D related to healthcare. In this article, we will introduce how to utilize the data acquired by the iPhone Healthcare App.
■ Introduction □ Target person ・I am interested in healthcare using mobile wearable devices ・I would like to see the data of the iOS healthcare app ・Those who have reached this article</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Send push notification to iOS app with Python 2 (with sample code)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f8c995462/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f8c995462/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Last time I wrote a similar article, I wrote it without experimenting and when I tried it, it didn&amp;rsquo;t work, so I&amp;rsquo;ll write the article again, including corrections!
Send push notifications to iOS apps with Python
Environment  Python 2.7.11 pip 8.1.2 apns==2.0.1  Environmental configuration Install apns with pip after building a virtual environment with Virtualenv
$ pip install apns Preparation Write out a pem file that sends push notifications from the keychain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>