<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ansible on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/ansible/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ansible on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/ansible/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Summary because I used Ansible&#39;s Vmware system module</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/4276985a6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/4276985a6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There was a case where I wanted to make a guest VM of Vmware with Ansible like the title and want to use it in various ways, so I tried it with the opportunity. By the way, I thought it would be convenient to use Dynamic Inventory, so I tried it.
Operation verification environment  Vmware side -VMware vCenter Server Appliance, 6.7.0, 42000 -VMware ESXi, 6.7.0, 13006603 Client (Ansible execution environment) side -OS: CentOS 7 -I also tried using python:latest of Docker -Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What I&#39;ve done to welcome the Python 2 EOL with confidence</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/77fe76859/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/77fe76859/</guid>
      <description>## Self-introduction  I am @yukin01 who is an SRE on the SRE/QA team. I used to use iOS and Firebase/GCP to develop applications until half a year ago, but now that I want to strengthen the infrastructure, I am using AWS and GCP as an SRE at GLOBIS.
Python2 EOL As you know, Python2 is announced to end support on January 1, 2020, but if you have any products or tools that are still dependent on Python2, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to get rid of them by EOL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Ansible Environment Construction For Mac</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f8aa97591/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f8aa97591/</guid>
      <description># Ansible 2.0 environment construction  Index ####1. Installation method ver.Mac ####2. Installation method ver. Client side
Output result list 1. How to install ####1. Delete the existing ansible
brew uninstall ansible --force ####2.pyenv-virtualenv installation ・Pyenv Switch between installing multiple versions of Python ・Pyenv-virtualenv Plugin of pyenv that can switch multiple environments with the same version of Python
brew install pyenv-virtualenv pyenv versions ####3.Python installation + Ansible2 environment creation
xcode-select --install # Command Line Tools installation pyenv install 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Ansible infrastructure automation tool for those who are not good at Ruby</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fcc83b23d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fcc83b23d/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I think I can start learning Ruby with Ruby, but I think it would be nice to be able to write the same thing in python. Nowadays, in the shadow of chef, which is famous as an infrastructure automation tool, automation tools using python I heard it was there and tried using it immediately. Here we will introduce the procedure to start a remote environment with vagrant and set up the remote machine with ansible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>