<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kdd2019 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/kdd2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kdd2019 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/kdd2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of research proposal that won first place at KDDCUP 2019 and adoption</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-research-proposal-that-won-first-place-at-kddcup-2019-and-adoption-09557/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-research-proposal-that-won-first-place-at-kddcup-2019-and-adoption-09557/</guid>
      <description>It is Docomo&#39;s Ochiai. In this article, we will introduce the [^1] initiative that won the 1st division of [KDD Cup](https://www.kdd.org/kdd2019/kdd-cup), a competition for data analysis held at KDD2019. I will.  KDD Cup 2019 Overview The outline of KDD was introduced in previous article, so focus on KDD Cup here. I will explain. The KDD Cup is a data science competition attached to the KDD and has a tradition of first being 1997 and more than 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I analyzed the data of the soccer FIFA World Cup Russia tournament with soccer action</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-analyzed-the-data-of-the-soccer-fifa-world-cup-russia-tournament-with-soccer-action-7a5c9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-analyzed-the-data-of-the-soccer-fifa-world-cup-russia-tournament-with-soccer-action-7a5c9/</guid>
      <description>**This is the 18th day article of ADVENT CALENDER of NTT DOCOMO Service Innovation Department. **  Hello! This is Osugi from NTT DoCoMo.
I spent soccer and futsal when I was a student, and now I am doing marketing related data analysis.
Today, I&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce socceraction, a python package for soccer, by analyzing the game data from the 2018 FIFA World Cup Russia tournament.
#Introduction socceraction is featured in the KDD2019 Appried Data Sciense Track Best Paper Award ”Actions Speak Louder than Goals: Valuing Player Actions in Soccer” [^1].</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>