<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> JavaScript on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  JavaScript on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Hospitable animal shogi AI was born! A story of making a hospitality entertaining AI.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hospitable-animal-shogi-ai-was-born-a-story-of-making-a-hospitality-entertaining-ai.-5989e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hospitable-animal-shogi-ai-was-born-a-story-of-making-a-hospitality-entertaining-ai.-5989e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since AI became stronger than professional shogi players.
On the other hand, Professor Zenji Hanyu** &amp;ldquo;** Things like entertaining shogi are difficult for AI**,&amp;rdquo; he said.
Then, what kind of point is difficult when actually trying to make entertainment AI, What level of &amp;ldquo;entertainment&amp;rdquo; can we do?
This is a development diary record of the difficult challenge of &amp;ldquo;entertainment shogi&amp;rdquo;. It is a story up to the idea of the entertainment AI obtained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Simple simulation of virus infection</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/simple-simulation-of-virus-infection-99363/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/simple-simulation-of-virus-infection-99363/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  The following article was published in the Washington Post of March 14, 2020.
 ***Why outbreaks like coronavirus spread exponentially, and how to “flatten the curve”***
https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2020/world/corona-simulator/  The Japanese version is below.
*** Why outbreaks such as coronaviruses can grow so fast and how to &amp;ldquo;flatten the curve&amp;rdquo; ***
https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2020/health/corona-simulation-japanese/
Using the simple principle of contact between balls, In an article that introduced how the number of people infected with the virus will increase and decrease, I think it was very easy to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Released a web service for handwriting scoring using DeepLearning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/released-a-web-service-for-handwriting-scoring-using-deeplearning-2cf76/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/released-a-web-service-for-handwriting-scoring-using-deeplearning-2cf76/</guid>
      <description>As a hobby, I personally developed a web service that AI automatically marks the readability of characters when I write them in a browser, and released it about 2 weeks ago: relaxed:  []((https://letters.choo.works/) Letters-AI handwriting scoring app
The core technology is front-end implementation with DeepLearning image recognition and Preact. In this article, we will describe Service outline, technical details, and impressions regarding the developed application.
Service overview Function introduction Since it has a small number of pages and is lightweight, it is probably faster to see the application regarding the function, but I will explain the function including an overview of the technology used with screenshots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The end of the programming beginner who wrote the code with the motivation to bring about the result rather than the technical viewpoint of programming (my pattern)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-end-of-the-programming-beginner-who-wrote-the-code-with-the-motivation-to-bring-about-the-result-rather-than-the-technical-viewpoint-of-programming-my-pattern-bc040/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-end-of-the-programming-beginner-who-wrote-the-code-with-the-motivation-to-bring-about-the-result-rather-than-the-technical-viewpoint-of-programming-my-pattern-bc040/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Introduction&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;  First of all, the target audience for this article is &amp;ldquo;non-engineers&amp;rdquo;.
As a non-engineer, I am aiming to acquire programming skills and explain what I did in the process.
By the way, I am not studying as a programmer now, and I am still studying, and since I was writing an article in the course of studying in the first place, the teacher who was suddenly made an adviser of the Kabaddi club decided the rules of the sport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Script language KINX (Introduction)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/script-language-kinx-introduction-ca08b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/script-language-kinx-introduction-ca08b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I wrote Things like this before, but as an artisan, I was tempted to make my own tools.
 https://github.com/Kray-G/kinx  Looks like JavaScript, feels like Ruby, and it is the script language fitting in C programmers.    Well, even if you say no, it&amp;rsquo;s something you can find somewhere (I won&amp;rsquo;t say it here), but I&amp;rsquo;m lonely even if I&amp;rsquo;m self-satisfied, so let&amp;rsquo;s leave a footstep for commentary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Is it still exhausted by MVC? ~ SPA development started with Django x React ~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/is-it-still-exhausted-by-mvc-~-spa-development-started-with-django-x-react-~-61268/</guid>
      <description>Recently, sites using JS framework are increasing.  In particular, JS frameworks such as React and Vue are often used for application development called SPA and bring many benefits not only to users of the site but also to developers.
Assumed readers  Web development experience People who have developed web applications using API Someone who knows JavaScript a lot and Python a little I know a little about Django People who have developed using MVC or MTV  There is an article written in more detail in another article, so please see here if you feel that this article is difficult or if you want to learn more deeply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 10 Open Source Web Crawlers for 2020</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/10-open-source-web-crawlers-for-2020-a104a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/10-open-source-web-crawlers-for-2020-a104a/</guid>
      <description>[Web crawler](https://www.octoparse.jp/blog/what-is-web-crawler/) is a database that automatically collects information such as texts, images and videos published on the Internet. It is a program stored in. Various web crawlers play an important role in the big data boom, making it easy for people to scrape data.  Among the various web crawlers, there are many open source web crawler frameworks. Open source web crawlers allow users to program based on source code or frameworks, also provide resources to assist with scraping, and simplify data extraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 2020 IT Conference Summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2020-it-conference-summary-c4621/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2020-it-conference-summary-c4621/</guid>
      <description># IT conference to be held in 2020  This is a summary as of January 20. We will update it from time to time.
#language ##PyCon JP Python conference Dates: Scheduled for August 28th and 29th Place: Ota-ku Sangyo Plaza PiO Official site
##PHP conference PHP conference Date: October 11 Place: Ota-ku Sangyo Plaza PiO 2019 Official Site 2020 official website
##PHPerKaigi PHP conference Date: February 9th 16:30 ~ February 10, 10:00- February 11th 10:00~ Place: Nerima Ward Residents &amp;amp; Industries Plaza Coconeri Hall 2020 Official Site</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [January 2020] Reiwa, let&#39;s start the development container at full speed with VS Code&#39;s Remote Container</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/january-2020-reiwa-lets-start-the-development-container-at-full-speed-with-vs-codes-remote-container-084a0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/january-2020-reiwa-lets-start-the-development-container-at-full-speed-with-vs-codes-remote-container-084a0/</guid>
      <description># Start a dash from &amp;quot;Development environment + container containing all projects&amp;quot; with Remote Conainer of VS Code! ?  Are you using VS Code Remote Conainer for development? You can use Remote SSH if you just enter an existing container, but let&amp;rsquo;s use Remote Container as a &amp;ldquo;part of local development environment&amp;rdquo;, rather as ** local development environment = Remote Container **. It&amp;rsquo;s Reiwa! ~~ (It&amp;rsquo;s been 2 years already&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make my own research tool using API of law [Smart Roppo]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-my-own-research-tool-using-api-of-law-smart-roppo-0e434/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-make-my-own-research-tool-using-api-of-law-smart-roppo-0e434/</guid>
      <description>```   Introduction I made a product that looks like a legal tech Smart Roppo concept Main functions and features of SmartRoppo Why did you decide to make it yourself? Future tasks in conclusion   ##1. Introduction This article inherits the baton from Janku ([@jank_2525](https://twitter.com/jank_2525)),and&amp;quot;**[LegalAffairsAdventCalendar2019](https://adventar.org/calendars/3900)**[^1]” I am writing as an entry for the 14th day. Everybody&#39;s entry is wonderful and full of individuality, and I look very interesting every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Persistent data structure created from scratch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/persistent-data-structure-created-from-scratch-72e7f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/persistent-data-structure-created-from-scratch-72e7f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Many data structures provide destructive operations. Arrays, for example, offer the ability to update one element with another. The processing time of the array update operation is excellent in that it does not depend on the length or value of the array. On the other hand, there are times when you want to perform non-destructive operations on data structures. For example, in each calculation of reduce/fold processing (convolution operation) that uses an array as a cumulative value, a new array should be generated nondestructively (it is possible to use the array after destruction as the calculation result, but Is hard to say).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 5 Youtuber Tech Tech Youtubers to Recommend to Engineers!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5-youtuber-tech-tech-youtubers-to-recommend-to-engineers-c2f8b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5-youtuber-tech-tech-youtubers-to-recommend-to-engineers-c2f8b/</guid>
      <description># Able Programming  Describes the python library required for machine learning and machine learning methods. Even beginners can learn about machine learning. Able Programming Sirien Sentai JUN TV The information that is available only to the engineers who are active engineers in Silicon Valley and who are working in Silicon Valley. Recommended for those who want to work or start a business in Silicon Valley in the future. Sirien Sentai JUN TV</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Beginners of GoogleMaps API and Twitter API made tweet map</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/beginners-of-googlemaps-api-and-twitter-api-made-tweet-map-c4b65/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/beginners-of-googlemaps-api-and-twitter-api-made-tweet-map-c4b65/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  If I knew when and where I tweeted, I thought it would be fun to look like a life log, so I made a tweet map.
It is the first time to touch GoogleMaps API and TwtterAPI. Thanks to various sites. .. .. ..
![Screenshot 2019-11-25 14.14.55.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/445408/d4ca8dcd-e24a-ca6e-b09c-(df19ed888805.png) ⬆️ This is when riding a bicycle on the Shimanami Kaido (It&amp;rsquo;s fun to know where you were and what you were doing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Why VBScript True is -1</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/why-vbscript-true-is-1-4ef82/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/why-vbscript-true-is-1-4ef82/</guid>
      <description>According to the following documentation, VBScript&#39;s True is equivalent to `-1`.  True keyword 
Also, False is equivalent to 0.
False keyword 
On the other hand, in the C language, true is equivalent to 1 and false is equivalent to 0 in stdbool.h.
#ifndef __cplusplus  #define bool _Bool #define true 1 #define false 0  #else /* __cplusplus */Also, in JavaScript, if you cast true to an integer type, it will be 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 7 trends in 2020 software development</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7-trends-in-2020-software-development-4d9c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7-trends-in-2020-software-development-4d9c3/</guid>
      <description>The following is an article by Tiara Brown Neil ([hackernoon](https://hackernoon.com/@theneil248)),[7SoftwareDevelopmentTrends2020Revealed](https://hackernoon.com/software-development-trends-2020-revealed-spi305m) is a Japanese translation.  7 Software Development Trends 2020 Revealed Did you know? Over half of IT projects have failed. For many of us who are aware of the complexity and dynamic nature of the software development industry, it&amp;rsquo;s less shocking.
Keeping pace is essential to survive in this unpredictable industry with constant innovation and progress. The wise not only take advantage of software development services, but weigh the pros and cons of all technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Discover the most dangerous functions on github</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/discover-the-most-dangerous-functions-on-github-2be90/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/discover-the-most-dangerous-functions-on-github-2be90/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  The other day, at work, I was excited by &amp;ldquo;I am renovating or writing Ichibanya Bay function&amp;rdquo;. Everyone told me a lot, but it was an overwhelming victory for the &amp;ldquo;command pattern main loop function (1500 lines)&amp;rdquo; I wrote. Why did you write such a code?
So, today, I will discover the &amp;ldquo;most world-wide function&amp;rdquo; from github to heal my injured pride. In other words, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to see a yaw function rather than the one I wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s seriously think about the definition of data scientists and skill sets</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-seriously-think-about-the-definition-of-data-scientists-and-skill-sets-f9bf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-seriously-think-about-the-definition-of-data-scientists-and-skill-sets-f9bf1/</guid>
      <description>## What is a data scientist?  As the subject of the title, let&amp;rsquo;s think about the profession of being a data scientist, which is being said variously these days. Even in the industry, the definition of this occupation is vague and there is no unified view.
Well, honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s a story that &amp;ldquo;a data scientist wants to give a name to a person who wants to give it a name&amp;rdquo;, but since it&amp;rsquo;s a big deal, I&amp;rsquo;ll write my personal thoughts during this period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to handle JSON with Ruby, Python, JavaScript, PHP</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-handle-json-with-ruby-python-javascript-php-f79ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-handle-json-with-ruby-python-javascript-php-f79ab/</guid>
      <description>I have confirmed how to encode and decode JSON with Python, Ruby, JavaScript, and PHP.  For Python #!/usr/bin/env python # -*- coding:utf-8 -*- # import json # Dictionary format data dic1 = {&amp;#34;key1&amp;#34;: None, &amp;#34;key2&amp;#34;: None} dic1[&amp;#34;key1&amp;#34;] = 24 dic1[&amp;#34;key2&amp;#34;] = 45 print dic1 # Convert from dictionary format to JSON json_data1 = json.dumps(dic1, sort_keys=True,indent=4) print json_data1 json_data2 = json.dumps(dic1,sort_keys=True) print json_data2 json_data3 = json.dumps(dic1) print json_data3 dic2 = json.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Should I fix that copy and paste?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/should-i-fix-that-copy-and-paste-fe1b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/should-i-fix-that-copy-and-paste-fe1b3/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s true that copy clones of source code are more reliable than code clones, but in many cases the existence of code clones often hurts us at the last minute.  After the person in charge escaped, corrected the source code until late at night, and released it, in fact, I was told that &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m making it with copy and paste, so please test all the other places again&amp;rdquo; and start over Is very, very sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A general-purpose tool that I think is lost to programmers who do not know this</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-general-purpose-tool-that-i-think-is-lost-to-programmers-who-do-not-know-this-f75d4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-general-purpose-tool-that-i-think-is-lost-to-programmers-who-do-not-know-this-f75d4/</guid>
      <description>please tell me.  # Addition [Over 100 general-purpose tools that I think I&amp;rsquo;m losing to a programmer I don&amp;rsquo;t know] Summary (http://qiita.com/items/2183) Suin summarized it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>