<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JSON on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/json/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JSON on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/json/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creation of TFRecord file for object detection</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/creation-of-tfrecord-file-for-object-detection-8ad0c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/creation-of-tfrecord-file-for-object-detection-8ad0c/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Last article summarized how to use the Object Detection API provided by TensorFlow. To use this API to teach &amp;ldquo;This object is ○○&amp;rdquo; from images and videos, Annotate and convert to TFRecord format, It will be used as teacher data and verification data, I feel that there are still few articles that mention the specific contents of this TFRecord format.
In this article, from the method that can be created without programming at the beginning, We will put together various angles to write and create Python code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to develop a Formatter that outputs Python log in JSON</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-develop-a-formatter-that-outputs-python-log-in-json-8fca6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-develop-a-formatter-that-outputs-python-log-in-json-8fca6/</guid>
      <description>I usually use Python mainly, but structural data is more convenient when setting up a log collection/analysis infrastructure for cloud services. However, using the normal logging formatter in Python&#39;s standard library, you have to convert it once into structured data. It&#39;s nogure to create another application just to convert.  Therefore, I tried to develop a Formatter that outputs the log in JSON.
#Environment
  OS (guaranteed operation) -MacOS Catalina -Ubuntu 18.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>