<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OpenPose on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/openpose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OpenPose on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/openpose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I shot Kamehameha using OpenPose</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-shot-kamehameha-using-openpose-ec501/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-shot-kamehameha-using-openpose-ec501/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I wanted to shoot Kamehameha so I made it.
You can also hide the estimation line.
The coordinates of the joint are acquired using OpenPose, the angle is calculated from that, and it is judged whether the pose looks like that.
About OpenPose How to set up I used tf pose estimation which is Tensorflow version of OpenPose. My environment was Windows10, GTX1070, etc., so I referred to the following page for setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to visualize Boeing playing violin with pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-boeing-playing-violin-with-pose-estimation-b3b85/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-boeing-playing-violin-with-pose-estimation-b3b85/</guid>
      <description># I tried to detect the feature point of the right wrist joint  #Introduction
This article was posted on the 22nd day of the Fujitsu Systems Web Technology Advent Calendar 2019. All content in the article is the personal opinion, and the content of the writing is the author&amp;rsquo;s own responsibility. It does not matter which organization you belong to. (Goodbye)
Overview I enjoy playing violin as a hobby, but playing the violin is difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A simple interactive music player made with Chuck and OpenPose</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-simple-interactive-music-player-made-with-chuck-and-openpose-2c8e1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-simple-interactive-music-player-made-with-chuck-and-openpose-2c8e1/</guid>
      <description>It is the 18th day of [ABEJA Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/abeja).  #Introduction
This is imais who joined ABEJA in October of this year. In my normal work, I am in charge of developing a flow line analysis that analyzes the movements of customers in the store with the ABEJA Insight for Retail development team. ..
In this article, pose estimation from 2D image OpenPoseandprogramminglanguageformusicChucK.
System overview &amp;ldquo;When humans clapping their hands, music tracks are added one by one&amp;rdquo; Build the following system on MacBook Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>