<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> numerical calculation on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/numerical-calculation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  numerical calculation on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/numerical-calculation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Numerical calculation of lens point spread function and MTF curve (diffraction calculation)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7af0814d7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7af0814d7/</guid>
      <description>I recently researched the point spread function (PSF), which often appears in the context of lens design, and the specific numerical calculation method for MTF curves, so I summarized them. I&#39;m not an expert in lens design, and I&#39;m not from a physics department, so I&#39;m afraid there are some mistakes, but I&#39;d appreciate it if anyone noticed.  About point spread function (PSF) Point spread function (PSF) is a function that represents the intensity distribution of light on the image plane when a point light source forms an image on the image plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Fluid simulation: Incompressible Navier-Stokes equation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/9d2a92ef4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/9d2a92ef4/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  While studying Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD), I would like to summarize the knowledge necessary for constructing a computational fluid dynamics analysis code. It seems that there are many mistakes, so please feel free to contact us if you find it.
Target audience  People who can use Python People who are interested in numerical calculation People who are interested in fluid mechanics Those who understand basic university physics and mathematics (simple differential equations and linear algebra?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Article that enables high-speed sparse matrix calculation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e5500ba6e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e5500ba6e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  **A sparse matrix is a matrix in which most of the elements of the matrix are 0. It is used in a wide range of fields such as numerical calculation, machine learning, and graph theory (I think). Since most of the matrix is 0, if you devise to ignore 0, you can perform matrix calculation at high speed. For example, if you use a large-scale sparse matrix (nearly 90% is 0) (1 million rows x 1 million columns) and only use non-zero parts, the calculation time will be about 1/10 and the calculation can be completed quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Fluid simulation: Implement diffusion equation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/97daa5099/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/97daa5099/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  While also studying Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD), which is a discipline related to the simulation of fluids such as air and water, I would like to summarize (in multiple articles) the knowledge necessary to construct a numerical fluid analysis code for water.
I feel that computational fluid dynamics is a difficult academic subject, so I would like to write it so that even beginners can understand it as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Fluid simulation: Implementing the advection equation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/354c85adb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/354c85adb/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  While also studying Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD), which is a discipline related to the simulation of fluids such as air and water, I would like to summarize (in multiple articles) the knowledge necessary to construct a numerical fluid analysis code for water.
I want to write it so that even beginners can understand it. It seems that many mistakes are included, so we would appreciate if you contact us when you discover it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Harlem] There are too many to choose! 13 ways to calculate pi in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7228644dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7228644dc/</guid>
      <description>Hello from the abyss of the universe!  \displaystyle\int {\rm d}\boldsymbol{r}\hat{\psi}^{\dagger}(\boldsymbol{r}) Poppin Friends \hat{\psi}(\boldsymbol{r}) is! This time, I would like to introduce **13 methods of calculating the circle ratio $\pi$ in Python.
In the past, I read the article [&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not worried about pi anymore! 10 ways to find pi&amp;rdquo;]&amp;rdquo; (https://www.procrasist.com/entry/pi_1) (famous in pi region) , The desire to &amp;ldquo;π seek&amp;rdquo; was amplified, so I came to write this article. And this time, I tried to implement almost all of the method of finding $\pi$ in the article in Python **!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Molecular dynamics simulation to try for the time being</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/4bacfcc7d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/4bacfcc7d/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I&#39;ll briefly explain about molecular dynamics and try a simple simulation. For the simulation, we will use a Python module called [Atomic Simulation Environment](https://wiki.fysik.dtu.dk/ase/index.html).  What is molecular dynamics? Molecular Dynamics (MD) obtains dynamic processes of atoms and molecules by solving equations of motion based on interactions (potentials) between atoms and molecules.
What we see around us is an aggregate of atoms and molecules, if we look at it in detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Numerical calculation of compressible fluid by finite volume method</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/03e8e20c5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/03e8e20c5/</guid>
      <description># 1.First of all  It is necessary to consider the compressibility of the fluid in the flow around a fast-moving object such as an aircraft or rocket, and in the phenomena involving strong pressure, temperature and density changes such as combustion and explosion. Compressible fluids have various phenomena such as sound waves, shock waves, and aerodynamic heating that are not found in incompressible fluids, and their numerical calculations have different difficulties from incompressible fluids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] pandas.DataFrame copy method defaults to deep copy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f8c562e09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f8c562e09/</guid>
      <description>The conclusion is according to the title. [Written in official documentation](https://pandas.pydata.org/pandas-docs/stable/generated/pandas.DataFrame.copy.html).  A colleague said, &amp;ldquo;The pandas assign method makes a copy of the data frame internally, so I&amp;rsquo;m having trouble eating up memory and being slow.&amp;rdquo;
I read &amp;ldquo;The Recursive Substitution Eradication Committee for Python/pandas Data Processing&amp;rdquo;, and I&amp;rsquo;m addicted to writing a clean batch of statistics using a method chain. It was.
However, if you look at the actual pandas code,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>