<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IPython on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/ipython/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IPython on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/ipython/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Jupyter Notebook essential for software development</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/25a5dd8ac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/25a5dd8ac/</guid>
      <description>Hello. I&#39;m a software engineer who makes various embedded systems, games, web apps, iOS apps, signage control systems, etc.  About two and a half years ago, I thought that I should write in Python as a general-purpose scripting language that is difficult to realize only with a shell, and I was trying to learn Python while suffering. Since I only use it occasionally, I was at a level where I forget how to write if and for loops every time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Process %time, %timeit results</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8c8a0b52a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8c8a0b52a/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s well known that you can measure execution time with `%time` or `%timeit` in Jupyter/IPython, but have you ever wanted to process or visualize this?  You can use standard output as a Python object by using %%capture. Let&amp;rsquo;s actually do it.
%%capture result %timeit 2 ** 100 The argument of %%capture is the object name, see help for other options.
 %capture [--no-stderr] [--no-stdout] [--no-display] [output] run the cell, capturing stdout, stderr, and IPython&#39;s rich display() calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to revive a cell in iPython notebook</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fb9100e5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fb9100e5d/</guid>
      <description># Problem  When working with Python, I often use the iPython notebook.
The trouble has happened recently. The cell where I wrote the script disappeared as if I had accidentally hit something on the keyboard.
The cause was that I pressed &amp;ldquo;x&amp;rdquo; (lowercase letters). iPython notebook seems to have &amp;ldquo;Edit mode&amp;rdquo; (state with focus in text box) and &amp;ldquo;Command mode&amp;rdquo; (state without focus in text box; press Esc to enter this mode).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create a table of contents with IPython notebook</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fb1daa15f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fb1daa15f/</guid>
      <description>Purpose  ======
I want to create a table of contents at the beginning of the IPython notebook like this
(Note: The image is from here)
manner It can be created using this library.
 github.com/kmahelona/ipython_notebook_goodies  Just paste the following 3 lines into Markdown cell. It will automatically acquire the Header cell and write the table of contents.
 &amp;lt;h1 id=&amp;quot;tocheading&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Table of Contents&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt; &amp;lt;div id=&amp;quot;toc&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script src=&amp;quot;https://kmahelona.github.io/ipython_notebook_goodies/ipython_notebook_toc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>