<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> beginners on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/beginners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  beginners on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/beginners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Understand the shortest] Python basics for data analysis</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7d8f5354d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7d8f5354d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For those who want to analyze data using Python &amp;hellip; or those who have decided to use Python for seminars and research but have never done programming &amp;hellip; Once you know this, the basics are okay for now (Maybe). I think it can be used as a review of knowledge. First, we will cover the basics of general-purpose Python syntax to a minimum, and then describe the basic tools and techniques used for data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] I tried to solve 100 questions of past questions that should be solved by beginners [Part 5/22]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2683c3988/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2683c3988/</guid>
      <description>**Aim for a light blue coder! ! ! ! ! ! **  So, [Red Coder&amp;rsquo;s Teaching Guidelines for Competitive At Coder Improvement [Intermediate: Aim Light Blue Coder! ]]( https://qiita.com/e869120/items/eb50fdaece12be418faa#2-3-%E5%88%86%E9%87%8E%E5%88%A5%E5%88%9D%E4%B8%AD%E7 %B4%9A%E8%80%85%E3%81%8C%E8%A7%A3%E3%81%8F%E3%81%B9%E3%81%8D%E9%81%8E%E5%8E %BB%E5%95%8F%E7%B2%BE%E9%81%B8-100-%E5%95%8F) (@e869120)
  In order to achieve a light blue coder or rating of 1200 with a small number of problems at AtCoder, we have collected 100 educational good questions that are appropriate for brown and green coders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] I tried to solve 100 questions of past questions to be solved by beginners and intermediates [Part 1/22]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8ae8beeba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8ae8beeba/</guid>
      <description>**Aim for a light blue coder! ! ! ! ! ! **  So, [Red Coder&amp;rsquo;s Teaching Guidelines for Competitive At Coder Improvement [Intermediate: Aim Light Blue Coder! ]]( https://qiita.com/e869120/items/eb50fdaece12be418faa#2-3-%E5%88%86%E9%87%8E%E5%88%A5%E5%88%9D%E4%B8%AD%E7 %B4%9A%E8%80%85%E3%81%8C%E8%A7%A3%E3%81%8F%E3%81%B9%E3%81%8D%E9%81%8E%E5%8E %BB%E5%95%8F%E7%B2%BE%E9%81%B8-100-%E5%95%8F) (@e869120)
  In order to achieve a light blue coder or rating of 1200 with a small number of problems at AtCoder, we have collected 100 educational good questions that are appropriate for brown and green coders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Every day in Python AtCoder #14</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/855eee1fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/855eee1fc/</guid>
      <description>### Introduction  Last time Day 14
#14 Today is B.
Thoughts ABC081-B ABC081-B divides by 2 when $A_i$ is even. When it is an odd number, I quit immediately.
n = int(input()) a = list(map(int,input().split())) counter = [] for i in range(n): count = 0 if a[i] %2 == 0: while a[i] %2 == 0: a[i] //= 2 count += 1 counter.append(count) else: print(0) quit() print(min(counter))  ABC087-B ABC087-B has a triple loop with thought stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s take a free Python introductory course for machine learning online until April 27th</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/93ebf1bc4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/93ebf1bc4/</guid>
      <description>Yes~mo :clap:  Today, I&amp;rsquo;m going to take &amp;ldquo;Python introductory course for machine learning **&amp;rdquo; online.
This is an online course for machine learning super beginners, developed by Skill-Up AI Co., Ltd. in cooperation with the Japan Deep Learning Association.
If it is true, it costs about 50,000 yen, but for people who are discerning with the example corona 2020/4/30By 2020/4/27 If you apply, 2020/ You can read the teaching materials until 4/30!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I thought about how to learn programming for free.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/97e123a01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/97e123a01/</guid>
      <description># Background  I thought about a low-cost way to learn programming from an empty situation. (Mac) Is the continuation of.
This time, I summarized how to take a smartphone and learn the program for free for those who are new to buying a PC.
OPAC-Library search system Perhaps it is OPAC that university graduates know but middle and high school graduates do not. If you are a university, you will be asked at the first orientation of your first year to search for books, magazines, papers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Process huge excel files with Python to improve productivity</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/33983de6c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/33983de6c/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;This article was published in November 2019 by [Benedikt Droste](https://towardsdatascience.com/@droste.benedikt),&amp;quot;[BoostyourefficiencyandprocessExcel-fileswithPython](https://towardsdatascience.com/boost-your-efficiency-and-process-excel-files-with-python-cae650c85d6c)”.  This article is published with the permission of the original author.
When you&amp;rsquo;re working with data, you inevitably come into contact with Excel. Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t use it for yourself, it will be needed by clients and colleagues. Excel excels in spreadsheets with small datasets.
But I always lamented when I saw an Excel sheet with tens of thousands of rows and hundreds of columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Steps to develop Django with VSCode</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/12a5df2d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/12a5df2d1/</guid>
      <description>2020/03/13 Modified slightly to match VSCode Version 1.43.0  Introduction A beginner yearned for the word debug, and learned that VS Code can actually do it, and tried setting it. The memorandum. I think that the advantage is that once you set it, you can enter the virtual environment and run the server just by pressing the Debug button. You can save yourself the trouble of going back and forth between the browser and Terminal and VS Code and entering source myenv/bin/activate or python manage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Hit the Spotify API with Django.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e991cd14a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e991cd14a/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is from Django Advent Calendar 2019. The target audience is for those who are new to Django.
The previous article was about @yuu-eguci&amp;rsquo;s 500 error. https://qiita.com/yuu-eguci/items/a1e4b0a2f238d5ccc985
This article is about trying to execute Spotify API with Django.
Advance preparation I need to create a user account for Spotify, but the following article by Class Method is very helpful. https://dev.classmethod.jp/etc/about-using-of-spotify-api/
If you want to execute the sample code of the article, please download the chart data in CSV format from the following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Kaggle&#39;s initial equipment-a cell that collects frequently used codes-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/c946ce417/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/c946ce417/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  When working on Kaggle1, which is a competition platform for data science, Python2 written in Notebook3(orJupyterNotebook[^JupyterNotebook]orGoogleColaboratory[^GoogleColaboratory])istheexecutionenvironment.]]Ithinkthereisa&amp;quot;highlyusedcode&amp;rdquo;.Inordertoreuseit,Iwillintroduceitinonecellasaformatthatiseasytocopyandpasteanyway.Wehopethatbyreusingthecontentsofthiscell,wecanimprovetheefficiencyofdataanalysisinKaggle.(Thisis“Kaggle&amp;rsquo;sinitialequipment”!)
*This article is based on the Notebook published by Kaggler (Kaggle participant) predecessors and the book [Technology of data analysis that wins at Kaggle]. However, it is the individual subjectivity as of December 2019. Therefore, please see for your reference.
#Conclusion
What is Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s initial equipment?
This cell!
#Display Notebook from IPython.core.interactiveshell import InteractiveShell InteractiveShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [First data science ⑤] I tried to help my friend&#39;s first property search by data analysis</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3aa0d6f88/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3aa0d6f88/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you. My name is S.I, a third year college student in the Department of Information Engineering.  My experience with Python is a little dealt with in a college experiment.
The data science division of Bracket Co., Ltd., where I am an intern, has the task of creating a crawler during the trial period to collect, process, visualize data, and briefly describe what I learned.
Task Theme My university friend will live alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] ``First time learning&#39;&#39; that even university students with no knowledge can do-AWS SageMaker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ffdfc936e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ffdfc936e/</guid>
      <description># My background  Amazon? Ah, you know, you know, a mail order app. Not long ago, knowledge about Amazon was that much. Of course, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know AWS.
I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed as an information undergraduate student. 
However, as a 3rd year university student, I was introduced to the lab and learned about AWS. In addition, I am addicted to the topic &amp;ldquo;Atsuhiko Nakata&amp;rsquo;s YouTube University&amp;rdquo;, which is a hot topic in this street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>