<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> AtCoder on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/atcoder/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  AtCoder on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/atcoder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoder ABC 107 B string manipulation solved with Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3f2be6fca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3f2be6fca/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Beginner Contest 107 B-Grid Compression Difficulty: 434
This theme, string operation
Ruby h, w = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) a = [] h.times do |i| s = gets.chomp a.push(s) if s.index(&amp;#39;#&amp;#39;) end (w-1).downto(0) do |i| if a.all?{|x| x[i] ==&amp;#39;.&amp;#39;} a.each do |x| x[i] =&amp;#39;&amp;#39; end end end puts a a.push(s) if s.count(&amp;#39;.&amp;#39;) != w a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Solving AtCoder ARC 086 C hashes in Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/1c6f21934/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/1c6f21934/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Regular Contest 086 C-Not so Diverse Difficulty: 431
This theme, hash sorting
Ruby Speaking of duplicate lists, it&amp;rsquo;s a hash.
n, k = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) a = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) h = Hash.new(0) a.each do |x| h[x] += 1 end puts n-h.values.sort.reverse[0, k].inject(:+) h.sort_by{|key, v| -v}.each do |key, v| puts n-h.values.sort.reverse[0, k].inject(:+) ~~Ruby doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a destructive sort of hashes, but it seems to have few uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Competitive Prototype [At Coder]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/c6bc5e4d7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/c6bc5e4d7/</guid>
      <description>Currently (2020/05/05) using  ** Templates for competitive professionals (for Python) such as AtCoder! ** Please use when it is good~ (I&amp;rsquo;m sorry if I make a mistake!)
#Competitive Pro Template Since I think that I often delete the first line and submit it, sys which is always used (on input) and other libraries Is divided into two lines! Also, sys.stdin.readline().rstrip() is obviously faster than input()! ! ! Reference article [It&amp;rsquo;s good to know Python 8 small differences in processing speed] (https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoder AGC 033 A breadth-first search solved with Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5d3059a10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5d3059a10/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Grand Contest 033 A-Darker and Darker Difficulty: 1245
This theme, breadth-first search
Ruby This is an advanced version of AtCoder Typical Contest 002 A-breadth-first search that I solved earlier. In particular, there are severe conditions such as execution time limit: 1 sec.
h, w = gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i) cm = Array.new(h + 2){Array.new(w + 2, 0)} que = [] 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Explanation of AtCoder] Control A, B, (C), D problems of ABC165 with Python!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/40eae13cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/40eae13cf/</guid>
      <description>I will explain how to solve **A,B,(C),D problem** of **AtCoder Beginners Contest 165** with **Python3** as carefully as possible.  I am aiming to explain a solution method that satisfies the following three points, not just a solution method.
 Simple: don&amp;rsquo;t worry about extra things Easy to implement: I&amp;rsquo;m happy with fewer mistakes and bugs No time required: Paphos go up and more time can be left for D problem  5/17 C Problem was very difficult and the article was long, so I separated it into another article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] I tried to solve 100 questions of past questions that should be solved by beginners [Part 5/22]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2683c3988/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2683c3988/</guid>
      <description>**Aim for a light blue coder! ! ! ! ! ! **  So, [Red Coder&amp;rsquo;s Teaching Guidelines for Competitive At Coder Improvement [Intermediate: Aim Light Blue Coder! ]]( https://qiita.com/e869120/items/eb50fdaece12be418faa#2-3-%E5%88%86%E9%87%8E%E5%88%A5%E5%88%9D%E4%B8%AD%E7 %B4%9A%E8%80%85%E3%81%8C%E8%A7%A3%E3%81%8F%E3%81%B9%E3%81%8D%E9%81%8E%E5%8E %BB%E5%95%8F%E7%B2%BE%E9%81%B8-100-%E5%95%8F) (@e869120)
  In order to achieve a light blue coder or rating of 1200 with a small number of problems at AtCoder, we have collected 100 educational good questions that are appropriate for brown and green coders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoderBeginnerContest164 Review &amp; Summary (First Half)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3bf22e2c5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3bf22e2c5/</guid>
      <description># AtCoder ABC164  This is a summary of the problems of AtCoderBeginnerContest164 performed on 2020-04-26 (Sun) in consideration of the problem A in order. The first half deals with problems up to ABC. The problem is quoted, but please check the contest page for details. Contest page is here Official explanation PDF
Problem A Sheep and Wolves  Problem statement There are $S$ sheep and $W$ wolves. When the number of wolves is greater than the number of sheep, the sheep will be attacked by the wolves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Until it turns light blue with AtCoder</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/c97b835b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/c97b835b3/</guid>
      <description># Self-introduction  Hello. I am a third year college student who became a light blue coder the other day. The language is python, started in June of last year (2019). I&amp;rsquo;m not very good at writing, but I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll see it to the end.
Background of starting competitive programming When I entered university, I started studying information systems, I got basic information in October of the same year, applied information in April of the next year, and I was wondering what to study next, but a friend who is not an information system machine learning with python It was ridiculous to discover that I was self-taught.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoder ABC 131 D Array Sorting Solved with Ruby, Perl, Java and Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a136574d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a136574d1/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  AtCoder Problems is used to solve past problems. Thank you, AtCoder and AtCoder Problems.
This time AtCoder Beginner Contest 131 D-Megalomania Difficulty: 594
This theme, array sort
Ruby It&amp;rsquo;s an array sort, so I think it&amp;rsquo;s easy to implement. ~~ I chose a lighter problem because it is the first Python. ~~
n = gets.to_i a = Array.new(n){gets.split.map(&amp;amp;:to_i)} a.sort_by!{|x| x[1]} ans = 0 n.times do |i| ans += a[i][0] if ans &amp;gt;a[i][1] puts &amp;#34;No&amp;#34; exit end end puts &amp;#34;Yes&amp;#34; a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] I tried to solve 100 questions of past questions to be solved by beginners and intermediates [Part 1/22]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8ae8beeba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8ae8beeba/</guid>
      <description>**Aim for a light blue coder! ! ! ! ! ! **  So, [Red Coder&amp;rsquo;s Teaching Guidelines for Competitive At Coder Improvement [Intermediate: Aim Light Blue Coder! ]]( https://qiita.com/e869120/items/eb50fdaece12be418faa#2-3-%E5%88%86%E9%87%8E%E5%88%A5%E5%88%9D%E4%B8%AD%E7 %B4%9A%E8%80%85%E3%81%8C%E8%A7%A3%E3%81%8F%E3%81%B9%E3%81%8D%E9%81%8E%E5%8E %BB%E5%95%8F%E7%B2%BE%E9%81%B8-100-%E5%95%8F) (@e869120)
  In order to achieve a light blue coder or rating of 1200 with a small number of problems at AtCoder, we have collected 100 educational good questions that are appropriate for brown and green coders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Every day in Python AtCoder #14</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/855eee1fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/855eee1fc/</guid>
      <description>### Introduction  Last time Day 14
#14 Today is B.
Thoughts ABC081-B ABC081-B divides by 2 when $A_i$ is even. When it is an odd number, I quit immediately.
n = int(input()) a = list(map(int,input().split())) counter = [] for i in range(n): count = 0 if a[i] %2 == 0: while a[i] %2 == 0: a[i] //= 2 count += 1 counter.append(count) else: print(0) quit() print(min(counter))  ABC087-B ABC087-B has a triple loop with thought stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What to use for Python stacks and queues (speed comparison of each data structure)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/107c42372/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/107c42372/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is primarily about competitive programming.
There are several ways to implement stacks and queues in Python.
 Stack -Use list (append(), pop()) -Use collections.deque (append(), pop()) Queue -Use list (append(), pop(0)) -Use collections.deque (append(), popleft()) -Use queue.Queue (put(), get())  Which of these is the best to use? This time I will investigate it focusing on the speed aspect.
#Measurement method For each data structure, elements are added and extracted 10 times, 100 times, 1000 times, 10000 times, 100000 times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Minimal implementation for doing UnionFind in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/52fd4149b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/52fd4149b/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I am happy.  Sometimes I had problems with UnionFind, but I tended to use other people&amp;rsquo;s libraries, so I&amp;rsquo;ll write about it as a review. If you think that it&amp;rsquo;s like a forgetful personal note
Important example AtCoder Typical Contest 001 B-Union Find https://atcoder.jp/contests/atc001/tasks/unionfind_a
Union Find&amp;rsquo;s pure problem An explanation slide is also attached, so I will follow along with this.
https://www.slideshare.net/chokudai/union-find-49066733 Union find (primary set data structure) from AtCoder Inc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python3] A//B and math.floor(A/B) are not always the same! ?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ee26e8cce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ee26e8cce/</guid>
      <description># Note  **This article contains spoilers for &amp;ldquo;Atcoder Beginner Contest 148 E-Double Factorial&amp;rdquo;. Please refrain from browsing if you plan to solve this problem yourself. **
Overview I got into a problem with the title while solving Atcoder, so I&amp;rsquo;ll post this article to keep it as a memorandum and to hear the opinions of Python experts.
Problem Atcoder Beginner Contest 148 E-Double Factorial
Define f(n) as follows for an integer n of 0 or more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Introduction to Python (Python version APG4b)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b9418d7b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b9418d7b5/</guid>
      <description># About this article  At AtCoderofthecompetitionprogrammingsite,thereis&amp;rdquo;AtCoderProgrammingGuideforbeginners(APG4b)&amp;rdquo; which is an introductory material for programming. There is. C++, which is the mainstream language for competitive programming, is used as an introductory material for programming. So, in this article, I wrote a Python version of APG4b. Basically, please read APG4b, and refer to this article for Python-specific parts.
Most are based on APG4b, so if this article seems to be a problem, remove it immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] AtCoder Beginner Contest 122 Review</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d5b8579e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d5b8579e3/</guid>
      <description>#Time required  #Impression The last problem was that experimentation was important or I was aware of the essence, but I could not put the solution into a simpler one.
#A problem
Properly output using the ternary operator.
b=input() print(&amp;#34;A&amp;#34; if b==&amp;#34;T&amp;#34; else &amp;#34;T&amp;#34; if b==&amp;#34;A&amp;#34; else &amp;#34;G&amp;#34; if b==&amp;#34;C&amp;#34; else &amp;#34;C&amp;#34;) #B Problem
If one of the AGCTs comes, add it, and if any other character comes, reset it to zero again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python Golf Tech (AtCoder)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/bcf069487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/bcf069487/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Introducing the short writing technique in Python3 that has been cultivated so far with AtCoder. In addition, AtCoder&amp;rsquo;s Python 3 version is 3.4.3, and it seems that functions that are likely to become shorter, such as f-strings and walrus operators, cannot be used. It&amp;rsquo;s just a technique on AtCoder (I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it can be used elsewhere). I think it&amp;rsquo;s messy because I write down what I came up with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Automates AtCoder directory creation, sample case testing, and submission. atcoder-cli and online-judge-tools</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d07180669/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d07180669/</guid>
      <description>Here are two CLI tools to help you solve AtCoder comfortably.  The environment used in this entry is Windows 10, Python 3. Of course, other OS and languages are also supported.
What you can do Create a contest directory 
 acc new {contest ID} A contest directory will be created.  The directory for the contest is cut off for each problem. Under the problem directory, a main.py file that writes the answers and a test file that describes the input and output of the sample case are created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Atcoder][C&#43;&#43;]I made a test automation tool that can be used during the contest</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a542c8f85/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a542c8f85/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m doing Atcoder (competitive programming) as a hobby, but I&#39;ve been slowing down recently.  I think it would be nice to automate the test work during the contest, I made a test automation tool with python.
Introduction Below are more features than the homebrew tools introduced in this article.
 https://github.com/kyuridenamida/atcoder-tools https://github.com/nodchip/OnlineJudgeHelper  Please compare the above when using.
1. What has been achieved  Automatically get test cases from Atcoder problem page without overloading the server Build and grade the created code (c++) before submitting, and judge AC, WA, TLE, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>