<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> competitive programming on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/competitive-programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  competitive programming on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/competitive-programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 095 Review</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-095-review-fe2c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-095-review-fe2c6/</guid>
      <description>#Time required  #Impression
I was regrettable that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve problem D before, but I was relieved because I could solve it this time. I think that more speed will be required in the future, so I will try to acquire the typical ideas firmly.
#A problem
The number of toppings corresponds to the number of ○, so you can count and output.
s=input() print(700+s.count(&amp;#34;o&amp;#34;)*100) #B Problem
It is problem B, but it requires a little attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every day in Python AtCoder #44</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#44-f967b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#44-f967b/</guid>
      <description>### Introduction  Last time Solve 5 boot camp problems
#44 ABC056-C
Thoughts The sum of non-negative integers up to i is $\frac{1}{2}n(n+1)$}}. This sum becomes $X$ when $\frac{1}{2}n(n+1)=X$, and when solving for $n$, $n=\frac{-1\pm{ It will be \sqrt{8X+1}}}{2}$. If you add the ceil symbol to the solution of this equation, it becomes $\lceil \frac{-1\pm{\sqrt{8X+1}}}{2} \rceil$. This is the answer.
import math x = int(input()) f = (-1+math.sqrt(8*x+1)) / 2 print(math.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every day in Python AtCoder #41</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#41-f9a60/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/every-day-in-python-atcoder-#41-f9a60/</guid>
      <description>### Introduction  Last time I have ABC today so I have only one question.
#41 Problem
Thoughts It&amp;rsquo;s a long-standing problem. When I tried to solve this time, I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand why I was having a difficult time. Since the range of the solution is small, check all with for. I have placed a flag to check if the M conditions are met.
n, m = map(int,input().split()) sc = [list(map(int,input().</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 115 Review</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-115-review-fed4f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-115-review-fed4f/</guid>
      <description>#Time required  #Impression I forgot to write my impressions (2020/04/18). When I was solving while taking classes, the results were halfway&amp;hellip; After all, I should imagine it as a production contest and usually do it&amp;hellip;
#A problem
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a smart way to change the number of Eve depending on how many days before Christmas, but I decided to divide it because it is not troublesome to divide it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 162 復習</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-162-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-ff5b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-162-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-ff5b1/</guid>
      <description>#This grade  #This impression
It&amp;rsquo;s not bad in performance (although it took 1 hour), I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve either E or F, so I&amp;rsquo;m very sorry. For the time being, I would like to review what E and F were missing and review.
#A problem
Whether or not 7 is included can be handled as a character string. Why are you converting it to a list? My head is too bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] ABC159D (College Mathematics nCr) [AtCoder]</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/python-abc159d-college-mathematics-ncr-atcoder-f9f1e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/python-abc159d-college-mathematics-ncr-atcoder-f9f1e/</guid>
      <description>Competitive professionals will prepare notebooks and pens! ! !  (Especially if a mathematical formula comes out)
#ABC159D Difficulty:417 This time I will explain the explanation w First, quote from Explanation.
 ① Number of methods to select two different balls with the same written integer from N balls (2) Number of methods to select a ball in which the same integer as the kth ball is written from the N-1 balls excluding the kth ball Can be obtained by subtracting the latter from the former.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest 155 復習</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-155-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-fec2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/atcoder-beginner-contest-155-%E5%BE%A9%E7%BF%92-fec2d/</guid>
      <description>#This grade  #This impression
(I had no motivation for a competition professional because I was soaked in skis for 3 weeks, but I would like to resume from today (2/26)) I couldn&amp;rsquo;t solve up to C this time. I felt the importance of devotion because the assumed solution of D was not difficult as an idea when I saw the solution by binary search. For E, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do a good job of distinguishing whether to carry or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People who want to clear the D problem at ABC of AtCoder scratched the foot</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/people-who-want-to-clear-the-d-problem-at-abc-of-atcoder-scratched-the-foot-f9ae5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/people-who-want-to-clear-the-d-problem-at-abc-of-atcoder-scratched-the-foot-f9ae5/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction   An amateur writer tried AtCoder Beginner Contest several times. Language is python However, after the D problem, I have no teeth. For these problems, it is required to estimate the amount of calculation + how to use algorithms or libraries to improve processing speed or mathematical knowledge. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult and seems to vomit, but it&amp;rsquo;s funny. If you don&amp;rsquo;t solve it  Purpose  Learn how to solve AtCoder&amp;rsquo;s D-rank problem (400 points).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>