<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Paper reading on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/paper-reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Paper reading on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/paper-reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Deep Metric Learning based on the Softmax function works</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/why-deep-metric-learning-based-on-the-softmax-function-works-7ed56/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/why-deep-metric-learning-based-on-the-softmax-function-works-7ed56/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  In distance learning (metric learning) using deep learning, similarities (and dissimilarities) between images are used by using Contrastive Loss and Triplet Loss.) Is widely used, but it is also known that it is difficult to combine and select learning data, and learning itself is difficult in many cases. For that reason, various improvements and ideas have been proposed so far. However, recently, metric learning, which can learn based on the Softmax function as if it is a general class classification task without the difficulty of selecting learning data like this, has been attracting attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Paper and Implementation] When asked, Is this data set difficult?...</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/paper-and-implementation-when-asked-is-this-data-set-difficult...-74917/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/paper-and-implementation-when-asked-is-this-data-set-difficult...-74917/</guid>
      <description>Learning a convolutional neural network (CNN) takes time.  Especially, if you try to get accuracy without transfer learning, it takes about 5 days** There are times. The paper introduced in this paper quantitatively describes the difficulty of datasets. By evaluating, classification accuracy can be estimated quickly without learning CNN. Is that.
*The entire code was placed on here. *The figures in this paper are basically taken from the paper (Spectral Metric for Dataset Complexity Assessment).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>