<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> horse racing on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/horse-racing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  horse racing on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/horse-racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Prediction of horse racing: If I thought that the collection rate exceeded 100% in machine learning (Light GBM), I did it</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/prediction-of-horse-racing-if-i-thought-that-the-collection-rate-exceeded-100-in-machine-learning-light-gbm-i-did-it-3e099/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/prediction-of-horse-racing-if-i-thought-that-the-collection-rate-exceeded-100-in-machine-learning-light-gbm-i-did-it-3e099/</guid>
      <description>#Thank you  Note!!! This article is completely disguised
I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for the person who stocked it.
Thanks to @hal27 for pointing it out, thank you.
・What I did I made a fatal mistake from the scraping stage. I was going to get the data for the previous 3 races from the time of the race, but in fact I was getting the information for the latest 3 races from the scraping execution time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A python beginner, I was able to hit the triad in less than a year of horse racing.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-python-beginner-i-was-able-to-hit-the-triad-in-less-than-a-year-of-horse-racing.-99927/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-python-beginner-i-was-able-to-hit-the-triad-in-less-than-a-year-of-horse-racing.-99927/</guid>
      <description># **Introduction**  I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I will omit the explanation of horse racing terms. I think it is read by people who are interested in horse racing.
Information published on netkeiba.com (information taken by scraping) There are various types such as pedigree, running time, and mileage. As a premise, the scraped data is used as a model When I fit it, I don&amp;rsquo;t expect anything. It is necessary to select, organize and analyze information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Verification] There is no easy way to exceed 100% recovery rate for horse racing just because it is deep-planned.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/verification-there-is-no-easy-way-to-exceed-100-recovery-rate-for-horse-racing-just-because-it-is-deep-planned.-3f215/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/verification-there-is-no-easy-way-to-exceed-100-recovery-rate-for-horse-racing-just-because-it-is-deep-planned.-3f215/</guid>
      <description># Now, the beginning of the mystery solving  Original article: With a deep learning, the recovery rate can exceed 100% in horse racing
First try to move I will purchase the program and try it. As described in the explanation, basically it worked with copy and paste, but the following two places did not work as they are, so I fixed it here.
 Parsing date data Column names of features used for learning and inference  It doesn&amp;rsquo;t look exactly the same because it contains random elements, but the graphs also moved in roughly the same way, so it seems to have been reproduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] With deep learning, you can exceed 100% recovery rate in horse racing</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/with-deep-learning-you-can-exceed-100-recovery-rate-in-horse-racing-334a8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/with-deep-learning-you-can-exceed-100-recovery-rate-in-horse-racing-334a8/</guid>
      <description>![4370674310_b118d0f62a_c.jpg](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/280076/a136d9bb-956d-2b10-6418-85302ddbbc07.jpeg)  pohotos by Ronnie Macdonald
It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I was told that &amp;ldquo;AI takes away human work&amp;rdquo; **, but now some people say that &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m in a period of disillusionment&amp;rdquo; **. Thanks to that, I was not robbed of my work, and I am swayed by a crowded train every day. The scams that rob you are also a good thing.
While the development of such AI seems to take a little longer, it is now easy to obtain an environment for learning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>