<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BeautifulSoup on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/beautifulsoup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BeautifulSoup on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/beautifulsoup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] COVID-19 Hokkaido Data Edition (1) Initial data creation by scraping</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/covid-19-hokkaido-data-edition-1-initial-data-creation-by-scraping-b4798/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/covid-19-hokkaido-data-edition-1-initial-data-creation-by-scraping-b4798/</guid>
      <description>## Table of contents  COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition (1) Initial data creation by scraping etc. ←This article! COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition ②Open data + automatic update COVID-19 Hokkaido data edition ③ Fully automated
![Screenshot 2020-03-10 17.25.46.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/73197/db6e9de7-3071-9836-9aba-(be5d04c240d3.png)
Introduction Tokyo official corona virus protection sitewasreleasedbyTokyoandCodeforJapan,anditssourcecodewasreleasedonGitHubunderMITlicense&amp;hellip;Inotherwords,eveninotherprefectures,youcancreateawebapplicationthatvisualizesinthesameway(ifyoucanpreparesimilardata)(althoughyouactuallyneedserverresourcesetc.). This is a groundbreaking initiative.
Well, that&amp;rsquo;s why the movements around the country have become more active, and in Hokkaido, volunteers with diverse backgrounds such as Code for Sapporo, IT companies in Hokkaido, and local government employees JUST Road IT was formed, and a project that was forked from Tokyo on March 6 was released at noon on March 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to make a crawler-Basic</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-make-a-crawler-basic-c972f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-make-a-crawler-basic-c972f/</guid>
      <description>This is the first day of LAPRAS Output Relay!  Hello! This is @Chanmoro, a LAPRAS crawler engineer! This time, LAPRAS members will output articles daily by the end of March, entitled LAPRAS Output Relay! Study sessions and conferences have been canceled due to the recent corona shock, but I hope that this LAPRAS output relay will be useful for engineers&amp;rsquo; motivation to input and output as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Patent Analysis] I made a patent map in Python without spending money</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/patent-analysis-i-made-a-patent-map-in-python-without-spending-money-5966d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/patent-analysis-i-made-a-patent-map-in-python-without-spending-money-5966d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I thought it would be a good idea to do a patent analysis, so I decided to give it a try. Specifically, for patent analysis, for example, there is the following plot. (The figure is quoted from J-STORE Manual) The vertical axis shows the patent applicant, the horizontal axis shows the year the patent was issued, and the size of the circle shows the number of patents. This is called the bubble chart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Scraping with Tor in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/scraping-with-tor-in-python-81f4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/scraping-with-tor-in-python-81f4b/</guid>
      <description>## Note  :warning: This article does not recommend scraping with Tor.
Scraping is basically okay, but if you are prohibited by the terms of use of the target site or if you put an excessive load on the server of the target site, you may be punished.
What is Tor It is a technology that anonymizes the connection route. Theoretically, it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to determine who accessed using Tor.
Execution environment Homebrew 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Atcoder][C&#43;&#43;]I made a test automation tool that can be used during the contest</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/atcoderc-i-made-a-test-automation-tool-that-can-be-used-during-the-contest-a542c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/atcoderc-i-made-a-test-automation-tool-that-can-be-used-during-the-contest-a542c/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m doing Atcoder (competitive programming) as a hobby, but I&#39;ve been slowing down recently.  I think it would be nice to automate the test work during the contest, I made a test automation tool with python.
Introduction Below are more features than the homebrew tools introduced in this article.
 https://github.com/kyuridenamida/atcoder-tools https://github.com/nodchip/OnlineJudgeHelper  Please compare the above when using.
1. What has been achieved  Automatically get test cases from Atcoder problem page without overloading the server Build and grade the created code (c++) before submitting, and judge AC, WA, TLE, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s automatically display the lyrics of the song playing on iTunes with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-automatically-display-the-lyrics-of-the-song-playing-on-itunes-with-python-4d388/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-automatically-display-the-lyrics-of-the-song-playing-on-itunes-with-python-4d388/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There are times when you want to display lyrics while playing a song in iTunes (the name has changed from Catalina to music). However, it is troublesome to manually search and display the lyrics each time the song changes. Let Python do the hassle.
(Updated January 4, 2020) Improved. → &amp;ldquo;[Let&amp;rsquo;s automatically display the lyrics of the song playing on iTunes with Python (improved version)]&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/saba/items/22b44e1045dbc3f9b0bc)&amp;quot;
#Thing you want to do Play music with &amp;ldquo;Music&amp;rdquo;, a standard Mac app, and automatically display the lyrics on the lyrics site each time the song switches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Notify the chat of new articles of Qiita Organization to improve learning efficiency of the organization!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/notify-the-chat-of-new-articles-of-qiita-organization-to-improve-learning-efficiency-of-the-organization-fbebd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/notify-the-chat-of-new-articles-of-qiita-organization-to-improve-learning-efficiency-of-the-organization-fbebd/</guid>
      <description>We are promoting the output activity of Qiita articles in-house. It&#39;s G-awa. The learning method using output is highly recommended and is highly recommended. However, on the other hand, it is difficult for one person to continue alone, so it is important for the team and organization to support each other. If you are alone, you tend to break your heart.  &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-b_wxsoyflcs/WZP38JpI0LI/AAAAABGDA/troMJOw1KGUpq7yueRTgIdPc85o_kexXQCLcBGAs/s400/tamashii_nukeru_man.png&amp;rdquo; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; →=&amp;quot;30%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt; //2.bp.blogspot.com/-aIs9YKfGlEk/Vy2v2rXYgjI/AAAAAAAA6b0/PuaALahZfJsIluEeFOKgfgOy43qrc8bBQCLcB/s450/enjin_circle_wakamono.png&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;40%&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;
I read yesterday&amp;rsquo;s article and it was very helpful :thumbsup: It&amp;rsquo;s a great environment for engineers to grow when there is an environment in which they can encourage each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Meteorology x Python-From weather data acquisition to spectrum analysis-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/meteorology-x-python-from-weather-data-acquisition-to-spectrum-analysis-d25b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/meteorology-x-python-from-weather-data-acquisition-to-spectrum-analysis-d25b8/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve covered some ways to handle [Data from the Meteorological Agency](https://www.jma.go.jp/jma/menu/menureport.html)insomearticlessofar,butI&#39;veseenadifferentdataacquisitionmethod(currentsituation).,Thismethodisthemostefficient), and I will try to lighten the analysis of the acquired data.  ・Meteorology x Python ~ Automatic acquisition of AMeDAS point data ~ https://qiita.com/OSAKO/items/264c77b70843045bc12b ・Meteorology x Python-Automatic acquisition of AMeDAS point data (extra edition)- https://qiita.com/OSAKO/items/505ecee67df424963e53 ・Weather x Ruby ~Ruby scraping using Mechanize~ https://qiita.com/OSAKO/items/3c1cac0b5448be9ab243 #1. Crawling ▶ I want to get the numeric values or character strings embedded in the following table format all at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to predict horse racing by doing everything from data collection to deep learning</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-horse-racing-by-doing-everything-from-data-collection-to-deep-learning-55e49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-horse-racing-by-doing-everything-from-data-collection-to-deep-learning-55e49/</guid>
      <description># Overview  A student majoring in information systems at a certain T university. While looking at various articles of Qiita, I found such an article.
 If you have deep learning, you can exceed 100% recovery rate in horse racing  Regarding the 100% recovery rate in this article, it is unclear whether it will be valid in other periods because the number of betting tickets that were simulated for purchase is small.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>