<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> activation function on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/activation-function/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  activation function on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/activation-function/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>List of activation functions (2020)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/list-of-activation-functions-2020-73cd4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/list-of-activation-functions-2020-73cd4/</guid>
      <description># Target audience  I summarized what kind of activation function there are. **Latest Swish and Mish, plus tanhExp! ** I&amp;rsquo;m targeting a layer where I can&amp;rsquo;t find something good even if I search the list. New ones will be added as soon as they are found. If you have information on new functions or functions on the TODO list below, please let us know!
#TODO list
 Look up additional information for the hardShrink function Look up supplementary information of softShrink function Check supplementary information of Threshold function Look up supplementary information of logSigmoid function Look up additional information for the tanhShrink function Look up additional information for hardtanh function Check supplementary information of ReLU6 function Look up additional information for CELU function Check the supplementary information of the softmin function Look up additional information for the logSoftmax function Examine some unimplemented functions -Pytorch -What is the MultiheadAttention function -Learning method of PReLU function -Implementation of RReLU function -What is the cumulative distribution function that appears in the GELU function?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>