<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> PyPI on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/pypi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  PyPI on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/pypi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I will create a Python directory structure that I will not regret later</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-will-create-a-python-directory-structure-that-i-will-not-regret-later-aa427/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-will-create-a-python-directory-structure-that-i-will-not-regret-later-aa427/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve learned a little about directory structure a little after I started programming in Python, so I&#39;ll summarize it.  At first, I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand it at all, and I was doing a lot of googling, so I wrote the steps so that even beginners can understand.
The following is a memo by an engineer who has been developing in Python for about 6 months. ** We would appreciate if you could give us a lot of suggestions, suggestions, and questions from beginners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18 beautiful Python terms you want to read aloud. R18 with example sentence</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/18-beautiful-python-terms-you-want-to-read-aloud.-r18-with-example-sentence-519b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/18-beautiful-python-terms-you-want-to-read-aloud.-r18-with-example-sentence-519b2/</guid>
      <description>#Background  Python, which is known as a frozen tuna script language, It is also famous for its many beautifully named packages.
 PyPy pypan pypants  Reference: 7 Python terms to read aloud http://doloopwhile.hatenablog.com/entry/20120120/1327062714
Enchanted by these beautifully named packages, How beautifully named packages exist **I really decided to investigate. **
The reference information is a little old from 2012, If you look again now, you will surely find a more beautiful name!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>