<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> C# on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/c#/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  C# on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/c#/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] RaspberryPi sensor sample file distribution URL summary</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/raspberrypi-sensor-sample-file-distribution-url-summary-c0e65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/raspberrypi-sensor-sample-file-distribution-url-summary-c0e65/</guid>
      <description>#RaspberryPi sensor sample file distribution URL summary  The company that sells the sensors collectively records the sample files on a CD and sells them as a set, but I summarized the companies that publish the files on the Web.
##OSOYOO OSOYOO Raspberry Pi Learn electronic work kit Beginners&amp;rsquo; practice parts set Rasppie 11 actual example Circuit wiring diagram and sample sketch programming Raspberry Pi super introduction starter learning kit LED control switch I2C LCD temperature/humidity sensor micro servo human sensor A/D converter Buzzer Atmospheric pressure sensor Relay module control Infrared remote control etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Differences that C# engineers felt when they first learned python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/differences-that-c#-engineers-felt-when-they-first-learned-python-29944/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/differences-that-c#-engineers-felt-when-they-first-learned-python-29944/</guid>
      <description>Hi, this is [Muscle Training Clinical Engineering Engineer ken](https://twitter.com/ce_fitness_note).  This is my first post on Qiita.
I usually use C# to develop medical systems. I decided to focus on machine learning, so I started learning python.
Even though I learned about it, I went around Progate&amp;rsquo;s python course, but I will briefly summarize the differences between C# and how to write.
If you usually use C#, C++, VB and want to learn python from now on, I think that learning will be better if you know the difference between the two in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 20&#39;s Engineer Rating Check CODING-Special Study Session After Scheduled-Opening [In-house Study Session-Paiza]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/20s-engineer-rating-check-coding-special-study-session-after-scheduled-opening-in-house-study-session-paiza-0d319/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/20s-engineer-rating-check-coding-special-study-session-after-scheduled-opening-in-house-study-session-paiza-0d319/</guid>
      <description>Premise   My current affiliation is the system development department, and the department that refurbishes and maintains existing packages. We are active in a cycle of renovating and releasing our long-lived in-house package (LAMP configuration) once every two months. The members of the development department range from those with deep experience as engineers to employees who are new graduates.
In that situation, I checked the rating using Paiza, and it is a report and impression.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>