<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> time series data on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/time-series-data/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  time series data on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/time-series-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Time series plot started-python version-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/time-series-plot-started-python-version-9e6b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/time-series-plot-started-python-version-9e6b8/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 22nd day article of MicroAd Advent Calendar 2019.
Thing you want to do Time series plots are a very useful tool when visualizing log data. Until now, I have lived such a life that I replaced the dates on the horizontal axis with numbers and plotted and escaped. However, it&amp;rsquo;s different now. You can now plot well with the horizontal axis set to time series!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A struggle note after a machine learning amateur who changed jobs to a non-IT company was assigned to an AI project</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-struggle-note-after-a-machine-learning-amateur-who-changed-jobs-to-a-non-it-company-was-assigned-to-an-ai-project-11386/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-struggle-note-after-a-machine-learning-amateur-who-changed-jobs-to-a-non-it-company-was-assigned-to-an-ai-project-11386/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is the 8th day of How I learned machine learning by Nikkei xTECH Business AI ② Advent Calendar 2019. We hope that it will be helpful for those who are new to the market.
Programming experience  School days (robot engineering, fluid mechanics):  :new: C/C++; embedded, computational fluid dynamics, research tools :new: Matlab; A little in modern control theory   Previous job (ADAS):  C/C++; embedded, in-house tool :new: Python; Algorithm prototyping and data organization *Not related to AI   Current position (construction and civil engineering construction management):  C++; built-in Python; Machine Learning/Deep Learning :new: JavaScript (Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time series data abnormality detection for beginners</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/time-series-data-abnormality-detection-for-beginners-8dfa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/time-series-data-abnormality-detection-for-beginners-8dfa0/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article was posted as the sixth day of Cisco Advent Calendar 2019 by Cisco Systems LLC.
Seven years have passed since the SuperVision team at the University of Toronto, Canada won the ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Challenge (ILSVRC) 2012 in 2012. At this time, by using a model using deep learning, modeling in machine learning and deep learning is often done in the third AI boom, and it is common sense nowadays to use machine learning/deep learning for AI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>