<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> YouTube on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/youtube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  YouTube on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube live It analyzes the sentiment of the comment and judges the emo part from Youtube LIve.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/youtube-live-it-analyzes-the-sentiment-of-the-comment-and-judges-the-emo-part-from-youtube-live.-fa198/</guid>
      <description># TL;DR  It is a suggestion and experiment that it is possible to extract &amp;ldquo;emo&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;highlight&amp;rdquo; with better accuracy than just the number of comments per hour by performing sentiment analysis of comments on Youtube live. ..
In fact, we were able to get the result that the accuracy is likely to improve compared to just looking at the number of comments.
#Introduction
Last time, I borrowed COTOHA API and tried to think freely, not practical Article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upload videos using YouTube API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/upload-videos-using-youtube-api-5a728/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/upload-videos-using-youtube-api-5a728/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  This is an article that uploads videos using the youtube API. The language is Python3. You should proceed according to the following official document, but I have added some addictive points.
YouTube API-Upload Video
Environment  MacOS Python3.8 Pycharm  As a premise, it is assumed that the project has been created with GCP.
Advance preparation Install google-api-python-client Install the library to use google&amp;rsquo;s API.
$ pip install google-api-python-client GCP application registration 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The guy who predicts the number of views from the title of Jarjar&#39;s video</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-guy-who-predicts-the-number-of-views-from-the-title-of-jarjars-video-06f6f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-guy-who-predicts-the-number-of-views-from-the-title-of-jarjars-video-06f6f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This time, I will talk about making a model that predicts the number of views from the title of Jarjar&amp;rsquo;s video. Since NLP is a complete amateur, I tried to imitate the appearance by referring to the articles of other people.
What is jar jar JALJAL is a comedy group with the most momentum*, consisting of Junpei Goto and Shusuke Fukutoku, who belong to the Yoshimoto Kogyo Tokyo headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Youtube data in Python using Youtube Data API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-youtube-data-in-python-using-youtube-data-api-7c98e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-youtube-data-in-python-using-youtube-data-api-7c98e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Recently, I am investigating whether various data can be acquired using API. Since I investigated and practiced how to get information such as the number of video views and likes using the Youtube Data API, I wrote a memorandum. #reference I have referred to the following when using the Youtube Data API.
 Youtube video search with Python Outline of YouTube Data API Youtube Data API Reference  #Preparing to use API ##Youtube Data API registration You need a Google account to get Youtube Data API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s use pytube</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/lets-use-pytube-4ac9c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/lets-use-pytube-4ac9c/</guid>
      <description>#[IPFactory Advent Calender 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/ipfactory) Day 4  I do not have enough knowledge to write a large article, but I will write it on the 4th day. I&amp;rsquo;m pycys, 1 year from ISC, belonging to IPFactory.
What is pytube Python library. You can easily download videos on YouTube.
##environment
 Windows 10 Pro Python 3.7.4  Let&amp;rsquo;s install pip install pytube If you type the above into bash or command prompt, it will be installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Youtuber Tech Tech Youtubers to Recommend to Engineers!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5-youtuber-tech-tech-youtubers-to-recommend-to-engineers-c2f8b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5-youtuber-tech-tech-youtubers-to-recommend-to-engineers-c2f8b/</guid>
      <description># Able Programming  Describes the python library required for machine learning and machine learning methods. Even beginners can learn about machine learning. Able Programming Sirien Sentai JUN TV The information that is available only to the engineers who are active engineers in Silicon Valley and who are working in Silicon Valley. Recommended for those who want to work or start a business in Silicon Valley in the future. Sirien Sentai JUN TV</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>