<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mac on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/mac/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mac on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/mac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A note on creating a python development environment on macOS Catalina</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/521c67de9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/521c67de9/</guid>
      <description>*Memo will be updated at any time*  Aiming to build a python development environment
In the environment I upgraded from Mojave to Catalina, when I did it normally, it did not work as expected with python3 or pip3 due to the difference in version, so I try using pyenv and see if it works.
It&amp;rsquo;s actually better to use Docker, but for now&amp;hellip;
homebrew Start from here.
/bin/bash -c &amp;quot;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] Ikiri high school students will explain blockchain to beginners in 10 minutes! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f4991357e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f4991357e/</guid>
      <description>#1. About this article  ##1-1. Introduction This article was touched by me as a high school student when I received [Udemy: An Introduction to Blockchain Development from Scratch Beginning with Python Taught by Active Silicon Valley Engineers](https://www.udemy.com/share/1021OSAkIbdVdQQXo=/) , I wrote this article with the hope that everyone reading this article should attend. I completed this lesson in 2 days, so if you are already accustomed to development, I think it is sufficiently possible to understand and implement in 1 day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Only 8 Techniques to Watch Your Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ab06bbe3c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ab06bbe3c/</guid>
      <description>#Beware of data scientists  As of 2019, there should be a lot of people out there who want to be distracted by data scientists. However, those who don&amp;rsquo;t know how to be more pretentious than others. I completely removed the muddy data scientist aspect and wondered how I could be distracted. You can put your conclusion into practice immediately tomorrow. If you want to be a data scientist, give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Update Python on Mac from 2 to 3</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ff40e57d0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ff40e57d0/</guid>
      <description># Overview  This article is a step-by-step article on how a beginner himself developed a coupon distribution service for iPhone with RESTful API and swift. It was a very detouring implementation because we implemented it while examining the technical elements one by one.
Python is originally installed on the Mac, but the version is old as of OS 10.15. When actually writing Python, everyone seems to have been updated to 3 series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Get started with Amazon DynamoDB from Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fc34447eb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fc34447eb/</guid>
      <description>#0. Introduction  Let&amp;rsquo;s try various services that AWS recommends serverless. This time, I will use Amazon DynamoDB from Python.
1. Build a Python environment on your Mac There is no environment in the first place, so it is from the environment construction.
Build the environment by referring to the following (maybe it is as it is&amp;hellip;).
 Installing Python3 on Mac-Qiita Use pyenv to build Python environment on Mac-Qiita  If you do not set .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Text expansion using Mac service</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/faa5dd139/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/faa5dd139/</guid>
      <description># Service that evaluates and rewrites text selection range in Python  After reading the blog below, I was impressed and created the Python version. (The following article is a Ruby version)
I&amp;rsquo;ll write it down in the hope that it will be noticeable to everyone in Pythonista.
Reference site
  [Two functions &amp;ldquo;Automator&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo; that must be used if you are using Mac]](http://r-kurain.hatenablog.com/entry/20130219/1361270262)
  Debugging Automator</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>