<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> mathematical model on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/mathematical-model/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  mathematical model on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/mathematical-model/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s calculate the transition of basic reproduction number of new coronavirus by prefecture</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e68b34b60/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e68b34b60/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The center of infection with the new coronavirus infectious disease (COVID-19) is already shifting from mainland China to Europe and the United States, and urgent situations such as restricting free border movement within the EU region and issuing curfew It&amp;rsquo;s happening. In Japan, the threat of the new coronavirus began to be recognized on February 3, 2020, when the Diamond Princess entered Yokohama Port, on February 25, when the government announced its basic policy, and on February 28, in Hokkaido.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Understanding by Bayes&#39; theorem Significance of narrowing down the target of PCR test for new coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ee345ba45/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ee345ba45/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The number of people infected with the novel coronavirus infection (COVID-19) spread from China to the world, and as of March 14, 2020, the number of infected people was 145,637 and 5,436 dead, which is a very high number. However, looking at the situation in Japan, the number of infected people was 734, 9.1% of Korea&amp;rsquo;s 8086 and 4.2% of Italy&amp;rsquo;s 17,660. It has been pointed out that the reason for this apparent difference is that Japan is limiting the number of PCR tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Hypothesis of why the new coronavirus is not so many infected in urban areas such as Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/72286382b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/72286382b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  If you check the transition of the number of people infected with the new coronavirus infectious disease (COVID-19) with Map of new coronavirus infected people by prefecture, etc. As of March 7, 2020, there are 98 people in Hokkaido, 21 people in Sagamihara City, etc., while there are a considerable number of people locally, 73 people in Tokyo, 41 people in Osaka, 8 people in Kyoto and 8 people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>