<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> regular expression on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/regular-expression/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  regular expression on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/regular-expression/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular expressions that you can learn easily with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/regular-expressions-that-you-can-learn-easily-with-python-43b3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/regular-expressions-that-you-can-learn-easily-with-python-43b3d/</guid>
      <description>Although there are some cases where regular expressions are usually needed, I have not studied it systematically, so I will organize and summarize it. The language is Python.  It&amp;rsquo;s quite long. If you read this, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t get angry even if you tweet &amp;ldquo;I fully understand Python regular expressions&amp;rdquo;.
What is a regular expression in the first place? Regular Expression is in English. This is an expression (processing) that performs various processing by specifying a specific pattern when performing special operations related to character strings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Regular expression] Advanced string replacement using re.sub</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/regular-expression-advanced-string-replacement-using-re.sub-a42ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/regular-expression-advanced-string-replacement-using-re.sub-a42ca/</guid>
      <description># table of contents   Conclusion What is re.sub When to use Pass character string to replacement target repl -Commentary What is Advanced Replacement -Pass function to replacement target repl -Pass function with two or more arguments to replacement target repl -Advanced string replacement example -[Supplement] Advanced string replacement without using re.sub  #Conclusion
 You can pass a function to the repl replacement target repl You can pass a function with two or more arguments to the replacement target repl of re.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>