<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Vue.js on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/vue.js/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Vue.js on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/vue.js/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 3 months after graduating from programming school</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0f652c07c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0f652c07c/</guid>
      <description>In October 2019, I attended a certain programming school where I often see advertisements on youtube, and since November I have been in my current position as a machine learning engineer and data scientist.  Three months after graduating, I would like to write about what I learned from the school, what was useful, and what is difficult now.
Biography April 2015 Served as a research and development position for a food company for 4 years July 2019 Start of programming school learning October 2019, graduated from programming school November 2019 Job change as a machine learning engineer and data scientist</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried a visual regression test on GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8002695c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8002695c3/</guid>
      <description>#Motivation  Hello @glassmonkey. CI is Github Action. Since I wanted to try using images if I did CI, I tried a visual regression test easily. I made it in a rush, so I would appreciate any feedback.
#What is a visual regression test?
The explanation on Astamuse-sama&amp;rsquo;s blog was easy to understand, so I will quote it.
 The visual regression test is a visual regression test, specifically a test that takes a screenshot and extracts the differences.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>