<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GUI on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/gui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GUI on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/gui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Embed matplotlib graph in Tkinter</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/embed-matplotlib-graph-in-tkinter-45953/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/embed-matplotlib-graph-in-tkinter-45953/</guid>
      <description>#1.First of all  Recently, there were the following hurdles regarding programming.
(1) I want to create a GUI program in Python. → You can use Tkinter (2) I want to display some calculation results on a graph. → You can use matplotlib (3) I want to embed the graph written in matplotlib in (2) into Tkinter in (1). → NG
I tried to get over it by tampering with the example code, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw a graph with PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</guid>
      <description># What you can do by reading this article  With PySimple GUI, you can:
 You can draw bar graphs, line graphs, etc. Graph that refreshes display periodically  For the basic operation of PySimpleGUI, please refer to If you use Tkinter, try using PySimpleGUI.
Overview I think there are many people who analyze data as a way to use Python. Also, some people may want to visualize the results of analysis as line graphs or bar graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a drawing quiz with kivy&#43;PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/make-a-drawing-quiz-with-kivy-pytorch-75f1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/make-a-drawing-quiz-with-kivy-pytorch-75f1b/</guid>
      <description>#Summary  This article is the second day of Docomo Advent Calendar.
Do you know the drawing quiz? It is a quiz in which the questioner draws a picture and guesses what other people are drawing. There are many apps.
If you recognize the image drawn by the user and guess it, you can play it alone, so PyTorchofthemachinelearninglibrarywillcontinue.//pytorch.org/)andkivy, a library that can create apps, will be combined.
What is # kivy?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>