<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> statistics on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/statistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  statistics on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of Markov chain and Monte Carlo method</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-markov-chain-and-monte-carlo-method-d1089/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-markov-chain-and-monte-carlo-method-d1089/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Currently, I am learning about Bayesian statistics. From that, I will summarize the Markov chain Monte Carlo method. In this article, I will explain the outline of Markov chain and Monte Carlo method as an entrance.
Next article
Here is the book that I referred to this time.
 Bayes statistics from the basics: a practical introduction to the Hamiltonian Monte Carlo method  What is Markov chain Monte Carlo In Bayesian inference, when the observed data is $X$ and the set of unobserved variables such as parameters and latent variables is $Z$, consider the probabilistic model $P(X,Z)$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carefully understand the exponential distribution and draw it in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/carefully-understand-the-exponential-distribution-and-draw-it-in-python-5809f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/carefully-understand-the-exponential-distribution-and-draw-it-in-python-5809f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The exponential distribution that always appears when studying statistics, but the formula of the probability distribution in the example did not come into my head at all, so I thought about trying to understand it carefully from the derivation of the probability distribution. I also draw in Python to grab the image.
##reference In understanding the exponential distribution and drawing the distribution, I have referred to the following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of statistical data analysis methods using Python that can be used in business</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-statistical-data-analysis-methods-using-python-that-can-be-used-in-business-21c19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-statistical-data-analysis-methods-using-python-that-can-be-used-in-business-21c19/</guid>
      <description># Overview  I think it is very important to verify the effects after conducting various prototypes with WEB services, I think that basic statistics can be used enough as a method. This time, we summarized the method of statistical data analysis using Python+JupyterLab (Docker) for the purpose of basic statistics, verification of the effects of prototypes that can be used in business, and data analysis.
The notebook I used this time is also available below, so please refer to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to summarize the relationship between probability distributions starting from the Bernoulli distribution</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-relationship-between-probability-distributions-starting-from-the-bernoulli-distribution-10d19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-summarize-the-relationship-between-probability-distributions-starting-from-the-bernoulli-distribution-10d19/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For the purpose of understanding the relationship between probability distributions, we have implemented and summarized functions that generate various probability distributions starting from Bernoulli distribution in Python. This article is for the following people.
 I have studied the basic probability distribution I have touched Python I want to understand the relationship between probability distributions  The implemented Python functions are as follows. The function names are bernolli and binom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(First post) Talk about numerical calculation of influenza and new type pneumonia coronavirus with Tensorflow</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/first-post-talk-about-numerical-calculation-of-influenza-and-new-type-pneumonia-coronavirus-with-tensorflow-acd6e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/first-post-talk-about-numerical-calculation-of-influenza-and-new-type-pneumonia-coronavirus-with-tensorflow-acd6e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Summary  Flu Coronavirus  I analyzed about using a mathematical model.
###background This time I tried to numerically calculate the infectious disease model, but please understand that I am not a professional of mathematical models such as infectious disease model. Since I majored in physics at university and graduate school, I have only touched computer science a little. The background of this post is that I&amp;rsquo;m interested in coronavirus, which is a hot topic right now, for quantitative analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carefully understand Poisson distribution and draw with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/carefully-understand-poisson-distribution-and-draw-with-python-83682/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/carefully-understand-poisson-distribution-and-draw-with-python-83682/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The Poisson distribution that always appears when studying statistics, but the formula for the probability distribution did not come into my mind at all, so I tried to understand it carefully from the derivation of the probability distribution. I also draw in Python to grab the image.
##reference I have referred to the following to understand the Poisson distribution and draw the distribution.
 [University Mathematics] Poisson distribution (specific examples and their meanings, Poisson&amp;rsquo;s limit theorem) [Probability Statistics]  Introduction to Statistics (Basic Statistics I) What is Poisson distribution?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By clarifying the difference between statistics and machine learning, I can see why many business companies cannot use machine learning!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</guid>
      <description>#What is the difference between statistics and machine learning? Why can&#39;t I predict from machine learning today and make money?  Perhaps everyone wonders when they start studying machine learning. And why can&amp;rsquo;t many business companies use it for their daily work today? The question also comes up. There are various documents, but I was having trouble comprehending them, so I rearranged them myself. I&amp;rsquo;m putting together a lot of information by combining information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to learn newbies before they get into Bayesian statistics</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-newbies-before-they-get-into-bayesian-statistics-d02a8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-learn-newbies-before-they-get-into-bayesian-statistics-d02a8/</guid>
      <description># Purpose of this article and target audience  This article provides a guide to those who have barely studied statistics before being able to speak brilliantly about Young&amp;rsquo;s statistics in the now known Bayesian stats.
The goal of this article is to be able to tell correct things about Bayesian statistics with a doya face, and to be able to argue with people who are familiar with statistics.
Please note that studying this article will not make you familiar with Bayesian statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collection of Python statistical techniques-Statistical analysis against Python-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/collection-of-python-statistical-techniques-statistical-analysis-against-python-3a3fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/collection-of-python-statistical-techniques-statistical-analysis-against-python-3a3fe/</guid>
      <description>This is the [Open and Reproducible Science Advent Calendar 2019](https://adventar.org/calendars/4523): Day 13 article.  Article purpose S is the name for statistical analysis. But there are people like me who want to do anything with just Python. For such people, I will introduce useful libraries and techniques for doing statistical analysis in Python. There are many articles and books on the same subject, but I will focus on those that are not often introduced elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better than a horse race, a boat race, or a bicycle race? I think I found a way to win at the casino. .. .. This can go!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/better-than-a-horse-race-a-boat-race-or-a-bicycle-race-i-think-i-found-a-way-to-win-at-the-casino.-..-..-this-can-go-3a0d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/better-than-a-horse-race-a-boat-race-or-a-bicycle-race-i-think-i-found-a-way-to-win-at-the-casino.-..-..-this-can-go-3a0d1/</guid>
      <description># (Postscript) I&#39;m sorry!  The results of np.random.randint and random.randint are different, It turns out that you lose at the casino. For more information: https://qiita.com/mnoda/items/a75d350e1aa432eaf4f3
I think I&amp;rsquo;ve found a way to win at the casino (in Python). .. .. This can go! AI betting on horse racing has recently been talked about at Qiita, but I tried to program it from a different angle. I&amp;rsquo;m not a &amp;ldquo;professional&amp;rdquo; in programming, but I&amp;rsquo;m scared of making it myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matching application I tried to take statistics of strong people &amp; created a machine learning model</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/matching-application-i-tried-to-take-statistics-of-strong-people-created-a-machine-learning-model-54bab/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/matching-application-i-tried-to-take-statistics-of-strong-people-created-a-machine-learning-model-54bab/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hello everyone.
Do you use a matching app? ! I feel good as one of those who have recently matched with a matching app.
By the way, the matching app I was using was able to refer to the data of other popular members. (Probably people who have received more than 100 like are displayed.)
When I saw it, I was disappointed.
&amp;ldquo;Like, I didn&amp;rsquo;t get 100&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; ** &amp;ldquo;I want to be a man who exceeds 100&amp;rdquo; **</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>