<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Development Process on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/development-process/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Development Process on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/development-process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python beginner publishes web application using machine learning [Part 1] Introduction</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-beginner-publishes-web-application-using-machine-learning-part-1-introduction-52dc4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-beginner-publishes-web-application-using-machine-learning-part-1-introduction-52dc4/</guid>
      <description>### Purpose of this article  Obstetrician and Gynecologist Tomi&amp;lsquo;sarticle[[[Self-studypossible]LearningroadmapformachinelearningforPythonbeginners]](https://obgynai.Itriedtocreatetheroadmapmyselfbyreferringto(com/self-study-python-machine-learning/).
This article is the first in a series of memo articles. For readability, the article is divided into pieces! (After writing, we will publish an article that summarizes everything)
###Self-introduction My name is Tsuba Mukku. After graduating from Kyushu University, I re-entered the National University School of Medicine. While aiming to graduate from medical school and pass the national exam of doctors, I am also learning pure mathematics and computer science (I also take classes in mathematics and information science).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Articles that will allow system development with Django (Python)_Introduction</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/articles-that-will-allow-system-development-with-django-python_introduction-ed641/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/articles-that-will-allow-system-development-with-django-python_introduction-ed641/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Programming such as Python has become more familiar than before There are various obstacles to the challenge of service development.
** &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t graduate from the copybooks for introductory books and tutorials&amp;rdquo; ** &amp;ldquo;I tried making it with copy and paste, but I can&amp;rsquo;t arrange it after that&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I am not confident that the code I wrote is correct&amp;rdquo;
When these are analyzed, they can be decomposed into 5 factors as shown in the figure below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>