<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataScience on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/datascience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataScience on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/datascience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to build Python and Jupyter execution environment with VS Code</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-build-python-and-jupyter-execution-environment-with-vs-code-f0788/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-build-python-and-jupyter-execution-environment-with-vs-code-f0788/</guid>
      <description>I have summarized how to build Python and Jupyter execution environment with VS Code. I use Anaconda.  Also, I think that many people who analyze data with Python use Jupyter notebook and Jupyter Lab from their browsers. VS Code is also recommended for such people.
Also, this article is part of the article How to create a Python package using VS Code.
We will proceed on the assumption that Anaconda has been downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Python] First data analysis/machine learning (Kaggle)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-first-data-analysis-machine-learning-kaggle-8d77e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-first-data-analysis-machine-learning-kaggle-8d77e/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  As I was about to get a job (spring break in the fourth year of university), I suddenly wanted to become a data scientist, so I started working on Kaggle for the time being.
This time, I worked on a tutorial of Kaggle&amp;quot;Titanic&amp;rdquo;.
I have experience in statistical analysis in my research, but since I do not understand machine learning at all, I decided to study with reference to the code of the incredibly excellent person!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Looking Back on iOS&#39;Healthcare App&#39; 2019</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/looking-back-on-ioshealthcare-app-2019-0a3cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/looking-back-on-ioshealthcare-app-2019-0a3cc/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 9th day of the Docomo Advent Calendar.  It is Yamamoto of DoCoMo. In my work, I am engaged in R&amp;amp;D related to healthcare. In this article, we will introduce how to utilize the data acquired by the iPhone Healthcare App.
■ Introduction □ Target person ・I am interested in healthcare using mobile wearable devices ・I would like to see the data of the iOS healthcare app ・Those who have reached this article</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Only 8 Techniques to Watch Your Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/only-8-techniques-to-watch-your-data-scientist-ab06b/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/only-8-techniques-to-watch-your-data-scientist-ab06b/</guid>
      <description>#Beware of data scientists  As of 2019, there should be a lot of people out there who want to be distracted by data scientists. However, those who don&amp;rsquo;t know how to be more pretentious than others. I completely removed the muddy data scientist aspect and wondered how I could be distracted. You can put your conclusion into practice immediately tomorrow. If you want to be a data scientist, give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [For data science] Oreole Jupyter cheat sheet [Jupyter Notebook/Lab]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-data-science-oreole-jupyter-cheat-sheet-jupyter-notebook-lab-0f5dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-data-science-oreole-jupyter-cheat-sheet-jupyter-notebook-lab-0f5dd/</guid>
      <description>I usually do **data analysis and model construction** mainly on Jupyter.  I will make a note of how many times I will research it. (Updated from time to time)
Development I want to reload the modified .py module Modules that have already been imported will be cached, or will not be updated when imported normally. ** You can reload (reimport) with the following. **
import importlib importlib.reload(hoge) # hoge is an imported module I didn&amp;rsquo;t know this much until recently, and I restarted every time, so it&amp;rsquo;s really a scale.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>