<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> hy on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/hy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  hy on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/hy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Try GUI programming with Hy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-gui-programming-with-hy-3e217/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-gui-programming-with-hy-3e217/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 16th day of [Lisp Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/lisp).  Summary of this article As an introduction to GUI programming in Hy, generative art using tkinter, a GUI library included in the Python standard library. Implement
It is a specification that you can change the parameter by key input in the figure drawing using the trigonometric function like this. Target audience  People who want to do GUI programming with Hy  Environment The author&amp;rsquo;s environment is as follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hy environment construction for Lisper who is not touching Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hy-environment-construction-for-lisper-who-is-not-touching-python-6a343/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hy-environment-construction-for-lisper-who-is-not-touching-python-6a343/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 15th day article of [Lisp Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/lisp).  Summary of this article Hy is a Clojure-like Lisp dialect that runs on Python&amp;rsquo;s Virtual Machine. For Lisper (mainly Clojurian) who has never touched Python, I will focus on how to build Hy environment.
Target audience  Lisper who has never touched Python (mainly Clojurian)  For an introductory document to Hy itself, I suggest you to refer to the official tutorial or the one written by my ancestors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Blender Add-on Tutorial with Hy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/do-blender-add-on-tutorial-with-hy-e0c75/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/do-blender-add-on-tutorial-with-hy-e0c75/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 8th day article from [Lisp Advent Carendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/lisp).  Summary of this article Using Hy, a Clojure-like Lisp dialect running on Python, let&amp;rsquo;s create an Add-on for the DCC tool Blender.
  Hy -Documents -GitHub repository
  Blender -https://www.blender.org -Blender 2.81 Reference Manual -Blender 2.81 Python API Documentation
  Target audience  People who want to do what they do in Python with Lisp People who want to play with Blender in Lisp  Environment The following is for Windows 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>