<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Finance on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Finance on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Stock Price Prediction by Machine Learning Numerai</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/stock-price-prediction-by-machine-learning-numerai-fb401/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The general public may not have heard about it, but there is a hedge fund called &amp;ldquo;Numerai&amp;rdquo;. It is a hedge fund that has been known a little in the neighborhood by being covered by media such as Wired and Forbes from the latter half of 2016 to the first half of 2017. This hedge fund is a so-called crowdsourcing type fund that operates based on the forecast results of stock prices by an unspecified number of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Note that the average pairwise correlation calculation in pandas was very easy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/note-that-the-average-pairwise-correlation-calculation-in-pandas-was-very-easy-f90c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/note-that-the-average-pairwise-correlation-calculation-in-pandas-was-very-easy-f90c4/</guid>
      <description>## What is average pairwise correlation  I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many people in the world need to do this calculation.
The average pairwise stock correlation is the average of the correlation coefficients of price movements between stocks. In general, during the crisis such as the Lehman shock or the European debt crisis, the market as a whole will fall sharply, and then it will rise sharply in reaction, and the correlation coefficient between stocks will increase.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>