<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Jupyter-notebook on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/jupyter-notebook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Jupyter-notebook on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/jupyter-notebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Memo about using Colab Pro for about 2 months (good point / bad point)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/memo-about-using-colab-pro-for-about-2-months-good-point-bad-point-c5822/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/memo-about-using-colab-pro-for-about-2-months-good-point-bad-point-c5822/</guid>
      <description># What is Google Colaboratory  A free Jupyter Notebook environment where you can write and run Python code in your browser. There are restrictions on use, but you can also use the GPU.
Colab Pro A paid version ($9.99/month) of Google Colaboratory. There are various advantages over the regular version. Currently US only (contract requires US address and credit card).
Since I live in the United States, I signed up for Colab Pro at the same time as Launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A python beginner, I was able to hit the triad in less than a year of horse racing.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-python-beginner-i-was-able-to-hit-the-triad-in-less-than-a-year-of-horse-racing.-99927/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-python-beginner-i-was-able-to-hit-the-triad-in-less-than-a-year-of-horse-racing.-99927/</guid>
      <description># **Introduction**  I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I will omit the explanation of horse racing terms. I think it is read by people who are interested in horse racing.
Information published on netkeiba.com (information taken by scraping) There are various types such as pedigree, running time, and mileage. As a premise, the scraped data is used as a model When I fit it, I don&amp;rsquo;t expect anything. It is necessary to select, organize and analyze information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupyter Notebook essential for software development</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/jupyter-notebook-essential-for-software-development-25a5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/jupyter-notebook-essential-for-software-development-25a5d/</guid>
      <description>Hello. I&#39;m a software engineer who makes various embedded systems, games, web apps, iOS apps, signage control systems, etc.  About two and a half years ago, I thought that I should write in Python as a general-purpose scripting language that is difficult to realize only with a shell, and I was trying to learn Python while suffering. Since I only use it occasionally, I was at a level where I forget how to write if and for loops every time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Complete Edition] Jupyter Notebook Shortcut</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/complete-edition-jupyter-notebook-shortcut-baa2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/complete-edition-jupyter-notebook-shortcut-baa2a/</guid>
      <description># Jupyter Notebook Shortcut  The shortcut list that appears in h in Jupyter Notebook has been translated into Japanese for both Windows and Mac. I searched, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a list of all Windows and Mac in Japanese, so maybe it&amp;rsquo;s in demand?
Only the commands that you should remember are in bold.
Windows Command mode    Shortcut key Description     F Search/Replace   Ctrl-Shift-F Open Command Palette   Ctrl-Shift-P Open Command Palette   Enter Enter edit mode   P Open Command Palette   Shift-Enter ** Execute cell and move to cell below **   Ctrl-Enter ** Execute cell **   Alt-Enter Execute cell and add cell below   Y ** Make a code cell **   M ** Mark down cell **   R Raw cell   1 Heading 1   2 Heading 2   3 Heading 3   4 Heading 4   5 Heading 5   6 Heading 6   K ** Select upper cell **   Up Select upper cell   Down Select cell below   J ** Select cell below **   Shift-K Merge with the cell above   Shift-Up Merge with upper cell   Shift-Down Merge with cell below   Shift-J Combine with the cell below   A ** Add a cell above **   B Add a cell below   X ** Cut the selected cell **   C ** Copy selected cell **   Shift-V Paste on top   V ** Paste below **   Z ** Redo cell deletion **   DD ** Delete the selected cell **   Shift-M ** Merging cells (with lower cell if not selected) **   Ctrl-S Save   S Save   L Show/hide line numbers   O ** Show/hide cell output result **   Shift-O Output result scrolling/non-scrolling   H ** Display keyboard shortcuts **   I×2 ** Kernel interrupt **   0 Reboot the kernel   Esc Close Pager   Q Close Pager   Shift-L Show/hide line numbers of all cells   Shift-Space Scroll up   Space Scroll down    Edit mode    Shortcut key Description     Tab Code completion tab   Shift-Tab Tooltip   Ctrl-] Indent   Ctrl-[ ** Dedent **   Ctrl-A Select All   Ctrl-Z Redo   Ctrl-Shift-Z Redo   Ctrl-Y Redo   Ctrl-Home Move to beginning of cell   Ctrl-Up Move to beginning of cell   Ctrl-End Move to end of cell   Ctrl-Down Move to end of cell   Ctrl-Left Move to previous word   Ctrl-Right Move to next word   Ctrl-Backspace Delete previous word   Ctrl-Delete Delete next word   Ctrl-M Enter command mode   Ctrl-Shift-F Open Command Palette   Ctrl-Shift-P Open Command Palette   Esc Enter command mode   Shift-Enter **Execute a cell and select the cell below **   Ctrl-Enter ** Execute cell **   Alt-Enter Execute cell and add cell below   Ctrl-Shift-Minus Split cells   Ctrl-S Save   Down Move cursor down   Up Move cursor up   Ctrl-/ ** Comment out selected part **    Mac OS ↩ = Enter ⌘ = Command ⇧ = Shift ⌥ = Option ␣ = Space ⇥ = Tab Command mode    Shortcut key Description     F Search/Replace   ↩ ** Enter edit mode **   ⌘⇧ F Open Command Palette   ⌘⇧P Open Command Palette   P Open Command Palette   ** ⇧ ↩ ** ** Execute cell and move to cell below **   ⌃↩ ** Run the cell **   ⌥↩ Execute cell and add cell below   Y ** Make a code cell **   M ** Mark down cell **   R Raw cell   1 Heading 1   2 Heading 2   3 Heading 3   4 Heading 4   5 Heading 5   6 Heading 6   K ** Select upper cell **   ↑ Select upper cell   ↓ Select cell below   J ** Select cell below **   ⇧ K Combine with the cell above   ⇧↑ Combine with the cell above   ⇧↓ Combine with the cell below   ⇧ J Combine with the cell below   A ** Add a cell above **   B Add a cell below   X ** Cut the selected cell **   C ** Copy selected cell **   ⇧ V Paste on top   Z ** Redo cell deletion **   D→D ** Delete the selected cell **   ** ⇧ M** ** Merging cells (with lower cell if not selected) **   ⌘S ** Save **   S Save   L Show/hide line numbers   O ** Show/hide cell output result **   ⇧ O Output result scroll/non-scroll   H ** Display keyboard shortcuts **   I → I ** Interrupt the kernel **   0 Reboot the kernel   Esc Close Pager   Q Close Pager   ⇧ L Show/hide row numbers of all cells   ⇧␣ Scroll up   ␣ Scroll down    Edit mode    Shortcut key Description     ⇥ ** Code completion/tabs **   ⇧⇥ Tooltip   ⌘] ** Indent **   ⌘[ ** Dedent **   ⌘A ** Full selection **   ⌘Z ** Redo **   ⌘/ ** Comment out **   ⌘D Delete line   ⌘U Cancel selection   Insert Toggle overwriting   ⌘↑ Move to end of cell   ⌘↓ Move to end of cell   ⌥← Move to previous word   ⌥ → Move to next word   ⌥⌫ Delete previous word   ⌥⌦ Delete the word after   ⌘⇧Z Redo   ⌘⇧ U Redo selection   ⌃K emacs-style line kill   ⌘⌫ Erase to the left of the cursor   ⌘⌦ Erase to the right of the cursor   ⌃M Enter command mode   Esc Enter command mode   ⌘⇧ F Open Command Palette   ⌘⇧P Open Command Palette   ⇧↩ ** Run a cell and select the cell below **   ⌃↩ ** Run the cell **   ⌥↩ Execute cell and insert cell below   ⌃⇧ Minus ** Split cells **   ⌘S ** Save **   ↓ Move cursor down   ↑ Move cursor up    #Feelings I made a lot of momentum, so there may be mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[For data science] Oreole Jupyter cheat sheet [Jupyter Notebook/Lab]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/for-data-science-oreole-jupyter-cheat-sheet-jupyter-notebook-lab-0f5dd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/for-data-science-oreole-jupyter-cheat-sheet-jupyter-notebook-lab-0f5dd/</guid>
      <description>I usually do **data analysis and model construction** mainly on Jupyter.  I will make a note of how many times I will research it. (Updated from time to time)
Development I want to reload the modified .py module Modules that have already been imported will be cached, or will not be updated when imported normally. ** You can reload (reimport) with the following. **
import importlib importlib.reload(hoge) # hoge is an imported module I didn&amp;rsquo;t know this much until recently, and I restarted every time, so it&amp;rsquo;s really a scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>python3.8 jupyter notebook in venv environment</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python3.8-jupyter-notebook-in-venv-environment-f32bd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python3.8-jupyter-notebook-in-venv-environment-f32bd/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; Information as of 2019 1124. I write so lightly that I die because I am sleepy.   20191227 Addendum This article seems to be in demand
 Starting confirmation and initial setting.
python install I&amp;rsquo;m using the py launcher, so I cannot pass the path to python.
venv environment creation Environment creation. Then activate it. Console is git-bash
$ py -m venv hoge $ .hoge/scripts/activate install jupyter under venv environment Update pip and install jupyter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Jupyter Notebook extension and nbextensions settings</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/about-jupyter-notebook-extension-and-nbextensions-settings-20b04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/about-jupyter-notebook-extension-and-nbextensions-settings-20b04/</guid>
      <description>As the title says, about personal settings for nbextensions.  Introduction Referenced site https://www.pynote.info/entry/jupyter-notebook-nbextensions
#Install pip install jupyter-contrib-nbextensions (pip install jupyter-nbextensions-configurator) # It seems that it is at the above point? #activation jupyter contrib nbextension install --user jupyter nbextensions_configurator enable --user If you want to uninstall or disable it, follow the steps below. Referenced site https://github.com/ipython-contrib/jupyter_contrib_nbextensions/issues/1012
#Invalidation jupyter contrib nbextension uninstall --user jupyter nbextensions_configurator disable --user #Uninstall pip uninstall jupyter-contrib-nbextensions pip uninstall jupyter-nbextensions-configurator nbextensions settings Referenced site https://qiita.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>