<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Python3 on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/python3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Python3 on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/python3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Introduction] Satellite data analysis using Python (Google Colab environment)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-satellite-data-analysis-using-python-google-colab-environment-97b2e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-satellite-data-analysis-using-python-google-colab-environment-97b2e/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction-What is satellite data-   Artificial satellite data refers to data acquired by &amp;ldquo;remote sensing&amp;rdquo; using artificial satellites. Until now, satellite data required specialized tools and a large-capacity data processing platform, so the available organizations were limited to university institutions and some specialized institutions, but the spread of open source libraries and data By using the processing infrastructure cloud, an external environment has been set up in which general organizations can easily handle satellite data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to create a password generator to teach Python3 to children (bonus) * Completely remade</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-create-a-password-generator-to-teach-python3-to-children-bonus-completely-remade-24bba/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-create-a-password-generator-to-teach-python3-to-children-bonus-completely-remade-24bba/</guid>
      <description># It seems to be popular to change the password of my number card, so I made a password generator. Update: 2020/05/30  Actually, because I needed a password with an arbitrary number of digits, 1000 or more, at work&amp;hellip; Since it&amp;rsquo;s just a matter of course, I also studied Python and made a password generator with the following specifications.
Password generator specifications  Password with any number of digits Mix English lowercase letters (or choose) Mix English capital letters (or choose) Mix symbols (or choose) 3 consecutive characters are repelled (123, abc, 987, XYZ, 121, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made Othello to teach a child Python3 (5)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-othello-to-teach-a-child-python3-5-8be43/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-othello-to-teach-a-child-python3-5-8be43/</guid>
      <description>#Let&#39;s explain about Othello class 2  Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about types There are blood types, right? Type A, Type B, Type O, Type AB, etc. Whether it is true or not, aside from the fact that it is &amp;ldquo;A type that is well-organized&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;B type that is selfish&amp;rdquo;, the type has its own characteristics. In programming, types are used to make such important divisions as blood types.
Until now, I have explained various things about variables, but I have not touched on types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made Othello to teach a child Python3 (3)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-othello-to-teach-a-child-python3-3-e1123/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-othello-to-teach-a-child-python3-3-e1123/</guid>
      <description># You should learn the program by moving it and watching the movement  Anyway, the program is running and Nambo. There is also an effect that the understanding can be promoted by playing around with it, so today the source of the Othello game is a little long, but first I will release it. Let&amp;rsquo;s create this as a new PyCharom project.
Launch PyCharm and create a &amp;ldquo;New Project&amp;rdquo; from the File menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made Othello to teach Python3 to a child (1)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-othello-to-teach-python3-to-a-child-1-e578d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-othello-to-teach-python3-to-a-child-1-e578d/</guid>
      <description>#Python3 Let&#39;s make an Othello game for studying  Since my self-restraining life has been prolonged, it is inevitable to spend a dull day without doing anything, so I started studying Python3. python is a language, but applications of that language include standalone scripts, cloud services, games, science and technology calculation is really wide. For the time being, I would like to learn python by looking back at the basics of programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 techniques to improve BERT accuracy</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/10-techniques-to-improve-bert-accuracy-34330/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/10-techniques-to-improve-bert-accuracy-34330/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  It has become commonplace to fine-tune and use BERT for natural language processing tasks. It is expected that there will be more and more scenes where you want to improve the accuracy even a little when doing competitions such as Kaggle or projects where accuracy requirements are tight. Therefore, we will summarize the accuracy improvement method. Classification task is assumed as a task.
Adjust number of characters You can enter up to 512 words in the learned BERT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memo about using Colab Pro for about 2 months (good point / bad point)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/memo-about-using-colab-pro-for-about-2-months-good-point-bad-point-c5822/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/memo-about-using-colab-pro-for-about-2-months-good-point-bad-point-c5822/</guid>
      <description># What is Google Colaboratory  A free Jupyter Notebook environment where you can write and run Python code in your browser. There are restrictions on use, but you can also use the GPU.
Colab Pro A paid version ($9.99/month) of Google Colaboratory. There are various advantages over the regular version. Currently US only (contract requires US address and credit card).
Since I live in the United States, I signed up for Colab Pro at the same time as Launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python data structure and internal implementation -List-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-data-structure-and-internal-implementation-list-6087b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-data-structure-and-internal-implementation-list-6087b/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I use Qiita a lot, but this is my first post! Nice to meet you!
There are many useful articles on Python, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think many articles mention Python&amp;rsquo;s internal implementation so much, so I&amp;rsquo;m motivated to be able to link various data structure explanations with internal implementation. This time I will write about Python list.
About this article This article wrote about the Python list mechanism. However, it is impossible to write how all the methods in the list work, so mainly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Automation] Detect changes in website and notify LINE</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/automation-detect-changes-in-website-and-notify-line-431ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/automation-detect-changes-in-website-and-notify-line-431ce/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am a high school student. Due to the influence of this corona, I could not go to school, and I was told to regularly visit the website prepared by the school and study at home according to the instructions written on that site, but the website is heavy and every day Checking for updates is a hassle. But I want to get the information as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even beginners want to say I understand Python completely</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/even-beginners-want-to-say-i-understand-python-completely-10402/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/even-beginners-want-to-say-i-understand-python-completely-10402/</guid>
      <description>My child: &amp;quot;Oh, oh, oh, oh! Don&#39;t understand Python at all!!&amp;quot;  I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, my child who is new to Python doesn&amp;rsquo;t know Python and doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it today&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
I can&amp;rsquo;t say that Python is easy for anyone to program, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think the super-convenient features that are so boring are known to me. Moreover, when I try to use a convenient feature, it makes no sense at all. Nana no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try drawing a map with python&#43;cartopy 0.18.0</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/try-drawing-a-map-with-python-cartopy-0.18.0-d41b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/try-drawing-a-map-with-python-cartopy-0.18.0-d41b7/</guid>
      <description>When drawing a map with cartopy 0.18.0 or earlier, there were problems such as the axis labels only supporting equirectangular projection and UTM projection, and the axis label format being questionable. I wrote [this article](https://qiita.com/earth06/items/f5958a89a546dce00c36) about the adjustment of the axis label, but since the adjustment function around the axis of the cartopy has been significantly strengthened, the axis is very simple. You can now write labels.  In this article, we will plot the map with adjusted axis labels using the latest features of cartopy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implement JWT login function in Django REST framework</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/implement-jwt-login-function-in-django-rest-framework-bc32b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/implement-jwt-login-function-in-django-rest-framework-bc32b/</guid>
      <description># Previous article   Django REST framework + Vue.js &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s make SEIYU-like EC site&amp;rdquo; 6 times (plan) Let&amp;rsquo;s create a SEIYU-like EC site (1) Requirements analysis and project initialization Let&amp;rsquo;s create a SEIYU-like EC site (2) Renew the management screen using Xadmin Let&amp;rsquo;s make an SEIYU-like EC site (3) Let&amp;rsquo;s make an explosion API with Django REST framework Create a SEIYU-like EC site (4) Use Vue.js project initialization TypeScript  Even if you do not see the contents so far, you can understand the contents of this time, so I hope that you can have a relationship until the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Explanation of AtCoder] Control A, B, (C), D problems of ABC165 with Python!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/explanation-of-atcoder-control-a-b-c-d-problems-of-abc165-with-python-40eae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/explanation-of-atcoder-control-a-b-c-d-problems-of-abc165-with-python-40eae/</guid>
      <description>I will explain how to solve **A,B,(C),D problem** of **AtCoder Beginners Contest 165** with **Python3** as carefully as possible.  I am aiming to explain a solution method that satisfies the following three points, not just a solution method.
 Simple: don&amp;rsquo;t worry about extra things Easy to implement: I&amp;rsquo;m happy with fewer mistakes and bugs No time required: Paphos go up and more time can be left for D problem  5/17 C Problem was very difficult and the article was long, so I separated it into another article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Raspberry Pi] Stepping motor control with Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/raspberry-pi-stepping-motor-control-with-raspberry-pi-0c7f6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/raspberry-pi-stepping-motor-control-with-raspberry-pi-0c7f6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I bought a Razz pie, thinking that I might find a new hobby indoors during lockdown. I wondered if it would be useful for experiments later if I could control the motor, so I bought a stepper motor together, so I will control it. It is interesting just to rotate it at a constant speed, but the goal was to be able to do arbitrary movements. I started from almost zero knowledge of electric and electronic circuits, but it was easy to do because various information was dropped on the net.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differences that C# engineers felt when they first learned python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/differences-that-c#-engineers-felt-when-they-first-learned-python-29944/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/differences-that-c#-engineers-felt-when-they-first-learned-python-29944/</guid>
      <description>Hi, this is [Muscle Training Clinical Engineering Engineer ken](https://twitter.com/ce_fitness_note).  This is my first post on Qiita.
I usually use C# to develop medical systems. I decided to focus on machine learning, so I started learning python.
Even though I learned about it, I went around Progate&amp;rsquo;s python course, but I will briefly summarize the differences between C# and how to write.
If you usually use C#, C++, VB and want to learn python from now on, I think that learning will be better if you know the difference between the two in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python tricks] 5 useful but minor Python tricks</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-tricks-5-useful-but-minor-python-tricks-f49d6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-tricks-5-useful-but-minor-python-tricks-f49d6/</guid>
      <description>I would like to introduce a Python coding technique that I haven&#39;t seen before. I&#39;m sorry if it was unexpectedly major. I also want to put the sample code as much as possible and show how it is actually useful. Since it is a collection of niche technologies, it is a prerequisite that Python can be written to some extent.  #functools.partial This allows you to create a function with fixed arguments for a function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here are some grammars that if you know it in Python you may get a doya look</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/here-are-some-grammars-that-if-you-know-it-in-python-you-may-get-a-doya-look-3ac61/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/here-are-some-grammars-that-if-you-know-it-in-python-you-may-get-a-doya-look-3ac61/</guid>
      <description>I will introduce the python grammar that you may be able to do a drooling face if you know mainly new features.  1. Assignment expression New syntax added from python3.8. It&amp;rsquo;s good to know something new. An assignment expression can be written with the syntax :=, and conditional expressions and assignment statements can be used at the same time.
For example, the following common conditional expressions
text =&amp;#39;Hello New Expression!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to visualize the model with the low-code machine learning library PyCaret</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-the-model-with-the-low-code-machine-learning-library-pycaret-bdd48/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-visualize-the-model-with-the-low-code-machine-learning-library-pycaret-bdd48/</guid>
      <description># Overview   PyCaret, a library for machine learning with low-code, has finally become v1.0. Visualization of machine learning model is convenient, so let&amp;rsquo;s focus on Visualization of model and summarize.  If you check Source,youcanseeYellowbrick@HP(Yellowbrick@qiita). *In addition, it is taken up by Qiita in PyCaret tags below.  I tried using PyCaret at the fastest speed Introduction to the library &amp;ldquo;PyCaret&amp;rdquo; that automates machine learning    things to do The enumeration is as follows, but it can be executed in a few lines by automation of pycaret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Output tree structure of file in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/output-tree-structure-of-file-in-python-389ec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/output-tree-structure-of-file-in-python-389ec/</guid>
      <description># Overview  Note that I created a function that outputs the tree structure of files and directories nicely in Python, like a tree of commands.
#Conclusion
Just give the path of the directory you want to display as a tree to the following function. Since it is implemented for Mac, it is not supported when paths are not separated by slashes.
import pathlib import glob import os def tree(path, layer=0, is_last=False, indent_current=&amp;#39;&amp;#39;&amp;#39;): if not pathlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I will create a Python directory structure that I will not regret later</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-will-create-a-python-directory-structure-that-i-will-not-regret-later-aa427/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-will-create-a-python-directory-structure-that-i-will-not-regret-later-aa427/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve learned a little about directory structure a little after I started programming in Python, so I&#39;ll summarize it.  At first, I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand it at all, and I was doing a lot of googling, so I wrote the steps so that even beginners can understand.
The following is a memo by an engineer who has been developing in Python for about 6 months. ** We would appreciate if you could give us a lot of suggestions, suggestions, and questions from beginners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important units seen from Python lecture materials at Kyoto University</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/important-units-seen-from-python-lecture-materials-at-kyoto-university-dc3dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/important-units-seen-from-python-lecture-materials-at-kyoto-university-dc3dc/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  February 13 Kyoto University has released Python lecture materials free of charge. Relation: Lecture Material Repository Introduction article-Qiita Introduction article-CodeZine
The content is quite fulfilling. (Not perfect&amp;hellip;) It seems that learning at home will be the key for the future, partly because of COVID-19, so let&amp;rsquo;s make effective use of it. I myself use the basics of Python obscurely, so I would like to take this opportunity to fully understand it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[matplotlib] Graph creation sample function for scientific papers</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/matplotlib-graph-creation-sample-function-for-scientific-papers-9bf83/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/matplotlib-graph-creation-sample-function-for-scientific-papers-9bf83/</guid>
      <description># 0. Introduction  This article is a general function of graph creation using matplotlib of python and its brief description. In order to increase the versatility, we have devised a method that corresponds to the increase in the legend, etc. with a repeating function as much as possible. Also, since pandas.dataframe, which is often used in data processing, is used, it is easy to use it as it is for data after calculation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to detect the cross key input in Python3</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-detect-the-cross-key-input-in-python3-605ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-detect-the-cross-key-input-in-python3-605ad/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  You can detect the key by using the curses module. I will write the method which does not depend on it below https://docs.python.org/ja/3/library/curses.html#constants
Preface This is a memo for yourself. Stupid implementation. What I want to do is to detect the input of special characters such as the cross key.
It is desirable to have knowledge of Unicode control characters as a prerequisite. wikipedia
Clogged place getch gets the input character by character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular expressions that you can learn easily with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/regular-expressions-that-you-can-learn-easily-with-python-43b3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/regular-expressions-that-you-can-learn-easily-with-python-43b3d/</guid>
      <description>Although there are some cases where regular expressions are usually needed, I have not studied it systematically, so I will organize and summarize it. The language is Python.  It&amp;rsquo;s quite long. If you read this, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t get angry even if you tweet &amp;ldquo;I fully understand Python regular expressions&amp;rdquo;.
What is a regular expression in the first place? Regular Expression is in English. This is an expression (processing) that performs various processing by specifying a specific pattern when performing special operations related to character strings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note on creating a python development environment on macOS Catalina</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-note-on-creating-a-python-development-environment-on-macos-catalina-521c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-note-on-creating-a-python-development-environment-on-macos-catalina-521c6/</guid>
      <description>*Memo will be updated at any time*  Aiming to build a python development environment
In the environment I upgraded from Mojave to Catalina, when I did it normally, it did not work as expected with python3 or pip3 due to the difference in version, so I try using pyenv and see if it works.
It&amp;rsquo;s actually better to use Docker, but for now&amp;hellip;
homebrew Start from here.
/bin/bash -c &amp;quot;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Deep Learning] I tried to see if a machine learning beginner could make a prediction for the first place in a boat race.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-i-tried-to-see-if-a-machine-learning-beginner-could-make-a-prediction-for-the-first-place-in-a-boat-race.-c203f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/deep-learning-i-tried-to-see-if-a-machine-learning-beginner-could-make-a-prediction-for-the-first-place-in-a-boat-race.-c203f/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It&amp;rsquo;s been a month since I started studying deep learning.
I thought I could understand the basics, so I wondered if I could do something.
Then, suddenly, I came up with an estimate of the ranking of this boat race.
I was not convinced that I could predict the rank, but I knew that open source of boat race data was open to the public, so I thought I had to try this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A story about making a web application that records extensive reading with Django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-making-a-web-application-that-records-extensive-reading-with-django-7c44d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-story-about-making-a-web-application-that-records-extensive-reading-with-django-7c44d/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Extensive reading of English, it is troublesome to open and record an extensive reading notebook every time I read, and I can&amp;rsquo;t maintain my motivation. ． ． So I made the extensive reading notebook a web application. What I made → https://tadokuapp.herokuapp.com/tadoku/
#function It is not so nice to list dates, titles, word counts, etc. like a paper extensive reader, so the word counts are displayed on the calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an image processing viewer with PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-an-image-processing-viewer-with-pysimple-gui-30f54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-an-image-processing-viewer-with-pysimple-gui-30f54/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you can do with this article:   Viewer for selecting and displaying images Pass parameters to perform image processing Display the processed image  For a basic explanation of PySimPleGUI, please refer to If you use Tkinter, try using PySimpleGUI
Verification environment  windows10 macOS (catalina) Python3.7 Library -tkinter -PySimpleGUI -Pillow  Trigger It was interesting to see the article of Automatically generate ASCII art that created the above image and actually moved it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touch the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (2) Move from Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/touch-the-latest-physics-based-renderer-mitsuba2-2-move-from-python-2ad1d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/touch-the-latest-physics-based-renderer-mitsuba2-2-move-from-python-2ad1d/</guid>
      <description>What is #Mitsuba2  A free physically based renderer for academics. There are new features such as differentiable rendering and polarized rendering. This article is a continuation of Introduction. The assumption is that Mitsuba2 has been installed.
This is another related article I wrote.
-Try the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (1) Introduction -Try the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (3) Differentiable rendering -Try the latest physics-based renderer Mitsuba2 (4) Polarization rendering -Difference between BRDF and polarized BRDF (pBRDF)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to predict the number of domestic infections of the new corona with a mathematical model</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-the-number-of-domestic-infections-of-the-new-corona-with-a-mathematical-model-a6632/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-predict-the-number-of-domestic-infections-of-the-new-corona-with-a-mathematical-model-a6632/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  Since I found The Lancet&amp;rsquo;s paper 1 that predicts the number of infected people with a mathematical model, I implemented a mathematical model to predict the number of infected people in Japan and compared it with other infectious diseases.
Summary  The number of infected people was predicted by the SEIR model. The basic reproduction number of the new Corona is about 2.9, which is slightly higher than that of influenza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to discord.py (2)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-discord.py-2-b37e7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-discord.py-2-b37e7/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  We run an unofficial server for discord.py (although some developers). Questions are also accepted here. You can also create a personal channel and get support there for those who want long-term support**. If you would like to receive individual support, please enter from the invitation url below and DM to @@Smidora #8931`. https://discord.gg/KPp2Wsu **Please send any questions regarding this article here**
About this article This article is a step-by-step article about discord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flask introduction ~ Blueprint application note</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/flask-introduction-~-blueprint-application-note-fb7d1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/flask-introduction-~-blueprint-application-note-fb7d1/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s try the title as easily as possible.  Blueprint allows you to implement the functionality of your application in pieces. Blueprint is officially recommended as a way to organize bloated projects.
Install Flask $ sudo pip3 install flask Directory structure $ cd ~/workspace/sample-flask/ $ls server.py from flask import Flask app = Flask(__name__) @app.route(&amp;#39;/&amp;#39;) def func_1(): return&amp;#39;Hello world&amp;#39; @app.route(&amp;#39;/test&amp;#39;) def func_2(): return&amp;#39;Test&amp;#39; if __name__ ==&amp;#39;__main__&amp;#39;: app.run(host=&amp;#39;0.0.0.0&amp;#39;, port=80, debug=True) Execution command $python3 server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to use for Python stacks and queues (speed comparison of each data structure)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/what-to-use-for-python-stacks-and-queues-speed-comparison-of-each-data-structure-107c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/what-to-use-for-python-stacks-and-queues-speed-comparison-of-each-data-structure-107c4/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article is primarily about competitive programming.
There are several ways to implement stacks and queues in Python.
 Stack -Use list (append(), pop()) -Use collections.deque (append(), pop()) Queue -Use list (append(), pop(0)) -Use collections.deque (append(), popleft()) -Use queue.Queue (put(), get())  Which of these is the best to use? This time I will investigate it focusing on the speed aspect.
#Measurement method For each data structure, elements are added and extracted 10 times, 100 times, 1000 times, 10000 times, 100000 times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 services that even beginners can learn Python (for beginners to advanced users)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8-services-that-even-beginners-can-learn-python-for-beginners-to-advanced-users-3334b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8-services-that-even-beginners-can-learn-python-for-beginners-to-advanced-users-3334b/</guid>
      <description>After checking on various existing sites,  Since the fee display etc. were old, I tried to summarize it again.
If you are an introduction to programming, you can learn from the basics progate progate This is the most recommended learning site for beginners who want to learn programming from now on. The programming terms are very polite and easy to understand, so You will be able to proceed with your learning without any setbacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python description of a parent killed literally</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-description-of-a-parent-killed-literally-fe71b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-description-of-a-parent-killed-literally-fe71b/</guid>
      <description>@Raclett3&#39;s  Python programming whose parents were killed by literals of strings, numbers and truth values I think it&amp;rsquo;s very interesting :raised_hands:, but at the same time I couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand what was happening, so I looked into it. It&amp;rsquo;s a commentary or my own study.
I mainly write &amp;ldquo;small numerical values&amp;rdquo;. If you make a mistake, throw Masakari.
#0
int() # 0 This is as per @Raclett3&amp;rsquo;s link.
 or return 0 if no arguments are given</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realize microservices easily with Cloud Run × Flask</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/realize-microservices-easily-with-cloud-run-flask-7a5b8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/realize-microservices-easily-with-cloud-run-flask-7a5b8/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I am making an application by personal development, but I was making the back end with rails. One day. .. .. I saw this article. App development without backend engineer with Firebase, benefits and challenges experienced by Cookpad
Firebase enables development without the need for backend engineers
(゚Д゚) &amp;hellip; Magicka
I was inspired by this and made a backend with Cloud Function.
But
For some reason it quit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme: Standard output [Difficulty ★★★★★]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/theme-standard-output-difficulty-86f03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/theme-standard-output-difficulty-86f03/</guid>
      <description>Please output `Sh1ma` on standard output. The rules are as follows.   Do not include strings (&amp;quot;&amp;quot;, &#39;&#39;) in the code Do not include numbers in the code Prohibition of chr and ord  If you can, please.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw a graph with PySimple GUI</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/draw-a-graph-with-pysimple-gui-dc729/</guid>
      <description># What you can do by reading this article  With PySimple GUI, you can:
 You can draw bar graphs, line graphs, etc. Graph that refreshes display periodically  For the basic operation of PySimpleGUI, please refer to If you use Tkinter, try using PySimpleGUI.
Overview I think there are many people who analyze data as a way to use Python. Also, some people may want to visualize the results of analysis as line graphs or bar graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to save image feature point information in a file and use it for matching</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-save-image-feature-point-information-in-a-file-and-use-it-for-matching-8416b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-save-image-feature-point-information-in-a-file-and-use-it-for-matching-8416b/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I often use OpenCV feature point extraction and matching, When using multiple images, feature point extraction often took time. Therefore, this time, I made a program that outputs feature point information to a file and uses it for matching.
As an example, let&amp;rsquo;s find the girl with red glasses (target image) from the girls (12 source images) this time!
Source image ⬇︎ Target image ⬇︎ Development environment This time, it was developed in the following environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyPI package for easy use of Cotoha on Google colab</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pypi-package-for-easy-use-of-cotoha-on-google-colab-60f11/</guid>
      <description>## 2020/04/10 PyPI package has been released!  For details, see here(I&amp;rsquo;mreallyhappytohaveastar!)
If you want to use it quickly, please refer to the code below
$ pip install cotoha_at_python from cotohacall.main import cotoha_call import os os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_ID&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Your ID&amp;#39; os.environ[&amp;#39;CLIENT_SECRET&amp;#39;] =&amp;#39;Ypur Secret&amp;#39; sentence =&amp;#39;API service that enables highly accurate natural language analysis of Japanese. With the COTOHA API, you can easily use the natural language analysis technology that utilizes the research results of NTT Group for over 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python3] A//B and math.floor(A/B) are not always the same! ?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python3-a-b-and-math.floora-b-are-not-always-the-same-ee26e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python3-a-b-and-math.floora-b-are-not-always-the-same-ee26e/</guid>
      <description># Note  **This article contains spoilers for &amp;ldquo;Atcoder Beginner Contest 148 E-Double Factorial&amp;rdquo;. Please refrain from browsing if you plan to solve this problem yourself. **
Overview I got into a problem with the title while solving Atcoder, so I&amp;rsquo;ll post this article to keep it as a memorandum and to hear the opinions of Python experts.
Problem Atcoder Beginner Contest 148 E-Double Factorial
Define f(n) as follows for an integer n of 0 or more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RPC completed with Python3 standard module</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/rpc-completed-with-python3-standard-module-d7458/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/rpc-completed-with-python3-standard-module-d7458/</guid>
      <description>## table of contents  -There are too many types of Python RPCs today -Value that can be executed with standard library -Code description -Try it out
There are too many types of Python RPCs today As of 2020, many RPCs have been published as OSS, but there are too many types, and the increase in selection cost, the increase in evaluation cost, and the increase in learning cost are personal issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Python (Python version APG4b)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-python-python-version-apg4b-b9418/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-python-python-version-apg4b-b9418/</guid>
      <description># About this article  At AtCoderofthecompetitionprogrammingsite,thereis&amp;rdquo;AtCoderProgrammingGuideforbeginners(APG4b)&amp;rdquo; which is an introductory material for programming. There is. C++, which is the mainstream language for competitive programming, is used as an introductory material for programming. So, in this article, I wrote a Python version of APG4b. Basically, please read APG4b, and refer to this article for Python-specific parts.
Most are based on APG4b, so if this article seems to be a problem, remove it immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Response when ModuleNotFoundError: No module named&#39;XXX&#39; occurs in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/response-when-modulenotfounderror-no-module-namedxxx-occurs-in-python-df433/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/response-when-modulenotfounderror-no-module-namedxxx-occurs-in-python-df433/</guid>
      <description>This is a memo for dealing with the title.  This time, we assume there is no WTForms.
First, check if the module exists with pip show pip show WTForms Name: WTForms Version: 2.2.1 Summary: A flexible forms validation and rendering library for Python web development. Home-page: https://wtforms.readthedocs.io/ Author: Thomas Johansson, James Crasta Author-email: wtforms@simplecodes.com License: BSD Location: /Users/XXX/.pyenv/versions/3.7.5/lib/python3.7/site-packages Requires: Required-by: wtforms-validators, Flask-WTF  If it does not exist here, install the module (pip install Flask-WTF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to find the circle ratio of 100 million digits</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-find-the-circle-ratio-of-100-million-digits-4fc75/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-find-the-circle-ratio-of-100-million-digits-4fc75/</guid>
      <description># how?  \zeta(2) = \sum_{n=1}^{\infty}\frac{1}{n^2} = \frac{\pi^2}{6} (Basel Problem)
 You can use this formula to find an approximate value for $\pi$.  Calculating $\sum_{n=1}^{a}\frac{1}{n^2}$ using $1$ as an integer from 1 to $1$ $\times6$ for the answer obtained in 2.1 Calculate the square root of the answer obtained in 3.2. This value is an approximation of $\pi$.  So I implemented it in python. Code is omitted.
 It takes a few hours to calculate&amp;hellip; There is no sign of ending&amp;hellip; It takes about 18 hours to calculate the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Pandas to learn while suffering [Part1]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introductory-pandas-to-learn-while-suffering-part1-c0bd3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introductory-pandas-to-learn-while-suffering-part1-c0bd3/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Pandas is an inevitable library for data analysis in Python. However, this Pandas has a high hurdle for beginners&amp;hellip; I also had a hard time, so I&amp;rsquo;ll try to put it all together from the basics. I am not an advanced Pandas person, so I would appreciate any comments or advice. Also, this article will be divided into three parts. (Since it is a plan, it is very likely to change&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping with Tor in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/scraping-with-tor-in-python-81f4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/scraping-with-tor-in-python-81f4b/</guid>
      <description>## Note  :warning: This article does not recommend scraping with Tor.
Scraping is basically okay, but if you are prohibited by the terms of use of the target site or if you put an excessive load on the server of the target site, you may be punished.
What is Tor It is a technology that anonymizes the connection route. Theoretically, it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to determine who accessed using Tor.
Execution environment Homebrew 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikkei Prediction with Pytorch</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/nikkei-prediction-with-pytorch-c398a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/nikkei-prediction-with-pytorch-c398a/</guid>
      <description>I am a graduate student studying Pytorch recently.  I started studying neural networks by dreaming about stock price forecasts and horse racing forecasts.
At last, it is in shape, so I will write it as a memorandum. I hope it will be helpful for a beginner like me.
References, cited articles and books Overview of LSTM network This is an article about the network structure and mechanism of LSTM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried to automate the face hiding work of wear coordination images</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-automate-the-face-hiding-work-of-wear-coordination-images-dab3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-to-automate-the-face-hiding-work-of-wear-coordination-images-dab3b/</guid>
      <description>Do you all know Wear?  WEAR is a fashion coordination site and one of our services. In short, it is an SNS where you can share your fashion coordination.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why, but it seems to be popular to post with the face hidden by an icon. Is it because people without a face can see the coordination objectively?
However, the face hiding work is surprisingly troublesome, and I wish I could automate this&amp;hellip; so I implemented a program for automatic icon placement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Introduction to Docker] I tried to summarize various findings of Docker obtained by studying (Windows/Python)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-docker-i-tried-to-summarize-various-findings-of-docker-obtained-by-studying-windows-python-f7eea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-to-docker-i-tried-to-summarize-various-findings-of-docker-obtained-by-studying-windows-python-f7eea/</guid>
      <description>There was a person in charge of specialized infrastructure related things in the company, and he was kind to the environment, but it would be bad if I had to study Docker around myself as soon as possible. I&#39;ve finally been introduced to Docker recently, so I&#39;ll try to put together and try what I have learned as a memorandum.  Since I have been working on unfamiliar work such as infrastructure around my career, please forgive me for things that are rough (shallow) in terms of knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[#3] Make Minecraft with Python. -Improvement of player movement (concept of inertia) and collision detection-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/#3-make-minecraft-with-python.-improvement-of-player-movement-concept-of-inertia-and-collision-detection-3ea7d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/#3-make-minecraft-with-python.-improvement-of-player-movement-concept-of-inertia-and-collision-detection-3ea7d/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;font color=&amp;quot;grey&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Part of pictures, articles, images on this page are copyrighted by Mojang AB.&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;  #Overview This project reproduces the world-famous sandbox game &amp;ldquo;Minecraft&amp;rdquo; in the programming language &amp;ldquo;Python&amp;rdquo;.
** Previous article: [[2] Making Minecraft with Python. Model drawing and player implementation]**
#What to do this time Last time, we did everything from drawing models using test textures to implementing the player&amp;rsquo;s viewpoint.
 Improved player movement Examination of collision judgment  Improved player movement Don&amp;rsquo;t you think the movement of the player you implemented last time is unnatural?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to analyze the pitcher who achieved no hit no run</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-to-analyze-the-pitcher-who-achieved-no-hit-no-run-71d65/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-i-tried-to-analyze-the-pitcher-who-achieved-no-hit-no-run-71d65/</guid>
      <description>#Overview  On June 18, 2014, the Dodgers Clayton Kershaw pitched nine times in the Colorado Rockies v Los Angeles Dodgers match, achieving 15 strikeouts and no-hit nolan. This time we will compare it to our opponent Rockies pitcher and analyze why Clayton Kershaw achieved a no-hit nolan. #environment ・Python 3.7.5 ・Windows10 ・Jupyter Notebook (Anaconda3)
Start analysis (play ball) First, launch Jupyter Notebook with Anaconda Prompt $ jupyter notebook Then import the required libraries %matplotlib inline import requests import xml.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you want to build a PYTHON environment, you must understand it.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/if-you-want-to-build-a-python-environment-you-must-understand-it.-ca7ff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/if-you-want-to-build-a-python-environment-you-must-understand-it.-ca7ff/</guid>
      <description>#There are 3 types of installation formats  You will usually download the installer from the official page below to build a python development environment. Python Releases for Windows https://www.python.org/downloads/windows/
For example, as of January 21, 2020, python3.8.1 is distributed in the following format.
 Copy and paste web content   Download Windows help file Download Windows x86-64 embeddable zip file Download Windows x86-64 executable installer Download Windows x86-64 web-based installer Download Windows x86 embeddable zip file Download Windows x86 executable installer Download Windows x86 web-based installer  To explain in order from the top</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python naming convention (since PEP8)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-naming-convention-since-pep8-bc3bd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-naming-convention-since-pep8-bc3bd/</guid>
      <description>Python has &amp;quot;[PEP8: Python code style guide](https://pep8-ja.readthedocs.io/ja/latest/)&amp;quot;, which also describes naming conventions such as variable names and function names.  By matching the naming convention and coding style, you can reduce the burden on people who read the source code and those who review it. Please refer not only to the naming convention but also to the naming method described in &amp;ldquo;Readable Code&amp;rdquo;.
PEP8    Usage Naming Convention     Private, private One underscore at the beginning   Name collision avoidance in subclasses Two underscores at the beginning   Special property, special method Add two underscores before and after (Because it is prepared in the language specification, do not define it yourself)   Collision avoidance with reserved words and built-in function names Last one underscore       Usage Naming Convention     Package Short names in all lowercase, no underscores   Module All names in lowercase, separated by underscores   Classes, exceptions CapWords method (connect uppercase words only at the beginning, do not use underscore)   Function, Method Lowercase letters only, with words separated by underscores   Constant Uppercase letters only, words separated by underscores   Variable lowercase only, with words separated by underscores if necessary   1-character variable Never use l (lowercase ell), O (uppercase O), I (uppercase eye) (depending on the font the numbers 1, 0 (I can&amp;rsquo;t tell that))    Other than PEP8    Usage Naming Convention     Discard variable 1 underscore (when a variable is needed but not used in a for loop or split assignment)    Reedable code  Don&amp;rsquo;t abbreviate words (Obviously omitted names are OK) Information and meaning can be added to the name (flag and check do not know what flag or what value was checked) Communicate information by name so that no comment is required Use single-character variables for temporary variables that can be used within the viewable range (up to 25 lines)  Such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Golf Tech (AtCoder)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-golf-tech-atcoder-bcf06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-golf-tech-atcoder-bcf06/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Introducing the short writing technique in Python3 that has been cultivated so far with AtCoder. In addition, AtCoder&amp;rsquo;s Python 3 version is 3.4.3, and it seems that functions that are likely to become shorter, such as f-strings and walrus operators, cannot be used. It&amp;rsquo;s just a technique on AtCoder (I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it can be used elsewhere). I think it&amp;rsquo;s messy because I write down what I came up with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Harlem] There are too many to choose! 13 ways to calculate pi in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/harlem-there-are-too-many-to-choose-13-ways-to-calculate-pi-in-python-72286/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/harlem-there-are-too-many-to-choose-13-ways-to-calculate-pi-in-python-72286/</guid>
      <description>Hello from the abyss of the universe!  \displaystyle\int {\rm d}\boldsymbol{r}\hat{\psi}^{\dagger}(\boldsymbol{r}) Poppin Friends \hat{\psi}(\boldsymbol{r}) is! This time, I would like to introduce **13 methods of calculating the circle ratio $\pi$ in Python.
In the past, I read the article [&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not worried about pi anymore! 10 ways to find pi&amp;rdquo;]&amp;rdquo; (https://www.procrasist.com/entry/pi_1) (famous in pi region) , The desire to &amp;ldquo;π seek&amp;rdquo; was amplified, so I came to write this article. And this time, I tried to implement almost all of the method of finding $\pi$ in the article in Python **!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a day of the week from Zeller&#39;s congruence ceremony-and then the calendar</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-a-day-of-the-week-from-zellers-congruence-ceremony-and-then-the-calendar-61065/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-a-day-of-the-week-from-zellers-congruence-ceremony-and-then-the-calendar-61065/</guid>
      <description>From the Zeller congruence formula, calculate what day of the week is the day of the week.  #!/usr/bin/python3 import sys y = int(sys.argv[1]) m = int(sys.argv[2]) d = int(sys.argv[3]) youbia = [&amp;#34;Sun&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Month&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Tue&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Wed&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Thurs&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Fri&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Sat&amp;#34;] if (m == 1 or m == 2): md = m+10 yd = y-1 else: md = m-2 yd = y a = yd // 100 b = yd %100 youbi = (int(2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Features in Python 3.9 (Summary)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/new-features-in-python-3.9-summary-d5df9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/new-features-in-python-3.9-summary-d5df9/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;ve posted an article summarizing what&amp;rsquo;s new in Python 3.5.
 New in Python 3.5 New in Python3.6 New to Python 3.7 New features of Python 3.8 (Summary)  From now on, the release cycle will be faster, so the frequency of posting is likely to increase, but I can do it as an old engineer who has been chasing Python since 1.x. I just want to continue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By clarifying the difference between statistics and machine learning, I can see why many business companies cannot use machine learning!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/by-clarifying-the-difference-between-statistics-and-machine-learning-i-can-see-why-many-business-companies-cannot-use-machine-learning-ee074/</guid>
      <description>#What is the difference between statistics and machine learning? Why can&#39;t I predict from machine learning today and make money?  Perhaps everyone wonders when they start studying machine learning. And why can&amp;rsquo;t many business companies use it for their daily work today? The question also comes up. There are various documents, but I was having trouble comprehending them, so I rearranged them myself. I&amp;rsquo;m putting together a lot of information by combining information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a LINEBot with Django</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-linebot-with-django-f9aa5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-linebot-with-django-f9aa5/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I summarized the article about using LINEBot with Django because it was a little researched and it was old.
For the time being, I will create an Omukai Bot that returns the text sent as an introduction to LINE Bot.
Here article uses SDK, but I&amp;rsquo;m a Python beginner ~~ I can&amp;rsquo;t even throw an HTTP request with Python ~~ I want to do it.
I&amp;rsquo;m a Django beginner with less than a week of Django history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nest cog with discord.py</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/nest-cog-with-discord.py-59eae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/nest-cog-with-discord.py-59eae/</guid>
      <description># Premise   discord.py python3.6  The code in this article is a simplified code for explanation purposes only, so only nonsense code will appear. Please note.
#cog is getting complicated The command extension of discord.py (https://discordpy.readthedocs.io/en/latest/ext/commands/index.html) has a function called &amp;ldquo;cog&amp;rdquo; that groups together several commands and events. in this way
from discord.ext import commands as c class CogHogeFuga(c.Cog): def __init__(self, bot, hoge): self._bot = bot self._hoge = hoge @c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of Django tutorial for beginners by beginners ① (project creation ~)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/summary-of-django-tutorial-for-beginners-by-beginners-project-creation-~-6f2fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/summary-of-django-tutorial-for-beginners-by-beginners-project-creation-~-6f2fb/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python in fashion now&amp;hellip; Python for AI development/deep learning, Python for image processing, Python for log analysis, Python for Django to create web applications&amp;hellip;
I felt like I heard this voice &amp;ldquo;Python everyone is doing it, only you are not doing it&amp;rdquo;
No, I do Python.
We will learn from the official Django documentation. https://docs.djangoproject.com/ja/3.0/
The official document is in Japanese, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to read (maybe) as it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wai Can JOIN be done with Django?</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/wai-can-join-be-done-with-django-1c0d9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/wai-can-join-be-done-with-django-1c0d9/</guid>
      <description>(Note) This article is in Wy notation. Respect Taro @Yametaro with respect.  #One day my home Wai &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m making a Django app as a hobby Naya&amp;rdquo; Wai &amp;ldquo;You can make a table just by writing a model.&amp;rdquo; Wai &amp;ldquo;Django is too hungry to create an admin screen!&amp;rdquo;
DB normalized Y &amp;ldquo;Easy setting of external keys&amp;rdquo; Wai &amp;ldquo;For example, it would be better to have separate tables for player data and performance for each player 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creation of negative/positive classifier using BERT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/creation-of-negative-positive-classifier-using-bert-b0125/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/creation-of-negative-positive-classifier-using-bert-b0125/</guid>
      <description>This post is the 25th day of &amp;quot;Natural Language Processing Advent Calendar 2019-Qiita&amp;quot;.  siny.
In this article, I summarized the creation of a negative-positive classifier using BERT, which plays a major role in natural language processing in 2019.
#Introduction I think that knowledge about BERT has appeared in books, blogs, Qiita, etc. However, since most datasets that can be used for natural language processing are based on English, and there are not many Japanese datasets, it is quite difficult to use BERT using Japanese text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made blackjack with python!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-blackjack-with-python-45581/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-blackjack-with-python-45581/</guid>
      <description>#at first  Watch udemy&amp;rsquo;s Video about Object Orientation, I thought it might be object-oriented, so I made a blackjack instead of trying my arm!
Assumptions  There is no concept such as a deck. A is always treated as 1. No 5 cards, both bursts win the dealer.  ##code
import random CARDS = [&amp;#34;A&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;2&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;3&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;4&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;5&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;6&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;7&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;8&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;9&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;10&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;J&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Q&amp;#34; , &amp;#34;K&amp;#34;] CARDS_DIC = {&amp;#34;A&amp;#34;: 1, &amp;#34;2&amp;#34;: 2, &amp;#34;3&amp;#34;: 3, &amp;#34;4&amp;#34;: 4, &amp;#34;5&amp;#34;: 5, &amp;#34;6&amp;#34;: 6, &amp;#34;7&amp;#34;: 7, &amp;#34;8&amp;#34;: 8, &amp;#34;9&amp;#34;: 9, &amp;#34;10&amp;#34;: 10, &amp;#34;J&amp;#34;: 10, &amp;#34;Q&amp;#34;: 10, &amp;#34;K&amp;#34;: 10} class Hit(list): # Player or dealer hit def __init__(self, list): self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play with UI implementation of Pythonista [Screen transition]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/play-with-ui-implementation-of-pythonista-screen-transition-2aea6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/play-with-ui-implementation-of-pythonista-screen-transition-2aea6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The update is slow, but I&amp;rsquo;m still talking about the UI implementation of Pythonista! Continuing from the previous article, this time I will implement screen transitions. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t touched Pythonista yet, please read the following articles. (Since there is no story, you can understand this article without reading the following article if you have prerequisite knowledge)
[Past article] Play with UI implementation of Pythonista3 [super super introduction] Play with UI implementation of Pythonista [screen element] Play with UI implementation of Pythonista [Implementation of Action]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried sentiment analysis of the whole novel Weather&#39;s Child ☔️</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-sentiment-analysis-of-the-whole-novel-weathers-child-%EF%B8%8F-10f52/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-sentiment-analysis-of-the-whole-novel-weathers-child-%EF%B8%8F-10f52/</guid>
      <description>![752B7BFA-4985-442D-904C-BEB091269C6C.gif](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/327405/05e5f803-dc12-4db0-bcf5-47661a8e5329.gif)  #1. A brief overview In this article, I will explain how to analyze sentiment by natural language processing the text of the novel **&amp;ldquo;Weather Child&amp;rdquo;**!
In general, emotional analysis is to discover and quantify &amp;ldquo;emotion&amp;rdquo; contained in a sentence and judge the opinion of the sentence. This is an area of current interest because it allows us to mechanically categorize user opinions about our products and services.
On the other hand, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t it possible to use sentiment analysis in addition to reviews and reviews?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[No venv required] The strongest Python development environment created with Remote Containers [VS Code/Docker]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/no-venv-required-the-strongest-python-development-environment-created-with-remote-containers-vs-code-docker-1fc39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/no-venv-required-the-strongest-python-development-environment-created-with-remote-containers-vs-code-docker-1fc39/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Python has been attracting attention because it shines in the top 1 popular languages 1 and becomes a test subject for the IPA Basic Information Engineer Exam 2.
But wait a minute! Are you able to benefit from the Python ecosystem and develop properly?
By creating a good development environment, not only can the development be made more efficient by input interpolation and formatters , but also unexpected problems can be prevented by static analysis, ① Easy ② Explosion speed ③ You can write programs safely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can be used by competitive professionals! Python standard library</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/can-be-used-by-competitive-professionals-python-standard-library-9e75c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/can-be-used-by-competitive-professionals-python-standard-library-9e75c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction   Introducing the Python standard library that can be used in competitive programming. It also contains AtCoder problems and code solved using the Python standard library. Python3 version on AtCoder is 3.4.3. I will not explain the problem.  #Standard library
bisect ** Sequence bisection algorithm **
bisect_left(a, x, lo=0, hi=len(a))
Returns the position where $x$ can be inserted into $a$ for the sorted list $a$. If $a$ contains $x$, the insertion point is before (left) any existing $x$ value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An engineer who has noticed the emo of cryptography is trying to implement it in Python and defeat it</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/an-engineer-who-has-noticed-the-emo-of-cryptography-is-trying-to-implement-it-in-python-and-defeat-it-bc567/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/an-engineer-who-has-noticed-the-emo-of-cryptography-is-trying-to-implement-it-in-python-and-defeat-it-bc567/</guid>
      <description>It is no exaggeration to say that the modern information society is supported by cryptographic technology. Nevertheless, we are reaping the benefits without being particularly aware of cryptography. What&#39;s more, cryptography has been around for a long time, as it existed around 100 BC. In addition, Hyundai Cryptography is trying to ensure high security by making full use of advanced mathematics, and eventually it will be derived from blockchain technology.  What is the length of this history and the range of defense!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous communication only with Touch Designer</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/asynchronous-communication-only-with-touch-designer-7a3da/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/asynchronous-communication-only-with-touch-designer-7a3da/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  TouchDesigner (TD) can execute python script, If a process such as HTTP communication takes a long time, it will be hardened until the process is completed. At this time, the timeline of the whole TD also stops and the drawing is not updated, so In order to prevent it, I decided to communicate asynchronously.
If you just want to get the value asynchronously, you may use node etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faster Python release cycle!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/faster-python-release-cycle-a6578/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/faster-python-release-cycle-a6578/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  It was just over a month and a half ago that Guido van Rossum,thecreatorofPython,quitDropbox,whereheworkedforsixandahalfyears&amp;hellip;Itissaidthathewillnotchangejobsandwillberetiredasitis.63yearsold.Thankyouforallyourhardwork.I&amp;rsquo;vebeenaPythonBDFL(BenevolentDictatorForLife) over a year ago, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a big impact on Python development, but it&amp;rsquo;s a bit sad.
He started making Python in December 1989, exactly 30 years ago. He wanted to do hobby programming on Christmas holidays, so he decided to create an interpreted language, and that was what Python was today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static type checking that starts loosely in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/static-type-checking-that-starts-loosely-in-python-6341d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/static-type-checking-that-starts-loosely-in-python-6341d/</guid>
      <description>I had been writing TypeScript for about a year, but I started to work on Python3 for about a month.  Although Python is simple and fun, there are places that I inherited from other people, and it is hard to develop and have no type.
The hardest part is reading the code, and what does this function return? Do not know at first glance what this variable contains. &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;There is no type as a document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[2020 edition] How to install Python3 on EC2 of AWS</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2020-edition-how-to-install-python3-on-ec2-of-aws-2403a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2020-edition-how-to-install-python3-on-ec2-of-aws-2403a/</guid>
      <description>The other day I had the opportunity to install Python3 on EC2 on AWS.  At that time, I did a Google search with &amp;ldquo;AWS EC2 Python 3&amp;rdquo;, but the information on the page displayed at the top of the search results was not good enough. In particular,
 pyenv virtualenv  Although the method of preparing a virtual environment of Python3 was introduced using, you should use venv unless there is a special reason for preparing a virtual environment of Python3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Understanding and application of with syntax] Flexible switching of Python standard output destination</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/understanding-and-application-of-with-syntax-flexible-switching-of-python-standard-output-destination-4e462/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/understanding-and-application-of-with-syntax-flexible-switching-of-python-standard-output-destination-4e462/</guid>
      <description>This section describes how to use the standard output (file output, console output) of Python standard output (print or sys.stdout) by switching with the with syntax as appropriate.  Motivation The output destination of standard output can be changed according to the process as follows,
import sys # Temporarily change to file output sys.stdout = open(&amp;#39;out.log&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;a+&amp;#39;) ... sys.stdout.write(&amp;#39;fugahoge&amp;#39;) ... #return to console output sys.stdout = sys.__stdout__ When the processing is over, I thought that there might be something because it is troublesome to undo it, and remembering that using the with syntax made close() after file open() unnecessary, this article Came to write.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning with Python, a quick and easy analysis of the weather data of the last 10 years was started.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/beginning-with-python-a-quick-and-easy-analysis-of-the-weather-data-of-the-last-10-years-was-started.-ee6a3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/beginning-with-python-a-quick-and-easy-analysis-of-the-weather-data-of-the-last-10-years-was-started.-ee6a3/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I recently started studying Python. Since I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, I&amp;rsquo;d like to make a post that will be useful for those who are new to Python like me. Since I have never written Python, this time I would like to do a simple data analysis while understanding the syntax of python and what kind of library it has.
Reference book: [Immediately usable! Can be practiced in work! How to create AI/machine learning/deep learning apps with Python](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Latest version] Use discord.py to make the bot speak at regular intervals</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/latest-version-use-discord.py-to-make-the-bot-speak-at-regular-intervals-2917b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/latest-version-use-discord.py-to-make-the-bot-speak-at-regular-intervals-2917b/</guid>
      <description>## Overview  We will explain how to make bot perform periodical processing by using discord.py which is Python&amp;rsquo;s Discord API wrapper that can describe bot simply in chat tool Discord.
Note The code example did not actually work. We modified the code example on April 10, 2020.
Assumption  discord.py 1.3.0a Python 3.6  Version notes Although disc0.1.2 (so-called async version) has been provided for a long time in discord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Async/await with Kivy and tkinter</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/async-await-with-kivy-and-tkinter-973cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/async-await-with-kivy-and-tkinter-973cb/</guid>
      <description>2018 was a shock to me. I used to play around with [Kivy][kivy] of GUI Framekwork, but I found that using a generator can make ugly code full of callback functions surprisingly readable. Then, while trying various things, I became able to understand async/await asynchronous processing, which was a magic that was unfamiliar to me until then, and I was able to create a little asynchronous processing library. In this article   The process until I realized the wonderfulness of the generator and the native coroutine born from it How to implement async/await with Kivy and tkinter using it  I want to write it down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands-on to visualize your tweet while understanding BERT</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hands-on-to-visualize-your-tweet-while-understanding-bert-09fda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hands-on-to-visualize-your-tweet-while-understanding-bert-09fda/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 13th day article of [NTT Communications Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/nttcom).  Yesterday was @nitky&amp;rsquo;s article, &amp;ldquo;We deal with threat intelligence in a mood&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/nitky/items/ccefd0353b74aa21e357).
#Introduction Hi, my name is yuki uchida, and I belong to the SkyWay team of NTT Communications. This article is an article that visualizes your tweet using the language model BERT used for natural language processing, which was recently applied to Google search. I will write in a hands-on format so that as many people as possible can try it out, so if you are interested, please give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I haven&#39;t read the official documentation properly until I understand Django&#39;s static files</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-havent-read-the-official-documentation-properly-until-i-understand-djangos-static-files-109b6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-havent-read-the-official-documentation-properly-until-i-understand-djangos-static-files-109b6/</guid>
      <description>This is the 11th day of the Advent Calendar.  #Introduction Weekend/midnight Pythonista. It&amp;rsquo;s a person who flutters around pandas, numpy, scipy when collecting data at work. As a hobby, I often stumbled on static files when using Django, so I&amp;rsquo;d like to be able to summarize the stumbling points and solutions for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know what they don&amp;rsquo;t understand. We would appreciate if you could point out any mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is also useful in everyday life!? Semi-automation of Cospa&#39;s strongest experimental design method with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/it-is-also-useful-in-everyday-life-semi-automation-of-cospas-strongest-experimental-design-method-with-python-90838/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/it-is-also-useful-in-everyday-life-semi-automation-of-cospas-strongest-experimental-design-method-with-python-90838/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;!-- title How to get a lot of information with a small number of experiments with Python Automatically create an efficient experimental plan in Python Automatically create a good experiment plan for COSPA in Python I experimented 30,000 times, but actually 16 times was enough Reduce 30,000 experiments to 16 Also useful for everyday life!?--&amp;gt;  Overview  I will explain (roughly) the &amp;ldquo;experimental design method&amp;rdquo; that greatly improves the number of experiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[python] Check memory consumption of variables</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-check-memory-consumption-of-variables-83062/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-check-memory-consumption-of-variables-83062/</guid>
      <description>This article is from the 8th day of [Furukawa Lab Advent_calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/flab).  This article was written by a student of Furukawa Lab as part of their studies. The content may be ambiguous or the expressions may be slightly different.
#Introduction
As axes for comparing machine learning algorithms of the same task, learning stability (dependency of initial value), whether it can be explained, (Accuracy in learning with supervision (Precision), recall (Precision), recall ( (There is also an indicator called Recall)) and there is &amp;ldquo;computation amount&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Support System with Python3</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/presentation-support-system-with-python3-d3f44/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/presentation-support-system-with-python3-d3f44/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  It is @seigo2016 of 1st year N high school programming class. It will be N high ad curry day 8. I was worried about what to write because it was a neat article, but I talked a lot about the current main project &amp;ldquo;Itokake Mandala Color Simulator&amp;rdquo; at U22 etc. So, this time I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the recent short-term project &amp;ldquo;PSS ~ Presentation Support System~&amp;rdquo;.
Purpose of # PSS ~Presentation Support System~ I think that you often give presentations using PowerPoint, Google Slide, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Houdini with Python3! ! !</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/do-houdini-with-python3-a0194/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/do-houdini-with-python3-a0194/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The second adcare article this year. The first one was &amp;ldquo;[Verify new installation method of SideFX Labs Tool, Package function]&amp;rdquo; (https://qiita.com/takavfx/items/d1698b89df6fb1b86f9c). So this time, let&amp;rsquo;s take a different angle.
It is Python material.
Due to various reasons, the base of my work has already moved to Python3 series, and Python3 series is regularly used. When making a stand-alone tool, it is 3 series. When you have to write Python processing because of M○y○ etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands-on that automatically deploys an OCR app (Python, Flask) using Microsoft&#39;s AI service Cognitive Services to Azure with a git push trigger</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/hands-on-that-automatically-deploys-an-ocr-app-python-flask-using-microsofts-ai-service-cognitive-services-to-azure-with-a-git-push-trigger-e6909/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/hands-on-that-automatically-deploys-an-ocr-app-python-flask-using-microsofts-ai-service-cognitive-services-to-azure-with-a-git-push-trigger-e6909/</guid>
      <description>The web application we will create this time is an OCR (character recognition) application that will upload an image containing characters and will recognize it and display it as a string.  The app uses Python 3, Flask, Cognitive Services from Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s AI service, and more. Deployment to the cloud (Microsoft Azure) is automatic deployment of git push trigger.
Thank you! This OCR app is made by Microsoft engineer Christopher Harrison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suppressing method overrides in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/suppressing-method-overrides-in-python-ce3f5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/suppressing-method-overrides-in-python-ce3f5/</guid>
      <description>I posted it at 3 at the beginning, but I moved it because yesterday&#39;s part of 1 was unposted and empty.  Prohibiting method overriding during inheritance can be achieved with the final keyword in Java and C++, for example, but this is not a standard feature of Python. So, I investigated and thought about how to do it in Python3.
Environment  Ubuntu 18.04 Python 3.6 mypy: 0.750  Implementation All of this implementation is located at https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried Django 3.0 asynchronous server</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-django-3.0-asynchronous-server-17cff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-django-3.0-asynchronous-server-17cff/</guid>
      <description>#Foreword  Django 3.0 was officially released 3 days ago. Release node link I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in the addition of ASGI support, among many changes, I want to actually use it. :sunny:
Note: What is ASGI?:briefcase: ASGI (Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface) is the spiritual successor to WSGI and aims to provide a standard interface between asynchronous-enabled Python web servers, frameworks, and applications. While WSGI provided the standard for synchronous Python apps, ASGI provides both asynchronous and synchronous apps with a backwards-compatible implementation of WSGI and multiple servers and application frameworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I saw you not working</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-saw-you-not-working-d5220/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-saw-you-not-working-d5220/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There are people who smash without working in a club activity, so it is a story that I can always see the state of the club room. With OpenCV and WebSocket, I was able to easily create what I could see in real time. I will leave it.
Operating environment CentOS Linux release 7.5.1804 Python 3.6.8 Logitech Webcam C270
Implementation Install the following
pip install opencv-python pip install flask pip install gevent pip install gevent-websocket Directory structure ├ main.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made blackjack with Python.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-blackjack-with-python.-d0638/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-blackjack-with-python.-d0638/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The advent calendar was empty, so I&amp;rsquo;ll write it again. This time I made blackjack as the title says.
Click here for the previous article → I made an oracle fortune.  #environment Ubuntu18.04LTS Python3.6.9 vim #code
from random import shuffle class Deck: &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; Class that represents the deck &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; def __init__(self): &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; Initialize the deck and shuffle it. &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; suits = [&amp;#39;Spade&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;Club&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;Diamond&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;Heart&amp;#39;] values = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,&amp;#39;J&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;Q&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;K&amp;#39;] self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[TouchDesigner] Tips for for sentence by python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/touchdesigner-tips-for-for-sentence-by-python-8ffa1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/touchdesigner-tips-for-for-sentence-by-python-8ffa1/</guid>
      <description>## Nice to meet you  My name is ibuibu69 and I am making videos and music as a hobby! Until now, I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing instrumental bands with VJ using max and processing. .. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NswI72i6lCg
&amp;hellip;The band has disbanded and I want to do something new with Touch Designer. I live in Tokyo, so please make friends. ..
Now, let&amp;rsquo;s start posting the first Advent Calendar.
Main subject When trying to do difficult things with TouchDesigner, python control becomes essential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you know it unexpectedly? pip command</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/do-you-know-it-unexpectedly-pip-command-b407d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/do-you-know-it-unexpectedly-pip-command-b407d/</guid>
      <description>Introducing frequently used commands to complicated commands for each use case.  Case 1. Dependency care The script doesn&amp;rsquo;t work because of a package dependency issue&amp;hellip;
(1) Check for dependency issues.
$ pip check # If the package dependencies are okay, # No broken requirements found. # Is output. (2) After confirming the required version of the package, confirm the available version.
$ pip install &amp;lt;package&amp;gt;== # ERROR: Could not find a version that satisfies the requirement &amp;lt;package&amp;gt;== (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a fortune in Python.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-fortune-in-python.-627fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-fortune-in-python.-627fa/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  The advent calendar was empty so I&amp;rsquo;ll write a little bit about Python. I usually use Flask to create web applications, but I feel that I don&amp;rsquo;t understand Python very well because I rely on frameworks. So, first of all, I made an oracle for the purpose of practicing Python. (Currently Flask&amp;rsquo;s advent calendar is empty. If you know Flask, please join us!)
#environment Ubuntu18.04LTS Python3.6.9 vim
#code This time I made a fortune like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python newbie tried Hello World in 30 seconds using micro framework Flask</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-newbie-tried-hello-world-in-30-seconds-using-micro-framework-flask-44f93/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-newbie-tried-hello-world-in-30-seconds-using-micro-framework-flask-44f93/</guid>
      <description>## What is Flask   Python micro web framework Minimal functionality provided as standard Django for full stack framework Reference -Comparison of 4 types of Python Web framework  about me Python history 3 days
Reason for doing looks fun
What I did ** ① Flask installation **
pip install Flask ** ② Make hello.py in your favorite folder ** ③ Paste the following
from flask import Flask app = Flask(__name__) @app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST20 (UTF8 → SJIS) Kanji ranking that appears with garbled characters</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/best20-utf8-sjis-kanji-ranking-that-appears-with-garbled-characters-8a784/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/best20-utf8-sjis-kanji-ranking-that-appears-with-garbled-characters-8a784/</guid>
      <description>## Motivation  (Summary) Just because I wanted to know. There is no better reason.
More details There are many types of garbled patterns. Garbled characters that occur when displaying UTF8 files in SJIS, Garbled characters that occur when displaying UTF8 in EUC, Garbled characters that occur when displaying EUC in UTF8&amp;hellip; You can check what each looks like on this page (https://tools.m-bsys.com/ex/html-mojibake.php).
To be honest, since I work on UTF8 recently, I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen much garbled characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a chatbot that supports free input with Word2Vec</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/create-a-chatbot-that-supports-free-input-with-word2vec-7244b/</guid>
      <description>This article is the first day article of [Zeals Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/zeals).  Nice to meet you. This is Tamaki, who will join Zeals from the next fiscal year. Zeals operates a chatbot technology called chat commerce. Also, I am currently researching natural language processing at university. There are conversations in which bots do not have natural language processing, but I thought it would be interesting to add natural language processing technology to them, so I decided to make this the subject of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Awaitable with Python/C API</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/make-awaitable-with-python-c-api-1f737/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/make-awaitable-with-python-c-api-1f737/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  ========
This year is nearing the end of the year, so I will wastefully use Python C/API. Reversal of purpose and means. This time, we aim to use Awaitable as something like Coroutine obtained by executing the following coroutine function spam.
import asyncio import sys async def spam(): print(&amp;#39;do something&amp;#39;) ret = await asyncio.sleep(1,&amp;#39;RETURN VALUE&amp;#39;) return ret.lower() async def main(): ret = await spam() print(ret) if __name__ ==&amp;#39;__main__&amp;#39;: if sys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried Pandas&#39; Sql Upsert</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-tried-pandas-sql-upsert-b329c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-tried-pandas-sql-upsert-b329c/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  This is Miyano (@estie_mynfire) of estie CTO.
Since estie builds real estate data from various resources, pandas is used for data shaping. for that reason Data created with pandas -&amp;gt; DataBase It is important to carry out this flow smoothly.
Since there was only replace and append as it was, I had to do my best on the pandas side and then update it. (This is very troublesome)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Dynamic Mode Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-dynamic-mode-decomposition-702f6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/introduction-of-dynamic-mode-decomposition-702f6/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I could only think of Fourier transform or wavelet transform as the method of investigating temporal changes, but I learned that there is a good method called dynamic mode decomposition (DMD) that can extract modes in both temporal and spatial directions. I will record it here in order to deepen my understanding.
The content is almost the same as the reference site, but I will write a slightly translated Google translation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandas User Guide merge, join and concatenate (official document in Japanese)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pandas-user-guide-merge-join-and-concatenate-official-document-in-japanese-aea83/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pandas-user-guide-merge-join-and-concatenate-official-document-in-japanese-aea83/</guid>
      <description>This article is a machine translation of [User Guide-Merge, join, and concatenate](https://pandas.pydata.org/pandas-docs/stable/user_guide/merging.html) of Pandas official document. It is a rework of an unnatural sentence in a section.  If you have any suggestions for mistranslation, alternative translations, questions, etc., please use the comments or edit request.
merge, join and concatenate pandas provides various kinds of set operations and various functions of index and relational algebra function in join/merge type operations to easily join Series or DataFrame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Conversion summary of character string and numerical value (ascii code)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-conversion-summary-of-character-string-and-numerical-value-ascii-code-6eb48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-conversion-summary-of-character-string-and-numerical-value-ascii-code-6eb48/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  For myself, I have summarized how to calculate characters and ascii code in Python. It has been confirmed to work with Python 3.4.3 on AtCoder.
How to convert You can convert between ord(&#39;character&#39;) and chr(number).
s =&amp;#39;A&amp;#39; ord_s = ord(s) print(ord_s) # 65 chr_s = chr(ord_s) print(chr_s) #A Conversion table As a summary, the correspondence table of ascii codes and characters is shown. In addition, the item &amp;ldquo;ascii code&amp;rdquo; in the table below represents the decimal notation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Server Error (500) strategy [2019 adokare]</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/django-server-error-500-strategy-2019-adokare-a1e4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/django-server-error-500-strategy-2019-adokare-a1e4b/</guid>
      <description>This is my first time joining the Advent Calendar. Thank you.  Overview My hobby is Pythonista. This year I introduced to Django and made a website. This time, for the same Django beginner as I am, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to write a rough guide to how to get rid of things that will bother you and make you cry. It is Server Error (500).
At this time, try to display the error content on the screen even temporarily, output a log, or notify Slack of the error content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get value of specific key up to specified index of dictionary list in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-value-of-specific-key-up-to-specified-index-of-dictionary-list-in-python-4e765/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-value-of-specific-key-up-to-specified-index-of-dictionary-list-in-python-4e765/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&#39;t write an easy-to-understand title...  li = [ {&#39;name&#39;:&#39;col_a&#39;,&#39;length&#39;: 10}, {&#39;name&#39;:&#39;col_b&#39;,&#39;length&#39;: 8}, {&#39;name&#39;:&#39;col_c&#39;,&#39;length&#39;: 6}, {&#39;name&#39;:&#39;col_d&#39;,&#39;length&#39;: 4}, {&#39;name&#39;:&#39;col_e&#39;,&#39;length&#39;: 2} ] I want the total length up to the third item!
When
sum([d[&#39;length&#39;] for d in li[:3]]) You can get it at.
for idx in range(len(li)): print(sum(d.get(&#39;length&#39;, 0) for d in li[:i]])) Like
It can be adjusted within the range if a starting element is required.
Everyone loves (?) For fixed-length files etc&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I visualized Arashi&#39;s lyrics on WordCloud and tried to understand what I wanted to tell the fans 20 years after the formation</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-i-visualized-arashis-lyrics-on-wordcloud-and-tried-to-understand-what-i-wanted-to-tell-the-fans-20-years-after-the-formation-122ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-i-visualized-arashis-lyrics-on-wordcloud-and-tried-to-understand-what-i-wanted-to-tell-the-fans-20-years-after-the-formation-122ca/</guid>
      <description>#Trigger  It&amp;rsquo;s only one year left until Arashi&amp;rsquo;s activities stop. It&amp;rsquo;s been 20 years since the appearance of invisibility costumes. What did the national idol, who is active in multiplayer, want to tell the fans 20 years after the formation? I would like to meet you in person, but that&amp;rsquo;s why. So I decided to &amp;ldquo;visualize the lyrics&amp;rdquo; and convey the message I want to convey to the fans, ~~ the 6th member~~ to Arashi fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build an application with Clean Architecture while using DI&#43;Mock in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-an-application-with-clean-architecture-while-using-di-mock-in-python-93c1c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-an-application-with-clean-architecture-while-using-di-mock-in-python-93c1c/</guid>
      <description>When implementing a web application using Python in business, we decided to introduce the Clean Architecture to develop while separating the concerns for each layer.  We&amp;rsquo;ve put together a set of practices for developing testable applications, using progressive typing and Dependency Injection to share knowledge with team members.
Clean Architecture This time, since the purpose is a sample using Python, the explanation of Clean Architecture will be simple.
(Quoted from The Clean Architecture)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I searched GIL as much as possible to know if parallel processing in Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-searched-gil-as-much-as-possible-to-know-if-parallel-processing-in-python-5e1d5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-searched-gil-as-much-as-possible-to-know-if-parallel-processing-in-python-5e1d5/</guid>
      <description>Recently I had the opportunity to write an orchestration layer (BFF) application in Python.  Although asyncio was introduced from Python 3.4, I/O bound processing can be handled efficiently even with a single thread, but since GIL still exists for CPU bound processing, parallel processing is possible under a single process. It is limited.
From this, it can be seen as a language characteristic that it is more suitable for handling multiple I/O bound processes than CPU bound processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The matter that was skipped to Microsoft Store when trying to execute Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/the-matter-that-was-skipped-to-microsoft-store-when-trying-to-execute-python-2f2e5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/the-matter-that-was-skipped-to-microsoft-store-when-trying-to-execute-python-2f2e5/</guid>
      <description>## Target audience   People who started to run Python with PowerShell and were skipped to the Microsoft Store People who ran a Python script with PowerShell and nothing happened Those who have already set the path and were able to run Python originally  ##environment
 Windows10 Home Anaconda3  Conclusion ~~ Although the cause is unknown ~~ It seems that the following path is referenced. Let&amp;rsquo;s change the order of environment variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ohm&#39;s Law with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ohms-law-with-python-70126/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ohms-law-with-python-70126/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  While studying Python, I found that complex numbers could be easily calculated, so I tried to see if Ohm&amp;rsquo;s law used in electrical engineering could be implemented in Python really easily.
Ohm&amp;rsquo;s Law (DC) It&amp;rsquo;s one of the most important laws in electrical engineering and the first to learn.
V = IR  $V$: voltage, $I$: current, $R$: resistance The above Ohm&amp;rsquo;s law is written in Python. Set to calculate for empty parameter among $V$, $I$, and $R$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A guide to intermediate Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a-guide-to-intermediate-python-2aef9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a-guide-to-intermediate-python-2aef9/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  Are you programming in Python? For those who understand the basic grammar of Python to some extent, but want to learn more about it, I will explain intermediate techniques and writing methods.
If you master this article, could you become an intermediate Python person tomorrow? So let&amp;rsquo;s get started.
Regarding variable assignment In Python, multiple variables can be defined in one line.
If you substitute normally:
x = 10 y = 12 z = 35 print(x, y, z) # 10 12 35 When substituting in one line:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Python on Mac from 2 to 3</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</guid>
      <description># Overview  This article is a step-by-step article on how a beginner himself developed a coupon distribution service for iPhone with RESTful API and swift. It was a very detouring implementation because we implemented it while examining the technical elements one by one.
Python is originally installed on the Mac, but the version is old as of OS 10.15. When actually writing Python, everyone seems to have been updated to 3 series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granting and defeating positions by reactions</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/granting-and-defeating-positions-by-reactions-b50e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/granting-and-defeating-positions-by-reactions-b50e3/</guid>
      <description>#First of all  This article is a simple explanation in Japanese of the code of overseas developer Anson. In addition, since we have obtained confirmation and permission from the individual, secondary distribution is prohibited and it can be used only for personal use.
Original source page Your commentary video
#Overview Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been absorbed in the development of Discord bots, but a bot that is often included in a major server gives me a title if I add a reaction **Are, I wonder how I can do it well &amp;hellip; While I looked up the command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a Web application that graphs the life log recorded by Google Home like a Gantt chart.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-web-application-that-graphs-the-life-log-recorded-by-google-home-like-a-gantt-chart.-1941f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/i-made-a-web-application-that-graphs-the-life-log-recorded-by-google-home-like-a-gantt-chart.-1941f/</guid>
      <description>## I made a web application that graphs life logs like a Gantt chart  _ People people people people people people people people _
 LIFE LOG GRAPH GENERATOR &amp;lt; ￣ Y^Y^Y^Y^Y^Y^Y^Y^Y^Y^Y^Y￣
 A brief description   From the life log data in which the `date` and `content` are described. ． ． (Folded.) October 15, 2019 at 11:24PM Go to bed October 16, 2019 at 06:03AM Wake up October 16, 2019 at 07:08AM Outing October 16, 2019 at 08:17AM Start development October 16, 2019 at 10:49AM Development finished October 16, 2019 at 12:30PM Return home October 16, 2019 at 12:59PM Start reading October 16, 2019 at 04:32PM Finish reading October 16, 2019 at 10:31PM Go to bed October 17, 2019 at 06:46AM Wake up October 17, 2019 at 07:29AM Going out October 17, 2019 at 08:27AM Start development October 17, 2019 at 12:48PM Development ended October 17, 2019 at 01:48PM Return home October 17, 2019 at 02:35PM TV started October 17, 2019 at 04:54PM TV ends  A web application that creates such an interactive graph.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>