<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> データ analysis on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/%E3%83%87%E3%83%BC%E3%82%BF-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  データ analysis on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/%E3%83%87%E3%83%BC%E3%82%BF-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Summary of statistical data analysis methods using Python that can be used in business</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/21c19edf9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/21c19edf9/</guid>
      <description># Overview  I think it is very important to verify the effects after conducting various prototypes with WEB services, I think that basic statistics can be used enough as a method. This time, we summarized the method of statistical data analysis using Python+JupyterLab (Docker) for the purpose of basic statistics, verification of the effects of prototypes that can be used in business, and data analysis.
The notebook I used this time is also available below, so please refer to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Analyzing technology life with Qiita article data-Survival analysis using content log-</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/5ff105185/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/5ff105185/</guid>
      <description>This article is the 19th day of the NTT Docomo SI Department Advent Calendar.  Hello! It is Hashimoto of read-ahead engine team. In the business we are working to develop technologies of personal data analysis for the agent service.
In this article, we introduce a method to apply a survival time analysis to Qiita posted article data and quantitatively evaluate the lifespan of content (continuous article posting)**.
Survival time analysis is a method of analyzing the relationship between an event and the period until it occurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Visualize quickly with Pandas</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/16c20645c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/16c20645c/</guid>
      <description>There are several libraries that visualize data in Python, but Pandas alone is quite good.  Visualization using Pandas can be completed in the method chain, which can prevent random scattering of temporary variables. In this article, I will introduce visualization recipes, focusing on the ones I often use in practice.
#Preparation
Environment  Python 3.6.8 jupyter==1.0.0 pandas==0.25.3  data I borrow the following two data this time.
 Titanic: Machine Learning from Disaster | Kaggle Crimes in Boston | Kaggle  Create a DataFrame called titanic and crime respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>