<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pyenv on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/pyenv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pyenv on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/pyenv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Python environment construction (pyenv&#43;poetry&#43;pipx)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-pyenv-poetry-pipx-85f21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-environment-construction-pyenv-poetry-pipx-85f21/</guid>
      <description># What&#39;s this?  macbook Python environment
 pyenv poetry pipx  It&amp;rsquo;s a memo because it was built in. The environment is mac OS 10.14.6 Mojave. I will proceed with the assumption that homebrew is already included. (If you don&amp;rsquo;t have homebrew, please refer to Homebrew official) I will update it as appropriate.
#Install Python3 Install python3 of system with homebrew. If you have already put it in, please skip it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Get a clean Python development environment with pyenv&#43;pipx&#43;Poetry</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/get-a-clean-python-development-environment-with-pyenv-pipx-poetry-a3f09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/get-a-clean-python-development-environment-with-pyenv-pipx-poetry-a3f09/</guid>
      <description>It is as this article that had been a hot topic before. …Because it becomes a worthless article, I will explain it a little.  My Python Development Environment, 2020 Edition
The author of this article uses WSL, but I can use it almost as it is in OS X environment.
pyenv  Why? I need to run multiple Python versions, isolated from the system Python.pyenv makes it easy to install, manage, and switch between those multiple Pythons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] pyenv does not work with tcl-tk installed by homebrew.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/pyenv-does-not-work-with-tcl-tk-installed-by-homebrew.-5a8e2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/pyenv-does-not-work-with-tcl-tk-installed-by-homebrew.-5a8e2/</guid>
      <description># Problems encountered  When I tried to use tkinter from python installed using pyenv on Mac, I got the following error:
Traceback (most recent call last): File &amp;quot;./annotate.py&amp;quot;, line 3, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; import tkinter File &amp;quot;/Users/???/.pyenv/versions/3.7.4/lib/python3.7/tkinter/__init__.py&amp;quot;, line 36, in &amp;lt;module&amp;gt; import _tkinter # If this fails your Python may not be configured for Tk ModuleNotFoundError: No module named&#39;_tkinter&#39;  The environment is
 MacOS Catalina 10.15.1 pyenv 1.2.15  #How to find (and didn&amp;rsquo;t solve) Gugu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [python] For some reason, python on the Windows side is called during WSL pipenv install</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/python-for-some-reason-python-on-the-windows-side-is-called-during-wsl-pipenv-install-bfa90/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/python-for-some-reason-python-on-the-windows-side-is-called-during-wsl-pipenv-install-bfa90/</guid>
      <description># Overview   Why do I get an error when trying to install pipenv in a repository with wsl? .. .. Apparently it refers to python on windows side By specifying python with full path, countermeasures are completed for the time being  #Environment
 Windows10 1909 wsl ubuntu 18.0LTS pyenv 1.2.13-35-g22c0202 python 3.8.0 pipenv 2018.11.26  Phenomenon When I try to install pipenv in my project with WSL for the first time after python3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [Ubuntu 18.04] Build Python environment with pyenv&#43;pipenv</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ubuntu-18.04-build-python-environment-with-pyenv-pipenv-08036/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ubuntu-18.04-build-python-environment-with-pyenv-pipenv-08036/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Create a virtual environment management environment (?) using pyenv and pipenv. The version control of Python itself is done with pyenv, and the virtual environment for each project and package management are done with pipenv.
#Environment
 Ubuntu 18.04 You can use apt install  Install #!/bin/bash  # Install dependencies echo &amp;#34;user password&amp;#34; | sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt install -y --no-install-recommends \  build-essential \  libffi-dev \  libssl-dev \  zlib1g-dev \  libbz2-dev \  libreadline-dev \  libsqlite3-dev \  git # Download pyenv git clone https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Update Python on Mac from 2 to 3</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/update-python-on-mac-from-2-to-3-ff40e/</guid>
      <description># Overview  This article is a step-by-step article on how a beginner himself developed a coupon distribution service for iPhone with RESTful API and swift. It was a very detouring implementation because we implemented it while examining the technical elements one by one.
Python is originally installed on the Mac, but the version is old as of OS 10.15. When actually writing Python, everyone seems to have been updated to 3 series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] How to use tkinter in pyenv python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-tkinter-in-pyenv-python-a5f83/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/how-to-use-tkinter-in-pyenv-python-a5f83/</guid>
      <description>## Issue  The following error occurs when you do python -m tkinter or import tkinter with python installed by pyenv. When I read the article on the net, it said that it was cured by brew install tcl-tk, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work. However, apparently it seems that the recently released pyenv v1.2.14 fixes the compatibility with tcl-tk, and GitHub issue I also wrote a solution, so I will share it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 3 workarounds for the activate conflict problem when coexisting pyenv and anaconda</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/3-workarounds-for-the-activate-conflict-problem-when-coexisting-pyenv-and-anaconda-f732b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/3-workarounds-for-the-activate-conflict-problem-when-coexisting-pyenv-and-anaconda-f732b/</guid>
      <description>It is a supplement of [python environment construction final version](http://qiita.com/y__sama/items/5b62d31cb7e6ed50f02c).  20180312 Addendum It seems that conda activate was adopted in conda 4.4.0 released with 2017-12-20. conda/CHANGELOG.md It seems that source activate is not obsolete at the moment, but conda activate is recommended.
Since docker has become proficient recently (I do not feel stress even in a windows environment through a proxy), the need for sandwiching pyenv has decreased, and I am also moving to docker-anaconda, but for reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build environment with pyenv and pyenv-virtualenv</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/build-environment-with-pyenv-and-pyenv-virtualenv-feadf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/build-environment-with-pyenv-and-pyenv-virtualenv-feadf/</guid>
      <description>## A note on how to build your own environment  I will write it down because I need it when working remotely The referenced website may be easier to understand The environment is mac OSX: Yosemite.
#pyenv pyenv manages the python environment. You can create a python environment that is different from the standard environment.
Reference URL: How to use pyenv and virtualenv How to manage Python environment with pyenv Try using pyenv and virtualenv</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>