<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>othello on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/othello/</link>
    <description>Recent content in othello on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/othello/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I made Othello to teach a child Python3 (5)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8be4354e2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8be4354e2/</guid>
      <description>#Let&#39;s explain about Othello class 2  Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about types There are blood types, right? Type A, Type B, Type O, Type AB, etc. Whether it is true or not, aside from the fact that it is &amp;ldquo;A type that is well-organized&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;B type that is selfish&amp;rdquo;, the type has its own characteristics. In programming, types are used to make such important divisions as blood types.
Until now, I have explained various things about variables, but I have not touched on types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I made Othello to teach a child Python3 (3)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/e1123aa5f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/e1123aa5f/</guid>
      <description># You should learn the program by moving it and watching the movement  Anyway, the program is running and Nambo. There is also an effect that the understanding can be promoted by playing around with it, so today the source of the Othello game is a little long, but first I will release it. Let&amp;rsquo;s create this as a new PyCharom project.
Launch PyCharm and create a &amp;ldquo;New Project&amp;rdquo; from the File menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Othello game development made with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8794c4bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8794c4bed/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I developed an Othello game using Python. Anyone can easily play
github page https://github.com/chihina/othello-game-python
Development environment python3.7.1 For other, please check requirement.txt on the following github page. https://github.com/chihina/othello-game-python
Until the game starts First, execute git clone with the following command.
git clone https://github.com/chihina/othello-game-python.git Next, install the libraries in a batch with the following command.
pip -r install requirement.txt This concludes the environment construction. It&amp;rsquo;s easy. The following command will start the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Recognize the board surface of Othello board with OpenCV</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fe6b95ae9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fe6b95ae9/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This year, Othello Advent Calendar was planned and invited, so I decided to write an article. Actually, I wrote another article on Day 1, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what I was doing and I suddenly entered the article, so this time It is a little self-introduction.
I&amp;rsquo;m developing an app for iOS called Goki Box. As one of its functions, we have incorporated a function that images the Othello board with a camera and overlays the evaluation value on the board with AR.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>