<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> AWS on Memo Tut</title>
    <link>https://memotut.com/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  AWS on Memo Tut</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://memotut.com/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I want to know more about individual developers. YouDev has been released.</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ae2cd25ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ae2cd25ca/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;img width=&amp;quot;610&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;eyecatch.png&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/634341/275b16c8-3136-198f-fa76-a17a4cbb41e1.png&amp;quot;&amp;gt;  YouDev has been released. 2020.5.01
YouDev is a service that focuses on individual developers to let them know more about them (I want to know&amp;hellip;).
Even if the service is recognized, I think that the developers have not hit the spot, so individual developers may not only appeal the services released by themselves, but also the developers themselves. I created it.
I&amp;rsquo;m always looking for individual developers, so I&amp;rsquo;m an individual developer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If you create a program that automatically starts/ends the verification environment for pull requests, the verification progressed</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/216fcc604/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/216fcc604/</guid>
      <description># Article summary  I wanted to put the sales involved in the development with GitHub Flow, that is, the development with a simple pull operation, and created such an environment. At that time, I made and released a web application that supplements some missing functions, so I will write various stories about it. (It&amp;rsquo;s not about whether or not you can actually use this web app, but rather that you want to improve your development with a similar flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] When creating Lambda Layers, docker-lambda and yumda are convenient</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a6fd8ecfb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a6fd8ecfb/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  A layer corresponding to each runtime version can be created with the docker-lambda build image!
$ docker run --rm -v $(pwd):/var/task lambci/lambda:build-python3.8 \ &amp;gt; pip install -r requirements.txt -t python/lib/python3.8/site-packages/ Software packages that you want to run on AWS Lambda can be layered with yumda!
$ docker run --rm -v $(pwd)/git-layer:/lambda/opt lambci/yumda:2 yum install -y &amp;lt;package&amp;gt; Preparing the environment from scratch is quite difficult A common caveat with AWS Lambda and Lambda Layers is the handling of native binaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Make a washing and drying timer using RaspberryPi</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/b61d4f1b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/b61d4f1b2/</guid>
      <description>Make a washing and drying timer using # RaspberryPi  Introduction (purpose of production)  Because I work for a company, I am often absent during the day, and I can not take in the laundry when it rains. For this reason, laundry is basically dried indoors. However, since the clothes drying room is not sunny and the drying does not proceed as expected in winter, the timing of taking in may be missed, and the laundry accumulates in a snow dharma fashion, creating a vicious cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If not, let&#39;s create one, something like AWS Chatbot for Microsoft Teams</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/239c9e2b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/239c9e2b1/</guid>
      <description>## What is AWS Chatbot  https://aws.amazon.com/jp/chatbot/
Roughly speaking, you can notify Slack and Amazon Chime of events that occurred on AWS, and operate with slash commands.
At the time of writing this article, it is a beta version, so 1.10 Beta of this document In accordance with Service Participation, we will not make any further reference.
background At the moment, it&amp;rsquo;s only for Slack and Amazon Chime, so we&amp;rsquo;re going to make something like AWS Chatbot for Microsoft Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] 3 months after graduating from programming school</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/0f652c07c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/0f652c07c/</guid>
      <description>In October 2019, I attended a certain programming school where I often see advertisements on youtube, and since November I have been in my current position as a machine learning engineer and data scientist.  Three months after graduating, I would like to write about what I learned from the school, what was useful, and what is difficult now.
Biography April 2015 Served as a research and development position for a food company for 4 years July 2019 Start of programming school learning October 2019, graduated from programming school November 2019 Job change as a machine learning engineer and data scientist</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Learning roadmap that allows you to develop and publish services from scratch with Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/52a3bbacd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/52a3bbacd/</guid>
      <description>## at first  This article aims to &amp;ldquo;be able to develop services with Python from no programming experience&amp;rdquo;, We have arranged the skills to be learned as a learning roadmap.
** 2-3 hours every day (+2 hours on Saturdays and Sundays) ** If you continue, it will be completed in a minimum of 3 months. You can skip the skills you have already learned and proceed.
The outline is the same for other languages such as Ruby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let Siri do the job of reading AWS bills posted by Slackbot</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d85fda007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d85fda007/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the iPhone for less than a decade and I noticed that Siri wasn&amp;rsquo;t working at all. Now that smart speakers are popular, I want my Siri to do more, so I decided to read the AWS bill posted by Slackbot.
From the results, it looks like this. When you ask for the price&amp;hellip; He read the content I posted to Slack. Then, I will introduce various ways to make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Build Selenium environment on Amazon Linux 2 in the shortest time</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/371d2cc79/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/371d2cc79/</guid>
      <description>This article is the Amazon Linux 2 version of [Build Selenium environment with Amazon Linux at the shortest](https://qiita.com/onorioriori/items/4fa271daa3621e8f6fd9).  If you want to build Selenium environment on Amazon Linux, please refer to the link above.
Overview By the end of June 30, 2020, Amazon Linux security update provision will end, Made it possible to build a Selenium environment on Amazon Linux 2. The procedure is almost unchanged, but there are some changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [AWS SAM] Create API with DynamoDB&#43;Lambda&#43;API Gateway</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/119ec62c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/119ec62c8/</guid>
      <description># Content  Build an API that fetches DynamoDB data with AWS SAM
In short, from a table like this&amp;hellip;
   group(Hash) name(Range)     group1 name1   group1 name2   group2 name3    I want to make it look like this.
curl https://hogehoge/Prod/dynamo-api/v1/?group=group1&amp;amp;name=name1 { &amp;#34;result&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;group1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;group&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;name1&amp;#34; } ] } #Environment
 macOS Mojave -10.14 python3.7.4 sam 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Knowledge base &#43; Web API operated by NoSQL x PaaS</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/c4f315f91/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/c4f315f91/</guid>
      <description># What is this  It is a summary of know-how when building a knowledge base + Web API with NoSQL and PaaS.
When implementing an architecture called string tag oriented undirected graph type knowledge base, An example built with Heroku + Redis + FastAPI, Here is an example built with AWS(DynamoDB + Lambda + API Gateway).
All the code parts use Python3.8.0.
*Currently the AWS edition is incomplete. sorry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] The first step to get rid of slow queries! I tried to notify Chatwork of a slow query of RDS for MySQL using Lambda and AWS CLI v2</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/4f370f716/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/4f370f716/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  Hello. I am in charge of infrastructure at Mikatus Co., Ltd., and I am in charge of infrastructure construction, operation and maintenance centering on AWS. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll write about the case where the slow query of MySQL is notified to Chatwork.
Our system uses Amazon RDS for MySQL, and we used a monitoring tool to monitor the occurrence status for slow queries, but Chatwork will be able to make continuous improvements by sending notifications in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [2020 edition] How to install Python3 on EC2 of AWS</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2403ad9cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2403ad9cb/</guid>
      <description>The other day I had the opportunity to install Python3 on EC2 on AWS.  At that time, I did a Google search with &amp;ldquo;AWS EC2 Python 3&amp;rdquo;, but the information on the page displayed at the top of the search results was not good enough. In particular,
 pyenv virtualenv  Although the method of preparing a virtual environment of Python3 was introduced using, you should use venv unless there is a special reason for preparing a virtual environment of Python3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to make a document search slack command using Kendra announced at re:Invent 2019</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/67a5b9023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/67a5b9023/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is the eighth day of [ABEJA Advent Calendar](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/abeja).  Introduction An interesting service was announced at re:Invent 2019 the other day. Yes, enterprise search service Amazon Kendra release. There are various communication tools in the company. However, all of them tend to be flow information and are not well organized, and the problem that information disparities are likely to occur is emerging. This is exactly Kendra&amp;rsquo;s task. When announced, this has no choice but to try!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] A story of making an anonymous channel with Slack from zero knowledge</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/8561113fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/8561113fb/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  A memorandum when I struggled to create an anonymous channel on Slack without any knowledge of AWS, Lambda, or Python.
#Trigger When I was thinking that I had to write something on Qiita after being invited by the Advent Calendar
 Talk about creating a VIP channel for in-house slack https://qiita.com/peisuke/items/80984db8b47cd8243019  After reading this article, this looks interesting! I would like to introduce it to Slack where I participate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Rewriting Lambda to restart Workspaces of UNHEALTHY with python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f7ffae07e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f7ffae07e/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll do Hands Lab Advent Calendar this year as well  Overview We use Workspaces, a service that provides virtual desktops for AWS, Sometimes it’s unhealthy
\ Broken without doing anything /
Most of the time, it is possible to manage by restarting due to a temporary load drop. So there is Lambda that restarts for the time being It&amp;rsquo;s written in Node.js, so it supports frequent version upgrades&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s simple code, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d rewrite it to python anyway</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] [AWS/Tello] Construction of a system for operating drones on the cloud</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d0ab81024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d0ab81024/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  This article Evacuation advisory system using drones It is the first chapter of. Please refer to it for the production background.
Overview Build a system that can operate Tello drone on AWS. If you can operate it on AWS, you can link with various services, so let&amp;rsquo;s expand your dream.
About the drone to use We will use Tello edudevelopedbyChinesestartupRyzeTech.IntelandDJIaretechnicallydevelopingandtheofficialSDK has been released, and if it is edu version v2 can be used and the drone is a child machine It is recommended to purchase the edu version as it allows for formation flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] What I&#39;ve done to welcome the Python 2 EOL with confidence</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/77fe76859/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/77fe76859/</guid>
      <description>## Self-introduction  I am @yukin01 who is an SRE on the SRE/QA team. I used to use iOS and Firebase/GCP to develop applications until half a year ago, but now that I want to strengthen the infrastructure, I am using AWS and GCP as an SRE at GLOBIS.
Python2 EOL As you know, Python2 is announced to end support on January 1, 2020, but if you have any products or tools that are still dependent on Python2, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to get rid of them by EOL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Let&#39;s create a web chat using WebSocket with AWS serverless (Python)!</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/d8095afca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/d8095afca/</guid>
      <description>This article is the second day of NTT Technocross [Advent Calendar 2019](https://qiita.com/advent-calendar/2019/ntt-tx).  Hello. My name is Yasuda. I am in charge of new AI-related product development at NTT Technocross. It&amp;rsquo;s a gap from the main subject immediately, but drawing a manga is a recent break, and I&amp;rsquo;m drawing the following manga.
Data link understood by manga Enterprise architecture in the AI era understood with manga IT strategy understood by manga &amp;hellip; Well, in this article, I&amp;rsquo;d like to see how to do &amp;ldquo;WebSocket&amp;rdquo; without AWS server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Try AWS Lambda Destinations</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/efcb2ac3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/efcb2ac3d/</guid>
      <description>AWS has announced a great feature.  Introducing AWS Lambda Destinations https://aws.amazon.com/jp/blogs/compute/introducing-aws-lambda-destinations/
![Screenshot 2019-11-27 6.51.44.png](https://qiita-image-store.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/0/102769/8dcc8bb4-f376-17ae-1ccf-(b64739c3289b.png)
The following actions (AWS services) can be specified according to the execution result of Lambda. If you want to control the flow with success / failure conditions, you can now complete it only with Lambda without using Step Functions.
Try immediately.
Define the calling Lambda appropriately Write Python like this. (Using Python 3.7)
import json import logging logger = logging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] I tried to let Amazon Transcribe transcribe the example business integration news</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/2efcb99df/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/2efcb99df/</guid>
      <description>## Introduction  AWS&amp;rsquo;s automatic voice recognition service Amazon Transcribe is said to support Japanese, so try inputting Japanese voice and trying transcription It was.
Subject I used the following news video.
 Announcement of LINE integration with Yahoo-TV Tokyo NEWS  One announcer reads the news for about a minute, and there is no conversation between multiple people.
Transcription method Transcribe
 Management console AWS CLI AWS SDK for Python (Boto)  You can use it, but this time, I will try using the AWS CLI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] ``First time learning&#39;&#39; that even university students with no knowledge can do-AWS SageMaker</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ffdfc936e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ffdfc936e/</guid>
      <description># My background  Amazon? Ah, you know, you know, a mail order app. Not long ago, knowledge about Amazon was that much. Of course, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know AWS.
I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed as an information undergraduate student. 
However, as a 3rd year university student, I was introduced to the lab and learned about AWS. In addition, I am addicted to the topic &amp;ldquo;Atsuhiko Nakata&amp;rsquo;s YouTube University&amp;rdquo;, which is a hot topic in this street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] If the engineer asked for entertainment at the reception</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/7ce7c4bc3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/7ce7c4bc3/</guid>
      <description>The other day, at the wedding reception of an acquaintance, I was asked for entertainment for the first time, and I managed to survive.  What should I do I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to own. Singing and dancing are not masters. I can make some movies, but it seems to be done by the side of the bride. .. : Only programming! !
What you did &amp;ldquo;HAPPINESS SCOUTER&amp;rdquo;
If you send a photo via LINE, it will recognize the facial expression of the person in the picture and measure the &amp;ldquo;happy fighting power&amp;rdquo;**!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] When outputting S3 list with Boto3, use Bucket().objects.filter instead of list_objects_v2</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a513226b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a513226b7/</guid>
      <description># Low-level API and high-level API  It is boto3 which is aws python library, but there is a low level API which is a naive API and an object oriented high level API which wraps it.
Manipulating S3 Objects with Boto3 (High Level API and Low Level API)-Qiita https://qiita.com/sokutou-metsu/items/5ba7531117224ee5e8af
I used to use the low-level API client.list_objects_v2 to output the list of S3, but there is a corresponding high-level API, resource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Create a scraping app with Python&#43;Django&#43;AWS and change jobs</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/a9464983b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/a9464983b/</guid>
      <description>My name is mogken and I am in the business planning office of an IT venture company.  Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about changing jobs, and I&amp;rsquo;m studying programming to make it appeal to me. It&amp;rsquo;s not so appealing to say that you&amp;rsquo;re just studying with your mouth, so I made a simple web app with Python and Django, built it on AWS, and released the source to Github.
This time, I would like to explain the program (Python) I wrote myself, which also serves as an output for the fixation of knowledge within me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Get started with Amazon DynamoDB from Python</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fc34447eb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fc34447eb/</guid>
      <description>#0. Introduction  Let&amp;rsquo;s try various services that AWS recommends serverless. This time, I will use Amazon DynamoDB from Python.
1. Build a Python environment on your Mac There is no environment in the first place, so it is from the environment construction.
Build the environment by referring to the following (maybe it is as it is&amp;hellip;).
 Installing Python3 on Mac-Qiita Use pyenv to build Python environment on Mac-Qiita  If you do not set .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Explosive API construction ~chalice~</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fd9af5fc7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fd9af5fc7/</guid>
      <description>Send to those who want to release API at explosive speed  https://github.com/awslabs/chalice
What is # chalice
This chalice, which bears the name of the Holy Grail, is a tool rather than a framework, and if you have application code, you can configure AWS Lambda, AWS API Gateway, IAMRole etc., and deploy it on AWS. is. This will build the API at explosive speed and realize the production release.
First of all We will build APIs using rabbit services fully using rabbit services, so it is necessary to set credentials first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Install Python3 and Django on Amazon Linux (EC2) and run the web server</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f9cf37cfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f9cf37cfc/</guid>
      <description>Leave it as a memo instead.  It is a premise that the instance is staggered.
##Install Python3 The version of Python originally included in Amazon Linux is 2.7.12. That&amp;rsquo;s why I will install Python 3 series this time. Fortunately, Python3 is collected in YUM&amp;rsquo;s amzn-main repository.
# yum list | grep python35 python35.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-devel.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-libs.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-pip.noarch 6.1.1-1.23.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-setuptools.noarch 12.2-1.32.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-tools.x86_64 3.5.1-13.7.amzn1 @amzn-main python35-virtualenv.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Use a profile other than the default profile with boto3</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f9723d7ae/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f9723d7ae/</guid>
      <description>## In case of default  import boto3 s3 = boto3.resource(&amp;#39;s3&amp;#39;) for bucket in s3.buckets.all(): print(bucket.name) Specify ACCESS_KEY and SECRET_KEY document
 http://boto3.readthedocs.org/en/latest/guide/session.html#custom-session http://boto3.readthedocs.org/en/latest/guide/configuration.html  import boto3 from boto3.session import Session session = Session(aws_access_key_id=&amp;#39;&amp;lt;YOUR ACCESS KEY ID&amp;gt;&amp;#39;, aws_secret_access_key=&amp;#39;&amp;lt;YOUR SECRET KEY&amp;gt;&amp;#39;, region_name=&amp;#39;&amp;lt;REGION NAME&amp;gt;&amp;#39;) s3 = session.resource(&amp;#39;s3&amp;#39;) Specify with profile name of ~/.aws/credentials Pass profile_name to Session.
DocumentIdon&amp;rsquo;tunderstandit,andgithubissue found in
import boto3 from boto3.session import Session profile =&amp;#39;&amp;lt;YOUR_PROFILE_NAME&amp;gt;&amp;#39; session = Session(profile_name=profile) s3 = session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Generate S3 signed URL with boto</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/f8e00cb79/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/f8e00cb79/</guid>
      <description>Generate S3 signed URL using [boto](https://github.com/boto/boto) which is AWS SDK of Python.  Generate only URL If you only want to generate the URL of one item, it is easy to generate it directly from the connection.
conn = boto.connect_s3(aws_access_key_id, aws_secret_access_key) url = conn.generate_url(expire_second, method=&amp;#39;GET&amp;#39;, bucket=&amp;#39;bucket_name&amp;#39;, key=&amp;#39;path/to/file&amp;#39;) #Create a Bucket object and then create it
This is easier if you are looking for items in your bucket.
conn = boto.connect_s3(aws_access_key_id, aws_secret_access_key) bucket = conn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Support iOS private streaming (limited)</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/fadecf13e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/fadecf13e/</guid>
      <description>This article is a continuation related to [Video Streaming with AWS S3 + CloudFront](http://qiita.com/terapyon/items/b77ac981da790662e247).  Purpose  Streaming compatible with iOS Preliminary survey is here Delivered via CloudFront to private (browsing restricted) Preliminary survey is here Realizing the latest private while supporting HLS for iOS &amp;lt;This is the main purpose this time  Method JAWS Days 2014 announcement has instructions. There is a description in p17 of Secure Content Delivery and Effect Tracking with CloudFront.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Python] Deliver private content with AWS CloudFront</title>
      <link>https://memotut.com/ff2dd73bd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://memotut.com/ff2dd73bd/</guid>
      <description>This article is a continuation of [Video Streams with AWS S3 + CloudFront](http://qiita.com/terapyon/items/b77ac981da790662e247&amp;quot;VideoStreamswithAWSS3+CloudFront&amp;quot;).  Purpose Connect with a time-limited URL. (One-time URL) I want to restrict the viewing to the video stream and distribute it. (This time I tried with images) Finally, I want to distribute the video using Plone authentication. (Challenge after next time)
S3 and CloudFront settings Create a new bucket and put a trial image. Try distributing this image privately.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>