<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS on Some Title</title>
    <link>https://japan2018.github.io/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://japan2018.github.io/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[AWS] Data migration from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-data-migration-from-dynamodb-to-aurora-mysql-fe2f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-data-migration-from-dynamodb-to-aurora-mysql-fe2f9/</guid>
      <description>I have migrated data from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL, so I will write the method.  Please note that the data migration does not mean that all tables are migrated because we have migrated the data stored in one table.
Method I think there are several possible ways to migrate from DynamoDB to Aurora MySQL, but I wrote the code in disposable (?) Python to make the transition quickly and reliably Even though it is disposable, there is a possibility that data may be migrated again, so we made it possible to reuse</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Established a mechanism to download a large zip file by aws with Basic authentication</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/established-a-mechanism-to-download-a-large-zip-file-by-aws-with-basic-authentication-fd79d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/established-a-mechanism-to-download-a-large-zip-file-by-aws-with-basic-authentication-fd79d/</guid>
      <description># Article content in three lines   Let&amp;rsquo;s use EC2 and framework It can not be assembled without server (it can be assembled but NG due to capacity limitation) API Gateway convenient (difficult)  Overview When sharing a large file, if it exceeds about 8MB for mail, it will be blocked because it is a mail server. Even if it is not blocked, I think that it is quite annoying to send a large file by mail to the server in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Digest authentication using Python @Lambda</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/setting-up-digest-authentication-using-python-lambda-fe83c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/setting-up-digest-authentication-using-python-lambda-fe83c/</guid>
      <description>#Introduction  There was almost no information when I searched for Digest authentication, so I wrote it as a sequel to Basic authentication setting @ Lambda using Python. I have barely touched Digest authentication itself, and I also learned the mechanism.
#Code
import os import ctypes import json import base64 import time import hashlib import copy from Crypto.Cipher import AES accounts = [ { &amp;#34;user&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;user1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;pass&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;pass1&amp;#34; }, { &amp;#34;user&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;user2&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;pass&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;pass2&amp;#34; } ] realm = &amp;#34;sample@test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[AWS] I made a reminder BOT with LINE WORKS (implementation)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-i-made-a-reminder-bot-with-line-works-implementation-ff5a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/aws-i-made-a-reminder-bot-with-line-works-implementation-ff5a2/</guid>
      <description>It is the 14th day of LINEWORKS Advent Calendar.  This time, we will introduce the implementation of the reminder BOT introduced in LINEWORKS Advent Calendar Day 7.
[Repost] BOT screen and overall structure The reminder BOT consists of three Lambda, and is implemented with Python3.7.
①. Processing of messages sent from LINE WORKS and notification to SQS ②. Poll the events stored in the table and notify SQS ③. Notify the LINEWORKS server of the message received from SQS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use a command to upload data to s3 of aws and update it, and delete the used data (on the way)</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/use-a-command-to-upload-data-to-s3-of-aws-and-update-it-and-delete-the-used-data-on-the-way-fb390/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/use-a-command-to-upload-data-to-s3-of-aws-and-update-it-and-delete-the-used-data-on-the-way-fb390/</guid>
      <description>[Install AWS CLI version 1](https://docs.aws.amazon.com/ja_jp/cli/latest/userguide/install-cliv1.html)  Install the latest version of the AWS CLI pip3 install awscli --upgrade --user
It seems that you can install it, but aws --version Then, zsh: command not found: aws Will appear&amp;hellip; Add AWS CLI version 1 executable to macOS command line path Based on the above article, &amp;ldquo;Add aws program to PATH environment variable of operating system&amp;rdquo;. →But after all zsh: command not found: aws Will it come out&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rewriting Lambda to restart Workspaces of UNHEALTHY with python</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/rewriting-lambda-to-restart-workspaces-of-unhealthy-with-python-f7ffa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/rewriting-lambda-to-restart-workspaces-of-unhealthy-with-python-f7ffa/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll do Hands Lab Advent Calendar this year as well  Overview We use Workspaces, a service that provides virtual desktops for AWS, Sometimes it’s unhealthy
\ Broken without doing anything /
Most of the time, it is possible to manage by restarting due to a temporary load drop. So there is Lambda that restarts for the time being It&amp;rsquo;s written in Node.js, so it supports frequent version upgrades&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s simple code, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d rewrite it to python anyway</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>``First time learning&#39;&#39; that even university students with no knowledge can do-AWS SageMaker</title>
      <link>https://japan2018.github.io/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japan2018.github.io/first-time-learning-that-even-university-students-with-no-knowledge-can-do-aws-sagemaker-ffdfc/</guid>
      <description># My background  Amazon? Ah, you know, you know, a mail order app. Not long ago, knowledge about Amazon was that much. Of course, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know AWS.
I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed as an information undergraduate student. 
However, as a 3rd year university student, I was introduced to the lab and learned about AWS. In addition, I am addicted to the topic &amp;ldquo;Atsuhiko Nakata&amp;rsquo;s YouTube University&amp;rdquo;, which is a hot topic in this street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>